<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9027874421</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM 14-In-1 Camera Accessories Set For Fujifilm Instax Mini 9 Flamingo Pink/Yellow/Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsClose-up lens with mirror is perfect for taking photographs in a selfie modeColour lens set added in this bundle provides the best photographic effectsComes with a pocket album to preserve your memories and prevent the films from damageSpecificationsProduct Weight 739 gColour Name Flamingo Pink/Yellow/RedWhat's In The Box Camera Case, Coloured Filters, Wall Hang Frames, Film Frames, Border Stickers, Corner Stickers, Selfie Lens, Diamond StickersModel Number A01Item Quantity 14</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/10403f4a-dffe-421e-9ca9-5fa932746ac4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5b6b288a-830c-44d5-98c8-39fc3cdc82b3/web/1_1730712387351.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090278744218</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5163617061</g:id>
      <g:title>PROMAGE DSLR CAMERA BAG (Black )-5001</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMultiple Pockets &amp;amp; Big Opening DesignQuick Adjustable Shoulder Strap BuckleIncredible Materials, Our high-quality camera bag, is designed to protect your valuable equipment while providing ease of use and durability. Strong Storage for Camera Bag specially designed for DSLR and mirrorless cameras, lenses, and other accessories. With the removable dividers in the main compartment, you can customize the storage space according to your gear. OverviewEfficient Gear Storage: This camera bag is designed to conveniently store your DSLR camera along with two EF mount lenses and various photography accessories. It offers ample space to meet the needs of both professional photographers and hobbyists. Durable and Lightweight: Crafted from high-quality materials, this camera bag strikes the perfect balance between durability and lightweight design. It provides robust protection for your equipment without adding unnecessary bulk. Secure Zipper Closure: The camera bag features a durable zipper closure that ensures easy access to your gear while keeping it securely protected. Open and close the bag effortlessly, even in challenging conditions. Organized Interior: The interior of the bag is thoughtfully organized with a divider that separates the camera section from the lens section. This division helps keep your equipment neatly organized and easily accessible. Accessory Storage: In addition to your camera and lenses, you can store various accessories such as extra batteries, USB cables, memory cards, and more. This versatile bag accommodates all your essential photography gear. Comfortable Carrying Options: Carry your camera bag comfortably using the included shoulder strap or the convenient top grab handle. Whether you’re on the move or stationary, you’ll appreciate its comfortable and stylish design. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name BlackModel Number 5001Model Name 5001Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0c12d54a-3807-408e-80d0-9162bcd3e15c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6799262c-4a74-4f51-b0b2-1a0fcadc2f54/web/2_1730712187024.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051636170612</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5446280828</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Pack Of 10 Film Sheet For Instax Mini 7/7s/8/25/50 White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGlossy film yields superb results under both daylight and electronic flash conditionsDesigned for use in Fujifilm Instax mini series camerasImproved picture quality and greater ease of use make it ideal for snapshots and portraitsinstant film ensures clear, bright, sharp and vibrant picturesFeature a well-defined blank frame model along the borderlineSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box 10xSheetsProduct Length 8. 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 5. 4 cmModel Number CAM-FJ-A-102Item Quantity 10</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f17957c1-926f-4d4e-94b1-529db2bdd4fe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a610c664-ad77-457b-9772-3496045c58d7/web/1_1730714461789.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054462808285</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3984931248</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony SRS-XB100/D Wireless Bluetooth Portable Lightweight Super-Compact Travel Speaker, Extra-Durable IP67 Waterproof & Dustproof, 16 Hour Battery - Orange Orange</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSound: NUMBER OF SPEAKER Full range Unit: 1 SPEAKER TYPE full rangeDIMENSIONS (W X H X D): Approx. 2. 99" dia. x 3. 74"Interface: INPUT AND OUTPUT TERMINALS USB Type-C® (Charging Only)Application: COMPATIBLE SMARTPHONE APPS : Sony | Music Center (FOTA Only)Color: OrangeModel: SRS-XB100/DOverviewPortable and durable for life on the go Get more from your speaker Sound Quality: Listen loud and clear from a compact speaker Music is the soundtrack to our lives, and we want you to be able to enjoy your tunes wherever you are. So we’ve packed powerful, clear sound into a portable body. If you love good music and listening with friends, the XB100 is your perfect partner. Passive radiator for powerful sound A passive radiator works together with a full-range speaker to enhance low-end tones, giving bass a boost. Keep it clear with the off-center diaphragm The off-centre design and optimized weight balance enhance clarity, providing clear sound even at high volumes. A = Conventional diaphragm B = Off-centre diaphragm Sound Diffusion Processor for expansive sound Sound Diffusion Processor spreads sound in any space, for a richer and more expansive sound. Take your sound anywhere Let nothing hold you back Get out and explore with the XB100 by your side. This portable speaker is built for life on the go, and is durable and long-lasting enough to keep up with you wherever you go. Plus, it comes with a multiway strap that you can use to carry or attach. Up to 16 hours of battery life Listen longer—the XB100’s battery lasts up to 16 hours and has a convenient battery status indicator. 3 Take it wherever you want The durable exterior and strap make this speaker ready for just about anything. Hang it from your backpack, from your wrist, or even from a tree when you’re out in the sun, and the downward-facing speaker will project the sound down to where you are. IP67 rated waterproof and dustproof The extra-durable XB100 is waterproof and dustproof with an IP67 rating1,2 and a new UV coating, so you can take your tunes to go—whether it’s the pool or camping. Usability Better call quality with Echo Cancelling With the XB100’s Echo Cancelling technology, two people can talk at the same time with no clipping or cutting out. Add an extra speaker for stereo sound If you want an even bigger sound, connect two XB100 speakers wirelessly for stereo sound that will spread even further. USB Type-C® port You can charge the XB100 with the USB Type-C® port. Bluetooth® Connection and Fast Pair7 technology In one tap, the Sony XB100 enables quick effortless Bluetooth pairing with your Android™ devices. SpecificationsColour Name OrangeModel Number SRS-XB100/DModel Name SRS-XB100/DItem Quantity 1Model Compatibility SRS-XB100/D</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dbe77a6b-c0cb-414c-bdd5-bdf4e1be6da1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8e84269a-4c8a-43c9-a4ab-e8e9f965f1d7/web/1_1730714528894.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>179 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039849312487</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3727619959</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony WI-C100 In Ear Wireless Bluetooth Headphones Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPacked with features: The wi-c100 wireless in-ear headphones offer great value, with a wealth of features including long battery life, high-quality sound, splash-proof design and compatibility with the sony, headphones connect appLong battery life of up to 25 hours: Enjoy up to 25 hours of non-stop music and if your headphones are running low on power, a 10-minute quick charge will give you up to 60 minutes of playbackMusic source is compressed, it loses the high-frequency elements that add detail and richness to a track. Our digital sound enhancement engine dsee faithfully restores them to produce high-quality sound that's closer to the original recordingSpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessAudio Jack Type-CAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number WI-C100/BModel Name WI-C100/B</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1600b654-036b-4432-8b93-bb0bec3dc15e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/afb9dcb5-7380-48c7-89cb-f34011de043e/web/1_1730718316348.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>64.54 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037276199596</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2976860753</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM 20-Piece Instax Mini Instant Film For Mini8/8 Camera White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsIn black-and-white photographic film there is usually one layer of silver halide crystalsThe emulsion will gradually darken if left exposed to lightFilm renders all colors in shades of grey approximately matching their subjective brightnessOverviewDo not store in excessive heat or in any extreme temperature The photographic and physical properties of film are adversely affected by high temperature and humidity, and may cause the ink to dissolve, to minimize these adverse effects, film should be stored in a dry, well ventilated place. Long-term storage if you wish to storage the film For long term it is best to keep film in a refrigerator (at a temperature below 10° C). place opened film packs into polyethylene or vinyl bags before refrigerating them. After removing film from a refrigerator, you should wait (at least 12 hours) for it to reach room temperature before opening It. If you open the film while it is still cold, it may be adversely affected by condensation. (Note; do not store in a freezer). film temperature at time of use quick, instant developing is possible when working in temperatures between 41-104° fatter loading film into a camera, It is best you should expose it as soon as possible. Fujifilm Instax Mini 8 film is for all Instax Mini cameras and comes in a handy cartridge. It offers stunning instant pictures that you can fit into a purse, wallet or mini photo frame. Instax film ensures Sharp, clear reproduction, vivid color and natural skin tonsured you will get 20 film sheets (It is never enough of this films)SpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number 4. 33E+09</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eb6726d7-1d0d-4c2e-942c-597a4b0f5a21</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1d5d3132-73a3-4d28-a067-23beb7bbc122/web/1_1730713383513.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>99 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029768607535</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8375868841</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony WH-CH520 Wireless Bluetooth On Ear With Mic For Phone Call White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAll-day listening with quality sound - Listen to your music throughout the day without interruptionsThe WH-CH520 are wireless, lightweightHave a battery life long enough to keep up with youSpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessAudio Headphone Type On-EarModel Number WH-CH520/WZ EModel Name WH-CH520/WZ E</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8201a189-49e5-4c08-9177-eea94e1b13e1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/67ff4085-0407-4b7d-8c97-09590384609e/web/1_1730713193878.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>130 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083758688416</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6035030338</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony SRS-XB100 Wireless Bluetooth Portable Lightweight Super-Compact Travel Speaker, Extra-Durable IP67 Waterproof & Dustproof, 16 Hour Battery, Versatile Strap, and Hands-Free Calling New Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEnjoy powerful, clear sound, with a deep bassSound Diffusion Processor expands sound far and wideWaterproof and dustproof (IP67 rated)Up to 16 hours of battery life with indicatorCompact portable design with versatile strap included. Compatible with a second speaker for stereo sound. Connect and stream music easily with Bluetooth. Crystal-clear hands-free calling. Microphone w/ echo cancelling technology. USB Type-C portOverviewSony SRS-XB100 Wireless Bluetooth Portable Lightweight Super-Compact Travel Speaker, Extra-Durable IP67 Waterproof &amp;amp; Dustproof, 16 Hour Battery, Versatile Strap, and Hands-Free CallingSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothAverage Battery Life 16 HoursWhat's In The Box SpeakerFeatures BluetoothModel Number SRS-XB100Model Name SRS-XB100Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/76906140-99d8-4bd8-9128-f14b153169d9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d631d577-fb59-4c8b-80ab-198c7c459c22/web/1_1730713499831.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>169 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060350303381</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9966143462</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony Soft Carrying Case Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFor DSLR, HD camcorder, NEX, cyber-shotMovable interior dividerThree exterior side pouchesFront pouch with memory stick holderSnap coupler and zipper closureShoulder strap / Top carry handleOverviewThe black LCS-U21 Soft Carrying Case from Sony is a medium-sized case to hold your HD camcorder, Alpha DSLR, NEX or Cyber-shot camera. The case features a movable interior divider that will help you configure your gear to suit your need. Three exterior pouches-two on the side and one in front are provided for storage. The front pocket has a built-in Memory Stick holder. Access to the case is via its front snap coupler or zipper. The case is carried by its shoulder strap or top carry handle. The LCS-U21 Soft Carrying Case is backed by a limited one-year warranty from Sony. SpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number LCSU21Model Name SonyItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d0a925a1-166f-4dec-b0aa-b8b25d2d841b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d53fe81e-1e0a-4760-9a7d-98a66f0ca56f/web/1_1730719317135.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>79 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099661434620</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1655099437</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony Computer Entertainment ECM-G1 Shotgun Microphone (Battery- and cable-free), Black, ECMG1Z.SYU,</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsExcellent for recording human voicesLarge-diameter, 14. 6mm mic. capsule captures clear soundWind screen for trouble-free outdoor shootingAnti-vibration mount reduces minor bumps and mechanical noiseSuper-cardioid pickup for front-focused audio captureOverviewVlogger Shotgun Microphone, MI (Multi-interface) Shoe and 3. 5 mm cable compatible - ECM-G1SpecificationsColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Sony ECM-G1 Shotgun Microphone (Battery- and cable-free), Black, ECMG1Z. SYU,Model Number ECM-G1Model Name Sony ECM-G1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/93c63e80-f6af-4e37-bd1b-219ebac056fb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d923f663-6541-4b33-8cba-d34727a801c7/web/1_1730720153552.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>85 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016550994379</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6561371056</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 GVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version IOS 18Operating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber Of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone FlashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 MmProduct Height 163 MmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 MmModel Number MYWJ3AE/A , MYWJ3AH/AModel Name IPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f3b4d567-f1c2-4001-adae-4cb4df5f5695</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/751cda79-7097-42c2-88b7-13af387caa0b/web/1_1730724039865.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5200 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065613710562</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4320771546</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 GVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version IOS 18Operating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber Of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone FlashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 MmProduct Height 163 MmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 MmModel Number MYWH3AE/A , MYWH3AH/AModel Name IPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7a7908a0-a3b5-46f3-86bb-c1b9015068da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/226aab6f-2299-4137-98bb-446b6aea6ec8/web/1_1730724243936.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5200 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043207715469</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6983746047</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWL3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7910e583-c4c6-4d13-a780-adbc336d2ba6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7182a361-2202-4a02-815b-4e61008b983b/web/1_1730724458617.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6948.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069837460470</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2707839599</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/391a79f4-9c1c-417b-850c-2bece3248424</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/58919bdd-e944-4547-a276-2d4d01f80f32/web/1_1730725193698.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027078395999</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1672445576</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Single+ESIM Titanium Gray 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The legacy of Galaxy Note is alive and well. Write, tap, and navigate with the precision your fingers wish they had on the new, flat displayCapture stunning details with the most megapixels on a smartphone and AI processing. The enhanced ProVisual Engine recognises objects - improving colour tone, reducing noise, and bringing out detailWith 1. 6x larger pixels and a wider Tele OIS, photos and videos are brighter and more stable, making even distant subjects clearly stunning from sunup to sundown and everything in betweenSpace Zoom puts you in the middle of the action, even at night. With 1. 6x larger pixels and a wider Tele OIS, photos and videos are brighter and more stable — making even distant subjects clearly stunningWith massive capacity and greater energy efficiency, ultra's battery gives you extra life when it matters most you know, like the epic boss battle you've been gearing up forOverviewBehold the Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra smartphone, an exceptional amalgamation of incredible technology and superior sophistication. Whether you're typing up a storm or jotting something down, Note Assist makes a long story shortSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 8 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 3168x1440Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Titanium GrayDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature QuadFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24 UltraModel Name Galaxy S24 Ultra</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/46fd92d0-81da-40b3-8275-2b43b7dc8453</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aa1655f4-8f8a-4e1b-99ee-0200c2c1e995/web/1_1730725519042.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3190 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016724455767</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2148485769</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber Of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6R3AH/A,MU793AA/AModel Name IPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e77d8c28-60aa-475b-9f8e-0a7d162d94e5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bcad78a6-05d3-4768-a876-1a125b6a5540/web/1_1730697771903.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021484857690</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1962211776</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Bag Case Cover With Strap For Fuji Film Instax Mini 9/8/8 Plus Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsYou can just remove the top cover with two button snapsPremium synthetic leather with soft non-scratch microfiber interiorProvides great protection for your camera against dust, scratches and damagesPractical design and exquisite workmanship, high quality assurance, lightweight and extremely durable are the uniqueness of Instax Mini 8 CaseSpecificationsMaterial LeatherProduct Weight 159 gColour Name PinkWhat's In The Box Caiul Camera Case For Fuji film Instant Camera, StrapProduct Length 15 cmProduct Height 14. 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 7 cm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b15afb77-e8df-4c3a-91b6-0efb131d548d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c6dc1cd2-6b06-4336-9a9c-83573748c9ae/web/1_1730712039547.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019622117768</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9331714843</g:id>
      <g:title>enter Go Jam Brazen Z7 Earphones With Mic Black</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WiredModel Number Jam Brazen Z7Model Name Jam Brazen Z7</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1692b1a4-6b22-46a4-980b-4dac4f4a935f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/69c0b76c-6f1d-495d-bd3b-f032865a9c71/web/1_1730711884317.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>22 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093317148435</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2096658215</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony WH-CH520 Wireless Bluetooth On Ear With Mic For Phone Call Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAll-day listening with quality sound - Listen to your music throughout the day without interruptionsThe WH-CH520 are wireless, lightweightHave a battery life long enough to keep up with youOverviewWith up to 50-hour battery life and quick charging, you ll have enough power for multi-day road trips and long festival weekends. ;Great sound quality customizable to your music preference with EQ Custom on the Sony | Headphones Connect App. Boost the quality of compressed music files and enjoy streaming music with high quality sound through DSEE. ;Designed to be lightweight and comfortable for all-day use. Crystal clear hands-free calling with built-in mic. Multipoint connection allows you to quickly switch between two devices at once. ; Find your headphones easily with Fast Pair. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessAudio Headphone Type On-EarModel Number WH-CH520/BZ EModel Name WH-CH520/BZ E</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d32e6049-b374-450f-b6b0-9a201c849092</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b1a6a99a-89e8-41a1-ad91-a59c9acad7b5/web/1_1730712981424.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>130 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020966582150</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
