<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9525511126</g:id>
      <g:title>GEEPAS 55'' WEBOS 4K SMART Ultra HD LED TV With Full Color Optimizer, Voice Assistant Available, Gaming TV, Bluetooth Connectivity, App Store, Apple Airplay Support, Connectivity-AV-1, USB-2, HDMI-3</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStunning 55'' Ultra HD LED display with webOS for seamless smart functionalitySlim LED design enhances aesthetics while maximizing screen spaceFull Color Optimizer technology ensures vibrant and lifelike colorsVoice Assistance for convenient hands-free control and searchGaming TV feature for an immersive gaming experienceBluetooth Connectivity for wireless audio streaming and device pairingAccess to an extensive App Store for a wide range of entertainment optionsBuilt-in support for Apple AirPlay for easy streaming from Apple devicesUser-friendly interface for intuitive navigation and controlColor Temperature Adjustment for personalized viewing preferencesConnectivity options include AV IN-1, USB-2, and HDMI-3 for versatile device connectivityOverviewExperience the ultimate in home entertainment with our 55'' webOS 4K Smart Ultra HD LED TV. Featuring a stunning Ultra HD display, every scene comes to life with crisp detail and breathtaking clarity, providing an immersive viewing experience that will captivate your senses. The slim LED design not only enhances the aesthetics of your living space but also maximizes the screen space, allowing you to enjoy your favorite content without distraction. With Full Color Optimizer technology, this TV ensures that every color pops with vibrancy and lifelike accuracy, bringing your movies, shows, and games to life like never before. Say goodbye to traditional remote controls and hello to convenience with Voice Assistance, allowing you to control your TV and search for content using simple voice commands. Gaming enthusiasts will appreciate the Gaming TV feature, which delivers smooth motion and low input lag for a truly immersive gaming experience. Stay connected and stream effortlessly with Bluetooth Connectivity, enabling wireless audio streaming and device pairing for added convenience. Explore a world of entertainment with access to an extensive App Store, offering a wide range of apps and streaming services to suit every taste and preference. Plus, with built-in support for Apple AirPlay, you can easily stream content from your Apple devices to the big screen with just a tap. Navigating your TV has never been easier thanks to the user-friendly interface, providing intuitive navigation and control at your fingertips. Customize your viewing experience with Color Temperature Adjustment, allowing you to adjust the color temperature to suit your preferences for optimal viewing comfort. Connectivity options abound with AV IN-1, USB-2, and HDMI-3 ports, ensuring seamless connectivity with a variety of devices such as gaming consoles, Blu-ray players, and more. Whether you're watching movies, playing games, or streaming your favorite shows, our 55'' webOS 4K Smart Ultra HD LED TV delivers an unparalleled entertainment experience that will delight the senses and elevate your home entertainment setup to new heights. SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 3Video Format 4K Ultra HDRAM Size 1. 5 GBInternal Memory 8 GBScreen Size 55 inRefresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Remote Control , User manual and Warranty CardAudio Jack 3. 5 mmViewing Distance 3. 2 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 123 cmProduct Height 71 cmProduct Width/Depth 7. 5 cmModel Number GLED5507SWUHDModel Name GLED5507SWUHDNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6b32c3c2-ab49-4b08-92f2-0046336724a4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/95bc6de0-b933-40d4-9ff5-60d7e731104c/web/1_1730102261704.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>1075 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095255111267</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
