<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>6224633936</g:id>
      <g:title>Diamond Camera Lens for iPhone 13 Pro Max</g:title>
      <g:description>DescriptionHighlightsMaximum ProtectionFull ConvergeAnti ScratchHD ClarityHigh TransparencyShatter ProtectionAnti-Glare CoatingWater Resistant9H Durable GlassNano AbsorptionInnovative DesignEasy InstallationOverviewEnhance the resilience and clarity of your device's camera with the Green Lion Trio Camera Lens Protector, expertly designed to blend high performance with seamless usability. This protector is the ultimate solution for safeguarding your camera lens against everyday hazards while maintaining the quality of your photos. At the heart of its protection features is the 9H durable glass, which provides a robust shield against scratches, drops, and bumps. This top-grade hardness ensures that even sharp objects won't damage the lens surface, giving you peace of mind in various environments. The high transparency of the protector preserves HD clarity, ensuring that every photo you capture is as crisp and clear as without any protection. The protector’s anti-glare coating eliminates reflections and lens flares, enhancing photo quality under bright light conditions, while its shatter protection feature prevents the glass from breaking into sharp pieces, adding an extra layer of safety. Water resistance is another key feature, allowing the lens to perform optimally in rainy conditions or during accidental liquid spills. Moreover, the nano absorption technology in the Green Lion Trio Camera Lens Protector ensures that it adheres securely to the camera lens without leaving any residues, maintaining the sleek look of your device. This technology not only enhances the durability but also aids in keeping the lens free from dust and smudges. In terms of user experience, the innovative design of the lens protector does not interfere with your camera’s capabilities and is tailored to fit perfectly, ensuring maximum protection without sacrificing aesthetic appeal. Installation is straightforward and hassle-free, designed to be easily manageable right out of the box, ensuring that anyone can apply it with minimal effort. Whether you're a professional photographer or simply someone who loves capturing moments on your phone, the Green Lion Trio Camera Lens Protector is designed to meet your needs, offering unmatched protection and preserving the integrity of your camera’s lens. This protector is more than just a shield; it’s an essential companion to your device’s camera, ensuring longevity and performance.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dd176e71-36eb-43d2-8862-394128d504d0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/489ff955-7c32-4dac-8fbd-e619af37c26b/web/1_1727211737028.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>110 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062246339368</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8200512568</g:id>
      <g:title>HD Plus Camera Lens for iPhone 16 Pro/16 ProMax</g:title>
      <g:description>DescriptionHighlightsThe Ultra-Clear LensesHD ClarityAnti ScratchHigh TransparencyShatter ProtectionAnti-Glare CoatingAnti FingerprintWater Resistant9H Durable GlassNano AbortingInnovative DesignEasy InstallationOverviewThe Green Lion HD Plus Camera Lens Protector is meticulously crafted to provide comprehensive protection for your device's camera lenses while maintaining the highest level of clarity and performance. Designed for those who prioritize both functionality and aesthetics, this protector offers a nearly invisible shield that preserves the quality of your photos and videos, ensuring that every shot remains sharp, vivid, and true to life. The precision engineering of the lens protector ensures that your device's camera lenses are fully covered, safeguarding them from the daily wear and tear that can affect their performance. This lens protector is made with high-quality materials that allow light to pass through without any distortion, maintaining the natural clarity and color accuracy of your images. Its transparent design fits seamlessly over the lenses, providing an unobtrusive layer that blends perfectly with the device’s original look. The innovative surface treatment minimizes reflections and glare, helping to enhance image quality even in challenging lighting conditions, so your photos and videos stay clear and bright. Durability is at the core of this protector’s design. It acts as a robust barrier against scratches, smudges, and impacts, keeping your camera lenses in pristine condition. The surface effectively resists fingerprints, water, and dust, making it easy to keep clean and maintain a clear view for optimal shooting. The advanced adhesion technology allows for quick and easy installation, providing a secure fit that stays in place without any hassle. For those who demand the best from their device’s camera, the Green Lion HD Plus Camera Lens Protector offers a premium solution that combines protection, clarity, and ease of use. It is a thoughtful addition that not only enhances the longevity of your lenses but also ensures that every moment captured is as perfect as you envisioned.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a12cde76-169b-492a-9662-fee629f98664</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/29b58023-d3a7-4e2c-9fb4-10fd6b5fdda8/web/1_1727211962986.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>150 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082005125681</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4483096214</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab A9 Plus Graphite 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylish with a touch of cool, the galaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ features a sleek design and a smooth metal body. Enjoy samsung’s signature tablet design in graphite, silver and navy with each hue highlighting effortless charmGalaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ come with up to 8GB of RAM memory, ensuring less lag while you multi-task. Plus, the built-in 128GB storage saves all your hi-res videos, photos and files. You can expand the storage with a microSD card — up to 1TBConquer multiple tasks at once. With galaxy tab A9+, you can sketch out architectural plans and choose captivating visuals and video chat — up to three apps all on one screen without ever closing a windowTake a deep dive into a rich soundscape with speakers that provide an enveloping audio experience. Whether you're enjoying a movie or music, galaxy tab A9+ lets you fully engage in 3D sound with stunning clarity and depthKeep your information safe and sound. Store important data in the secure folder and monitor the overall security status of your device on the privacy dashboard. Make the most of your samsung galaxy experience, worry-free of security issuesSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name GraphiteCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTECamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless WirelessModel Number SM-X216BModel Name Tab A9 Plus</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e0b0afbc-7a84-4a29-9493-5b3424e05790</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3a7007ac-8b9c-4eba-b7cd-943789b16e06/web/1_1727154019479.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>739.55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044830962145</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2768861443</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Blue/Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A15Primary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dd4c373b-a25b-48ab-a2a8-20de1dea6bca</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/952c79f3-1a25-4a99-8fde-5ec8effb32bf/web/1_1727155220467.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>525 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027688614435</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7232950935</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro Dual SIM Midnight Black 8GB RAM 256GB - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS120Hz FHD+ amoled displayImmersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels67W turbo charging with 5000mAh typ batteryMediaTek helio G99-ultraOverviewUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS |120Hz FHD+AMOLED display | Immersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels | 67W turbo charging with 5000mAh (typ) batterySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 187 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 67 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Midnight BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 13Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number 7th_generation_intel_kaby_lake_7y30_processor 4nmFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile Phone/ Adapter/ USB Type-C Cable/ SIM Eject Tool/ Protective Case/ Quick Start Guide/ Warranty Card/ Safety informationNetwork Frequency Band LTENumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleCondition NewProduct Length 161. 1 mmProduct Height 74. 95 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 256 GBSensor Proximity Sensors, ambient_light_sensor, AccelerometerModel Number 23117RA68G , 2312DRA50GModel Name Note 13 Pro 8/256 BlackPrimary Camera (MP) 200MP+8MP+2MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/28ed0a45-dae6-4e7e-aae6-b5a47562283d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e9085c3c-fa92-401e-a11b-bda234735b79/web/1_1727156528847.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0072329509359</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3344061778</g:id>
      <g:title>OnePlus Buds 3 Deep Bass, ANC Immersive Sound Up To 44 Hour Playtime With Charging Case Bluetooth 5.3 Metallic Gray</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDual Dynamic Drivers - Experience deep bass and crisp highs with 10. 4mm woofers and 6mm tweeters, enhanced by BassWave️ technologyPersonalized Audio Experience - Tailor your audio experience with OnePlus Audio ID 2. 0, which creates a custom sound profile based on your unique hearingSilence the World: Adaptive Noise Cancellation - Block out distractions with up to 49dB noise reduction, which actively adapts to your environmentCrystal Clear Conversations - Enjoy superior call quality, even in noisy conditions, with AI Clear Call TechnologyLong-Lasting Listening - Stay powered with up to 44 hours of battery life, ensuring your music goes on as long as you doElegant Design - Ergonomically designed for comfort, available in Metallic Gray and Splendid Blue, complementing your styleOverviewThe earbuds feature dynamic drivers and BassWave™? for deep bass and crisp highs, complemented by adaptive noise cancellation and AI Clear Call technology. Tailored to your hearing with OnePlus Audio ID 2. 0 and boasting a 44-hour battery life, the OnePlus Buds 3 are your perfect, durable audio partner for any setting. SpecificationsColour Name Metallic GrayConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAudio Jack Type-CAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number E509AModel Name Buds 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/95cbb702-1797-4728-8aa0-bc8eb40869b4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/508e7baf-7afd-4a74-a7c4-53faa0699a33/web/1_1727154922781.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>200 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033440617781</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2667886422</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 Dual SIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung galaxy z flip6, AI phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB storage, blue, android smartphone, 50MP camera, flexcam, long battery lifeGalaxy AI: Your self-expression tool, galaxy z flip6, is compact and eye-catching, with galaxy al and a pro-level 50MP cameraDesign: Most compact. Big impact. Galaxy z flip6's new floating design is modern, slim and sleek50MP camera: The upgraded 50mp wide rear camera processes your pics through the provisual engine to capture stunning scenes and richer portraitsFlexcam: The flexcam uses auto zoom to zoom in or out on subjects, and provides a preview on the flexwindow for a hands-free selfie experienceSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 4 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Flip 6Model Name Flip 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7f5b69b5-3bfc-44e7-af12-76207d6bfe6e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/caf85a8f-da6c-4c75-b130-0816ef3102dd/web/1_1727156224728.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2333.45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026678864225</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5431411719</g:id>
      <g:title>iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWJ3AE/A , MYWJ3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c65b1f8-3e97-4de2-a0cb-67123777bdec</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5a8b577e-2887-4a82-af2f-f0a4e19d143c/web/1_1727352493519.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6080 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054314117190</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2843632944</g:id>
      <g:title> I PHONE 14 PRO COVER</g:title>
      <g:description>Crystal clear acrylic phone case. Compatible with Iphone 14 Pro. Scratch resistantSpecificationsMaterial AcrylicProduct Weight 2 gColour Name BLUE/PURPLEWhat's In The Box COVERPhone Case Material PVCModel Compatibility iPhone 14 ProType of Case Back CoverProduct Length 5 cmProduct Height 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 2 cmModel Number NAModel Name ISELLItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b370548-97ef-496d-9c36-b2d534948bb9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7cdaca42-080e-4243-948e-24737b5c1658/web/1_1727411846549.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028436329441</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7050133447</g:id>
      <g:title>cmf by NOTHING Watch Pro Smartwatch With Bluetooth Calling, AMOLED Display, IP68 Water Resistant Dark Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>Get reminder to drink water at set time intervalsGet reminder to stand and stretch after sitting for a certain period of timeGuidance to inhale and exhale to relax and relieve stressTrack and record sleep time and wake-uptime; monitor sleep stages awake, light sleep, deep sleep, REM and durationsTrack and record the daily average,maximum, and minimumstresslevels, and the ratio of relaxed, normal, medium, and high stresslevelsOverviewFrom running to high-intensity interval training, covering most of the daily sports. Track exercise duration (hours, minutes, seconds), calories, real-time heart rate, pace,steps, distance and more. Stay motivated by setting your exercise goals and achieve it. Resistant to water splash and sweatSpecificationsMaterial MetalBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 31. 1 gColour Name Dark GreyDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSFace/Dial Shape SquareBand Size LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 10 mmModel Number D395Model Name D395</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3d9e89d8-3da2-4b55-86a8-177ca3b8673c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c1cfac07-4260-4062-8daf-e899e35f5d1d/web/1_1727350981023.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>201 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070501334478</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7745440190</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MTL73 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU: 14.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 8GB Unified Memory, 512GB SSD Storage And Works with iPhone/iPad(International version) English Space Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>The Apple MacBook Pro is a high-performance laptop designed for professionals and power users. With its sleek and durable aluminum build, it exudes elegance and durability. The MacBook Pro boasts a stunning Retina display with vibrant colors and sharp details, making it ideal for creative work and multimedia consumption. Powered by Apple's powerful M-series chips, the MacBook Pro delivers exceptional performance for demanding tasks, from video editing and photo manipulation to software development. The efficient architecture of these chips ensures long battery life, allowing you to work or play for extended periods without needing to recharge. The MacBook Pro is equipped with a comfortable keyboard and spacious trackpad for precise navigation. It also features a wide range of ports, including Thunderbolt 4 for fast data transfer and connection to external displays. With its combination of power, portability, and premium features, the MacBook Pro is a top choice for those seeking a high-performance laptop. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MTL73LL/A / MTL73ZS/A/MTL73X/A / MTL73ZP/A/MTL73HN/A MTL73B/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/18b292a8-250c-4378-9aa0-e78de4275fdd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8e4b681f-f089-4b58-8f9f-7fd8ae2a93e8/web/1_1727351830539.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077454401905</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6259340550</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Blue - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Blue 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3282a349-5589-47bb-9614-c50a96b4b7e1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2b4dec55-e288-4d94-858d-8a828ea25fb4/web/1_1727352380306.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1435 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062593405501</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3407355921</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLXY3 13-Inch Display : Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 256GB/ English Keyboard(International version) Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies and music with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youComfortable and quiet, Magic Keyboard now has a full-height function key row for quick access to favourite controls and shortcuts. Touch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverLaptop Type NotebookDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 0 GBModel Number MLXY3/MLXY3B/A/MLXY3LL/A / MLXY3X/A / MLXY3HN/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2HDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noProcessor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b60d38cf-6608-44e5-aadb-32367f437757</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/77e4cf6b-a5db-4a18-9fd9-f40bab7ce8c9/web/1_1727354476204.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4269 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034073559219</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4087536078</g:id>
      <g:title>Original JBL GO3 wireless Bluetooth Speaker Subwoofer Outdoor Speaker Waterproof Bass Sound Mini Speaker multiple colour</g:title>
      <g:description>JBL Introducing the JBL GO 3 Bluetooth Speaker: portable, ultra-compact, with bold style and JBL Sound Pro. It combines with your style and accompanies you on the go Stream your music from your phone or tablet and enjoy up to 5 hours of music in a single charge with this Bluetooth speaker: wireless and hassle-free At the beach, pool, or even in the rain, the party never stops: the GO 3 features an IP67 certified waterproof and dustproof design Express your style: The GO 3 impresses with its modern design and expressive details. It is also available in a wide variety of colours inspired by the most current fashion Box contents: 1 x JBL GO 3 portable Bluetooth speaker, dimensions: 87. 5 x 75 x 41. 3 mm, 1 x quick start guide, 1 x safety plug, 1 x USB type C cable, blue/pinkSpecificationsColour Name BLUEProduct Length 8 cmProduct Height 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 3 cm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/806fb278-1cfe-42bd-9206-d4d4408e5bef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ce9e11ea-26e1-47be-bfe6-ec91563b7a2f/web/1_1727354705535.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>189 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040875360786</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9187790574</g:id>
      <g:title>iPhone 15 Pro 128GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 1” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for a 3x optical zoom and 15x digital zoom. Up to 23 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MTU73AH/A,MTUV3AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c77e534b-920c-41f5-bd41-a358c8411e91</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/29bb9219-8f3d-43ff-988e-eadf046a0210/web/1_1727352747364.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3729 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091877905741</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4006726207</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXCR3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU Processor/16GB RAM/512GB SSD/Intel UHD Graphics(International version) English Space Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXCR3JA/A, MXCR3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3984fd70-a1e6-4a67-8b57-b7986cfcb54a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2894e56e-a4ae-47aa-972b-a85d59eb4423/web/1_1727353661839.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040067262072</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2276786413</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Navy 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome NavyOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356EZKPMEAModel Name SM-A356EZKPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3136c375-4cb3-4445-90ed-a10f6923ea87</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aaee1c95-fe0a-4c1e-aca9-1df2e1d99690/web/1_1727414295965.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>805 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022767864138</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6526765557</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Blue Black 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Blue BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZKDMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/1D6NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/592136ef-d382-482f-a551-efff72e99511</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/abfe370b-fea4-416e-96bf-ad064997aeee/web/1_1727415037528.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>625 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065267655578</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5012558264</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Lilac 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome LilacOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356ELVPMEAModel Name SM-A356ELVPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/82208da8-cca6-45eb-b5d2-dbc01ab8e7f4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/49d2f014-2613-4110-9fbd-f9246d8c8110/web/1_1727415455732.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>805 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050125582646</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6908109943</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Blue BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZKHMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2723d877-1dac-4d1c-a8da-b81f96b40dc9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/796e7d65-c13b-47a5-8d7c-62e16da72fb2/web/1_1727416690053.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>713 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069081099433</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3534268759</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro Dual SIM Forest Green 8GB RAM 256GB - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS120Hz FHD+ amoled displayImmersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels67W turbo charging with 5000mAh typ batteryMediaTek helio G99-ultraOverviewUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS |120Hz FHD+AMOLED display | Immersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels | 67W turbo charging with 5000mAh (typ) batterySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 187 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 67 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Forest GreenDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 13Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number 7th_generation_intel_kaby_lake_7y30_processor 4nmFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile Phone/ Adapter/ USB Type-C Cable/ SIM Eject Tool/ Protective Case/ Quick Start Guide/ Warranty Card/ Safety informationNetwork Frequency Band LTENumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleCondition NewProduct Length 161. 1 mmProduct Height 74. 95 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 256 GBSensor Proximity Sensors, ambient_light_sensor, AccelerometerModel Number 23117RA68GModel Name Redmi Note 13 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 200MP+8MP+2MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3fe76258-4531-40d0-af10-425893e3addf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/33b0b5b5-8c37-4b3c-a693-45d8b5b50b60/web/1_1727416970617.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>710 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035342687596</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2292482472</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab A9 Plus Dark Blue/Navy 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylish with a touch of cool, the galaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ features a sleek design and a smooth metal body. Enjoy samsung’s signature tablet design in graphite, silver and navy with each hue highlighting effortless charmGalaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ come with up to 8GB of RAM memory, ensuring less lag while you multi-task. Plus, the built-in 128GB storage saves all your hi-res videos, photos and files. You can expand the storage with a microSD card — up to 1TBConquer multiple tasks at once. With galaxy tab A9+, you can sketch out architectural plans and choose captivating visuals and video chat — up to three apps all on one screen without ever closing a windowTake a deep dive into a rich soundscape with speakers that provide an enveloping audio experience. Whether you're enjoying a movie or music, galaxy tab A9+ lets you fully engage in 3D sound with stunning clarity and depthKeep your information safe and sound. Store important data in the secure folder and monitor the overall security status of your device on the privacy dashboard. Make the most of your samsung galaxy experience, worry-free of security issuesSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name Dark Blue/NavyCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTECamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless WirelessModel Number SM-X216BDBEMEAModel Name Tab A9 Plus</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/20a37858-afa5-4b3f-8a45-bd49f723743f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76450799-836e-41f8-b75c-b5ae496f3e10/web/1_1727413968977.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022924824722</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8749643574</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 6 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVHMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/da5d55ba-4a3d-4142-a1a7-93579746c19c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/192056ff-571f-4002-bc3f-08cecffd95ce/web/1_1727415631676.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>453.60 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087496435745</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2008445987</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Light Blue 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FLBGMEAModel Name Galaxy A15Primary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2ee5ee27-10c4-476b-8904-0f2033946ce3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7b2caae4-c750-49b0-9d0f-316782c70d2a/web/1_1727415864517.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>520 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020084459877</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5077103008</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor X9b Dual SIM 5G Sunrise Orange 12GB RAM 256GB - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 1. 5K Retinal Resolution / SGS 5-star Whole-device Drop Resistance Certification / 5-fold Eye Protection[12GB RAM + 25G GB Memory] Enjoy great performance &amp;amp; plenty of room for photos, movies, songs, and apps—and 20GB Super large memory(RAM Turbo)108MP Lossless Capture Camera, 108MP main Camera/ Motion Capture/ 3X lossless Zoom[Superfast 5G performance] Unleash entertainment at 5G speed with the Qualcom Snapdragon, a powerful octa-core processor with frequencies up to 2. 1GHz. [Massive battery and speedy charging] Work and play nonstop with a long-lasting 5800mAh battery, then recharge quickly. OverviewA luxury look and Xtra power, Honor X9b 5G is designed to stand out with HONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 360° Anti-Drop Protection, 6. 78" Amoled+ 120Hz display. Capture incredibly clear photos and smoother videos with a 108MP+5MP+2MP camera system featuring motion capture &amp;amp; 3X lossless zoom. Honor X9b 5G is a device you will fall in love with at first touchSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5800 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 185 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 78 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Sunrise OrangeDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13Processor Number Qualcomm snapdragon SM6450Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 163. 6 mmProduct Height 75. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Accelerometer, Proximity SensorsModel Number ALI-NX1Model Name X9bPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1d414497-2937-42f9-ae76-520c1f38066f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fc181b5a-fafb-49f1-86db-aa3946483255/web/1_1727420860669.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>925 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050771030089</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9193742585</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab A9 Plus Silver 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylish with a touch of cool, the galaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ features a sleek design and a smooth metal body. Enjoy samsung’s signature tablet design in graphite, silver and navy with each hue highlighting effortless charmGalaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ come with up to 8GB of RAM memory, ensuring less lag while you multi-task. Plus, the built-in 128GB storage saves all your hi-res videos, photos and files. You can expand the storage with a microSD card — up to 1TBConquer multiple tasks at once. With galaxy tab A9+, you can sketch out architectural plans and choose captivating visuals and video chat — up to three apps all on one screen without ever closing a windowTake a deep dive into a rich soundscape with speakers that provide an enveloping audio experience. Whether you're enjoying a movie or music, galaxy tab A9+ lets you fully engage in 3D sound with stunning clarity and depthKeep your information safe and sound. Store important data in the secure folder and monitor the overall security status of your device on the privacy dashboard. Make the most of your samsung galaxy experience, worry-free of security issuesSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTECamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless WirelessModel Number SM-X216BModel Name Tab A9 Plus</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2035feea-8531-40b0-a543-c4be925cd952</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f0f000d8-9b2e-4d17-b103-f6307aed7a9c/web/1_1727421191077.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>734 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091937425851</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2597776176</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Blue/Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A15Primary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e0199873-60f0-4efb-a06f-8004589f01f5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b371e715-2a57-48f3-8ece-f92ccdf4085b/web/1_1727413698081.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>525 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025977761761</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3838226993</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A55 Dual SIM Awesome Navy 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A55 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 32MP front camera, the 12MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 32 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 32 MP &amp;amp; AboveRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome NavyOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A556EZKVMEAModel Name SM-A556EZKVMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+12+5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/874480f6-91d2-489e-bd08-a9d1bd9dcbb2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/34c9742e-62c9-42f9-a365-23bbef39ac91/web/1_1727154509465.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1010 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038382269937</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5823905468</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FZKDMEA / SM-A055FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8f5102c2-77f8-4fab-a12f-259fab868a16</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4773a11d-16fb-4bc0-82c6-1c8e897ac93e/web/1_1727155569599.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>285 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058239054684</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
