<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>4119954193</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Mini Portable Thermal Printer Blue/White</g:title>
      <g:description>Colour Name Blue/WhiteConnection Type BluetoothModel Number D9997BL-QModel Name D9997BL-Q</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1a33470e-00fd-40ac-9b3d-3f2ca60dc37e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cd001d35-9e6e-4bc2-ab7e-0c4cfc69f897/web/1_1724735001032.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041199541936</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6861172591</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic BAK4 Monocular Telescope</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsProvides a clear view of long distance objectsLen renders clear images with improved light transmissionCompact and lightweight design enables easy operationSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 42 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 140 mmProduct Height 55 mmProduct Width/Depth 55 mmModel Number HW1717802Zoom Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9e74c381-f02c-413e-bf28-a8e69fd2389c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5b1f0037-7a40-4017-bc7e-74c294871179/web/1_1724745273892.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>58.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068611725910</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3182590241</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery Wireless WiFi Light Bulb Camera,360 Panoramic ring Camera,Full-HD 1080P with Infrared Human Motionsecurity Detection and Alarm Night Vision Light Camera,for Outdoor,Home,Baby,Pet Monitor</g:title>
      <g:description>Overview1080P &amp;amp; Panoramic Viewing: This bulb camera can provide you with a clear vision at any time. You can use the APP to control the camera to achieve 360 viewing without blind area. Wireless &amp;amp; Simple installation:This camera can be installed using a normal E27 bulb base(110V~240V),then you just need to connect the camera system to the router and open the app to setup the camera within minutes. Remote Viewing &amp;amp; Night Vision:This bulb camera can control the viewing angle through APP,you can access remotely view anywhere and any time through your Phone. Even in complete darkness, you can view clear images. Two-Way Audio &amp;amp; High Quality Service:Designed with built-in mic and speaker,this bulb security camera allows you to listen to your guests and to talk with your family in real-time. Motion Detection &amp;amp; Real-time Alerts:As soon as motion detection is triggered,this bulb will automatically send out email alerts and app alarm pushes. Thus,you can know what happened in your house and take appropriate precautions in time Overview Features: 1080P &amp;amp; Panoramic Viewing: This bulb camera can provide you with a clear vision at any time. You can use the APP to control the camera to achieve 360 viewing without blind area. Wireless &amp;amp; Simple installation:This camera can be installed using a normal E27 bulb base(110V~240V),then you just need to connect the camera system to the router and open the app to setup the camera within minutes. Remote Viewing &amp;amp; Night Vision:This bulb camera can control the viewing angle through APP,you can access remotely view anywhere and any time through your Phone. Even in complete darkness, you can view clear images. Two-Way Audio &amp;amp; High Quality Service:Designed with built-in mic and speaker,this bulb security camera allows you to listen to your guests and to talk with your family in real-time. Motion Detection &amp;amp; Real-time Alerts:As soon as motion detection is triggered,this bulb will automatically send out email alerts and app alarm pushes. Thus,you can know what happened in your house and take appropriate precautions in time. Specification: Sensor：1/3 inches CMOS Frame Rate：15 fps Resolution：1080P Illumination：0. 02Lux@(2. 0,AGC ON),0Lux with IR Lens：6mm Movement Tracking：Support Voice Intercom：Support two-way voice intercom Night Vision Mode：IR-CUT Auto Switch Movement Detection：Support Local Storage：Support TF card storage，Connect video/event recording， Maximum support 128G TF card Wired connection：Standard Powered by：DC 110V-220V Power consumption：&amp;lt;24W Working Temperature：-20°C ~ 80°C Non-condensing Working humidity：10% ~ 95% Non-condensing Package List: 1x Camera 1x User Manual 1x Bag of ScrewsSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box 1x Camera 1x User Manual 1x Bag Of ScrewsModel Name Ip Wifi CameraItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/882dbf7b-cc79-454e-af72-46135a565271</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/223145e6-8019-4a5e-a467-6b8fd5c22873/web/3_1724735827830.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031825902415</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4138560610</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Handheld Wireless Game Console</g:title>
      <g:description>With powerful rechargeable battery pack, it offers about 3-4 hours playing time and takes only 1-2 hours to chargeBuilt-in 500 classic games ensures endless happiness, you can share with your friends and have a good time3. 0 inch large screen gives you good visual experience. And AV out function makes you enjoy big screen gamePortable game console, easy and convenient to carry. Ergonomic design provides great touch feelingEquipped with a wired gamepad, the game machine can achieve 2 players mode, so you can share with your friends and have a good time. OverviewWith compact size and lightweight, the game console is easy to carry. And 600mAh battery ensures 3-4 hours playing time, perfect for traveling. It has 500 different games and equips with a wired gamepad, achieving 2 players mode, and you can enjoy great happiness by playing games with your friend. Featuring large screen and AV out function, it offers you great visual experience. Features: With powerful 600mAh battery, it offers about 3-4 hours playing time and takes only 1-2 hours to charge. Built-in 500 classic games gives endless happiness and it takes you back to your childhood. Compact size and lightweight, it is perfect for playing while traveling or on the go. Large screen ensures good visual experience. And AV out function makes you enjoy big screen game. Equipped with a wired gamepad, the game machine can achieve 2 players mode, so you can share with your friends and have a good time. Specifications: Product Name: Handheld Game Console Battery Capacity: 600mAh Playing Time: 3-4 Hours Charging Time: 1-2 Hours Item Size: 11. 5*7. 8*2cm / 4. 5*3. 1*0. 8in Item Weight: 99. 8g / 3. 5oz Package Size: 14*10*5. 8cm / 5. 5*3. 9*2. 3in Package Weight: 298. 7g / 10. 5oz Color: Black / White / Red / Blue (Optional) Packing List: 1 * Handheld Game Console 1 * Wired Gamepad 1 * AV Cable 1 * Charging Cable 1 * User Manual (English / Chinese)SpecificationsColour Name RedModel Number F1907</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/df782cd1-1aaa-4003-a29b-4eb0937a187b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4ed923ca-25ac-4e14-ab9a-c7c105bbf25d/web/1_1724735800558.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041385606104</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9200316218</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic 40X HD Night Vision Monocular Telescope With Phone Clip Tripod</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsLarge objective lens diameter offers a brighter and wider field of viewFeatures a rugged, high-quality finish with sure-grip coating for a comfortable holdScrupulously crafted optics ensure high brightness and render top-quality imagesSpecificationsColour Name BlackNight Vision Lens YesModel Number 40X60</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/980d207c-122d-4f54-99cf-f443d4536c4b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e337005c-7a89-4f52-84bd-3eeccedffd20/web/1_1724746414099.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>58.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092003162182</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2735978158</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic USB Magnetic Charger For Huawei GT/GT2/Honor Magic Smartwatch White</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewFeaturing magnetic absorption design, can stably charge the watch. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number DWYYC4978313Model Name DWYYC4978313</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e787d295-d307-438b-bde3-0f0004a175b8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3fe9cae8-66cd-40da-b09f-64b8b42a83a7/web/1_1724748377250.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>58.05 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027359781589</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>Sharpdo MGY-001 Laser Landscape Projector Light With Tripod Blue/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEmits a powerful beam of light which illuminates the area with a bright radiancePremium housing construction proffers added protectionVersatile fixture perfectly harmonises with both modern and contemporary home decor schemesOverviewMaterial Composition: Aluminium, Alloy, Laser Colour: Red/Green, Working Life: 3000 hours, Output Power: DC 5V/1. 0A, Laser Classification: 3BSpecificationsColour Name Blue/BlackModel Number 165342102Model Name MGY-001Item Quantity 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e0b65714-bd3d-4a3d-909d-19a241b4aa8e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b032144a-9959-4ec2-8ff5-ff89ac54989f/web/1_1724747847436.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8528574157</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6R3AH/A,MU793AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5f4fbfa4-0179-4bc4-8471-a887f1777d3d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d17f0cf8-211f-4ba9-b896-0ae9406a8833/web/1_1728374567885.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085285741572</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9686869344</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - White Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN13</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/73d88b22-09ca-4571-a7f4-77533dc86fe3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/635679a0-5095-4ce0-bbfa-8797abe7a9c9/web/1_1728377844192.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096868693447</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3362915653</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro - 256 GB/Desert Titanium (Discounted)</g:title>
      <g:description>Description: • STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass• TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. • MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra-Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. • PRO VIDEO—Take your videos to a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. • PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. • THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. • A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. • CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. • VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/112916ec-8740-492c-8191-7b30743ba07b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7e849fa8-da17-4f85-8560-c9355ac369e5/web/1_1728367134820.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033629156537</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5468691327</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Foldable Laptop Table Stand Vented Computer Desk Bed Lap Tray 360 Degree Adjustable with Mouse Pad Cooling Fans Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGood Seam Strength For DurabilityAdds More Grace To Your Beautiful Interior DécorMade Of High Quality MaterialsSpecificationsMaterial AluminiumColour Name BlackModel Number 4649756163Model Name Laptop Table Stand VentedItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1108bffd-2206-41bf-8069-52b29d25189b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9e2e185c-937d-4b5b-aba7-e165cc595649/web/1_1724740969807.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>57.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054686913277</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8743950977</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Desert Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWN3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e895e7a6-cb51-44ff-b029-88b7ed494de1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/37a5dfb3-fe31-41d9-842c-8815d0783f24/web/1_1728378506822.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6900 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087439509779</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4787613899</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Built-in 168 Retro Classic Handheld Mini Portable Game With 2.8 inch LCD Display</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmall enough to carry in your pocket, you can play it anywhere and anytime, perfect for travel or on the go. 2. 8in color screen; built-in rechargeable li-ion battery. Shares tremendous retro game fun, helps to kill the boring time and brings back the best childhood memory. Built-in 168 games allows you play all your favorite games. Great gifts for friends, family members. OverviewThe Handheld Game Console features built-in 168 games which allows you play all your favorite games, it's suitable for kids to develop intelligence, and expand thinking ability. , Features:, Small enough to carry in your pocket, you can play it anywhere and anytime, perfect for travel or on the go. , 2. 8in color screen; built-in rechargeable li-ion battery. , Shares tremendous retro game fun, helps to kill the boring time and brings back the best childhood memory. , Built-in 168 games allows you play all your favorite games. , Great gifts for friends, family members. , Specifications:, Colors: red, blue, white, black, yellow (optional), Recommended age: up of 3 ages, Screen: 2. 8 inch LCD, Battery: 5V, 800mAh lithium battery, Item size: 113 * 78 * 20mm / 4. 45 * 3. 07 * 0. 79in, Item weight: 85g / 3. 00ounce, Package size: 140 * 100 * 55mm / 5. 51 * 3. 94 * 2. 17in, Package weight: 185g / 6. 53ounce, Package list:, 1 * Handheld Game Console, 1 * Lithium Battery, 1 * User Manaul, 1 * USB Charge Cable, 1 * AV CableSpecificationsProduct Weight 85 gColour Name BlueConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PC GamesProduct Length 4. 45 cmProduct Height 0. 79 cmProduct Width/Depth 3. 07 cmModel Number 1759-ZModel Name 1759-Z</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/19867abc-eeb4-4872-9539-e863d753d5d8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5da04728-62e6-42eb-8e20-9d325d0c79ea/web/1_1724684782300.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>56 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047876138994</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2868148873</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColor Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN23AE/A , MYN23AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a26ef76a-a288-4b6a-8d2e-7a562cb04866</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/15c3a526-09ba-4224-8c61-31465721d953/web/1_1728372091998.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5185 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028681488733</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5741094890</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWL3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6d773a00-8e2f-4d6c-8bd2-5e5da1975b9f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b7688dbd-e682-4644-bdd5-75090b8a82f0/web/1_1728377475058.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057410948903</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4749313841</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Natural Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN33</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/94fd327f-aaee-4210-9715-1a1b4dd89d66</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3d79ba97-72b6-4a37-ac2f-49739f73420b/web/1_1728372986469.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047493138414</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
