<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9403015132</g:id>
      <g:title>IPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWJ3AE/A , MYWJ3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8d209fd4-5d9b-49cb-817c-b97db4225e79</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/53a60e40-186b-4429-8f6b-c5360273c536/web/1_1727437818532.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094030151320</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6397001402</g:id>
      <g:title>Iphone 13 Pro 256</g:title>
      <g:description>iphone 13 pro 256gb excellent condition working perfectly with charger</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/32f6facc-cb0a-4958-9a41-dc4c81e02d51</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8a79d079-e919-4586-b7ef-52146ff1c2d9/web/1_1728237223911.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>1950 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063970014026</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3688274103</g:id>
      <g:title>Galaxy z flip5</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy zflip 5 with 8GB, not used less than four month, new</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/29827d12-a27a-416e-bf41-02930843e2dd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/203ca51f-2f75-4422-9a03-d0932de4d02d/web/image_picker_6976B8CD-438A-4975-946C-51E6FF5B57ED-19038-0000141AE3B97234.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2200 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036882741038</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6534830155</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Handheld Retro Wireless Game Console</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsWith powerful rechargeable battery pack, it offers about 3-4 hours playing time and takes only 1-2 hours to chargeBuilt-in 500 classic games ensures endless happiness, you can share with your friends and have a good time3. 0 inch large screen gives you good visual experience. And AV out function makes you enjoy big screen gamePortable game console, easy and convenient to carry. Ergonomic design provides great touch feelingSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number F1906</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0f43a12e-3940-490c-98eb-a98d09d5c63c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b5b9d640-635a-494e-873a-118a01fdcbcd/web/1_1724760297440.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065348301554</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
