<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9733956277</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple HomePod Smart Speaker White</g:title>
      <g:description>Use HomePod to send messages using just your voice. And when you receive a text, Siri can read it to youHomePod is a hub for controlling your smart home accessories - from a single light bulb to the whole house - with just your voiceApple Music unlocks virtually every song you can imagine. Siri helps you find exactly what you want to hear, and what you want to hear next - including new music across a huge range of genres and moodsPlace HomePod anywhere in the room. It automatically analyzes the acoustics, adjusts the sound based on the speaker’s location, and separates the music into direct and ambient soundMulti-room speaker support with AirPlay 2, Six-microphone array for far-field Siri, Internal bass-EQ Microphone, High-excursion woofer with custom amplifier, Stereo pair capable, Array of seven horn-loaded tweeters, each with its own custom amplifierOverviewThe all-around sound of home. HomePod is a breakthrough speaker that adapts to its location and delivers high-fidelity audio wherever it’s playing. Together with Apple Music and Siri, it creates an entirely new way for you to discover and interact with music at home. And it can help you and your whole family with everyday tasks — and control your smart home — all with just your voice. Major sound, minor scale. This purposefully designed speaker creates rich, nuanced sound that defies its size. HomePod combines custom Apple-engineered audio technology and advanced software to deliver precision sound that fills the room. And at less than 18 centimetres tall, HomePod fits anywhere in your home. Deep bass with range you can feel. The Apple-designed high-excursion woofer is positioned at the top of the speaker facing upwards, creating a wide range of deep bass that surpasses any traditional speaker. A six-microphone array, along with an internal bass-EQ microphone, analyses and compensates for the effect of the room on the bass response, providing rich, consistent sound. And a powerful motor drives the diaphragm a remarkable 20 millimetres, so the bass shines through even when the volume is low. Far and away an incredible listener. Six microphones positioned around HomePod allow it to pick up all the sound in a room. When you say “Hey Siri”, advanced signal processing, together with echo and noise cancellation, allows HomePod to hear you without the need to raise your voice — even if you’re across the room with loud music playing. After HomePod recognizes the words “Hey Siri”, what you say is encrypted and sent anonymously to Apple servers without being tied to your Apple ID. High-fidelity audio that’s all around you. A custom-designed array of seven beamforming tweeters, each with its own amplifier, creates tremendous directional control. Placed around the base and using a folded-horn design, they send the flow of music towards the centre and then out the bottom in a 360-degree pattern, resulting in an all-encompassing sense of space. This virtually eliminates early table reflections and allows for consistent high-definition sound. The biggest brain ever in a speaker. An Apple-designed A8 chip orchestrates all the remarkable audio innovations inside HomePod. Like advanced signal processing so Siri can hear you over the music. Real-time studio-level processing that maximizes the bass while minimizing distortion. Buffering that’s even faster than real time. And upmixing of both direct and ambient audio. You get amazing sound, every single time. Designed to be seen and heard. HomePod is wrapped in a seamless mesh fabric designed for aesthetics and acoustic performance. Available in white and space grey, it’s gorgeous from every angle — yet virtually transparent to the sound waves passing through it.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/08925468-d530-4225-a5e8-61655fe201c2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3a2f2c14-9c55-48f3-aede-aa85a773c2da/web/1_1733995958189.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1327.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097339562774</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5304540450</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Pink - International Versio</g:title>
      <g:description>Expandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name PinkCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Pink 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f15ce5ce-3fc6-4625-afad-2db34e12cf94</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3970800c-a578-4f67-b0ef-98838b8b6896/web/1_1733994934851.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1198.45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053045404500</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2434572034</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Dual SIM Titanium Yellow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The Samsung Galaxy S24 is universally use the new Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 across the world. The Galaxy S24 have AI-optimized main camera photos. Night mode is also better. Nightography Zoom will bring brighter nighttime photos with the zoom camerasThe Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra comes with emergency texting via satellite support over the 3GPP standard. OverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 8 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Titanium YellowOperating System AndroidNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number S24 Ultra Titanium Yellow 12/512 International VersionModel Name S24 Ultra Titanium Yellow 12/512 International VersionPrimary Camera (MP) 200+10+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6b892dc6-1881-4b66-9ac6-eb65d906bf5d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/86269ce1-4788-414e-a9da-b9cee603cc5f/web/1_1733996190114.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3469 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024345720348</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4744124263</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS 45mm Midnight Aluminium Case With Midnight Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneEmergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimatesBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Midnight Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 45 mmModel Number MR993QA/A , MR9A3QA/A, MR9A3ZP/A , MR993ZP/A, MR993LL/A, MR9A3LL/A, MR9Q3LL/A, MR9C3LL/A, MR9A3CLA/A, MR9A3LW/A, MR9A3CL/A, MR9A3CH/A, MR993LW/AModel Name MR993QA/A , MR9A3QA/A, MR9ALW/A, MR993LW/A, MR9A3LW/A, MR993HN/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/95b16876-aa12-48e1-a7d0-e8a62954adfa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/78dfa58e-7b67-4ec5-933c-72b6ac3f149e/web/1_1733995146349.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1321 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047441242637</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6175787286</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MTL73 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MTL73 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU: 14. 2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 8GB Unified Memory, 512GB SSD Storage And Works with iPhone/iPad(International version) English Space GreyThe Apple MacBook Pro is a high-performance laptop designed for professionals and power users. With its sleek and durable aluminum build, it exudes elegance and durability. The MacBook Pro boasts a stunning Retina display with vibrant colors and sharp details, making it ideal for creative work and multimedia consumption. Powered by Apple's powerful M-series chips, the MacBook Pro delivers exceptional performance for demanding tasks, from video editing and photo manipulation to software development. The efficient architecture of these chips ensures long battery life, allowing you to work or play for extended periods without needing to recharge. The MacBook Pro is equipped with a comfortable keyboard and spacious trackpad for precise navigation. It also features a wide range of ports, including Thunderbolt 4 for fast data transfer and connection to external displays. With its combination of power, portability, and premium features, the MacBook Pro is a top choice for those seeking a high-performance laptop. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MTL73LL/A / MTL73ZS/A/MTL73X/A / MTL73ZP/A/MTL73HN/A MTL73B/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8983a2da-370b-456e-b73a-d741cd4595ea</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ea8ef6e1-d8ee-4403-a5ed-a5d0b55fb3d6/web/1_1733995568057.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4742.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061757872869</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
