<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>5147651175</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Plus 128GB Teal 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 16 is called the ""iPhone 16 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A18 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4006 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1290x2796Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name TealDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MXVF3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a2940baf-a9ed-4300-8e7b-5a4d3f12b511</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1670e43b-aa0d-4795-9844-8f9eb839b8eb/web/1_1732857036692.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3691 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051476511750</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8914551086</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Plus 128GB Ultramarine 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 16 is called the ""iPhone 16 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A18 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4006 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1290x2796Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name UltramarineDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MXVE3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dbd4af99-1dfe-40fc-86ea-e62b74ae5268</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/06479123-91f4-449a-bd2a-009f3342bba2/web/1_1732858529593.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3671 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089145510865</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5665831328</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Natural Titanium Case With Natural Titanium - L</g:title>
      <g:description>Featuring a stunning, new black titanium case, Apple Watch Ultra 2 is the ultimate sports and adventure watch. It has all the connectivity, health and safety features for the every day. And it takes training further with the most accurate GPS in a sports watchUltra 2 is built for extremes. Now available in black titanium, the 49 mm case is designed for the toughest environments, and it’s certified to EN13319, the internationally recognised standard for diving accessoriesAction on the spot. The customisable Action button gives you precise control over starting a workout, marking a segment or moving on to the next intervalA battery made for the long run. Wherever you find yourself, the last thing you want to worry about is your battery. Ultra 2 is engineered to perform at peak conditions longer, so you can perform at yoursApple Watch Ultra 2 is the perfect partner whether you’re riding indoors, road cycling, mountain biking or commuting. From Bluetooth-enabled accessories to metrics to seeing them easily while you’re riding, you’re always ready to rollOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Natural Titanium Milanese Loop - LConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MX5T3QA/AModel Name MX5T3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d01087f9-2a97-4866-baa1-0eebbb5f5164</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1d800646-ff46-4dd3-9721-94113be98e8c/web/1_1732859059445.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3641 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056658313283</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5442524459</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN43AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/df67c1f7-1dee-4037-9213-195f6bc1e835</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b0618e6c-20db-4e9f-9c54-2202ddf81fa2/web/1_1732859575364.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5789 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054425244594</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5840270847</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRYT3 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU/8GB RAM/512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name StarlightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRYT3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5f75b9e2-230a-41f6-9b2d-9dfb14c7ac93</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3e1a3585-7508-4022-aba3-d9ecec043a22/web/1_1732861021525.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5081.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058402708475</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2555765515</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRXR3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU/8GB RAM/512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRXR3JA/A MRXR3X/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/99c8be8b-5c9b-4e99-a4e7-6970178319f9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/85c2099e-b75a-4d46-a8a5-fbd923e0a1cf/web/1_1732860769924.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4742.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025557655152</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2388333439</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MRW63 Laptop M3 Pro chip with 12‑core CPU, 18‑core GPU,36GB ,512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>Go all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 36 GBInternal Memory 512 TBScreen Size 16 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRW63LL/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Pro chip with 12‑core CPU, 18‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0c828466-822f-40ff-a1cd-38a2f7fba83a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b486eaee-4f44-4c81-8f8e-cca35abf3915/web/1_1732860543249.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>9495.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023883334390</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6237369411</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Gen) 10.9 inch Pink 64GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name PinkCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Pink 64GB 5GModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2ee5e5ce-ffb5-46df-bbd1-f462e813834d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/684bf42a-fde6-4b8b-ab02-932a45f3729e/web/1_1732859915895.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1791.15 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062373694118</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9988440071</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS + Cellular 45mm Starlight Aluminium Case With Starlight Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app. ECG app. High and low heart rate notifications. Irregular rhythm notification. Emergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimatesOverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Starlight Sport LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 45 mmModel Number MRMA3QA/A , MRP43ZA/AModel Name MRMA3QA/A, MRMA3ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/103282f2-ff6e-4545-a3ee-b70e2b1a756c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7671e7b0-db66-4869-b3b0-e8f833dce3cb/web/1_1732860056072.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1568.55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099884400716</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2091500151</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Physical Dual Sim 512GB White Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 ProModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2edd818c-5342-44f3-90e8-d498e8bded46</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/290a4dc4-2b2d-4d88-b46e-142ec0e93db6/web/1_1732861259875.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020915001510</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6255705691</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 15 Pro Max 1TB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6Y3AH/A,MU7G3AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e85b8254-e349-4890-b598-69252f17fb4f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ceccdc5c-95e0-46f0-b389-8c758cddbd36/web/1_1732859170891.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5879 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062557056916</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4911504705</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 FE Gray 6GB RAM 128Gb 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The vibrant screen lets details shine, and the cinematic experience is enhanced with the incredible sound by AKGYou can multi-task with ease and launch up to three apps all at once. And with over 1TB of storage when you use a microSD card, your important files can stay at handYou're watching videos, giving you plenty of time for a streaming marathonSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 12. 4 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name GrayCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band LTECamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless BluetoothModel Number SM-X516BZAAMEAModel Name Tab S9 FEPrimary Camera (MP) 8 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/522f098e-4842-467d-8b76-ba214e76395a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/34127b8d-0979-48a1-8670-361d59a0be2e/web/1_1732861534408.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1641 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049115047050</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7992910549</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Air 2024 (6th Generation) M2 13-Inch 128GB Purple 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M2, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad AiriPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Air packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Air and an expansive 13″ iPad Air that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name PurpleCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad AirModel Name iPad AirPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/06a5b9fe-dd1f-4b17-8273-eeff15595822</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/47d159fa-5012-4c69-886f-321413d30e91/web/1_1732858868017.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3049 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079929105493</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2329232626</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 FE Lavender 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The vibrant screen lets details shine, and the cinematic experience is enhanced with the incredible sound by AKGYou can multi-task with ease and launch up to three apps all at once. And with over 1TB of storage when you use a microSD card, your important files can stay at handYou're watching videos, giving you plenty of time for a streaming marathonSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 12. 4 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name LavenderCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band LTECamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless BluetoothModel Number SM-X516BLIAMEAModel Name Tab S9 FEPrimary Camera (MP) 8 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4b23eec5-3a15-4a2c-9bc8-2b166f818412</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1c30be7d-d351-48e9-b600-4446765f687d/web/1_1732854673777.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1641 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023292326269</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1569306122</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS + Cellular 41mm (PRODUCT)RED Aluminium Case With (PRODUCT)RED Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app, ECG app, High and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimates. OverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name (PRODUCT)RED Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 41 mmModel Number MRY63QA/A , MRY83QA/A , MRY73ZA/A , MRY93ZA/AModel Name MRY63QA/A , MRY83QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/323778d8-dde3-469a-8c2a-7436a0877ef8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a132f566-ec35-4146-a799-d4026ef0fe44/web/1_1732855312020.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1241 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015693061221</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3588808017</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2021 (9th Generation) 10.2-Inch, 256GB, WiFi, 4G LTE, Silver - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The A13 Bionic chip makes everything more responsive, from messaging to web browsing to using multiple apps at onceUp to 20% faster GPU gives you the graphics performance you need. Perfect for playing immersive games and moreA more powerful Neural Engine drives machine learning–based features like Live Text in iPadOS 15The A13 Bionic chip effortlessly powers advanced apps like Adobe Fresco and ProcreateWith all-day battery life, iPad is ready to work or play for as long as you need itSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPProcessor Speed 2. 65 GHzRAM Size 3 GBBattery Size 8557 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 2 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System iOSTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2021Voice Calling Capability yesProcessor Number A13 BionicNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraModel Number Apple iPad 9th genModel Name iPad 2021 (9th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4103727c-96ef-4d95-adca-8a5abf17d7c8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a4ef0875-a25a-4613-9064-729b3eddca18/web/1_1732857627030.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1949 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035888080172</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4509845279</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 256GB WiFi Yellow - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name YellowCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number MPQA3AB/AModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0c956a35-0528-430e-8cf6-566a83c3fe2f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cd621d79-e1fd-46a7-a305-52df3958855f/web/1_1732855157593.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1891 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045098452799</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2548743757</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 ( 5th Generation) M4 11-Inch, 256GB, 5G, Space Black - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b6b10b81-cba1-4510-b2b4-9649bfcf53c5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f0945cbe-c194-4513-9688-c96e71a3592e/web/1_1732855912799.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4495.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025487437576</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2747723427</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 15 Pro 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 1” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for a 3x optical zoom and 15x digital zoom. Up to 23 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number iPhone 15 ProModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1de03e49-60a9-43ce-ae47-59f416c77ec8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cdb0220b-78c8-4328-9b99-14ab2038838f/web/1_1732856263131.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4771 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027477234271</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1382809203</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRYM3 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU/8GB RAM/256GB</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRYM3JA/A MRYM3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e95b1429-0f53-428c-ae19-0bb1adbc025d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/efe470a0-209c-4982-8dc4-8b24eb4bf1b9/web/1_1732857317152.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4618.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013828092034</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4520340822</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Watch FE 40mm International Version Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>Body Composition, Advanced running analysis, Personalized Heart Rate Zone, Health monitoring: Heart Package (HR Alert, IHRN &amp;amp; ECG), Sleep ApneaCamera remote view, Quick camera access, Find my phone, All-in-one digital wallet, parental control, family setupOverviewSamsung Galaxy Watch FESpecificationsMaterial AluminumBattery Size None NoneColour Name SilverBand Material SiliconeDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSWhat's In The Box StrapFace/Dial Shape RoundBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number SM-R861NZSAMEA-InternationalModel Name WatchFE 40mm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1de872f8-0e6c-4d84-b8b3-b559fd01ea3e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/727d13be-cbde-4ee6-b497-8cb32ec30ff2/web/1_1732857463494.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>426.25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045203408222</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3534463224</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS 41mm Aluminium Case With Red Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app, ECG app, High and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimates. OverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Red Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 41 mmModel Number MRXG3QA/A , MRXH3QA/A, MRXH3ZP/AModel Name MRXG3QA/A , MRXH3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/958bc742-f5d2-483f-81d9-e9fcf4a399fb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/318da262-12a6-4224-832b-2acf79fa69e0/web/1_1732856908882.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035344632242</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8306504150</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Natural Titanium Case With Tan Alpine Loop - Large</g:title>
      <g:description>Featuring a stunning, new black titanium case, Apple Watch Ultra 2 is the ultimate sports and adventure watch. It has all the connectivity, health and safety features for the every day. And it takes training further with the most accurate GPS in a sports watchUltra 2 is built for extremes. Now available in black titanium, the 49 mm case is designed for the toughest environments, and it’s certified to EN13319, the internationally recognised standard for diving accessoriesAction on the spot. The customisable Action button gives you precise control over starting a workout, marking a segment or moving on to the next intervalA battery made for the long run. Wherever you find yourself, the last thing you want to worry about is your battery. Ultra 2 is engineered to perform at peak conditions longer, so you can perform at yoursApple Watch Ultra 2 is the perfect partner whether you’re riding indoors, road cycling, mountain biking or commuting. From Bluetooth-enabled accessories to metrics to seeing them easily while you’re riding, you’re always ready to rollOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Tan Alpine Loop - LargeConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MX4H3QA/AModel Name MX4H3QA/A, MX4H3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c0dd7160-93e9-4ad0-9729-e2a2ba71db6f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fdff9575-17bd-4d24-acbe-0c902fae764a/web/1_1732862392222.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2957.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083065041508</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1653620758</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 15 Pro 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 1” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for a 3x optical zoom and 15x digital zoom. Up to 23 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MTUH3AH/A,MTV73AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3e22643d-5a44-4411-8013-ad1dbc461992</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2484606e-995e-4cfb-a5db-945b1150e8e2/web/1_1732862572351.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4919 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016536207585</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4538646557</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRYP3 15-inch Display, 10-Core GPU Processor/8GB RAM/256GB</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRYP3JA/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1d177895-b02a-4255-af8f-c4dcf4768adb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fcac57bf-91cd-4ad0-b406-2e0a5017697c/web/1_1732862276268.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4661 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045386465579</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6264927475</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MQKU3 15-Inch Display, Apple M2 Chip with 8-Core CPU And 10-Core GPU, 256GB SSD</g:title>
      <g:description>15-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youTouch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 1 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name StarlightDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 MBModel Number MQKU3LL/AMQKU3X/A / MQKU3HN/A / MQKU3B/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 0Processor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c5d915fb-1a26-4033-89cf-f05b3a7629cf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f23d8fad-6ce4-4a11-ab1c-29d3337745bf/web/1_1732862849147.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4276 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062649274754</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9322292532</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Watch FE 40mm International Version Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>Body Composition, Advanced running analysis, Personalized Heart Rate Zone, Health monitoring: Heart Package (HR Alert, IHRN &amp;amp; ECG), Sleep ApneaCamera remote view, Quick camera access, Find my phone, All-in-one digital wallet, parental control, family setupOverviewSamsung Galaxy Watch FESpecificationsMaterial AluminumBattery Size None NoneColour Name SilverBand Material SiliconeDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSWhat's In The Box StrapFace/Dial Shape RoundBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number SM-R861NZSAMEA-InternationalModel Name WatchFE 40mm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e08b43cd-c895-4325-80a7-073eb76ddb25</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/851b9489-7c11-4423-ad49-d0405cb1949a/web/1_1732863054833.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>426.25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093222925329</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9971141256</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-/16GB RAM/256GB</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Monitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name MidnightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedModel Number MC8K4LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot YesNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/94d61ffa-be98-410b-9b9b-b127c144798e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fa415d62-1dfc-4bf4-aca2-8bcf325d8416/web/1_1732863830255.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099711412561</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1136219609</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air 13-Inch Display : Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 16GB RAM/256GB</g:title>
      <g:description>13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies and music with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youComfortable and quiet, Magic Keyboard now has a full-height function key row for quick access to favourite controls and shortcuts. Touch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 5 GHzRAM Size 16 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Monitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProcessor Version M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPUModel Number MC7V4LL/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2HDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3e4fb15e-c93a-4e93-ab51-09bd9056f3b7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3c68ac6b-b298-4981-92d0-d62929e0c57a/web/1_1732865054467.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011362196096</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7506869586</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU /16GB RAM/256GB</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Monitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name Space GreyKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedModel Number MC8G4LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot YesNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d2e1cd7b-0467-4839-8779-e9d4b2bb2fd6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6589ce44-8c3c-4c3b-af13-26e2db5d5812/web/1_1732865252955.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075068695864</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6808087118</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Physical Dual Sim 1TB Black Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 ProModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/baf99b44-dc23-4c49-b683-0e7272f7fe46</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f1e76fad-7c71-40d3-b3e5-da88cfd28d6a/web/1_1732865372178.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068080871187</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6251586687</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU /16GB RAM/256GB</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Monitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedModel Number MC8H4LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot YesNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1230e163-4c35-41c2-88e7-63b7cdad221e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4fd67126-3f03-4d2f-9987-099368cf23ab/web/1_1732864852885.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062515866878</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8109788991</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 13.6-inch MacBook Air: Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 16GB, 256GB SSD </g:title>
      <g:description>Front: Two USB‑C ports, headphone jackSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 256 GBScreen Size 13. 6 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyKeyboard Language English/ArabicGraphics Processor Version Intel UHD 600Display Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version Mac OS X High SierraOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProcessor Version M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPUModel Number MC7U4AB/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/44369553-2057-4cf8-a9a9-fec0faacde79</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e3a8b0e2-e47d-44fe-8668-a4a324f84d53/web/1_1732865798591.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3785 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081097889914</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6376188770</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MX2K3AB/A Liquid XDR Retina 14-Inch Display, M4 Max Chip 14-Core CPU/36GB RAM/1TB</g:title>
      <g:description>16-core Neural Engine14-inch Liquid Retina XDR display²Three Thunderbolt 4 ports, HDMI port, SDXC card slot, headphone jack, MagSafe 3 portMagic Keyboard with Touch IDForce Touch trackpad 70W USB-C Power Adapter Apple IntelligenceSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 36 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 14. 2 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackKeyboard Language English/ArabicDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS SequoiaOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number MX2K3AB/AModel Name MacBook ProHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version M4 Max Chip 14-Core CPU 32-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bbfba02c-cca2-4efd-9a50-df8473f82248</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a0800c16-4998-4c1e-8091-79d7361603cd/web/1_1732864208779.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>13666 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063761887709</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8026403276</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MW2V3ZS/A Liquid XDR Retina 14-Inch Display, M4 Chip 10-Core CPU/16GB RAM/1TB</g:title>
      <g:description>16-core Neural Engine14-inch Liquid Retina XDR display²Three Thunderbolt 4 ports, HDMI port, SDXC card slot, headphone jack, MagSafe 3 portMagic Keyboard with Touch IDForce Touch trackpad 70W USB-C Power Adapter Apple IntelligenceSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 14. 2 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS SequoiaOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProcessor Version M4 chip with 10-core CPU and 10-core GPUFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number MW2V3ZS/AModel Name MacBook ProHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version M4 Chip 10-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fbf814b7-026f-4508-b7dd-8e6bff20b5ab</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dca7b5b0-4a32-4077-aa06-15ea17253b6a/web/1_1732869553831.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>8799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080264032764</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4486393367</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 512GB, WiFi - Space Grey - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space GreyCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 512 - Space GreyModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 512 - Space GreyPrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8bd919ad-f392-4c26-97eb-67925aafe3cf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c75f1436-f63f-42b3-96a1-2d87529d24fa/web/1_1732865638215.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2911 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044863933679</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3791178253</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS + Cellular 45mm (PRODUCT)RED Aluminium Case With (PRODUCT)RED Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app, ECG app, High and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimates. OverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name (PRODUCT)RED Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 45 mmModel Number MRYE3QA/A , MRYG3QA/A , MRYF3ZA/A , MRYH3ZA/AModel Name MRYE3QA/A , MRYG3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fe8391b7-aaac-49dc-9e43-1fbc1441bc89</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/38efe3f6-25ff-4681-b162-d7edeca5d0d1/web/1_1732863925997.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1351 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037911782534</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9448859634</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS + Cellular 45mm Graphite Stainless Steel Case With Midnight Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimates. Up to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. SpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelColour Name Midnight Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 45 mmModel Number MRMV3QA/A , MRMW3QA/AModel Name MRMV3QA/A , MRMW3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/78525edd-7d3b-47b6-8d67-5409714df7a5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/011e6014-a231-4eaf-bea6-a4db9982c442/web/1_1732864019935.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1711 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094488596346</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9564338856</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MQKP3 15-Inch Display, Apple M2 Chip with 8-Core CPU And 10-Core GPU, 256GB SSD</g:title>
      <g:description>15-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youTouch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 1 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 MBModel Number MQKP3HN/A, MQKP3LL/A, MQKP3LL/A, MQKP3X/A, MQKP3B/A, MQKP3PA/A, MQKP3BZ/A, MQKP3ZS/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 0Processor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0894683e-fc55-4a17-8194-34fb91fba7ff</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e9b59b53-4056-44a0-8108-976719280a56/web/1_1732866017669.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4377.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095643388561</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4628968144</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXD23 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU/16GB RAM/512GB </g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXD23LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2b7f3dd0-729d-4743-9d84-b44485a2455b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/53917c94-49a0-477c-8712-eb773a1687e7/web/1_1732870863059.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5908.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0046289681448</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2060856425</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Natural Titanium Case- M</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple new LaunchSpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Natural Titanium Milanese Loop - MConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size Small/MediumSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MX5R3QA/AModel Name RZ410633739C</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c12be78f-8fbc-43e3-8640-6464eb4fbf3d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3d4db194-eb93-47db-b7c5-b31a32f2c5f5/web/1_1732870165978.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3694 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020608564254</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2698785438</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLXX3 13.6-Inch Display: Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU, 512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies and music with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youComfortable and quiet, Magic Keyboard now has a full-height function key row for quick access to favourite controls and shortcuts. Touch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 0 GBModel Number MLXX3 / MLXX3LL/A/MLXX3B/A/MLXX3X/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2HDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noProcessor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1026d5ed-4b04-4e3c-a1f7-54af77d82158</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c47e5df7-64bf-4848-b993-21d6e7bb56b9/web/1_1732869363390.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3948.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026987854382</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1451326506</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MX313AB/A Liquid XDR Retina 16-Inch Display, M4 Max Chip 16-Core CPU/48GB RAM/1TB</g:title>
      <g:description>16-core Neural Engine16-inch Liquid Retina XDR display²Three Thunderbolt 5 ports, HDMI port, SDXC card slot, headphone jack, MagSafe 3 portMagic Keyboard with Touch IDForce Touch trackpad 140W USB-C Power Adapter Apple IntelligenceSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 48 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 16. 2 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackKeyboard Language English/ArabicDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS SequoiaOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProcessor Version M4 Max Chip 16-Core CPU 40-Core GPUFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number MX313AB/AModel Name MacBook ProHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version M4 Max Chip 16-Core CPU 40-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7822f5c1-f222-4de5-a0e4-afe4e66fe5c6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e51bf496-f7dd-4532-8981-3c965c60aa4c/web/1_1732869112607.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>15789 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014513265061</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8693955532</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWQ3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9d7ef51d-1261-4947-9f23-864701f70755</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9b05d7b5-35d8-49f0-8480-6a3107de35ad/web/1_1732869943065.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6849 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086939555323</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6258422470</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS + Cellular 42mm Silver Aluminium Case With Blue Cloud Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Blue Cloud Sport LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWX53QA/AModel Name MWX53QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fa271646-e486-4cc5-83f9-8f80f184f054</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eda39491-d7b2-4ced-8ba6-65cb454f8058/web/1_1732866874862.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1763 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062584224708</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2661886278</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 512GB, WiFi - Purple- International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name PurpleCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 512 - PurpleModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 512 - PurplePrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5bb2b1b4-3fd4-43e1-bae1-69500feb8254</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/921f13e8-2855-48ba-86fc-df633b8ea9a0/web/1_1732866686939.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3297.55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026618862786</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1310335034</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 14 Plus 128GB Blue 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverview"The iPhone 14 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 14 is called the ""iPhone 14 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 14 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A15 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 14 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A15 chip offers a 6-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 14 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. "SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Lightning PortSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 4323 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1284x2778Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlueOperating System Version iOS 16Operating System iOSOperating System Number 16Processor Number A15Fast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Lightning PortModel Year 2022Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MQ523AA/A / MQ4H3AH/AModel Name iPhone 14 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 12+12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f546d446-a5df-4ade-ac62-e4466f777f69</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/92c01bf9-1a89-45df-9c94-9ff64076a7bc/web/1_1732867018544.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3083.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013103350347</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4657976357</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS 41mm Silver Aluminium Case With Winter Blue Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app. ECG app. High and low heart rate notifications. Irregular rhythm notification. Emergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimatesBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Winter Blue Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 41 mmModel Number MR923QA/A, MR923LL/A, MR923QH/A, MR923LW/A, MR923CH/A, MR923ZP/AModel Name MR923QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bb472c2f-0fc8-43d7-96e1-13a1370ce99f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3c5b1876-15b4-4b49-82b0-ed0cd9b1dc73/web/1_1732866204216.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0046579763571</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5968596752</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple HomePod Mini Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HomePod mini delivers unexpectedly big sound for a speaker of its size. At just 3. 3 inches tall, it takes up almost no space but fills the entire room with rich 360‑degree audio that sounds amazing from every angle. Add more than one HomePod mini for truly expansive soundBoundary-pushing computational audio creates the full, detailed tones of a much larger speaker — and HomePod mini turns it up without missing your voice commands. HomePod mini is designed to fit anywhere in the house. Its elegant shape is wrapped in a perfectly seamless mesh fabric that’s virtually transparent to the sound passing through it. A backlit touch surface on the top provides quick controlWith multiple HomePod mini speakers placed around the house, you can have a connected sound system for your whole home. Ask Siri to play one song everywhere or, just as easily, a different song in each room. Having powerful audio everywhere in the house couldn‘t be simpler — and each HomePod mini gives you total control, no matter where you are. HomePod mini also works with your Apple devices for features like Intercom, letting you quickly communicate by voiceThe HomePod mini will work effortlessly with other Apple devices such as your MacBook and iPhone. Heading out, You can continue listening to your podcast via your iPhone. All you have to do is bring your phone close to the HomePod mini to continue listening. Oh, and you can even perform various chores at home with the help of Siri. Easily communicate with your family members using your voice. You can use the Intercom feature if you have multiple HomePods in your house the HomePod mini will keep your personal information safe so it is an assistant who you can trust and make a part of your daily routineWrapped in a perfectly seamless mesh fabric, the HomePod mini is an attractive addition to your home. Oh, and its backlit touch surface on the top will ensure a quick and easy control. If you have multiple HomePod mini speakers in the house, you can even have a connected sound system for your homeOverviewLooking for a trusted assistant who can also play your favourite music seamlessly? Meet the HomePod mini whose compact size will fit perfectly wherever you place it. With the help of Siri, you can count on it to do your daily tasks efficiently. As for music, its 360-degree audio will enliven your room with your favourite tunes. Get set for an enthralling aural experience, as the HomePod mini will fill your room with 360-degree audio that sounds great from almost every angle! Its boundary-pushing computational audio will help in creating the tone of a larger speaker. Wrapped in a perfectly seamless mesh fabric, the HomePod mini is an attractive addition to your home. Oh, and its backlit touch surface on the top will ensure a quick and easy control. If you have multiple HomePod mini speakers in the house, you can even have a connected sound system for your home!SpecificationsProduct Weight 345 gColour Name BlueConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box Portable Bluetooth SpeakersProduct Length 8. 3 cmProduct Height 8. 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 10 cmModel Number MJ2C3ZP/AModel Name MJ2C3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7cbbded2-16df-44d4-9476-865000e60889</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/774570d4-0e50-41bf-bcff-5d853dcc7b33/web/1_1732866359869.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059685967528</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4445566104</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWR3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7a635671-be6c-4f8c-973d-e19e6cff8f6d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/038d6cef-beb3-47e2-ba65-0deab0991d5b/web/1_1732877433762.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6951 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044455661041</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4421551377</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Watch 7 (44mm) BT International Version SILVER</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy Al-powered health insights: Understand your body better and start your day smarter with Energy ScorePersonalized Sleep Coaching: A better bedtime routine starts with sleep trackingAdvanced fitness tracking: Take your fitness game to the next level with Galaxy Watch7. Craft your perfect Workout Routine with warm-ups, cooldowns and breaks in between, or compete against your past records to stay motivatedNext-level processing power: The new 3nm processor supercharges your daily routine. Quickly switch from checking the weather to tracking your workouts in no timeEasily track your exercise even in the water wich Water Lock modeOverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Watch7 Smartwatch, Silver, 44mm, Bluetooth, Sleep Coaching, Fitness TrackerSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CMaterial AluminumBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 33. 8 gColour Name SILVERDisplay Type AMOLEDWhat's In The Box Smartwatch, User Manual GuideFace/Dial Shape RoundBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Product Length 9. 7 mmProduct Height 44. 4 mmProduct Width/Depth 44. 4 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number SM-L310NZSAMEA-InternationalModel Name Galaxy Watch 7 (44mm)Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7f2a70bb-13cb-444f-8b6a-93e35237925f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/631131f4-77b2-4d6c-932c-81218fcce22a/web/1_1732880861736.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1201.45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044215513771</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7703515617</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRYQ3 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU/8GB RAM/512GB </g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRYQ3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b0322895-fd7f-4028-96c2-76d2e4810dc7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/54632a05-f223-4c25-9b99-2fc3e0bce541/web/1_1732878736721.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5081.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077035156170</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4837419114</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MQKV3 15-Inch Display, Apple M2 Chip with 8-Core CPU And 10-Core GPU, 512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>15-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youTouch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 1 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name StarlightDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 MBModel Number MQKV3ZS/A/MQKV3LL/A / MQKV3B/A MQKV3B/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 0Processor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4dd76d03-2b54-4c04-9b59-f77c214b1a58</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d5d9a0d6-0e94-4fb8-9460-f1ba50b44ce6/web/1_1732883180378.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4541 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048374191146</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7511457819</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MRX83 Laptop M3 Max chip with 14‑core CPU,30‑core GPU,36GB RAM, 1TB</g:title>
      <g:description>Go all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 36 GBInternal Memory 1 TBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRX83ZS/A/MRX83LL/A/MRX83HN/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Max chip with 14‑core CPU, 30‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eb0aef6d-6b4f-465c-8034-c34cb87f753f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/74934634-d36c-4ffd-8437-b65869ba1966/web/1_1732881111752.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>10755.25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075114578196</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8269139077</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MQKX3 15-Inch Display, Apple M2 Chip with 8-Core CPU And 10-Core GPU, 512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>15-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youTouch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 1 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name MidnightDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 MBModel Number MQKX3LL/A | MQKX3X/A | MQKX3ZP/A / MQKX3B/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 0Processor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/be384ccc-f79d-4027-ac7e-cac7bcf44b61</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4d115c1e-c73f-403b-9df1-03496b1cdbf3/web/1_1732879635064.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4545 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082691390776</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9104971887</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Physical Dual Sim 1TB Desert Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 ProModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/04fc464b-90ca-459f-a159-b4d711656d29</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/782a250c-f1a4-4db0-9053-d5ecf026d62e/web/1_1732880279954.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6710 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091049718872</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5535603499</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro 1TB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN83AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f05df41b-87fe-4a99-b21f-911bb9899061</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a79f3e68-b6f3-4da4-80e5-ccd12097ba01/web/1_1732879775797.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6490 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055356034995</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1965604646</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max Physical Dual Sim 1TB White Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d64f61dd-69b3-48e6-8abc-2f9643ec6637</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e830cd8d-a6fe-45f3-8e87-a10b795f6c41/web/6_1732879258951.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019656046461</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3696582030</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MRW73 Laptop M3 Max chip with 14‑core CPU,36GB Unified Memory,1TB</g:title>
      <g:description>Go all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 36 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 16 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRW73ZS/A/MRW73HN/A / MRW73X/A MRW73LL/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Max chip with 14‑core CPU, 30‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/94a9e0f2-4a02-4a1a-ba76-5c9aed3db807</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/36eaff15-b483-4f80-bc27-429f7bcb5ed6/web/1_1732880675977.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>12000 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036965820308</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3769524027</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MW2W3ZS/A Liquid XDR Retina 14-Inch Display, M4 Chip 10-Core CPU/16GB RAM/512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>16-core Neural Engine14-inch Liquid Retina XDR display²Three Thunderbolt 4 ports, HDMI port, SDXC card slot, headphone jack, MagSafe 3 portMagic Keyboard with Touch IDForce Touch trackpad 70W USB-C Power Adapter Apple IntelligenceSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBScreen Size 14. 2 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS SequoiaOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProcessor Version M4 chip with 10-core CPU and 10-core GPUFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number MW2W3ZS/AModel Name MacBook ProHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version M4 Chip 10-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8eb22d64-0d1b-4048-9789-7338935dbecf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a3355bc1-8ebb-4e99-8165-f4bfcdfda77a/web/1_1732880148933.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>7499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037695240275</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1790849942</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS 45mm Starlight Aluminium Case With Starlight Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app. ECG app. High and low heart rate notifications. Irregular rhythm notification. Emergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimatesBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Starlight Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 45 mmModel Number MR983QA/A , MR983ZP/A, MR9P3LL/A, MR963LL/A, MR983LL/AModel Name MR983QA/A, MR983LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/12375e75-1fc0-4a3c-aede-32b6e5ba0a94</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/085a7775-2d00-41fc-98e0-40adc155e3c4/web/1_1732877649244.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1570.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017908499423</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5858350212</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWU3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3dde28a7-f3f1-41d3-98a2-7b938b85fbec</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6514d87e-9efe-4895-ab83-97fbb2fa5cb7/web/1_1732878939866.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6879 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058583502121</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7381175836</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro-2024(5th Generation)M4 11-Inch,256GB, 5G, Silver With Standard- International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/61d7bab0-e35e-4024-82a0-9ce4e0c77193</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c3777231-d88a-4878-b2a9-a19164469308/web/1_1732877302726.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4509 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073811758361</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1078948507</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS + Cellular 42mm Rose Gold Aluminium Case With Plum Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Plum Sport LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWXC3QA/AModel Name MWXC3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4d39f676-9f80-48bb-9060-52131ea2ba91</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c75c6465-51b0-471f-8435-f75cd9931bdb/web/1_1732878421564.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2098.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010789485073</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5006869525</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro 1TB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYNC3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1ea4496c-6c71-42bb-ac71-3e90b27df691</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3157291c-bca3-46f9-b738-8eec5c35f750/web/1_1732883780198.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6490 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050068695250</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6848023379</g:id>
      <g:title>e World Pack of 2 Portable Airplane Phone Holder - Universal Travel Essentials Phone Mount with Multi-Directional 360° Rotation - Travel Must Have Phone Stand for Flying, Table, Outdoor Accessories.</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemTRAVELING ESSENTIALS - The airplane phone holder is a vacation essential for your journey, whether you're on a flight or any other mode of transportation. Easily attach airplane travel essentials to the back seat or tray table, and then it will free up your hands while using phones!MOUNT IT EVERYWHERE - With a foldable feature, the cruise travel phone holder is compact and can be carried around. You can mount your phone to a table tray, luggage handle, desktop, bed, kitchen cabinet, shelf, chair, etc. FLEXIBLE VIEWING ANGLES - The airplane phone mount features adjustable joints and a 360° rotation design, allowing you to easily position your device at the ideal viewing angle. (NOTICE: It's Normal to Make a Clicking Sound During Adjustment. )WIDE COMPATIBILITY – Eworld flying phone holder is designed for 4. 7-6. 9 inches phones. Such as iPhone 15/15 Plus/15 Pro/15 Pro Max 14/14 Plus/14 Pro/14 Pro Max/13/13 Pro/13 Pro Max/12/12 Pro/12 Pro Max/11/11 Pro/11 Pro Max/mini SE/Galaxy M12/Galaxy M32/Google Pixel 6/X'iaomi Redmi Note 10 Pro, etc. SATISFACTION GUARANTEED – We believe in the quality of our phone holder and satisfaction of our customers is our top priority. If you are not happy with our airplane holder for any reason, Please feel free to contact us to get a FULL REFUND. Item dimensions L x W x H 16. 2 x 15. 7 x 4. 8 centimeters</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4c05bb1f-8b83-465f-aa6c-aff81fda3545</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a9553839-c784-4c56-b536-cdf620680b58/web/1_1729153188493.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>29.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068480233790</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6181026508</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro 1TB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYNA3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/843bebac-e3a4-4aa6-8e4c-e08cfcfb5c3f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3d4de6fe-4462-4941-8b0a-4ea6d803b792/web/1_1732883910515.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6490 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061810265089</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9064356489</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 FE Dual SIM Blue 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy Al is here: Meet the Galaxy S24 FE with Galaxy Al, where every photo sparks endless creativity. Immerse yourself in the full Galaxy Al experience and unlock countless ways to explore your imagination. Photo Assist: Resize it, retouch it with Photo Assist. Use Photo Assist to easily resize, move, and remove unwanted objects in your photos. Transform everyday images into stunning works of art with our Al-powered editing tool. Design &amp;amp; Durability: Colorfully crafted for you. Discover the Galaxy S24 FE in stylish colors, featuring the Galaxy S24 design and slimmer bezel display. Camera: Meet the most powerful camera on Galaxy FE series yet. The ProVisual Engine is a comprehensive suite of Al-powered tools that enhances photos and videos with sharp details and rich texturesNight Portrait: Stunning low-light portraits with ProVisual Engine. Bring out vivid moments in dark settings. The Al-powered camera ensures your subject stays bright and clear even in low-light. OverviewSamsung Galaxy S24 FE, AI Phone, Android Smartphone, 8GB RAM, 128GB Storage, 50MP Camera, Long Battery Life, Large Screen, Blue (UAE Version)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 3. 1 GHzSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4700 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 67 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name BlueDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number Exynos 2400eFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name Samsung ExynosNumber of Cores Hexa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 4KAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewSensor Ambient Light Sensor, gyroscope, AccelerometerModel Number SM-S721BLBBMEAModel Name Galaxy S24 FEPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP+8MP+12MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7f124b75-a9a8-451d-84d9-49e785aa9e98</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/68000c63-77e6-4608-a52f-dcca1da09976/web/1_1732883680689.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1781 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090643564892</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9043290429</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MW2X3ZS/A Liquid XDR Retina 14-Inch Display, M4 Chip 10-Core /16GB RAM/1TB</g:title>
      <g:description>16-core Neural Engine14-inch Liquid Retina XDR display²Three Thunderbolt 4 ports, HDMI port, SDXC card slot, headphone jack, MagSafe 3 portMagic Keyboard with Touch IDForce Touch trackpad 70W USB-C Power Adapter Apple IntelligenceSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 14. 2 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS SequoiaOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProcessor Version M4 chip with 10-core CPU and 10-core GPUFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number MW2X3ZS/AModel Name MacBook ProHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version M4 Chip 10-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d0dee001-6b5d-4364-9fbc-6d71d6f5eaa6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/433ab82c-27b7-452f-9583-7cce22ad939d/web/1_1732883421033.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>8798.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090432904298</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
