<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>7930161144</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 15 Pro 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number iPhone 15 ProModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6894b8f9-187b-423b-9b5f-8bd41e5f05ef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/530d92b9-848f-4927-ad5b-f085da80ce0a/web/1_1735216046016.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079301611444</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3815349037</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 256GB, WiFi - Blue With Facetime</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YESFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - BlueModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - BluePrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b18f741e-42fa-4631-8cb5-20858fdc0035</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/51d103f2-98d3-4173-aec5-aac3f1c349cf/web/1_1735216691921.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2267.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038153490379</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7630459022</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 512GB, WiFi, Silver With Standard Glass</g:title>
      <g:description>The all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number MVX53AB/AModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2e336c69-01e7-41f4-bd70-2dbff3207932</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/59759526-0c6c-4d0f-a66f-25a2846a1269/web/4_1735216887957.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0076304590226</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3777156809</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWR3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/da1b5ad9-3003-4cf5-8451-50179db74874</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3f6c72ed-c05a-408b-ae0c-af9c46e594fc/web/1_1735217034813.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>7149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037771568095</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1432598577</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 512GB, WiFi, Silver With Standard Glass</g:title>
      <g:description>The all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7089f4ad-4278-4904-96d9-7cf58e3aa0b4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4d380efc-b08b-43fb-8716-d4550fbf9cb1/web/1_1735216453672.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5514 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014325985775</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
