<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>6008338512</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy M55 5G (Black, 256 GB) (8 GB RAM)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights8 GB RAM | 256 GB ROM17. 02 cm (6. 7 inch) Display50MP Rear Camera5000 mAh BatteryOverview16. 95 Centimeters (6. 7"Inch) Super AMOLED Plus Display with 19. 5:9 Aspect Ratio, FHD+ Resolution with 1080 x 2400 Pixels , 394 PPI with 16M Colors and 120Hz Refresh Rate 50MP (F1. 8) Main Wide Angle Camera + 8MP (F2. 2) Ultra Wide Angle Camera + 2MP (F2. 4) Macro Angle Camera | 50MP (F2. 4) Front Camera | Video Maximum Resolution of UltraHD 4k (3840 x 2160) @30fps Latest Android 14 Operating System having One UI 6. 1 platform with Snapdragon 7 Gen 1 Processor | 2. 4GHz, 2. 36GHz, 1. 8GHz Clock Speed with Octa-Core Processor Get a massive 5000mAh Lithium-ion Battery (Non-Removable) with C-Type Super Fast Charging (45W Charging Support) Get upto 4 Generations of AndroidOS Upgrades &amp;amp; 5 Years of Security Updates with Samsung Galaxy M55. Includes 1 Year Manufacturer Warranty for Device and 6 Months for In-Box Accessories. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 180 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Mobile, User Manual, SIM Ejector Pin, Smartphone, Data Cable (Type C-to-C)Processor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080p (100fps), 1080p(30fps), 1080p(60fps), 1440P (30fps), 1440P (60fps), 4K (30fps), 720P(200fps)Wireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Sensor, Gyro Sensor, Geomagnetic Sensor, Light Sensor, Proximity SensorModel Number SM-M556BModel Name Galaxy M55 5GPrimary Camera (MP) 50. 0 MP + 8. 0 MP + 2. 0 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/07103bdb-e6d5-4554-8ab9-db843987a1d4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9137b2c6-bb62-461d-8048-525af08dd019/web/1_1727687815622.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>980 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060083385128</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9520350867</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 10A Dual Sim Charcoal Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G - Chinese Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAndroid 11, MIUI 12. 5Fingerprint (rear-mounted), accelerometer, proximityMediaTek MT6762G Helio G25 (12 nm)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Chinese VersionScreen Size 6. 53 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Charcoal BlackDisplay Type IPS LCDOperating System AndroidProcessor Number MediaTek MT6762G Helio G25 (12 nm)Network Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDModel Year 2022Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number RM10A-4G-64GB4GB-BLKModel Name Redmi 10APrimary Camera (MP) 13 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b479a111-67ee-434c-8b4b-22360e1945b6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ffa76c6a-ba3c-4290-84a8-63f31786450e/web/1_1727687001160.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>273.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095203508675</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2473286288</g:id>
      <g:title>PlayStation VR2 Headset</g:title>
      <g:description>Escape into worlds that feel, look and sound truly real as virtual reality gaming takes a huge generational leap forward with PlayStation VR2. Experience new sensations with stunning 4K HDR visuals1, ground-breaking new controllers and genre-defining games, all made possible by the power of PS5Experience breath-taking virtual reality environments in clear focus with 4K High Dynamic Range visuals and up to 120fps1, as two 2000 x 2040 OLED displays deliver over four times the resolution generated by the original PlayStationVR headset. Enjoy comfortable play sessions through a vast 110º field of view and a light, well-balanced Fresnel lensInteract in new and lifelike ways, as the PS VR2 headset detects the motion of your eyes1, allowing for heightened emotional response and enhanced expression when meeting fellow players online. Version International VersionColour Name WhiteType of Console SoftwarePlayStation 5 (PS5)Model NumberCFI-ZVR1Model NameCFI-ZVR1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8e80e011-1711-4535-ac94-0629a8b187f2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/10a12b6a-09e8-4341-bdd6-6bb5d6e5813f/web/3_1727687751187.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024732862880</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3218648880</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea Smart Android Tablet 8-Inch IPS Screen Tempered Glass, 5G LTE Single SIM WiFi,Kids Tab Zoom Supported Face Unlock Tablet PC Purple</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThis 8"Inch WVGA Capacitive IPS touch screen LCD of CM815 android tab provides consistent and accurate colors from all viewing angles. Afixed a tempered glass on tablet screen for durable. In this tablet uses the Android 12. 0 operating system. Powerful and energy-efficient Quad-core processor,which has a more energy-efficient operation method and faster processing speed than previous generations of systems and chips. The tablet has 5MP front + 8MP rear cameras to record the beautiful pictures in life, also allows you to use smooth video chat and Zoom App by calling. This 8'' tablet is very light, and can be held in one hand. Tablet PC comes with an extra case that protects it well. Protect the tablet from scratches, drops, shocks, etc. In this leather case has folding feature to make stand keep on table. OverviewCidea Cm815 WVGA Capacitive IPS Touch Screen LCD 1080p Full HD, Lithium Polymer battery allowing you to enjoy reading, watching TV shows, surfing the web, playing light games and more, providing over 4 to 5 hours of mixed use. It also has an TF card slot that can be plugged into 64GB of expanded memory, can more store lots of music, pictures, videos. In this device have only one SIM card slot, and therefore, can only have one mobile network service active at a time. The compact and thin body can be easily put into a pocket backpack and carry it with you, suitable for any scene such as travel, business, home, and outdoor. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPRAM Size 6 GBInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 324 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 8 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name PurpleCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Micro SIMDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 12. 0What's In The Box Android Tablet*1, UK Charger*1, USB to Type-C cable*1,OTG*1, Kids Watch*1,Touch Pen*1,Bluetooth Wireless Earbuds*1,Key Ring*1, User Manual*1, Warranty card*1 , Screen Protector*1, Flip Case Cover*1Network Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pBattery Type Lithium PolymerFinish PlasticProduct Length 20. 6 cmProduct Height 1. 08 cmProduct Width/Depth 12. 3 cmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM815Model Name C idea CM SeriesPrimary Camera (MP) 8. 0</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f2e6a7ed-41df-4bde-87a1-b327f92dc5b7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e9585527-6ec8-4b10-81c7-fb7925dc6e6e/web/1_1727687574721.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>179.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032186488808</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9196304697</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber Of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6R3AH/A,MU793AA/AModel Name IPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2abd6b0a-6286-497d-992e-101a8932de95</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/70becc03-3c9f-4b0b-983e-d9c00c1bb6ee/web/1_1727696693541.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091963046976</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2766416811</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 9A Dual Sim Clear Blue 4GB RAM 64GB 4G - Chinese Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAura design - An experience that surrounds you with the concentric design that delivers an additional grip and overall practicalityFeatures P2i Nano-coating to protect your smartphones against everyday water splashes and spillsAI face unlock for instant unlocking with a glance, The feature gives quick, secure and convenient access to your smartphone using intelligent face recognition systemThe 13MP AI Primary Camera delivers dynamic and intelligent range of photographyHyperEngine Game Technology ensures your games load faster and you have a smoother gameplay every timeBrowse and download apps, magazines, books, movies, and television programs directly to your phoneShare your 4G data connection with other compatible wireless devicesRedmi 9A supports dual Nano-Sim card + micro-SD expansion, either card can be set as the primary card. Support 4G/3G/2G and support dual SIM VoLTE HD callingOverviewRedmi 9A brings a 16. 58cm (6. 53) display with wider, more immersive aspect ratio of 20:9. The clarity of HD+ IPS Display promises a captivating viewing experience for movies, videos and more. Protects eyes and reduces harmful blue light for an enhanced reading experience. 5000mAh enhanced lifespan battery delivers 25% increased charge cycles and ensures longevity. Redmi 9A's battery delivers 2 days of uninterrupted entertainment. Charge fewer times with a battery that lasts longer. The battery has a charge cycle count as high as 1000, meaning that the phone can be used daily for more than 2. 5 years without any nota-ble degradation to the battery. The high-performance Helio G25 delivers faster processing and a seamless smartphone experience with smooth browsing, messaging and video calling. HyperEngine Game Technology ensures your games load faster and you have a smoother gameplay every time. The 13MP AI Primary Camera delivers dynamic and intelligent range of photography, from cinematic landscapes to detailed portraits. AI face unlock for instant unlocking with a glance! The feature gives quick, secure and convenient access to your smartphone using intelligent face recognition systemSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBProduct Weight 196 gVersion Chinese VersionScreen Size 6. 53 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Clear BlueDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Android 11Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 11Processor Number MT6762GFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Smartphone, User Manual, Warranty Card, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantFinish PlasticModel Year 2020Network Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 1 mmProduct Height 164. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 9 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 512 GBSensor Accelerometer, Proximity, CompassModel Number 9AModel Name Redmi 9APixels Per Inch 269 ppiPrimary Camera (MP) 13 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bc14616d-46c3-4781-8f9b-0540a87d5308</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bc73e860-c1c4-4878-bfeb-cca4947904fb/web/1_1727687296222.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>258.25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027664168112</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7824582701</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A04e Dual SIM Light Blue 3GB RAM 32GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights720 x 1600 (HD+) PLS LCD Display13 MP Rear Camera with Digital Zoom Up To 10xand 5 MP Front CameraNano-SIM (4FF), MicroSD Up to 1TB and USB Type-C ChargerAccelerometer, Light Sensor, Proximity SensorSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 3 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 32 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEModel Year 2022Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1000 GBModel Number SM-A042FLBDMEA / SM-A042F/DSModel Name Galaxy A04ePrimary Camera (MP) 13+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f291e976-8148-497d-917c-79b1f28ca05d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d5bd8e93-8bba-4114-a441-bddfb84ec966/web/1_1727679448692.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>275 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078245827010</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3641796909</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea 10-Inch Smart Android Tablet PC Dual Sim 5G LTE Network WiFi Wireless Keyboard/Mouse/Protective Cover Zoom/TikTok Supported</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe 10-inch tablet, with its IPS hd 1280x800 touch screen, wide 178° viewing angle, and dual speakers, provides a clear and high-quality sound for an exceptional audiovisual experience in multimedia activitiesThe 2-in-1 device seamlessly blends smart tablet and computer design, easily transforming into a laptop with a bluetooth keyboard. With cost-effectiveness in mind, it's an ideal choice for families and personal useAndroid12 tablet with dual sim allows two phone numbers in one device. Offering 2. 4G/5G wifi and network 5G LTE/4G/3G/2G options, it ensures versatile internet connectivity. Whether using wifi or data plans, the tablet ensures seamless online accessFeaturing an ultra-large battery, it serves as an excellent companion for extended enjoyment, making it ideal for leisure and entertainmentOverviewC idea CM8500 Plus smart tablet comes with 10" WVGA IPS touch screen with HD(1280*800) resolution for a great view. WVGA Full HD 1280*800 IPS resolution is immersive, high-definition picture quality and high fidelity dual-speaker design gives you a more powerful visual &amp;amp; auditory experience when watching movies and listening to songs. There are many gifts like bluetooth keyboard,Dual Mode Wireless Mouse,Bluetooth Speaker,Wireless Bluetooth,Touch pen,key ring and lots of accessories comes with this tablet to surprise you. ●Item Name : Smart Tablet PC ●Brand: C idea ●Model : CM8500 Plus Specification: Display size and resolution : 10. 1 inch WVGA IPS Touch Screen LCD(FHD 1280*800) Network :2G,3G,4G, 5G LTE/Wifi Operating System : Android 12. 0(none updated) CPU: MTK6735 Chipset : Quad core Flash+Ram : 512GB+8GB Expandable Memory : Up to 64GB Support Zoom : Yes Camera : Front - 13. 0M Back - 16. 0M (Kids version) Falsh Light: Yes Sim Type : Dual-Sim Sim Size : Nano (not included) Wi-Fi Support : Yes Bluetooth Connect : Yes Face Unlock : Yes Charging Type: Type-C Power Input : 5V/2A Dimension : 10. 8mm Slim Body item size:241. 1*159. 9*8. 0mmSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10 inPrimary Camera Resolution 16 MPColour Name GreyCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 12Operating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesWhat's In The Box Android Tablet: 1, Protective Case Cover: 1, UK Charger: 1, Type-C USB cable: 1, Touch Pen: 1, Bluetooth Earbuds: 1, Bluetooth Keyboard: 1, Dual Mode Mouse: 1, Speaker: 1, Protective Film: 1, Type-C OTG: 1, Key Ring: 1, User Manual: 1, SIM Injector: 1. Network Frequency Band GSM/LTENumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless 5GProduct Length 28 cmProduct Height 6. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 19. 8 cmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM8500+Model Name 10" Smart Tablet PCPrimary Camera (MP) 16</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e12d8bf3-7a8f-4db7-88c7-0fbdff07a6cc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fe578a8d-0c1d-461f-8d4e-09bc4f9ec14c/web/1_1727678215268.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>288 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036417969098</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5539600121</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy F15 5G (Ash Black, 128 Gb) (6 Gb Ram)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights6 gb ram | 128 gb rom | Expandable upto 1 tb16. 51 cm (6. 5 inch) full hd+ display50MP + 5MP | 13MP front camera6000 mAh lithium ion batteryMediaTek dimensity 6100+ processorOverviewThe Samsung Galaxy F15 is a pinnacle of mobile brilliance, featuring a vibrant sAMOLED display for an immersive visual journey. Experience unmatched battery endurance, lasting up to two days, and revel in four years of hassle-free performance with a powerful MediaTek Dimensity 6100+ and up to 12 GB of RAM. Silence background sounds with noise cancellation, seamlessly share across devices, and enjoy superfast 5G speeds. Capture every detail with the 50 MP triple camera setup and have fun with the front-facing camera's creative features. Fortify your security with the Samsung Knox Vault Chipset and personalise your experience with Smart UI features. The Galaxy F15 redefines smartphone excellence in a compact and versatile package, catering to every aspect of a modern, connected lifestyle. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 217 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Ash BlackDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesWhat's In The Box Handset, Data Cable (USB Type C-to-C), Ejection Pin, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name MediaTekNumber of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassWireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 9. 3 mmProduct Height 160 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 8 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer,Fingerprint Sensor,Gyro Sensor,Geomagnetic Sensor,Light Sensor,Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-E156BLVGINS, SM-E156B/DSModel Name Samsung F15 5GPixels Per Inch 2340 x 1080 PixelPrimary Camera (MP) 50 + 5 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a668c623-175f-4ca5-ac1e-0b810bfb5d8c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d4ddb4b8-29f1-4c80-b84b-3fe358070b21/web/1_1727678558278.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>599.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055396001216</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5297110777</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Silver 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name SilverOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZSGMEA / SM-A057FZSDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f754d963-286f-4496-b138-0b0c7bb557f7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/da3157ba-e188-4f4c-bb22-f467587e024e/web/1_1727674672783.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>371.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052971107776</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5032476375</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi A3 Dual SIM Forest Green 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRefined and Stylish DesignSmooth 6. 71'' 90Hz Dot Drop displayMassive 5000mAh (typ) battery, and provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W chargingSecure fingerprint and AI face unlockSupports up to 1TB expandable storageOverviewThe ultra-thin design, paired with the clean flat frame, appears exquisite and stylish. Hold the phone with one hand to embrace trends and lightness. Provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W charging*. 5000mAh ultra-large battery, reducing battery life anxiety and ensuring full-day range. Powerful octa-core processor with a maximum CPU frequency of 2. 2GHz, more balanced performance, reduced lags, and more fun to enjoy. You can choose the side fingerprint or AI face to easily unlock your phone. Suitable for more unlocking scenarios, safer and more convenient. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 193 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 71 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Forest GreenDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 14Processor Number G36What's In The Box Mobile Phone | Adapter | USB Type-C Cable | SIM Eject Tool | Quick Start Guide | Safety InformationNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pNetwork Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 168 mmProduct Height 8. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 3 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number 23129RN51XModel Name Redmi A3 (4+128)Primary Camera (MP) 8+QVGA MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1ebc031d-35ab-449b-9f02-16010aaddce1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1042730f-9c1b-42a8-8411-05f08a6efdd0/web/1_1727679062574.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>299.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050324763754</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6417607055</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 200 Lite Midnight Black Dual SIM 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights108MP rear camera, portrait in the spotlightHonor 200 lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your handExtra-large AMOLED view, boundless with brightness and clarityOverviewThe Portrait Master 108MP &amp;amp; 50MP Glorious Portrait Risk-free Dimming AMOLED Display Lightweight Drop-resistant Design 108MP Rear Camera, Portrait in the Spotlight 50MP Light-sensitive Selfie, Fantastic group photo Ultra-slim in Shape, Crafted in Style Drop-Proof, Trust Enhanced Risk-Free Dimming Eye-Care Display 256GB Ultra-large Storage Dynamic in Design, Elegant in Heart HONOR 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, Exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your hand. 6. 78mm Thickness 166g Weight Selfie Light 50MP Front Camera 108MP Main Camera f/1. 75 aperture Marco Camera f/2. 4 aperture Wide &amp;amp; Depth Camera f/2. 2 aperture AI Wide-angle Selfie 78° FOV mode works while taking selfies, and switches to 90° FOV mode whlie taking groupfies. Multi-focal Portrait, the Art of Boken The Rear camera features three focal choices, each showing a side of your unique charm. 108MP image,Uncompromising Clarity The 108MP HD Rear camera can capture the excitement of your life clearly and vividly. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4500 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Colour Name Midnight BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number 6080Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek DimensityNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number LL-NX1 , LLY-NX1Model Name HONOR 200 LITEPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/31fd1c2e-7a80-474e-b4ae-23177d33caf8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/26e274c9-9331-435f-bf4c-cf975fc0906e/web/1_1727678775963.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>819.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064176070557</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2843632944</g:id>
      <g:title> I PHONE 14 PRO COVER</g:title>
      <g:description>Crystal clear acrylic phone case. Compatible with Iphone 14 Pro. Scratch resistantSpecificationsMaterial AcrylicProduct Weight 2 gColour Name BLUE/PURPLEWhat's In The Box COVERPhone Case Material PVCModel Compatibility iPhone 14 ProType of Case Back CoverProduct Length 5 cmProduct Height 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 2 cmModel Number NAModel Name ISELLItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b370548-97ef-496d-9c36-b2d534948bb9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7cdaca42-080e-4243-948e-24737b5c1658/web/1_1727411846549.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028436329441</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1813118012</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 46mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Black Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSeries 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 46 MmModel Number MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/AModel Name MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5e4b86fc-c828-4c48-a5a9-42b37bc02f4d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6cc881d1-ae06-4927-920f-0e935aae851f/web/1_1727680025843.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1899 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018131180126</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3407355921</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLXY3 13-Inch Display : Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 256GB/ English Keyboard(International version) Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies and music with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youComfortable and quiet, Magic Keyboard now has a full-height function key row for quick access to favourite controls and shortcuts. Touch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverLaptop Type NotebookDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 0 GBModel Number MLXY3/MLXY3B/A/MLXY3LL/A / MLXY3X/A / MLXY3HN/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2HDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noProcessor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b60d38cf-6608-44e5-aadb-32367f437757</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/77e4cf6b-a5db-4a18-9fd9-f40bab7ce8c9/web/1_1727354476204.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4269 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034073559219</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9187790574</g:id>
      <g:title>iPhone 15 Pro 128GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 1” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for a 3x optical zoom and 15x digital zoom. Up to 23 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MTU73AH/A,MTUV3AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c77e534b-920c-41f5-bd41-a358c8411e91</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/29bb9219-8f3d-43ff-988e-eadf046a0210/web/1_1727352747364.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3729 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091877905741</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4006726207</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXCR3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU Processor/16GB RAM/512GB SSD/Intel UHD Graphics(International version) English Space Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXCR3JA/A, MXCR3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3984fd70-a1e6-4a67-8b57-b7986cfcb54a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2894e56e-a4ae-47aa-972b-a85d59eb4423/web/1_1727353661839.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040067262072</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4087536078</g:id>
      <g:title>Original JBL GO3 wireless Bluetooth Speaker Subwoofer Outdoor Speaker Waterproof Bass Sound Mini Speaker multiple colour</g:title>
      <g:description>JBL Introducing the JBL GO 3 Bluetooth Speaker: portable, ultra-compact, with bold style and JBL Sound Pro. It combines with your style and accompanies you on the go Stream your music from your phone or tablet and enjoy up to 5 hours of music in a single charge with this Bluetooth speaker: wireless and hassle-free At the beach, pool, or even in the rain, the party never stops: the GO 3 features an IP67 certified waterproof and dustproof design Express your style: The GO 3 impresses with its modern design and expressive details. It is also available in a wide variety of colours inspired by the most current fashion Box contents: 1 x JBL GO 3 portable Bluetooth speaker, dimensions: 87. 5 x 75 x 41. 3 mm, 1 x quick start guide, 1 x safety plug, 1 x USB type C cable, blue/pinkSpecificationsColour Name BLUEProduct Length 8 cmProduct Height 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 3 cm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/806fb278-1cfe-42bd-9206-d4d4408e5bef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ce9e11ea-26e1-47be-bfe6-ec91563b7a2f/web/1_1727354705535.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>189 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040875360786</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7545112454</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7d0f3626-e449-473c-b231-fa5b46f7ca95</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0b7bf3bb-904d-420a-9b45-aab7925b44ba/web/1_1727437069747.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075451124544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7050133447</g:id>
      <g:title>cmf by NOTHING Watch Pro Smartwatch With Bluetooth Calling, AMOLED Display, IP68 Water Resistant Dark Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>Get reminder to drink water at set time intervalsGet reminder to stand and stretch after sitting for a certain period of timeGuidance to inhale and exhale to relax and relieve stressTrack and record sleep time and wake-uptime; monitor sleep stages awake, light sleep, deep sleep, REM and durationsTrack and record the daily average,maximum, and minimumstresslevels, and the ratio of relaxed, normal, medium, and high stresslevelsOverviewFrom running to high-intensity interval training, covering most of the daily sports. Track exercise duration (hours, minutes, seconds), calories, real-time heart rate, pace,steps, distance and more. Stay motivated by setting your exercise goals and achieve it. Resistant to water splash and sweatSpecificationsMaterial MetalBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 31. 1 gColour Name Dark GreyDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSFace/Dial Shape SquareBand Size LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 10 mmModel Number D395Model Name D395</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3d9e89d8-3da2-4b55-86a8-177ca3b8673c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c1cfac07-4260-4062-8daf-e899e35f5d1d/web/1_1727350981023.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>201 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070501334478</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6259340550</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Blue - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Blue 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3282a349-5589-47bb-9614-c50a96b4b7e1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2b4dec55-e288-4d94-858d-8a828ea25fb4/web/1_1727352380306.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1435 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062593405501</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9470959924</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery 360 Degree Wireless WIFI Light Bulb Security Camera with Motion Detection and two Way Audio system.</g:title>
      <g:description>Overview1080P &amp;amp; Panoramic Viewing: This bulb camera can provide you with a clear vision at any time. You can use the APP to control the camera to achieve 360 viewing without blind area. Wireless &amp;amp; Simple installation:This camera can be installed using a normal E27 bulb base(110V~240V),then you just need to connect the camera system to the router and open the app to setup the camera within minutes. Remote Viewing &amp;amp; Night Vision:This bulb camera can control the viewing angle through APP,you can access remotely view anywhere and any time through your Phone. Even in complete darkness, you can view clear images. Two-Way Audio &amp;amp; High Quality Service:Designed with built-in mic and speaker,this bulb security camera allows you to listen to your guests and to talk with your family in real-time. Motion Detection &amp;amp; Real-time Alerts:As soon as motion detection is triggered,this bulb will automatically send out email alerts and app alarm pushes. Thus,you can know what happened in your house and take appropriate precautions in time Overview Features: 1080P &amp;amp; Panoramic Viewing: This bulb camera can provide you with a clear vision at any time. You can use the APP to control the camera to achieve 360 viewing without blind area. Wireless &amp;amp; Simple installation:This camera can be installed using a normal E27 bulb base(110V~240V),then you just need to connect the camera system to the router and open the app to setup the camera within minutes. Remote Viewing &amp;amp; Night Vision:This bulb camera can control the viewing angle through APP,you can access remotely view anywhere and any time through your Phone. Even in complete darkness, you can view clear images. Two-Way Audio &amp;amp; High Quality Service:Designed with built-in mic and speaker,this bulb security camera allows you to listen to your guests and to talk with your family in real-time. Motion Detection &amp;amp; Real-time Alerts:As soon as motion detection is triggered,this bulb will automatically send out email alerts and app alarm pushes. Thus,you can know what happened in your house and take appropriate precautions in time. Specification: Sensor：1/3 inches CMOS Frame Rate：15 fps Resolution：1080P Illumination：0. 02Lux@(2. 0,AGC ON),0Lux with IR Lens：6mm Movement Tracking：Support Voice Intercom：Support two-way voice intercom Night Vision Mode：IR-CUT Auto Switch Movement Detection：Support Local Storage：Support TF card storage，Connect video/event recording， Maximum support 128G TF card Wired connection：Standard Powered by：DC 110V-220V Power consumption：&amp;lt;24W Working Temperature：-20°C ~ 80°C Non-condensing Working humidity：10% ~ 95% Non-condensing Package List: 1x Camera 1x User Manual 1x Bag of ScrewsSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box 1x Camera 1x User Manual 1x Bag of ScrewsModel Name Ip wifi cameraItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c3288acf-137d-4b40-b67a-9b73f69b1f2c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/914dfba1-4983-469b-9216-d287f2ee7a64/web/1_1724917557432.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>69 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094709599248</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3032416182</g:id>
      <g:title>SUP 400 In 1 Portable Handheld Retro Console</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMultiplatform Digital Device That Can Be Played On A Television. Support The Av Interface400 Games Update, In Addition To Big Screen, It Will Take You Back To ChildhoodEquipped With Rechargeable Lithium Battery And Usb Cable, Playing Games For 6 Hours In A RowConvenient size and light weight, perfect for traveling or going out, sharing with friendsEnjoy your game anywhere, at any time, with this portable, lightweight devicePlease feel free to buy. If you have any problem with the handheld game console, please contact us anytimeAlways the one that can raise your childhood memory. Enough games for you to play for a long time. Along with original sound for better playing experienceMany vintage games are included like Mario and Contra. So this is a great gift for kids as well as 90s adultsOverview400 retro games that can be played on a TV are incorporated inside the handheld 400 in 1 Sup Game Box, which also has a rechargeable battery and USB cord. After a full charge, the device offers 4-5 hours of nonstop play. Children, collectors, and aficionados of vintage video games will love receiving this game box as a present. Games are available in Chinese and English. We provide Mario, Tank, Turtle, Contra, arcade vintage games, logic and mathematical, sports, puzzle, arcade, shooting, action, racing, fighting games, strategy, adventure, card games, and more to fulfil your desire to play a range of games that you enjoy. It offers you a high-quality gaming and viewing experience, as well as assisting you in unwinding and feeling better. It also supports AV output and features a brilliant LCD screen. Meanwhile, because to its slim design, you could carry it wherever. SpecificationsProduct Weight 200 gColour Name Black/WhiteConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box Portable ConsoleType of Console Software Retro Handheld ConsoleProduct Length 10 cmProduct Height 16 cmProduct Width/Depth 5 cmModel Number 965478Model Name Retro Console</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b66a4d98-435e-4481-8f52-662cdb6600e0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1496431a-135e-40ff-9c93-1e856cfa39a0/web/1_1724933182803.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030324161828</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9200316218</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic 40X HD Night Vision Monocular Telescope With Phone Clip Tripod</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsLarge objective lens diameter offers a brighter and wider field of viewFeatures a rugged, high-quality finish with sure-grip coating for a comfortable holdScrupulously crafted optics ensure high brightness and render top-quality imagesSpecificationsColour Name BlackNight Vision Lens YesModel Number 40X60</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/980d207c-122d-4f54-99cf-f443d4536c4b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e337005c-7a89-4f52-84bd-3eeccedffd20/web/1_1724746414099.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>58.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092003162182</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9624993088</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Digital Camera Tripod Stand Black/Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsTake control over your composition with increased camera performance and sharper images that will exceed your expectations. Extremely sharp pictures even at shorter focal lengths and in macro applicationsMaximum image quality whether you are shooting stills or video. Incredible portability and flexibilitySpecificationsColour Name Black/SilverSecondary Reflector NoProduct Height 50 inFeatures Ergonomic, Travel, PersonalModel Number Pstore92Model Name Digital CameraItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4a122755-7d6a-465b-9bcb-0753687916da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/640577d2-cda6-460b-8f4c-0ef492ec34d5/web/1_1724655042428.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096249930888</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6376375792</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Wireless WiFi USB Baby Home Security IP Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAPP monitor and control, you can check baby or older any time any where on mobiles, PC or iPad. Automatic Recording 24 hours all day, alarm recording, qudio recording and video recording. Built-in MIC and speaker for two-way talk, you can talk to your baby with super clear sound. The Infrared Night Vision will automatically start in dim light, providing clear video even in dark room. You can modify the camera user name and password, ensure safety. OverviewGeneric Digoo BB-M1 Wireless WiFi USB Baby Monitor Alarm Home Security IP Camera HD 720P Audio Netip One PieceSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number 1553668312482</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a61bc659-b9c0-4983-a2af-121ee6d67250</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/84f4d91e-5738-4c3a-82de-17ff1d5f6bbd/web/1_1724658703687.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>87.15 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063763757925</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4100291630</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Camera Tripod Stand For Nikon D5300, D3300, D800, D7100 And D7000 Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSecure clip locks your photography device so that it can have a no slip gripFlexible grip can be pivoted at any direction to get the perfect shotEach leg can be adjusted individually to deliver an even surfaceSpecificationsColour Name Silver/BlackModel Number OYA-1666Model Name OYA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f55585c2-c8e1-4ce7-8987-43c45a69221c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/14c54980-4b43-4bc7-8eaa-524efc7e291b/web/1_1724661264855.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041002916302</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2635780460</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Monocular With Smartphone Adapter</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsProvides clear and distortion-free viewing owing to the reflection-reducing coated lensesQuality armouring protects the scope from knocks and offers a high degree of weather resistanceGreat companion for any nature or outdoor enthusiastSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number 2724697229633</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/28d36fc5-113a-4ee2-8def-15db5e8881c9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/535f2f8d-0c04-4115-844c-c2bb470b4bfe/web/3_1724672422411.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>51.25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026357804603</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6518123348</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Aluminium Foldable Tripod Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAluminum alloy and high quality plastic material construction makes it extremely lightweight and durableThree-way pan head lets you adjust the camera for an excellent shooting experienceFor easy installation, it offers quick-release leg locksFeatures non-slip rubber grips for stable operationSpecificationsProduct Weight 380 gColour Name Silver/BlackModel Number WT-3110A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/39d46492-29f4-42bd-8c09-9b9f4cd2d6a6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/214e322d-41cc-40c8-b968-42e0eef84ad3/web/1_1724650605412.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065181233487</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7745440190</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MTL73 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU: 14.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 8GB Unified Memory, 512GB SSD Storage And Works with iPhone/iPad(International version) English Space Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>The Apple MacBook Pro is a high-performance laptop designed for professionals and power users. With its sleek and durable aluminum build, it exudes elegance and durability. The MacBook Pro boasts a stunning Retina display with vibrant colors and sharp details, making it ideal for creative work and multimedia consumption. Powered by Apple's powerful M-series chips, the MacBook Pro delivers exceptional performance for demanding tasks, from video editing and photo manipulation to software development. The efficient architecture of these chips ensures long battery life, allowing you to work or play for extended periods without needing to recharge. The MacBook Pro is equipped with a comfortable keyboard and spacious trackpad for precise navigation. It also features a wide range of ports, including Thunderbolt 4 for fast data transfer and connection to external displays. With its combination of power, portability, and premium features, the MacBook Pro is a top choice for those seeking a high-performance laptop. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MTL73LL/A / MTL73ZS/A/MTL73X/A / MTL73ZP/A/MTL73HN/A MTL73B/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/18b292a8-250c-4378-9aa0-e78de4275fdd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8e4b681f-f089-4b58-8f9f-7fd8ae2a93e8/web/1_1727351830539.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077454401905</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9810767408</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/af7074dc-eaa4-4cd3-9793-a5b32fb3126e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aae5939e-73e7-4a59-a62c-76f98f4b5769/web/1_1727440889602.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098107674088</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1348518604</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/69da9ac5-acdb-47c3-bc5a-4e4fc8905449</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a373eec9-6c7a-4a80-8a3d-774096d392a6/web/2_1727442153685.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013485186046</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5840374594</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy F15 5G (Jazzy Green, 128 Gb) (6 Gb Ram)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights6 gb ram | 128 gb rom | Expandable upto 1 tb16. 51 cm (6. 5 inch) full hd+ display50MP + 5MP | 13MP front camera6000 mAh lithium ion batteryMediaTek dimensity 6100+ processorOverviewThe Samsung Galaxy F15 is a pinnacle of mobile brilliance, featuring a vibrant sAMOLED display for an immersive visual journey. Experience unmatched battery endurance, lasting up to two days, and revel in four years of hassle-free performance with a powerful MediaTek Dimensity 6100+ and up to 12 GB of RAM. Silence background sounds with noise cancellation, seamlessly share across devices, and enjoy superfast 5G speeds. Capture every detail with the 50 MP triple camera setup and have fun with the front-facing camera's creative features. Fortify your security with the Samsung Knox Vault Chipset and personalise your experience with Smart UI features. The Galaxy F15 redefines smartphone excellence in a compact and versatile package, catering to every aspect of a modern, connected lifestyle. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 217 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Jazzy GreenDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesWhat's In The Box Handset, Data Cable (USB Type C-to-C), Ejection Pin, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name MediaTekNumber of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassWireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 9. 3 mmProduct Height 160 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 8 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer,Fingerprint Sensor,Gyro Sensor,Geomagnetic Sensor,Light Sensor,Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-E156BLVGINSModel Name Samsung F15 5GPixels Per Inch 2340 x 1080 PixelPrimary Camera (MP) 50 + 5 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/580ed5eb-a364-436c-a318-253ab5b80a4c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4f592071-69e5-492c-add9-a4f5d0e85f69/web/1_1727678386520.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>599.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058403745943</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7513954994</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 7-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in Black, Silver and Light Green, Galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the Galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front Camera, the 2MP Depth Camera and the 50MP Wide-angle CameraEquipped with a powerful octa-core, 4/6GB of memory and 64/128GB internal storage, Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handThe 5,000mAh (typical)** battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of Super Fast Charging, Galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVDMEAModel Name SM-A057FLVDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/05d34c81-1185-456e-a8f5-390e597cb446</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5b4617ed-92c6-4628-96a4-5acbe1bb7204/web/1_1727673153057.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>375.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075139549942</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6219561389</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 4 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZKGMEA / SM-A057FZKDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e16dbfa4-5f6a-417a-9539-87f3cb65db69</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2f200f95-df7c-4a1f-bb71-2274937251eb/web/1_1727674159558.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>354.25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062195613892</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9141423083</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy F34 5G 6GB RAM 128 Storage dual sim Mystic Green -Indian version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights50MP (OIS &amp;amp; VDIS) Triple No Shake Cam | 13MP Selfie Camera16. 42cm (6. 5") FHD+ sAmoled, 120 Hz, 1000 Nits6000mAh Battery4 times of Android Updates, 5 Years of Security UpdatesOverviewSamsung pay and Samsung Care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name GreenModel Year 2023Condition NewModel Number SM-E346BZGDINSModel Name F34</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ae0b994e-0da3-4367-93ef-ef58dd2175f7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/476ce21a-ebf6-4bb6-bff2-af579d39fee3/web/1_1727682892920.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>587.45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091414230831</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9267782077</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 200 LITE Starry Blue Dual SIM 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights108MP rear camera, portrait in the spotlightHonor 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your handExtra-large AMOLED view, boundless with brightness and clarityOverviewThe Portrait Master 108MP &amp;amp; 50MP Glorious Portrait Risk-free Dimming AMOLED Display Lightweight Drop-resistant Design 108MP Rear Camera, Portrait in the Spotlight 50MP Light-sensitive Selfie, Fantastic group photo Ultra-slim in Shape, Crafted in Style Drop-Proof, Trust Enhanced Risk-Free Dimming Eye-Care Display 256GB Ultra-large Storage Dynamic in Design, Elegant in Heart HONOR 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, Exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your hand. 6. 78mm Thickness 166g Weight Selfie Light 50MP Front Camera 108MP Main Camera f/1. 75 aperture Marco Camera f/2. 4 aperture Wide &amp;amp; Depth Camera f/2. 2 aperture AI Wide-angle Selfie 78° FOV mode works while taking selfies, and switches to 90° FOV mode whlie taking groupfies. Multi-focal Portrait, the Art of Boken The Rear camera features three focal choices, each showing a side of your unique charm. 108MP image,Uncompromising Clarity The 108MP HD Rear camera can capture the excitement of your life clearly and vividly. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4500 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Colour Name Starry BlueDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number 6080Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek DimensityNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number LLY-NX1Model Name HONOR 200 LITEPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/115e0f75-a62c-419d-8309-0fa07f12e26a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/004f7bb5-0ed5-404a-970a-c3fbbd2fa576/web/1_1727673590390.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>810 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092677820777</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5483353974</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi A3 Dual SIM Midnight Black 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRefined and Stylish DesignSmooth 6. 71'' 90Hz Dot Drop displayMassive 5000mAh (typ) battery, and provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W chargingSecure fingerprint and AI face unlockSupports up to 1TB expandable storageOverviewThe ultra-thin design, paired with the clean flat frame, appears exquisite and stylish. Hold the phone with one hand to embrace trends and lightness. Provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W charging*. 5000mAh ultra-large battery, reducing battery life anxiety and ensuring full-day range. Powerful octa-core processor with a maximum CPU frequency of 2. 2GHz, more balanced performance, reduced lags, and more fun to enjoy. You can choose the side fingerprint or AI face to easily unlock your phone. Suitable for more unlocking scenarios, safer and more convenient. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 71 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Midnight BlackDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 14Processor Number G36What's In The Box Mobile Phone | Adapter | USB Type-C Cable | SIM Eject Tool | Quick Start Guide | Safety InformationNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pNetwork Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 168 mmProduct Height 8. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 3 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number 23129RN51XModel Name Redmi A3 (4+128)Primary Camera (MP) 8+QVGA MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6ce530ed-88fb-4dfd-9e2c-ba1235fb45e2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ed08874d-91b6-443d-9948-0e6ccdedd336/web/1_1727676140069.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>302.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054833539749</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5356466722</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G Indian Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ display6. 5" FHD+ super amoled5G x Octa-core processor50MP cameraOverviewProcessor 2. 2GHz, 2GHz CPU Type Octa-Core Size (Main_Display) 163. 9mm (6. 5") Weight (g) 200SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Blue BlackDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name Samsung Exynos 7Number of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla Glass 5Primary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080p (100fps), 1080p(30fps), 1080p(60fps), 1440P (30fps), 1440P (60fps), 4K (30fps), 720P(200fps)Wireless 5GWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Sensor, Gyro Sensor, Geomagnetic Sensor, Light Sensor, Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-A156EZKGMEA, SM-A156M/DSN, SM-A156E/DSModel Name Galaxy A15Pixels Per Inch 1080 x 2340Primary Camera (MP) 50</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/db15346e-9e05-4801-ad8b-1855147e8ddd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ca6e77cc-9270-4d62-86ef-0a452b928986/web/1_1727676284712.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>679.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053564667226</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9623228108</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Yellow 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name YellowOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZYHMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bcf0798c-4884-4a40-8d77-37af71b3f8cc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8622c477-cd72-483e-a307-20bc45163d6f/web/1_1727674430025.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096232281089</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2002951012</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Silver 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPremium and stylish designHigh quality cameraSmooth and fast performanceLong-lasting batteryOverviewDive into immersiveness Enjoy it all in stellar clarity. With the 6. 7-inch FHD+ display, your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless, vivid picture quality. Embracing the essentials A refined build and finish. Available in Light Green and Black Galaxy A05s brings the style in form factor. Your moments to savor and share It’s all there. Revisit your landscapes captured with the 50MP Main camera, detailed shots with the 2MP Macro camera, portraits with the 2MP Depth camera for more dimensions, and your favorite selfies with the 13MP Front camera. Equipped for superior performance Carry on doing what you love. With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor**, 4/6GB of memory and 128GB internal storage*, Galaxy A05s is equipped with the performance capacity for seamless gaming, viewing, and sharing on social media. Extend your memory with RAM Plus Galaxy A05s intelligently reads your phone usage pattern to provide extra virtual RAM* up to 6GB, allowing you to run apps smoothly and enjoy multitasking Power that keeps you going The 5,000mAh (typical)* battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W** of Super Fast Charging, Galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quickly. Go beyond the ordinary listening experience with Dolby Atmos Simply plug in your headphones and you’ll be transported to the middle of your music and movies. With Dolby Atmos, you’ll hear sound that’s full, loud and seems to surround you in the scene. Awesome experience with One UI Core Own something truly yours. Customize your Galaxy with One UI and give your phone an edgy look to match your vibes. Create a bespoke tool that assists your tasks seamlessly and makes your favorite features readily accessible. Keep your device in tip-top condition with us Enjoy peace of mind when you choose to buy a Samsung Galaxy smartphone The interactive diagnostics and optimization on the Samsung Members app makes it easy to tune up the performance of your devices, while our helpline helps you troubleshoot problems when you need the extra support. SpecificationsSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion UAE VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Micro SIMColour Name SilverCondition NewModel Number SG-SM-A057FZSHMEAModel Name Samsung Galaxy A05s</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/315c88f8-747c-4d60-a2ad-5e085ba0a080</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1ae24847-fb38-4b99-8aa5-eafc676f1f52/web/1_1727675140828.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>448.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020029510120</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2356782291</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea 9-Inch Smart Tablet PC Android Tab IPS Display Single Sim 5G LTE WiFi Zoom And Tiktok Supported With Protective Case</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights9-inch full hd display: 9-inch android tablet pc featuring a vivid full hd IPS display. Enjoy wide viewing angles and high-resolution imagery, immersing yourself in a visual journey that is both realistic and compellingPowerful battery capacity: It is furnished with a sustainable powerful battery, With the capability to last up to 4-5 hours on a single charge, it proves ideal for extended commuting, travel, reading, watching movies, dramas, and enjoying musicDual camera &amp;amp; wifi supported: With a 5mp front camera and an 8mp rear camera, making it an excellent companion for live chatting, and spontaneously taking photos in your daily life. Supports wi-fi bluetooth, GPS, and FM functionalitiesQuad core &amp;amp; 5g LTE: 5g tablet operating on the Android 12 system and powered by a quad-core processor, this 9-inch tablet ensures improved graphics and overall performance. Additionally, it supports 2. 4G/5G wifi for seamless connectivityExcellent protection: The tablet comes with a foldable cover and a lightweight, adjustable angle, hardback design that adds minimal bulk while providing excellent protection for your deviceOverviewThe C idea CM915 smart tablet features a 9" WVGA IPS touch screen with 1080p FHD resolution, providing a vibrant and clear display. It is powered by a highly-integrated application processor designed for mainstream tablet applications. Running on the latest Android 12. 0 operating system, the tablet comes pre-installed with essential apps and grants access to the Google Play Store for downloading a wide range of applications. The 9'' display is well-suited for various activities, including watching movies, capturing moments through pictures, and enjoying music. Popular apps like YouTube, WhatsApp, Instagram, Viber, and more are already included for added convenience. ●Item Name : Smart Tablet PC ●Brand: C idea ●Model : CM915 Specification: Display size and resolution : 9 inch WVGA IPS Touch Screen LCD Network :2G,3G,4G, 5G LTE/WiFi Operating System : Android 12. 0(none updated) CPU: MTK6735 Chipset : Quad core Flash+Ram : 256GB+8GB(actual running speed and storage lower then this ) Expandable Memory : Up to 32GB Support Zoom : Yes Camera : Front - 5. 0M Back - 8. 0M (Kids version) Flash Light: Yes Sim Slot : Single Sim Sim Size : Micro (not included) Wi-Fi Support : Yes Bluetooth Connect : Yes Face Unlock : Yes Charging Type: Type-C Power Input : 5V/2A Thickness : Ultra Slim Body Item size:22. 4*14*0. 8cmSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name RedCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Micro SIMDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 12Operating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesWhat's In The Box Android Tablet*1,Protective Case Cover*1, UK Charger*1, Type-C USB cable*1, Touch Pen*1, Bluetooth Airpod*1,Protective film*1,Type-C OTG*1,Key Ring*1,User manual*1Network Frequency Band GSM/LTENumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pWireless 5GProduct Length 25 cmProduct Height 25. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 4. 4 cmMaximum Expandable Memory 32 GBModel Number CM915Model Name Smart tablet PCPrimary Camera (MP) 8</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ebe7974e-2953-435a-8587-6b50ce4b76da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0fb827d5-8d6b-4557-8d1e-504ad4af0a1d/web/1_1727681139909.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023567822915</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1736146315</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 9A Dual Sim Lake Green 4GB RAM 64GB 4G - Chinese Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAndroid 10, MIUI 12MediaTek MT6762G Helio G25 (12 nm)microSDXC (dedicated slot)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Chinese VersionScreen Size 6. 53 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Lake GreenDisplay Type IPS LCDOperating System AndroidProcessor Number MT6762GNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDModel Year 2020Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number 9AModel Name Redmi 9APrimary Camera (MP) 13 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0cfafc5d-aafb-473a-a13f-067e7190e753</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7143f4d6-919c-4533-aefb-0685ed47739b/web/1_1727683456451.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>258 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017361463153</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7572470508</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 4G -International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Blue/BlackModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number Galaxy A15Model Name Galaxy A15</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7ccbd96c-b0c3-4e7a-8977-dc7062da6a62</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7157c7b0-ac39-4ef6-9ecb-209f18f00915/web/1_1727679640111.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>645 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075724705081</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3498663341</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Light Blue 8GB RAM 256GB 5G Indian Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ display6. 5" FHD+ super amoled5G x Octa-core processor50mp cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 13Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yedsNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name Exynos OctaNumber of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla Glass 5Primary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080p (100fps), 1080p(30fps), 1080p(60fps), 1440P (30fps), 1440P (60fps), 4K (30fps), 720P(200fps)Wireless 5GWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofFinish AluminumModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A156ELBGMEA / SM-A156E/DS, SM-A156M/DSNModel Name samsung a15 5gPrimary Camera (MP) 50</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b9acef86-18bc-44de-9197-82f4c3eb1252</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c4bde3e1-92c9-45fc-b3c8-f4568b3f1ed1/web/1_1727679244939.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>679.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034986633419</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6529205085</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A04e Dual SIM Black 3GB RAM 32GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights720 x 1600 (HD+) PLS LCD Display13 MP Rear Camera with Digital Zoom Up To 10xand 5 MP Front CameraNano-SIM (4FF), MicroSD Upto 1TB and USB Type-C ChargerAccelerometer,Light Sensor,Proximity SensorSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 3 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 32 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEModel Year 2022Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1000 GBModel Number SM-A042FZKDMEA / SM-A042F/DSModel Name Galaxy A04ePrimary Camera (MP) 13+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c0d81e10-6d83-44e8-9cf1-e8806eb45602</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c77c85ba-bb36-4e42-9981-0705fc9b9bb5/web/1_1727681464221.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>274.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065292050850</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4373652452</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Light Blue 8GB RAM 256GB 4G -International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A15 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A15 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Light BlueNetwork Frequency Band LTEModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number Galaxy A15Model Name Galaxy A15</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/90983ec6-3c8f-4a86-89e8-eb7c2caebcc1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/01f3ca06-1c80-4fb8-af20-261d7e58e50f/web/1_1727683080521.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>645 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043736524525</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5939869110</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy M14 4G (Sapphire Blue,4Gb,64Gb) | 50MP Triple Cam | 5000mAh Battery | Snapdragon 680 Processor | 2 Gen OS Upgrade And 4 Year Security Update | 8Gb Ram With RAM Plus</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsInterface &amp;amp; processor- Android 13 operating system having One UI 5. 1 platform with Qualcomm snapdragon 680 processor | 2. 4GHz, 1. 9GHz octa-core processorCamera - 50 mp (F1. 8) main wide angle + 2 MP (F2. 4) Macro + 2 MP (F2. 4) depth | 13MP (F2. 0) front camera | Video maximum resolution of full hd (1920 x 1080) @60fpsBattery - Get a massive 5000mAh Lithium-ion Battery (Non-removable) with C-Type fast charging (25W charging support)Display - 17. 08 centimeters (6. 7"Inch) PLS LCD display, FHD+ Resolution with 1080 x 2400 pixels , 391 PPI with 16M colors and 90Hz refresh rateOS updates &amp;amp; security- Get upto 2 generations of AndroidOS upgrades &amp;amp; 4 years of security updates with Samsung galaxy M14 4G. Includes 1 year manufacturer warranty for device and 6 months for in-box accessoriesSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 17 cmSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name blueDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Smartphone Data Cable (Type C-to-C) SIM Ejector Pin User ManualProcessor Name Qualcomm Snapdragon 660Glass Technology Gorilla GlassFlash LEDWireless 4G/3G/Wireless/BluetoothModel Year 2024Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number Samsung Galaxy M14Model Name M14 4GPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP Triple Cam</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5226fa55-cff1-4c91-a5de-fcde432c599b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4b5150b4-07ab-4eb8-8250-c42d23cd9f03/web/1_1727682648933.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>373.60 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059398691109</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7569780526</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy F34 5G (6GB RAM) 128GB -dual sim Electric Black Indian Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights50MP (OIS &amp;amp; VDIS) Triple No Shake Cam | 13MP Selfie Camera16. 42cm (6. 5") FHD+ sAmoled, 120 Hz, 1000 Nits6000mAh Battery4 times of Android Updates, 5 Years Security UpdatesOverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type Micro SDXCCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Colour Name Electric BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 12Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 2. 4GHz, 2GHzProcessor Number 2. 4GHz, 2GHzProcessor Name Octa-CoreNumber of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashVideo Recording Resolution Type UHD 4KWireless 5GWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77 mmProduct Height 161 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 8 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-E346BZKDINSModel Name F34Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/02a52cf7-05dc-41f7-9385-01b0aa36e7ae</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0188844f-c336-4840-b2d9-239bfd3c410f/web/1_1727682066097.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>594.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075697805269</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6208714620</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 9A Dual Sim Sand Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G - Chinese Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAura design - An experience that surrounds you with the concentric design that delivers an additional grip and overall practicalityFeatures P2i Nano-coating to protect your smartphones against everyday water splashes and spillsAI face unlock for instant unlocking with a glance, The feature gives quick, secure and convenient access to your smartphone using intelligent face recognition systemThe 13MP AI Primary Camera delivers dynamic and intelligent range of photographyHyperEngine Game Technology ensures your games load faster and you have a smoother gameplay every timeBrowse and download apps, magazines, books, movies, and television programs directly to your phoneShare your 4G data connection with other compatible wireless devicesRedmi 9A supports dual Nano-Sim card + micro-SD expansion, either card can be set as the primary card. Support 4G/3G/2G and support dual SIM VoLTE HD callingOverviewRedmi 9A brings a 16. 58cm (6. 53) display with wider, more immersive aspect ratio of 20:9. The clarity of HD+ IPS Display promises a captivating viewing experience for movies, videos and more. Protects eyes and reduces harmful blue light for an enhanced reading experience. 5000mAh enhanced lifespan battery delivers 25% increased charge cycles and ensures longevity. Redmi 9A's battery delivers 2 days of uninterrupted entertainment. Charge fewer times with a battery that lasts longer. The battery has a charge cycle count as high as 1000, meaning that the phone can be used daily for more than 2. 5 years without any nota-ble degradation to the battery. The high-performance Helio G25 delivers faster processing and a seamless smartphone experience with smooth browsing, messaging and video calling. HyperEngine Game Technology ensures your games load faster and you have a smoother gameplay every time. The 13MP AI Primary Camera delivers dynamic and intelligent range of photography, from cinematic landscapes to detailed portraits. AI face unlock for instant unlocking with a glance! The feature gives quick, secure and convenient access to your smartphone using intelligent face recognition systemSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBProduct Weight 196 gVersion Chinese VersionScreen Size 6. 53 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Sand blackDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Android 11Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 11Processor Number MT6762GFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Smartphone, User Manual, Warranty Card, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantFinish PlasticModel Year 2020Network Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 1 mmProduct Height 164. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 9 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 512 GBSensor Accelerometer, Proximity, CompassModel Number M2006C3LCModel Name Redmi 9APixels Per Inch 269 ppiPrimary Camera (MP) 13 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/adac3139-56c5-4404-af7c-30b41bc710cd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c38238c2-17fc-4dae-968d-faa8bea81a45/web/1_1727680764941.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>262 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062087146200</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4086284429</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Flexible Camera Tripod Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsErgonomically designed to offer better gripCompact and sleek for easy portabilityDurably designed for prolonged useSpecificationsColour Name Silver/Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/84fc0aa7-e44e-4e58-a744-e31df1c291aa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c44d5f1e-a6c0-4afb-ad43-84d391e8d816/web/1_1724659244689.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040862844299</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1256533276</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Digital Camera Tripod Stand Black/Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsTake control over your composition with increased camera performance and sharper images that will exceed your expectations. Extremely sharp pictures even at shorter focal lengths and in macro applicationsMaximum image quality whether you are shooting stills or video. Incredible portability and flexibilitySpecificationsColour Name Black/SilverSecondary Reflector NoProduct Height 104 cmFeatures Ergonomic, Travel, PersonalModel Number Pstore96Model Name Digital CameraItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d1c28549-e5c6-4661-a874-cb959b3479b5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/87082a73-722c-48cd-8792-4a9578b3985b/web/1_1724662316101.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012565332762</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1716165694</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic High Power 40X60 HD Monocular Shimmer lll Outdoor Hiking Portable Telescope Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsExtra large plating increases the amount of light, making the image clearer and brighterPortable and detachable, it lets you snap photos with your devices at any timeAllows you to take the best shot you craved forBest gift for travelersSpecificationsColour Name BlackCountry of Origin ChinaModel Number Panda133Model Name Zoom Lens</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/232f243f-3556-4064-b87f-c8ae5b97e10f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f1726876-811b-4fea-9b4f-abeb2100961c/web/1_1724671892821.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>52.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017161656946</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2015976361</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Universal Adjustable Tripod Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsErgonomically designed to offer better gripCompact and sleek for easy portabilityDurably designed for prolonged useSpecificationsColour Name Silver/Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e5d309da-d742-48b5-ab4e-c71d10ff04ef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7834eb35-e5f8-4752-b350-695c70b4c820/web/1_1724663975777.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020159763618</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8240684748</g:id>
      <g:title>Panda Portable 35x50 mm Monocular Telescope</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFully multi-green coated lenses offer clear images with improved light transmissionAnti-slip and water-resistant rubber and aluminium alloy body ensures prolonged service lifeComes with triangle support and phone clip for all cellphones in different sizesRoof BAK-4 prism provides a high definition view for an excellent experienceThe compact size and lightweight body make it extremely portable and convenient to useSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 32 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 16 cmProduct Height 6. 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 5. 5 cmModel Number 2262416</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/af5c2935-c1a6-49cf-bfa6-1a6b8c2660b6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e2b0cac3-7375-4928-a9cf-9c38b114575a/web/1_1724667836205.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>51.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082406847489</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8743882030</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Condenser Microphone With Accessories Set BM-800 Black/Gold</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStandard pick-up minimizes background noise and isolates the main sound sourceAdopt demanding complete electronic circuit control, capture rich, full-bodied soundShock mount effectively reduces trill caused by vibrationSpecificationsProduct Weight 1. 4 KGColour Name Black/GoldProduct Length 42 cmProduct Height 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 24 cmModel Number BM-800Model Name BM-800</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/54bc9b9f-d64f-4f9f-af8a-0b3a23bc0f09</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/66f96e0c-72f9-4d01-a53b-27c227ff13ad/web/1_1724840291522.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>109 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087438820301</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4119954193</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Mini Portable Thermal Printer Blue/White</g:title>
      <g:description>Colour Name Blue/WhiteConnection Type BluetoothModel Number D9997BL-QModel Name D9997BL-Q</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1a33470e-00fd-40ac-9b3d-3f2ca60dc37e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cd001d35-9e6e-4bc2-ab7e-0c4cfc69f897/web/1_1724735001032.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041199541936</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3182590241</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery Wireless WiFi Light Bulb Camera,360 Panoramic ring Camera,Full-HD 1080P with Infrared Human Motionsecurity Detection and Alarm Night Vision Light Camera,for Outdoor,Home,Baby,Pet Monitor</g:title>
      <g:description>Overview1080P &amp;amp; Panoramic Viewing: This bulb camera can provide you with a clear vision at any time. You can use the APP to control the camera to achieve 360 viewing without blind area. Wireless &amp;amp; Simple installation:This camera can be installed using a normal E27 bulb base(110V~240V),then you just need to connect the camera system to the router and open the app to setup the camera within minutes. Remote Viewing &amp;amp; Night Vision:This bulb camera can control the viewing angle through APP,you can access remotely view anywhere and any time through your Phone. Even in complete darkness, you can view clear images. Two-Way Audio &amp;amp; High Quality Service:Designed with built-in mic and speaker,this bulb security camera allows you to listen to your guests and to talk with your family in real-time. Motion Detection &amp;amp; Real-time Alerts:As soon as motion detection is triggered,this bulb will automatically send out email alerts and app alarm pushes. Thus,you can know what happened in your house and take appropriate precautions in time Overview Features: 1080P &amp;amp; Panoramic Viewing: This bulb camera can provide you with a clear vision at any time. You can use the APP to control the camera to achieve 360 viewing without blind area. Wireless &amp;amp; Simple installation:This camera can be installed using a normal E27 bulb base(110V~240V),then you just need to connect the camera system to the router and open the app to setup the camera within minutes. Remote Viewing &amp;amp; Night Vision:This bulb camera can control the viewing angle through APP,you can access remotely view anywhere and any time through your Phone. Even in complete darkness, you can view clear images. Two-Way Audio &amp;amp; High Quality Service:Designed with built-in mic and speaker,this bulb security camera allows you to listen to your guests and to talk with your family in real-time. Motion Detection &amp;amp; Real-time Alerts:As soon as motion detection is triggered,this bulb will automatically send out email alerts and app alarm pushes. Thus,you can know what happened in your house and take appropriate precautions in time. Specification: Sensor：1/3 inches CMOS Frame Rate：15 fps Resolution：1080P Illumination：0. 02Lux@(2. 0,AGC ON),0Lux with IR Lens：6mm Movement Tracking：Support Voice Intercom：Support two-way voice intercom Night Vision Mode：IR-CUT Auto Switch Movement Detection：Support Local Storage：Support TF card storage，Connect video/event recording， Maximum support 128G TF card Wired connection：Standard Powered by：DC 110V-220V Power consumption：&amp;lt;24W Working Temperature：-20°C ~ 80°C Non-condensing Working humidity：10% ~ 95% Non-condensing Package List: 1x Camera 1x User Manual 1x Bag of ScrewsSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box 1x Camera 1x User Manual 1x Bag Of ScrewsModel Name Ip Wifi CameraItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/882dbf7b-cc79-454e-af72-46135a565271</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/223145e6-8019-4a5e-a467-6b8fd5c22873/web/3_1724735827830.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031825902415</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2735978158</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic USB Magnetic Charger For Huawei GT/GT2/Honor Magic Smartwatch White</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewFeaturing magnetic absorption design, can stably charge the watch. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number DWYYC4978313Model Name DWYYC4978313</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e787d295-d307-438b-bde3-0f0004a175b8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3fe9cae8-66cd-40da-b09f-64b8b42a83a7/web/1_1724748377250.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>58.05 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027359781589</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5413280220</g:id>
      <g:title>Beauenty Professional Condenser Audio Streaming Kit Black/Gold</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights3. 5mm aux jack condenser microphone mic works with laptops and computersAdjustable shock mount allows for a customized fitIdeal for radio broadcasting, voice-over sound and audio recordingLarge condenser microphone element for warm, rich recordings. The cardioid pick-up pattern minimizes background noise and isolates the main sound source. . Smooth, extended frequency response is excellent for singing, speech and instrumentsOverload-protection switch (-10dB) minimizes distortion from loud sound sources. . Bass-reduction switch reduces room noise. The professional condenser microphone internally adopts precise full electronic circuit control and has fine features of cardioid-directional pick-up, high-sensitivity output, low noise, wide dynamic range, etc. It is widely used in specialized occasions such as in the recording studio, the broadcast radio, the stage performance, the late-stage production of movie and television plays and the household computer recording. OverviewLarge condenser microphone element for warm, rich recordings. The cardioid pick-up pattern minimizes background noise and isolates the main sound source. . Smooth, extended frequency response is excellent for singing, speech, and instruments. Overload-protection switch (-10dB) minimizes distortion from loud sound sources. Bass-reduction switch reduces room noise. The professional condenser microphone internally adopts precise full electronic circuit control and has fine features of cardioid-directional pick-up, high-sensitivity output, low noise, wide dynamic range, etc. . It is widely used in specialized occasions such as in the recording studio, the broadcast radio, the stage performance, the late-stage production of movie and television plays, and the household computer recording. SpecificationsProduct Weight 1. 55 KGColour Name Black/GoldConnection Type WiredBrand Compatibility GeneralMobileWhat's In The Box 1xMicrophone, 1xStand, 1xCable, 1xMount, 1xNet and 1xMicrophone CoverProduct Length 44 cmProduct Height 9 cmProduct Width/Depth 26 cmFeatures Business, Ergonomic, PersonalModel Number BM700Model Name BM700Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/31070192-053f-40ce-8785-fc1f845b4c62</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5a3f8cbc-d438-4908-90b1-252d299324e0/web/1_1724907428506.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054132802209</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2171310075</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Home-Security IP Camera Wirelessly Intelligent WiFi Cameras WI-FI Audio Record Baby Monitor</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsIt has the functions of AP hotspot, remote control, two-way voice, infrared night vision and mobile alarm. Simple operation and installation, quick completion. Clear Two-Way audio. Level 355 °, 100 ° vertically mobile phone remote flexible rotation. Realize no dead angle monitoring, arbitrary installation. SpecificationsColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box CameraModel Number PA4711B-EU_PModel Name Black &amp;amp; European standard wireless wifi camera pet baby monitoring network surveillance camera</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6251627b-1ea7-4522-bdba-b9de97fc31d7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0df807b8-4605-4b22-b8a2-528c52fb7339/web/1_1724916856885.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>98.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021713100757</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2964551012</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Telescope Compact HD</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHave the best view of your outdoor adventure project , understand that the 12 x image is clear and bright, and the 50 mm objective lens is wideEnhances the key monocular to ensure high-quality light transmission and brightness, making your line of sight brighter, cleaner and providing clear imagesNon-slip armor provides a firm gripSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number DT014</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0abcc0e8-9393-4dec-bbff-bbf9f76feb02</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/05c7ba69-d950-4012-aa9d-e07747dc1602/web/1_1724921896561.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>69 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029645510125</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6861172591</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic BAK4 Monocular Telescope</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsProvides a clear view of long distance objectsLen renders clear images with improved light transmissionCompact and lightweight design enables easy operationSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 42 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 140 mmProduct Height 55 mmProduct Width/Depth 55 mmModel Number HW1717802Zoom Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9e74c381-f02c-413e-bf28-a8e69fd2389c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5b1f0037-7a40-4017-bc7e-74c294871179/web/1_1724745273892.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>58.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068611725910</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1247632236</g:id>
      <g:title>SUP Retro Portable Mini Handheld Gaming Consoles</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsApplicable to tv system, so that you can easily enjoy vivid and exciting games on a big screen. With extra controler (included) 2player can play together. High definition display, precise images transmission without delaying. Rechargeable lithium battery, support up to 3-4 hours of continuous game play. Good gift for your children, friends, both boys and girls will like it. Dual language(English, Arabic),Compact size and lightweight, convenient for carrying. OverviewSup Game Box Retro Classic Game Two-Player Machine with Remote Handheld Game Player Console Built-in 400 classic games Can be played on TV Rechargeable Lithium-ion battery and USB cable 6 hours of continuous game play after full charge Small size and light weight, suitable for traveling Perfect gift for children, retro game lovers, collectors Classic 8 bit games player. High quality video game portable console. With free built-in 400 classic games. Can connect to the TV, Support AV output. Language: English 7. 600mah rechargeable Li-ion battery supply. Digital gaming system, the handheld game console is very slim, portable and stylish. ]A digital multi-platform device that can be played on a TV. High-definition pictures of the game, no Caton. Arcade retro games, football, sports, puzzles, arcade, shooting, action, racing, fighting games, adventures, etcSpecificationsProduct Weight 200 gColour Name RedConnection Type WiredWhat's In The Box 1 x Retro game console FC, 1 x Handle,1 x User manual, 1 x AV cable, 1 xUSB cable, 1x 600MA lithium ion battery. Type of Console Software Game Boy Advance ClassicProduct Length 16 cmProduct Height 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 11 cmModel Number Retro Game ConsoleModel Name Retro Game Console</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b22cd3a3-994c-4159-9674-f274ea6b3e57</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8d3530f1-54f8-4410-9d2d-a2d618a66ebe/web/1_1724846382932.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012476322364</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9476059396</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Digital Camera Tripod Stand With Cover Black/Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsTake control over your composition with increased camera performance and sharper images that will exceed your expectations. Extremely sharp pictures even at shorter focal lengths and in macro applicationsMaximum image quality whether you are shooting stills or video. Incredible portability and flexibilitySpecificationsProduct Weight 360 gColour Name Black/SilverSecondary Reflector NoProduct Height 104 cmFeatures Ergonomic, Travel, PersonalModel Number Pstore97Model Name Digital CameraItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/53946396-a1a1-4c63-8193-991ba76d4a99</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3fb0faa5-8364-45e5-bc4c-9767e674a052/web/1_1724663187822.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094760593964</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3184003887</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery Mini Photo Printer, Portable Thermal Printer For Android Or IOS APP, Inkless Printer Gift For Friends, Used In Home, Office, Study, Work</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMultifunctional thermal printer, support photo printing, label printing, card printing, document printing, web printing, perfect for study or daily work. BLE4. 0 BT wireless connection, just download the APP and connect, easy and quick; 200 DPI resolution, ensuring clear printing quality. One-button printing, quick and convenient; no ink needed, energy-saving and environmentally-friendly. Built-in 1000mAh large capacity rechargeable lithium battery, the stand-by time is very long, no trouble of low battery and frequent charging. Compact size and light weight, convenient for carrying; cute cat appearance design, a nice birthday gift or festival gift for boys and girls. SpecificationsColour Name Pink</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f732b56a-0062-4363-9286-8e50c3749f06</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/797f3663-b786-4f8f-b763-27df308aa3d4/web/1_1724765954890.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031840038878</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9732708154</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic 3110 Flexible Camera Tripod Black/White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsQuick release plate for easy connecting to camera or camcorderRealizing any angle shooting, precise and efficientHigh quality material, durable and light weightSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 42 KGColour Name Black/WhiteSecondary Reflector NoProduct Length 36 cmProduct Height 7. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 8 cmFeatures BusinessModel Number XD4262700</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bb0c0e01-86b8-4276-bcc7-39a35487ce41</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/64bb8df7-169d-494b-b136-8e43f51b97b4/web/1_1724650279986.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097327081546</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3837449267</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic V380 Mini Home Monitoring Security Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe premium quality material offers superior performanceWell-defined circuit ensures efficient functioningEffectively replaces your damaged part, ensuring the device is back to it's prime conditionSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDProduct Weight 340 gColour Name WhiteVideo Recording Resolution Type HDSensor Type CMOSNight Vision Lens YesProduct Length 8. 7 cmProduct Height 11. 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 7 cmFeatures Wi-Fi enabled, Removable Memory Card, HD Movie ModeModel Number V380</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8a808cb7-02d8-4b54-9cb6-1083a20cb789</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5e779e85-4f3c-4cae-a3ae-e69deff36ce3/web/1_1724906278768.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>98.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038374492671</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8082892613</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic 12X50 Telescopio Bak4 Prism Night Vision Dual Green Film Monocular Zoom Telescope For Phone Hunting Professional Hiking Eyepiece</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsModel Number BAK4</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c7eed9c2-7bb6-4c32-aa69-7ee00082b841</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0044c176-6f71-48bf-91d8-880e508b9cf2/web/1_1724834862017.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080828926133</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7381462087</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery Artificial Fall Tree with Lights Pre Lit LED Tree for Indoor Outdoor Home Porch Fall Decoration</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsOccasion RamadanBase Material PlasticColour Name WhiteSet Includes Package Includes: 1 X 4FT Birch Tree 1 X Adapter 1 X Instructions</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/addea134-bd55-4528-b30c-510fd0ef43e8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ed259820-4501-44c4-a121-dcdad3567f4c/web/2_1724672864414.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073814620870</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1326877010</g:id>
      <g:title>Panda 10X HD Monocular</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsObjective lens coated with FMC green film to provide crystal clear imagesRoof BAK-7 Prism optimizes light transmission to offer clear, bright, high resolution imagesAnti-slip rubber exterior offers a comfortable and secure gripAdjustable focusing system helps you to sharpen your field of viewSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 39 KGColour Name BlackMagnifying Factor 10xModel Number 1451182</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/01df06b8-6261-4f47-849d-973ef889f042</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/90e41647-c519-4fcb-b3f6-001cd2004b32/web/1_1724678443804.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013268770103</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6534830155</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Handheld Retro Wireless Game Console</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsWith powerful rechargeable battery pack, it offers about 3-4 hours playing time and takes only 1-2 hours to chargeBuilt-in 500 classic games ensures endless happiness, you can share with your friends and have a good time3. 0 inch large screen gives you good visual experience. And AV out function makes you enjoy big screen gamePortable game console, easy and convenient to carry. Ergonomic design provides great touch feelingSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number F1906</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0f43a12e-3940-490c-98eb-a98d09d5c63c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b5b9d640-635a-494e-873a-118a01fdcbcd/web/1_1724760297440.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065348301554</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3969316771</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Tripod Stand With Carry Case Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAnti-skidding pads design, suitable for different kind of environmentHigh quality aluminium alloy material, firm and durableIdeal for digital camera, card camera and universal smart phone, flashlight etc. . Light, portable and easy to carrySupport 360°full rotation, convenient for you to take a photoSpecificationsProduct Weight 450 gColour Name SilverProduct Length 300 mmProduct Width/Depth 0. 66 inFeatures Ergonomic, Travel, Business, PersonalModel Number Pstore1029Model Name Tripod Camera Holder</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7d21a84e-dcdb-4cf7-9364-7ac347b77d46</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3a93e921-6ee1-4c01-8f46-10b3417101c4/web/1_1724665401447.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039693167714</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8722943578</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic 40X High Power HD Telescope Shimmer Monocular</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number CH-1266Model Name High Power</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d3d7c2a3-1de6-46ee-a772-2b56cb5ff08c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eaa99bc6-b0b3-4c0b-9f13-f4e9f4ae7aee/web/1_1724669699319.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>51.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087229435783</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4720286699</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Wi-Fi Wireless 720P/0.9MP HD IP Security Surveillance Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>Motion detection works perfectly with app message alarm (no photo)Make sure you are always the first when things happenNo ethernet cable is required during the entire network connection processSpecificationsProduct Weight 302 gColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 0. 92 MPModel Number 440835</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/557351c6-4668-4dbf-84ba-140f39b2a856</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fb3c40ef-4dee-4fcb-96b2-1ad2b60bcaf7/web/1_1724838323467.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>93.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047202866997</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5468691327</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Foldable Laptop Table Stand Vented Computer Desk Bed Lap Tray 360 Degree Adjustable with Mouse Pad Cooling Fans Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGood Seam Strength For DurabilityAdds More Grace To Your Beautiful Interior DécorMade Of High Quality MaterialsSpecificationsMaterial AluminiumColour Name BlackModel Number 4649756163Model Name Laptop Table Stand VentedItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1108bffd-2206-41bf-8069-52b29d25189b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9e2e185c-937d-4b5b-aba7-e165cc595649/web/1_1724740969807.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>57.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054686913277</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4138560610</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Handheld Wireless Game Console</g:title>
      <g:description>With powerful rechargeable battery pack, it offers about 3-4 hours playing time and takes only 1-2 hours to chargeBuilt-in 500 classic games ensures endless happiness, you can share with your friends and have a good time3. 0 inch large screen gives you good visual experience. And AV out function makes you enjoy big screen gamePortable game console, easy and convenient to carry. Ergonomic design provides great touch feelingEquipped with a wired gamepad, the game machine can achieve 2 players mode, so you can share with your friends and have a good time. OverviewWith compact size and lightweight, the game console is easy to carry. And 600mAh battery ensures 3-4 hours playing time, perfect for traveling. It has 500 different games and equips with a wired gamepad, achieving 2 players mode, and you can enjoy great happiness by playing games with your friend. Featuring large screen and AV out function, it offers you great visual experience. Features: With powerful 600mAh battery, it offers about 3-4 hours playing time and takes only 1-2 hours to charge. Built-in 500 classic games gives endless happiness and it takes you back to your childhood. Compact size and lightweight, it is perfect for playing while traveling or on the go. Large screen ensures good visual experience. And AV out function makes you enjoy big screen game. Equipped with a wired gamepad, the game machine can achieve 2 players mode, so you can share with your friends and have a good time. Specifications: Product Name: Handheld Game Console Battery Capacity: 600mAh Playing Time: 3-4 Hours Charging Time: 1-2 Hours Item Size: 11. 5*7. 8*2cm / 4. 5*3. 1*0. 8in Item Weight: 99. 8g / 3. 5oz Package Size: 14*10*5. 8cm / 5. 5*3. 9*2. 3in Package Weight: 298. 7g / 10. 5oz Color: Black / White / Red / Blue (Optional) Packing List: 1 * Handheld Game Console 1 * Wired Gamepad 1 * AV Cable 1 * Charging Cable 1 * User Manual (English / Chinese)SpecificationsColour Name RedModel Number F1907</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/df782cd1-1aaa-4003-a29b-4eb0937a187b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4ed923ca-25ac-4e14-ab9a-c7c105bbf25d/web/1_1724735800558.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041385606104</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4785529343</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery Drone With 4K Camera For Adults Children RC Quadcopter With Four Way Obstacle Avoidance Follow Me Fly Altitude Hold My Ball</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsColour Name BlackVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pCamera Resolution 1080 MPModel Number H8Model Name H8 RC Mini Drone</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c6d61155-6362-49f0-b5af-914212fb79c0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/67603fd0-c48a-4cc8-88fe-55eeeb994b90/web/1_1724238210490.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047855293430</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8418182781</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Tripod Stand For DSLR Camera With Bag Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsErgonomically designed to offer better gripCompact and sleek for easy portabilityDurably designed for prolonged useSpecificationsColour Name Silver/Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/47746677-a13a-4223-9d41-09329ac36ab8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/397790b0-956b-4988-92f1-655af43aa476/web/1_1724656896060.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084181827816</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8277566361</g:id>
      <g:title>Axiom DIY Acrylic Panel and Metal Arcade Case kit for 2 Player 2P Joysticks Replacement Arcade Game Machine Cabinet Controller Arcade Stick Empty Box</g:title>
      <g:description>【About Games】Pandoras 3D Box ,12000 in 1 support WIFI arcade game board with 300 3D games, support Chinese Traditional, English, Korean, Japanese, Spanis ,can download 3D games by Game classification:such as fighting games, shooting games, Stage Clear games, , puzzle games, sports games Or you can also download games by format such as MAME/N64/PS/PSP/FC/SFC/GBA/GBC/MD/PCE/DC 【HD Game Screen】It is compatible with HDMI and VGA, the resolution is 1280 x 720,support PC/PS3/4 USB joysticks online,can adjust the position of the handle，with pause,archive file, read file and play again next time;Support machine becomes gamepad mode, supports two-player online, supports any 1p position setting of the handle, and supports 4 gamepad at the same time. 【ADD 3D GAMES 】this product can support players to expand their own 3D games (Temporarily do not support 2D):(1)Prepare a TF card and choose the capacity according to the size of the game(2)Create a new folder in the root directory of the TF card with the name(roms): under the directory,create a new(game name folder),and place the game mirror under the game name Folder,for example: put Tekken 6 in TF,the complete path should be: roms/ tekken/tekken. 【About 3D Game】iso,cso,pbp,cdi,gdi,n64,c64,z64,NMI;among them,the iso of the PSX version needs to be converted to pbp. (Currently only supports game mirroring with the above suffixes,the H3 main chip only supports the expansion of PS games,and the NAOMI emulator currently only supports the 912 main chip)SpecificationsModel Name AXIUM</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7bf3cafa-daee-4c04-8219-3f9b5c0f44e5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cf02a49a-8969-4107-bab4-657fce0c8696/web/1_1724647959520.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>219 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082775663611</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7586275105</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery E99 K3 Drone With Camera Quadcopter Fpv Profesional Rc Plane Remote Control Helicopter Dron Hd 4k Professional Gift Toys.</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewModel: K3/E99 Type: Single/Dual Camera Operation mode: remote control/APP control Frequency: 2. 4GHz Gyroscope: 6Axis Channel: 4CH Charging method: Universal USB interface Battery capacity: 3. 7V 1800mAH modular battery Flight time: about 10-15 minutes Charging time: 60 minutes Remote control distance: about 150 meters Camera mode: FPV Lens: Built-in camera Video resolution: 4K single camera/4K dual camera Speed adjustment: slow/medium/fast Product size: 25*25*6cm (expanded size) 12. 5*8*5. 5cm (folded size)SpecificationsColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Drone*1, Remote Control*1, Battery *1, Spare Wing Blades*2, USB Cable*1, Screwdriver*1, Manual *1Model Number E99 K3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/30bdbf18-7276-4e21-86a7-0dde5b58b3e0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6b79fca6-5ec2-43d7-bfeb-adb3dbf08247/web/1_1724662900267.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075862751056</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4787613899</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Built-in 168 Retro Classic Handheld Mini Portable Game With 2.8 inch LCD Display</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmall enough to carry in your pocket, you can play it anywhere and anytime, perfect for travel or on the go. 2. 8in color screen; built-in rechargeable li-ion battery. Shares tremendous retro game fun, helps to kill the boring time and brings back the best childhood memory. Built-in 168 games allows you play all your favorite games. Great gifts for friends, family members. OverviewThe Handheld Game Console features built-in 168 games which allows you play all your favorite games, it's suitable for kids to develop intelligence, and expand thinking ability. , Features:, Small enough to carry in your pocket, you can play it anywhere and anytime, perfect for travel or on the go. , 2. 8in color screen; built-in rechargeable li-ion battery. , Shares tremendous retro game fun, helps to kill the boring time and brings back the best childhood memory. , Built-in 168 games allows you play all your favorite games. , Great gifts for friends, family members. , Specifications:, Colors: red, blue, white, black, yellow (optional), Recommended age: up of 3 ages, Screen: 2. 8 inch LCD, Battery: 5V, 800mAh lithium battery, Item size: 113 * 78 * 20mm / 4. 45 * 3. 07 * 0. 79in, Item weight: 85g / 3. 00ounce, Package size: 140 * 100 * 55mm / 5. 51 * 3. 94 * 2. 17in, Package weight: 185g / 6. 53ounce, Package list:, 1 * Handheld Game Console, 1 * Lithium Battery, 1 * User Manaul, 1 * USB Charge Cable, 1 * AV CableSpecificationsProduct Weight 85 gColour Name BlueConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PC GamesProduct Length 4. 45 cmProduct Height 0. 79 cmProduct Width/Depth 3. 07 cmModel Number 1759-ZModel Name 1759-Z</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/19867abc-eeb4-4872-9539-e863d753d5d8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5da04728-62e6-42eb-8e20-9d325d0c79ea/web/1_1724684782300.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>56 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047876138994</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2162747145</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Fashion Touch Screen Cell Phone Shoulder Bags Women Transparent Pocket Mini Crossbody Bag Card Purse Ladies Small Female Messenger Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewPattern: solid Lining texture: Polyester Source category: spot Color: yellow Product category: mobile bag Processing method: soft surface Material: PU leather Length: medium and long Applicable gender: Female Hardness: medium to soft Bag shape: vertical square Cover opening mode: zipper Internal structure of small package: large banknote clipSpecificationsColour Name PinkWhat's In The Box 1 x Shoulder Bag (Others Not Included)Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/aaf6e555-1127-4e4e-bc5d-bf511a4331fa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c3d72ce5-ab2d-47bb-bfd3-96015e90cab9/web/1_1724678923565.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021627471455</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1523348474</g:id>
      <g:title>PHLGHT LCD Mini Projector YG300 Basic Multicolour</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBright rooms are no match for this projector – this powerful yet affordable model delivers exceptionally bright yet colourful images with clear detailsIt utilises Epson’s renowned 3LCD technology, which produces an equally high White and Colour Light OutputDurable and affordable, this model's long-lasting lamp light source means you'll be able to project your content every day for six yearsPortable and quick to set up: Easy to position with keystone sliderSo smart and lightweight you can put it in your pocket or bag and travel with it multiple compatible devicesOverviewThe projector features a lamp that produces bright light to display and clarify the image details as closely as possible, an ideal resolution for viewing content, all you have to do is adjust the clarity in relation to the distance and the size of the display to enjoy unparalleled viewing. Portable projector is usually used for presentations and data show. Its small portable size enables you to take it with your bag, whether to display content to students in schools, universities and institutes, or at companies and inform employees about everything new through a suitable display. The projector comes with multiple plug and play ports, with the ability to play via multimedia audio and video together. Playing and viewing content is no longer easier than it appears now, all you have to do is connect the device and adjust the contrast of the image simply without much effort. SpecificationsNumber of Charging Ports 1 PortTV HDMI Ports 1Product Weight 484 gScreen Size 55 inDisplay Resolution 1440x1080Colour Name MulticolourDisplay Type LCDDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Windows 10Usage Type EducationalWhat's In The Box LCD Mini Projector</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cb6d9e1c-18b8-49e7-beca-a33cf90da763</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/51c12f90-785e-4d1b-aece-1365644aa36d/web/1_1724820296398.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>110 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015233484749</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
