<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>6535843799</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas 3 Way Extension Socket 13A - Charge Multiple Devices with Child Safe</g:title>
      <g:description>This Geepas 3 Way Extension Socket/Strip is damage-resistant and fireproof housing protects circuits from fire, impact or rust, and prevents dents and scratches. The built-in power indicator light makes it easy to know its ON/OFF mode. Compatible for connecting various devices like washing machines, Iron boxes, TV, Hair Dryer, Mobile, Drill machines, Printer, Computer, Refrigerator, Vacuum cleaners and more. 1. PREMIUM PROTECTION FOR YOUR ELECTRONICS -The Geepas strip features high-quality construction and a durable design with damage-resistant housing that protects circuits from fire, impact, and rust. Three protected AC outlets make this surge protection strip an ideal solution for home offices, media rooms, and other areas where multiple devices need to be connected. 2. 750 Degree Flame Retardant Material - Built with durable material which is fireproof ABS plastic and has a high melting and heating point, protecting your connected devices. The material is 750 degree Celsius Flame Retardant. 3. ERGONOMIC DESIGN -This extension strip has 3 plugs that are angled so it does not block the other outlet. This keeps it free for use with additional items. The size of this socket is 34. 2x13. 8x3. 4cm. 4. 3 METER POWER CORD - Along with its slim, sleek design that effortlessly slides into narrow spaces, the three-outlet, power strip provides a 3-meter extra long power cord to prevent a tripping hazard and to minimize clutter. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteSize 34. 2x13. 8x3. 4 cmVoltage 250 VModel Number GES58011Model Name Multi-Purpose</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bfc51ee7-b4cd-440a-a1a6-fb826c06f939</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/89f5932b-f883-403c-be66-a517784edcd4/web/1_1736915464322.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>31 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065358437991</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2235714990</g:id>
      <g:title>6 Way Extension Socket 13A - Extension Strip with 6 Led Indicators with Power Switches</g:title>
      <g:description>This Geepas 6 Way Extension Socket/Strip is damage-resistant and fireproof housing protects circuits from fire, impact, or rust, and prevents dents and scratches. The built-in power indicator light &amp;amp; power switches for all ports make it easy to know its ON/OFF mode. Compatible for connecting various devices like washing machines, Iron, TV, Hair Dryer, Mobile, Drill Machine, Printer, Computer, Refrigerator, Vacuum cleaners, and more. 1. PREMIUM PROTECTION FOR YOUR ELECTRONICS -The Geepas strip features high-quality construction and a durable design with damage-resistant housing that protects circuits from fire, impact, and rust. Four protected AC outlets make this surge protection strip an ideal solution for home offices, media rooms, and other areas where multiple devices need to be connected. 2. 750-Degree Flame Retardant Material - Built with durable material which is fireproof ABS plastic and has a high melting and heating point, protecting your connected devices. The material is 750 degrees Celsius Flame Retardant. 3. ERGONOMIC DESIGN -This extension strip has 6 plugs that are angled so it does not block the other outlet. This keeps it free for use with additional items. 4. 3 METER POWER CORD - Along with its slim, sleek design that effortlessly slides into narrow spaces, the four-outlet, power strip provides 3-meter extra-long power cord to prevent a tripping hazard and to minimize clutter. \' 'SpecificationsMaterial ABSColour Name White/BlueWhat's In The Box 1 x Extension SocketModel Number GES4093</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f4c0d961-e0cc-4db1-83d0-d64eb94ac85c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/312f049c-309e-48d0-916c-7eb6629fa1bb/web/1_1736918094497.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>44 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022357149904</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4990738261</g:id>
      <g:title>Portable Bluetooth Speaker With Microphone | Large Circle Dazzle LED Light Black</g:title>
      <g:description>USB/TF/FM/AUX INLarge circle dazzle LED lightWith handle, easy to carry anywhereWith microphoneCan put phone on the speaker to enjoyingOverviewGeepas Portable Bluetooth Speaker Have fun with your family and friends with this karaoke machine designed for amazing sounds and lighting effects. Large circle dazzle LED light and change color, while a dimmer gives you complete control over the party atmosphere. With this Bluetooth, you can easily stream your favorite music. compatible system or download the Singing Machine app to access thousands of karaoke favorites. This Bluetooth speaker has a built-in amplifier that can stream music to your instruments. Boom box's microphone speaker has multi-colored flashing LED lights that bring any occasion to life. Ideal for parties/gatherings at night when a colorful presence can be seen. This unit supports connection to mobile devices via Bluetooth or an AUX cable for music, TF or USB cards for music sources are also supported. SpecificationsColour Name Black/ BlueConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box User Manual , Warranty CardProduct Length 19. 5 cmProduct Height 25. 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 11 cmModel Number GMS11156Model Name Portable Bluetooth Speaker, With Microphone</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/91479051-ba2d-4887-9bdb-57b796380605</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/57da5fab-94c3-4396-b329-dea8949a5ae0/web/1_1736924550528.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>54 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049907382611</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1452012155</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Rechargeable Professional Speaker 40000W PMPO With Wireless Microphone And Remote Control</g:title>
      <g:description>LED Light - The Bluetooth speaker gives an exceptional audio performance and has an elegantly textured finish. It is designed with innovation and is decorated with embedded LED lights to set up the mood for a celebration. Enhanced Stereo Sound Geepas speaker machine adopts a big size speaker and is designed with multi-functions for full-range stereo sound reproduction. It makes the bass stronger and more balancedRechargeable Battery And Portable This high-powered heavy-duty wireless system has a 7. 4V/3600mAh rechargeable battery which is capable to give you longer workingWireless Bluetooth Streaming Geepas speaker has instant wireless music streaming abilityCompatible Wireless Microphone The wireless microphone input allows the speaker to be used as a portable machine With this wireless microphone and sing your heart out to your favorite tunes. Connect With Ease Multi Function The all-in-one portable Bluetooth speaker can be quickly and easily connected to any Bluetooth-enabled device and supports FM radio wireless connection wired AUX input music playback via USB disk TF cardFM Radio USB/TF Card slot Bluetooth TWS FunctionMenu Control Treble Bass Echo Mic volume effectOverviewA powerful speaker with a breath-taking sound! This speaker with a compact design is ideal for listening to music anywhere, alone, with friends and family! Its woofer and its tweeter give a clear and powerful sound. It turns into karaoke thanks to the included microphone to liven up all your parties. Adjust the sound of your music as you like thanks to the many settings possibilities: Adjusting the bass, treble, and equalizer to adjust the musical style. Create an atmosphere of your dreams wherever you want! This speaker with multi-colored disco lights is ideal for illuminating your evenings. In addition, its rechargeable battery ensures a long time working for moments of music! The built-in rechargeable battery is ideal for when you're located away from the mains plug, the ultimate companion for spoken-word performers, fitness instructors, musicians, and parties! This speaker is multifunctional and can be connected via USB, has a Micro SD card slot, and can also be connected via Bluetooth. This makes it compatible with your iPhone, iPad, and Computers. connect effortlessly as you wish! This light speaker connects easily wirelessly with all devices equipped with Bluetooth function. It also has a USB port, a micro-SD / AUX-IN jack (with cable not included) to connect an external audio player. SpecificationsProduct Weight 6. 5 KGColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box User Manual, Warranty CardProduct Length 35. 5 cmProduct Height 112. 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 35. 5 cmWattage 40000 WFeatures USB, WirelessModel Number GMS11168Model Name GMS11168</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/84b6dc13-4a2f-4ac9-a648-a5f3664565b3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ca861b0f-d64c-41c5-b8ce-2542579f1970/web/1_1736927675679.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>341 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014520121558</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1106973321</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas 50" Smart Ultra HD LED TV With 4K Resolution, Android 14 , Frameless Design</g:title>
      <g:description>4K Ultra HD Resolution: Enjoy stunning visuals with a resolution of 3840 x 2160 pixels, providing exceptional clarity and detail for all your favorite content. Frameless Design: The sleek, frameless design maximizes screen space and enhances the aesthetic appeal of your living room, making it a stylish addition to any decor. HQ Sound: Experience immersive audio with high-quality sound that brings every dialogue and sound effect to life, enhancing your overall viewing experience. Multiple HDMI &amp;amp; USB Ports: Connect various devices effortlessly with multiple HDMI and USB ports, allowing for easy switching between gaming consoles, Blu-ray players, and more. Progressive Scan Technology: This feature reduces flicker and improves image stability, ensuring smooth playback of fast-moving scenes, perfect for action movies and sports. Full Color Optimizer: The Full Color Optimizer technology enhances color accuracy and vibrancy, ensuring that every hue is displayed as intended for a lifelike viewing experience. Progressive Scan: This feature enhances the quality of video playback by reducing flicker and improving image stability. It ensures that fast-moving scenes are displayed smoothly, making it ideal for action movies and sports. Smart TV: This TV is equipped with smart technology, allowing you to access a variety of streaming services and apps directly from the screen. Enjoy seamless browsing and a user-friendly interface that makes finding your favorite shows and movies a breeze. AV Mode: The AV mode automatically adjusts sound and picture quality depending on the content you're watching, providing the best audiovisual experience for movies, sports, and gaming. Brightness/Contrast: Featuring 200 cd/m2 brightness and a 3000:1 contrast ratio, this TV delivers sharp and vibrant images with deep blacks and bright whites for enhanced picture quality. Energy Saving Technology: Equipped with energy-saving features, this TV optimizes power consumption without compromising performance, ensuring an eco-friendly viewing experience. Convenience: Progressive scan, UHD, color temperature adjustment. OverviewThe Geepas 50" Ultra HD Smart LED TV is designed to transform your home entertainment experience with its stunning 4K resolution of 3840 x 2160 pixels. This TV delivers exceptional clarity and detail, making every movie, show, and game come to life. The frameless design not only enhances the aesthetic appeal of your living space but also maximizes the screen area, allowing you to immerse yourself fully in the action. Equipped with smart technology, the offers seamless access to a variety of streaming services, including Netflix, YouTube, and more. The user-friendly interface makes it easy to navigate through apps and settings, ensuring that you can find your favorite content quickly. The high-quality sound system complements the stunning visuals, providing an immersive audio experience that enhances every scene. Connectivity is a breeze with multiple HDMI and USB ports, allowing you to connect various devices such as gaming consoles, Blu-ray players, and external storage. The TV also features Progressive Scan technology, which reduces flicker and improves image stability, making it ideal for fast-paced action scenes. With its Full Color Optimizer, colors are rendered accurately and vibrantly, ensuring that every hue is displayed as intended. Whether you're hosting a movie night or enjoying a quiet evening at home, the Geepas 50" Ultra HD Smart LED TV promises to elevate your entertainment experience, making it a must-have for any media enthusiast. SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 3Video Format 4K Ultra HDProduct Weight 7. 7 KGScreen Size 50 inColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Remote Control , Users Manual and Warranty CardViewing Distance 3. 2 mModel Year 2024Features Android, Bluetooth, HDMI, Smart TV, USBModel Number GLED5023SCUHDModel Name GLED5023SCUHDNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ff06411e-8141-4bdd-a9b8-7279d55d4258</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0ca22fac-8230-4035-a796-aab59335de11/web/1_1736943275473.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011069733211</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8869664994</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Rechargeable Bluetooth Speaker, BT/USB/TF Card/FM , Lithium Battery Speaker</g:title>
      <g:description>Truly Wireless Speaker enables you to easily connect Geepas Bluetooth speakers via Bluetooth 5. 0 and form a truly wireless stereo left channel and right channel and get the stereo sound effect in few seconds. Its design makes it look very elegant and handy. You can easily carry it anywhere you go, use it in your car, on a trip, an outdoor party, while walking and more. Bluetooth offers better signal quality for noise-free audio. Not only supports hands-free calling, but also supports FM radio. The audio cable can be connected to the computer and the car, and the TF card and USB can be plugged in to play music. Compatible with all Bluetooth-enabled devices, make music more wonderful and make your parties or picnic time more shining, full of youthful style, glowing you are energetic. Made up of ABS material it is a polymer known for its strength and durability. This device is resistant to breakage and built to give a long-term performance. GRAB, GO, LISTEN - Lightweight, yet robust design provides the perfect soundtrack for the park, yard, or anywhere else at home or away. DURABLE &amp;amp; PORTABLE - The Bluetooth speaker is a built-in rechargeable battery and supports long hours of playback time. The ultra-small size and portable design with an attached hanging loop make it ideal for outdoor travel. 1200 MAH RECHARGEABLE LITHIUM BATTERY - Rechargeable built-in large capacity rechargeable lithium battery. Takes 3 to 5 hours to get fully charged and will give you continuous long hours working. TOP MOUNTED CONTROLS, GRIP HANDLE - Easy to use with the top placed controls easily accessible with rubber finish manages to stay waterproof. Easy to carry with the grip handle while travelling with your friends and family. 'SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box warranty card &amp;amp; user manualModel Number GMS11181Model Name GMS11181</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/df3c19c9-4e9a-4e40-9084-9492ed76cb27</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/48168232-7c71-47b5-a1d6-f2918c3fbc7c/web/1_1736927145166.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>54 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088696649949</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
