<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>1813118012</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 46mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Black Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSeries 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 46 MmModel Number MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/AModel Name MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5e4b86fc-c828-4c48-a5a9-42b37bc02f4d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6cc881d1-ae06-4927-920f-0e935aae851f/web/1_1727680025843.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1899 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018131180126</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9810767408</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/af7074dc-eaa4-4cd3-9793-a5b32fb3126e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aae5939e-73e7-4a59-a62c-76f98f4b5769/web/1_1727440889602.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098107674088</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5778822495</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXD33 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU Processor/16GB RAM/512GB SSD/Intel UHD Graphics English Starlight</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name StarlightLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Graphics Processor Series Intel UHDDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3Usage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXD33LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/11b2a137-1e9f-4d10-a1e9-5d07c145de18</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e4026745-35c2-431b-b954-0bf326e4c27c/web/1_1725020847241.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057788224951</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7379715380</g:id>
      <g:title>Dji Mini 3 With Remote Control</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMini size powerful imagingStunning footage al all hoursAmazing results effortlesslyGo far with 10km transmission51 Min extended flight timeOverviewFilm in 4K HDR Video for crystal clear aerial shots. With Dual Native ISO Fusion, Mini 3 enables the capture of details in highlights and shadows, both day and night. With True Vertical Shooting, you can easily capture tall landmarks like skyscrapers and waterfalls. And after capturing, it's in the perfect orientation to post to Instagram or TikTok. Its flight time can be extended up to 51 minutes with the Intelligent Flight Battery Plus (sold separately), but the aircraft will weigh more than 249 g. Fly More combo offers up to 114 minutes of total flight time. Wind Resistant and 3-Axis Gimbal for Stable - With its Level 5 wind resistant and 3-axis mechanical gimbal, Mini 3 can capture consistently smooth 4K imagery. rushless motors enhance power and allow takeoff at altitudes up to 4,000 meters. Up to 10 km (32,800 feet) [5] of HD video transmission and has excellent anti-interference capabilities, giving you the ability to freely explore vast landscapes and see clearer. SpecificationsColour Name GreyModel Number DJI-MVM300-SC / MT3PDModel Name DJI-MVM300-SC</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1f52255c-7435-42c4-8699-3d29a583c22d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/367f4920-9e03-4df7-87c5-9e9b4a712404/web/1_1725007082282.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>DJI</g:brand>
      <g:price>1629 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073797153808</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5811700566</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 Dual SIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Samsung galaxy z flip6, AI phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB storage, blue, android smartphone, 50MP camera, flexcam, long battery lifeGalaxy AI: Your self-expression tool, galaxy z flip6, is compact and eye-catching, with galaxy al and a pro-level 50MP cameraDesign: Most compact. Big impact. Galaxy z flip6's new floating design is modern, slim and sleek50MP camera: The upgraded 50mp wide rear camera processes your pics through the provisual engine to capture stunning scenes and richer portraitsFlexcam: The flexcam uses auto zoom to zoom in or out on subjects, and provides a preview on the flexwindow for a hands-free selfie experienceSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 4 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Flip 6Model Name Flip 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a3638170-d734-43c5-b663-7ef0d34909fe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/75691e34-5bc3-46c7-90d4-c65f33b415d4/web/1_1725623503879.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058117005661</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6969523284</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Pink 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>SAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 1TB Storage, Pink, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BLIHMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fdca7c22-7e68-4324-bad7-780d0a1b9859</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e019b391-8be4-46e4-8e6c-5529dec31255/web/1_1726574644260.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069695232844</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1348518604</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/69da9ac5-acdb-47c3-bc5a-4e4fc8905449</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a373eec9-6c7a-4a80-8a3d-774096d392a6/web/2_1727442153685.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013485186046</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1975931898</g:id>
      <g:title>SAMSUNG Galaxy Buds 2 Pro Bora Purple</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsComfort fit - We redesigned the earbuds to be 15% smaller than Buds Pro to fit snugly in your ear. Sound quality - Every note sounds like the real thing because clear audio starts at the source with your favorite Samsung Galaxy device. The ultimate wireless listening experience with 24bit Hi-Fi sound. Active Noise Cancelling - With 3 high SNR (Signal-to-Noise Ratio) microphones, Galaxy Buds2 Pro track and eliminate more outside sound — even soft sounds like wind. OverviewGalaxy Buds2 Pro will automatically pop up on your Samsung Galaxy devices and are ready to connect with a tap. As simple as that. Walk away from your Galaxy Buds2 Pro and the integrated alarm is ready to let you know — and your phone will send you a notification so that you don't accidentally leave them behind. With Intelligent 360 Audio, the sound feels more realistic. 360 Audio can even pinpoint the direction of the sound as you move your head, giving you the spatial experience. Simply start talking and Voice Detect will turn off ANC and activate Ambient sound — allowing you to clearly hear the conversation without removing your Buds2 Pro. SpecificationsConnection Type WirelessColour Name Bora PurpleAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WirelessEarplug Type EarbudsModel Number SM-R510NLVAMEA, SM-R510NLVAEUEModel Name SM-R510NLVAMEA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6a3e308e-2161-4a67-9dba-574037adf712</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/971beba9-83b6-4d44-a1bb-e33f57693790/web/2_1719464868184.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>347 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019759318984</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3134983340</g:id>
      <g:title>Xbox Series S 512 GB Digital Console With Wireless Controller</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsWith Quick Resume, you can seamlessly switch between multiple different titles and resume instantly from where you left offIt brings elegant design, refined comfort and instant sharing to a familiar favoriteSignificantly reduced load times and stunning visuals at up to 120 FPSYour games, saves and backups are safe in the cloudGo all-digital and enjoy disc-free, next-gen gaming with the smallest Xbox console ever madeOverviewNext-gen performance in the smallest Xbox ever Go all-digital with the disc-free gaming of Xbox Series S. Get started with an instant library of 100+ high quality games, including all-new Xbox Game Studios titles, like Halo Infinite, the day they release, when you add Xbox Game Pass Ultimate (membershipsold separately). Xbox Game Pass Ultimate Download and play over 100 high-quality games, including all-new Xbox Game Studios titles the day they release, with Xbox Game Pass Ultimate. 1 Plus, get all the benefits of Xbox Live Gold and EA Play when you subscribe. Meet the new Xbox Wireless Controller Experience the modernized Xbox Wireless Controller, designed for enhanced comfort during gameplay. All digital All your games, saves, entertainment, and more are accessible in the cloud. Plus, pre-install games and play the moment they drop. Get a grip Stay on target with textured grips on the trigger and bumpers. Full circle The hybrid D-pad offers players a familiar yet refined twist on the classic Xbox Wireless Controller. Go ahead, show off Tap the dedicated Share button to seamlessly capture and eternalize your conquest. SpecificationsColour NameWhite - Series S 512 GBConnection TypeWirelessWhat's In The Box1xSeries S Console, 1xController, 1xUltra High Speed HDMI Cable and 1xPower CordType of Console SoftwareXbox Series SLanguageEnglishStorage Capacity512 GBModel NumberXSeriesS/1883Model NameXSeriesS</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b004d189-891b-440e-b92e-e754167be9f9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b6bbada3-5c4f-4c90-9172-e3437f661650/web/2_1727764642334.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031349833400</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1905008405</g:id>
      <g:title>H8 Mini Drone 4k Dual Camera Rc Aircraft Four Side Obstacle Avoidance Optical Flow Positioning Foldable Quadcopter</g:title>
      <g:description>Specifications Colour Name Black Video Recording Resolution Type 1080p Camera Resolution 1080 MP Model Number H8 Model Name H8 RC Mini Drone</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e901ad89-6081-4798-801f-cf8f86e9deb3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9f222068-204e-4904-8ee2-5edf52047350/web/2_1727769170454.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019050084052</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
