<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9764500654</g:id>
      <g:title>Bakeey GT112 bluetooth Wireless Speaker </g:title>
      <g:description>Bakeey GT112 bluetooth Wireless Speaker Colorful LED Stereo Surround Sound Subwoofer Portable FM Radio RED CCOLOR</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3dc106a1-c557-4713-a184-d0fd6eab9745</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/55eef291-c38d-4922-857f-1c9a74423d1b/web/1_1732281900198.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097645006542</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7373605164</g:id>
      <g:title>TP-LINK Access Point/ Wireless N Router - 300Mbps White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAPs support a host of different functions that makes your wireless networking experience more flexibleFlexible Deployment- Up to 30 meters (100 feet) of flexible deployment with included Passive Power over Ethernet InjectorMultiple Modes – Supports Access Point, Multi-SSID, Client, and Range Extender modesSpecificationsColour Name WhiteAntenna Type ExternalWireless Standard 4GModel Number TL-WR840NModel Name Router-21Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d7c66e99-50d5-41fe-b247-97791f22cbca</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/51dca9d1-ebe8-490e-a501-752bce1d7e2f/web/1_1732283834329.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>49 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073736051646</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6290467207</g:id>
      <g:title>TP-LINK Wireless N Router TL-WR840N 300Mbps Tp-link White</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights300Mbps wireless transmission rate is ideal for both bandwidth sensitive tasks and basic workIP based bandwidth control allows administrators to determine the allocated bandwidth in each PCWDS wireless bridge provides seamless bridging to expand your wireless networkAllows easy setup of an encrypted secure connection at a push of the WPS buttonTp link’s tl wr840n is a high speed solution that is compatible with ieee 802. 11b g n based on 802. 11n technology tl wr840n gives users wireless performance at up to 300mbps which can meet your most demanding home networking needs such as hd streaming online gaming and large files downloadingOverviewThe 300Mbps Wireless N Router TL-WR840N is a combined wired/wireless network connection device designed specifically for small business and home office networking requirements. The TL-WR840N creates an exceptional and advanced wireless performance, making it ideal for streaming HD video, VoIP and online gaming. Also, Wi-Fi Protected Setup (WPS) button on the sleek and fashionable exterior ensures WPA2 encryptions, preventing the network from outside intrusions. TP-LINK’s TL-WR840N is a high speed solution that is compatible with IEEE 802. 11b/g/n. Based on 802. 11n technology, TL-WR840N gives users wireless performance at up to 300Mbps, which can meet your most demanding home networking needs, such as HD streaming, online gaming and large files downloading. Processor-Single-Core CPU,External Power Supply-9VDC / 0. 6A,Frequency-2. 4-2. 4835GHzSpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableSet Includes Routers, manualWhat's In The Box Routers, manualWireless Technology WiFi 4Band Technology Dual BandConnector Type RJ45Antenna Type ExternalWireless Standard NProduct Length 182 mmProduct Height 35 mmProduct Width/Depth 128 mmWi-Fi Range 300 ft²Max Data Transfer Rate 300 MBpsFeatures Eco Friendly, Ergonomic, Business, AmbidextrousModel Number TL-WR840NModel Name TL-WR840NItem Quantity 1Number of Ports 5Wireless Standard Value 802. 11n</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a75029df-ba66-4ade-bd83-62589b44ed31</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c0a8ea37-cd9d-46f9-a077-18a3dcbe5fa0/web/1_1732427191049.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>53 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062904672073</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2902119374</g:id>
      <g:title>Alde Aldeepo 10,000 mAh Digital Display Charging Power Bank- Black</g:title>
      <g:description>AldeAldeepo 10,000 mAh Digital Display Charging Power Bank- Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f078262b-67a5-4542-9455-70f776632d87</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1a61627d-89f7-4527-92c3-e6a00d7d76d4/web/1_1732454499141.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>85 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029021193744</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4204561812</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Birf iPhone 16 series EcoGuard Camera Lens Protector</g:title>
      <g:description>GenericBirf iPhone 16 series EcoGuard Camera Lens Protector</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5b8f7553-fb77-49f8-9022-8d66ddc313dc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5e7fdc4b-bb04-4c85-8f87-764e38739df2/web/1_1732456110087.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>99 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042045618123</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6035291301</g:id>
      <g:title>Zentality Ultra Smart 2.02Inch Amoled Display</g:title>
      <g:description>Zentality Ultra Smart 2. 02Inch Amoled Display</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/29a378d2-83dd-4f68-8c31-2116543322e0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bf53f11a-637c-4378-8d53-74254b619d5d/web/1_1732459970807.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>135 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060352913014</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3536042555</g:id>
      <g:title>TP-LINK Wireless N Router TL-WR840N 300Mbps Tp-link White/Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights300Mbps wireless transmission rate ideal for both bandwidth sensitive tasks and basic workAccess point mode to create a new Wi-Fi access pointRange extender mode to boost the existing wireless coverage in your roomIPTV supports IGMP proxy/snooping, bridge and tag VLAN to optimize IPTV streamingGuest network provides separate access for guests while securing the home networkOverviewFounded in 1996, TP-Link is a global provider of reliable networking devices and accessories, involved in all aspects of everyday life. The company is consistently ranked by analyst firm IDC as the No. 1 provider of Wi-Fi devices, supplying distribution to more than 170 countries and serving billions of people worldwide. With a proven heritage of stability, performance and value, TP-Link has curated a portfolio of products that meet the networking needs of all individuals. Now, as the connected lifestyle continues to evolve, the company is expanding today to exceed the demands of tomorrow. Specifications-Product Weight 380 g-Colour Name White/Grey-Connection Type Wired-Set Includes 2000 mAh WIFI Router White/Grey-What's In The Box WIFI Router-Wireless Technology WiFi-Band Technology Single Band-Connector Type RJ45-Antenna Type External-Wireless Standard 4G-Product Length 18. 2 cm-Product Height 12. 8 cm-Product Width/Depth 3. 5 cm-Wattage 5 W-Max Data Transfer Rate 100 MBps-Features Personal, Indicator Lights, Business, Personal-Model Number WR840N-Model Name N Router-Item Quantity 1-Number of Ports 1-Wireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11n</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/53031e1e-09f4-4851-9f97-55ddbc93dbf9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/776c27f2-1a5b-44f4-91d9-080070a83834/web/4_1732360208879.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>51.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035360425552</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1167961917</g:id>
      <g:title>Switch 10000.0 mAh Powerpack Ultra Power Bank Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPowerful voltage boost technology delivers optimised charging cycles to your deviceSlim design keeps your devices charged on the goBuilt-in voltage protection to ensure the safety of connected devicesSpecificationsBattery Size 10000 mAhColour Name BlackModel Number ACSWTPP10PDQCGM</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c3ce0e9b-fda5-479b-b601-f8b7a601e42e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b9660fb9-a974-41cb-b2d9-71605ff86db8/web/1_1732456166732.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>69 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011679619172</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1142460574</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Remote For Apple TV 2nd/3rd Generation Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsConnect your iPod to a home stereo, powered speakers or TV setExperience your songs, slideshows and more from across the roomPlug your iPod into the Apple Universal Dock and choose a playlist, slideshow or video. Just press the Next button on the Apple RemoteOverviewApple Remote with iPod and iPhone - If you connect your iPod to a home stereo, powered speakers or TV set, the Apple Remote lets you experience your songs, slideshows and more from across the room. Plug your iPod into the Apple Universal Dock and choose a playlist, slideshow or video. Just press the Next button on the Apple Remote. Apple Remote with Mac, The Apple Remote gives you total command of your music, photos, videos and DVDs from anywhere in the room. SpecificationsProduct Weight 41 gColour Name Silver/BlackProduct Height 13. 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 4. 2 cmModel Number MM4T2ZM/AItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9a39fdb0-0467-41a5-9c5b-0524d4f2c548</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/19e554d9-a8b4-4b88-aae7-1605871b6ebf/web/1_1732463021187.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>255 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011424605740</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7815299285</g:id>
      <g:title>Renewed - iPhone 15 Pro Max With Facetime 256GB White Titanium 5G</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Overview"Renewed Premium: Never been used/Negligible use, but may have been looked at. These items have zero scratches or bruises. They are checked, renewed and re-packed in a generic/OEM box. You will get original accessories With 3 -months warranty. 1. Product is Never been used/Negligible use. It is Renewed like new with zero scratches and packed in a new generic box. It comes with original accessories. 2. Product has passed standard functionality checklist and has been renewed by certified sellers to Like new condition3. All products sold on are 100% functional. The grade of any product only signifies its physical appearance4. Product will come with 3 -months warrantySpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSGrade PremiumVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition RenewedModel Number iPhone 15 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d9da90ea-ad2f-4784-88c9-4872f07a5f2f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cd8df4e2-ee9b-4c6c-b90d-1b9f3af05f1e/web/6_1732516110344.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078152992856</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4857813295</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Replacement LCD Screen For Apple iPhone 6s White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsIntegrated digitizer efficiently and quickly converts touch gestures into digital signalsPremium quality display panel produces vibrant colours in rich contrastReinstates your damaged screen, ensuring the device is back to its prime conditionWell defined circuitry seamlessly re-establishes the display functionalityFestooned with quality grade body that offers high sensitivity to touchOverviewReplacement LCD Screen Assembly + Touch Glass Digitizer Phone Repair Tool Kit for iPhone 6S Instructions:- Use a card pin to push out the SIM card holder- Remove the screws, use the sucker, pry tools and crow bars to open the screen carefully- Remove the battery and battery flex cable- Remove the screen assembly accessories and now the disassembly work is completed- Installation steps shall be carried out in accordance with the reverse stepsPack of Mount Accessories:- 1 x LCD screen touch digitizer panel outer glass pre-assembled frame for iPhone 6S- 1 x 0. 8mm star screwdriver- 1 x phillips screwdriver- 1 x flathead screwdriver- 2 x crow bar- 2 x pry tool- 1 x sucker Package weight: 0. 149 kgPackage Size(L x W x H): 20. 30 x 13. 10 x 3. 50 cm / 7. 99 x 5. 16 x 1. 38 inchesPackage Contents: 1 x LCD Display Touch Screen Digitizer, 1 x Pack of Mount AccessoriesSpecificationsModel Number WR</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/14212aa0-614e-4fc8-8ddb-d511428a9f6f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/90b6391d-b638-4ab3-bb1f-23a9fd0285fa/web/1_1732455939590.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>68 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048578132952</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1872725035</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 128GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYMV3AE/A , MYMV3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4088b4e5-1074-46cb-8211-ce383837da14</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/495ed102-bbd1-4353-93b2-1be3c20d3b51/web/1_1732526394182.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4519 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018727250356</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2420042826</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 128GB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYMW3AE/A , MYMW3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/40d86728-3ba3-4b9f-acb5-bc2c28cc95e9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/234bb3bc-e531-4b53-8f34-079970076d22/web/1_1732526569826.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4580 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024200428266</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4882834009</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 128GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYMY3AE/A , MYMY3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/980563af-e22a-48d2-91b0-365c091ade85</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5ce20bda-eadb-4af3-992a-87c9eda14b76/web/1_1732526749241.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4580 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048828340090</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9829505034</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2021 (9th Generation) 10.2-Inch, 64GB, With Facetime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The A13 Bionic chip makes everything more responsive, from messaging to web browsing to using multiple apps at onceUp to 20% faster GPU gives you the graphics performance you need. Perfect for playing immersive games and moreA more powerful Neural Engine drives machine learning–based features like Live Text in iPadOS 15The A13 Bionic chip effortlessly powers advanced apps like Adobe Fresco and ProcreateWith all-day battery life, iPad is ready to work or play for as long as you need itOverviewApple is a premium brand masquerading as a luxury one, It is one of the best- regarded brands globally, Apple's brand is valued at over $200 billion, in part because of the iPhone. But there's one thing it does that makes it more valuable than the rest, and it's something you can do too. It's almost hard to get a sense of the scale of a company like Apple From latest features to packaging the products, Apple does everything in a way that exhibits the company's uniqueness. Versatility and planning sets the company apart from the rest, making its products loved and coveted by the majority of people. Almost all the characteristics determining apple quality can be measured or classiﬁed. Consumers assess apples by its appearance (colour, size, shape, absence of defects) and then by its eating quality, although the latter may determine the willingness to buy the product again. Get the most out of the devices you love with high‑quality content and services. Award‑winning series and films, amazing music in spatial audio, world-class workouts and meditations, trusted news publications, superfun games even the ways you pay for things and they’re only on Apple. Since Apple has a large market share and is known for its versatile and fast operating system, developers prefer to launch their apps and high-end games first on iOS and then on Android. Further, iOS runs on consistent hardware, while Android comes in different iterations and versions depending on the phone. Apple is a fashion company, and in fashion companies, the role of design is style definition. When they released iOS7 in 2013, Apple signaled a major change in how UI and digital experience played into their company strategy. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPProcessor Speed 2. 65 GHzRAM Size 3 GBBattery Size 8557 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBProduct Weight 487 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 2 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name Space GrayCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2021Voice Calling Capability noOperating System Number iOS15Processor Number A13 Bionic chipFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box iPad 2021 (9th Generation)Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantFinish MetalMaximum Expandable Memory 2 TBSensor Barometer, Three‑axis Gyro, Ambient Light SensorModel Number Apple iPad 9th genModel Name iPad 2021 (9th Generation)Primary Camera (MP) 8MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7b35cba4-440b-4f31-83ce-c745f8be038f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ce99ab9b-4674-47ff-8b38-c3d50bf6f7eb/web/1_1732531892217.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>849 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098295050343</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6844279834</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 256GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN03AE/A , MYN03AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0599116c-0265-42c4-a67b-53ab4533d332</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1ab87dfa-5f29-4409-a3cf-6798baf2dd62/web/1_1732526958429.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5130 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068442798343</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4314147220</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your home screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your lock screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the action buttonIn the redesigned photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like people and petsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/be01afdb-0c0a-4eb7-a4f8-5df8944fc3a8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1a6852d7-38c2-44d0-b17a-96f546be8fcf/web/1_1732527131212.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043141472206</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7172320503</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWG3AE/A , MYWG3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d94a60b7-78ca-492d-8b65-8f1aa191d506</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0b44ef76-44bd-4e53-93c0-aa2bdfeff6a8/web/1_1732527270297.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5440 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071723205034</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3454374468</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 ProModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c9e3897f-ae20-4cf7-94ce-aa77a1b3b06d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fcde881c-4b20-400b-a97c-2b0db7e4fc3a/web/1_1732527469205.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5559 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034543744688</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6660866175</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN43AE/A , MYN43AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b003e911-882a-4e1a-b42f-62efe12a8a35</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d08cdb44-f00e-4d9e-be0d-d181d41f68c9/web/1_1732528167195.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6019 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066608661753</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5345391249</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWM3AE/A , MYWM3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fba3a1a2-cc94-4a09-9cf3-d334e92782e1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ef8ef8b7-6f9e-471b-9174-16d14f7cc531/web/1_1732528355175.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6349 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053453912499</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2490694690</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWL3AE/A , MYWL3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3542a754-63e6-4aa1-837d-6bbb19aa4b11</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ef02273a-8fd9-4122-a90e-7be74e2cd02d/web/1_1732528726448.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6370 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024906946903</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7810820887</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 1TB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYNA3AE/A , MYNA3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/300c576f-20a4-4d28-82c2-95bf743dae36</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a8b53c49-57be-460c-aa03-ace4f4cab75e/web/1_1732529095314.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>7000 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078108208871</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9901305765</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWT3AE/A , MYWT3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a5eb4ed7-bbcb-4798-aabb-f0f44a5bdf85</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5cf9d9eb-ba67-428e-968b-45ed02dcb91b/web/1_1732529232196.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>7349 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099013057651</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6336652489</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Wearable x headliner RW4009 601/9A 50 Polar G15 Green Shiny Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCapture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban | Meta Headliner With Ray-Ban Meta Headliner smart glasses you can express yourself with the most unique perspective there is – yours. Integrated with AI-enhanced wearable tech, the lightweight frame enables you to listen, call, capture and livestream, all while staying present in the moment. The Headliner panthos shape is a hybrid of the Wayfarer and the Round, bringing together the best of two icons. SpecificationsColour Name Shiny BlackStorage Capacity 32 GBModel Number RW4009Model Name RW4009Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1eb0856b-aba9-473d-abd3-4b556dbc1611</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6ad10f93-7336-4306-9193-c43dad7ecaed/web/1_1732118754579.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063366524894</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9403791888</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation VR2 Headset</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEscape into worlds that feel, look and sound truly real as virtual reality gaming takes a huge generational leap forward with PlayStation VR2. Experience new sensations with stunning 4K HDR visuals1, ground-breaking new controllers and genre-defining games, all made possible by the power of PS5Experience breath-taking virtual reality environments in clear focus with 4K High Dynamic Range visuals and up to 120fps1, as two 2000 x 2040 OLED displays deliver over four times the resolution generated by the original PlayStationVR headset. Enjoy comfortable play sessions through a vast 110º field of view and a light, well-balanced Fresnel lensInteract in new and lifelike ways, as the PS VR2 headset detects the motion of your eyes1, allowing for heightened emotional response and enhanced expression when meeting fellow players online. SpecificationsVersion International VersionColour Name WhiteType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFI-ZVR1Model Name CFI-ZVR1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/50906d32-f9d5-4d4c-bd29-afef8969952c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bee0ad62-e066-4289-b94e-cda45dbb002f/web/1_1732011459978.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094037918889</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9705902999</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWP3AE/A , MYWP3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c439a0ea-fc3d-4cfc-8a7b-e2f0572cb6e8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cc358963-53b0-4efd-8611-b02903af33aa/web/8_1732528917571.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097059029991</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8784905146</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ea2ccf61-abe8-4e55-a6ed-d5773472fcb8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/15d8c291-73e1-4983-b779-a165156df917/web/1_1728634708657.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087849051462</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3238983540</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 46mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Black Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 46 mmModel Number MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/A, MWWQ3ZP/A, MWWQ3LW/A, MWWP3ZP/AModel Name MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/A, MWWP3LW/A, MWWQ3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ba05a26a-07f9-47fb-9b5b-a5a8dd9283b8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c754322e-1a79-484e-9b0d-055284f1b128/web/1_1732526067893.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1488 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032389835409</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4019816698</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Blue - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Blue 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/62d116a7-f12d-4b43-9806-0b9d28288c4c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f4b2b61c-cbc1-4a8f-a8ba-8c0a0235b1d7/web/1_1732526300557.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1305 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040198166980</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6305689680</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 512GB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN53AE/A , MYN53AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9dd2182b-7930-4d43-ae07-8eda9edf4913</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b71c5547-08bc-4c05-8b43-2b1b90c22a00/web/1_1732528008198.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6019 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063056896805</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6287991340</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWH3AE/A , MYWH3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/746d14e4-6202-4afc-affa-4577564eae42</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/27203b20-4078-4273-8906-11ad6cd61803/web/1_1732527659270.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062879913409</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1194019963</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN63AE/A , MYN63AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c82ab518-c6b1-438c-a6b1-82196cc2e3c1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b6778ea0-04df-4a63-8a81-e85bb2dc0990/web/1_1732527857226.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6019 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011940199631</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3335751148</g:id>
      <g:title>Panasonic Pocket AM/FM Radio RF-P50 Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact design and user-friendly interfaceOffers stunning audio output by rendering crisp highs and subtle lowsWith ultra portable slim design so that you can easily carry it in your pocketInbuilt speakers so you can now enjoy your favorite tunes and even you get an earphoneShows the status of signal tuning so that you can correct manual tuning to the appropriate frequencyOverviewAbout the Brand The Panasonic brand name was created in 1955 and was first used as a brand for audio speakers. It is a combination of the words, "Pan", and "Sonic", sound and has a meaning of bringing sound our Company creates to the world. Since 2008, it is used as the corporate brand representing the Company, products and services. Panasonic is committed to creating a better life and a better world, continuously contributing to the evolution of society and to the happiness of people around the globe. SpecificationsProduct Weight 4. 96 ozColour Name SilverModel Number RF-P50</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/37f92f1f-c093-414c-ace6-a0dbc21ce978</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e355dd3f-244a-423c-9713-49ff1d05077c/web/1_1732529510710.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>62.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033357511486</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4883106206</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWN3AE/A , MYWN3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1431ff3b-65ad-4646-a715-c725cc1e9494</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cf971112-47e4-4c04-a17c-23d5da569a91/web/1_1732528521265.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6349 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048831062064</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8602561793</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 42mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Black Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWWE3QA/A, MWWF3QA/A,MWWF3ZP/A, MWWE3ZP/A, MWWE3LW/AModel Name MWWE3QA/A, MWWF3QA/A, MWWE3LW/A, MWWF3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/adb343ea-6f70-4bc7-b5c8-d8a05e4f80fb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b3f6a72c-76e1-412a-8c4f-fbd6bf0e6d8a/web/1_1732534708649.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1337 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086025617935</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1273562562</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 42mm Rose Gold Aluminium Case With Light Blush Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Light Blush Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWWH3QA/A, MWWJ3QA/A, MWWJ3ZP/A, MWWH3ZP/AModel Name MWWH3QA/A, MWWJ3QA/A, MWWH3LW/A, MWWJ3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7d4ee1b3-82dd-4784-8475-9016ec7ccbae</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/568131f9-3c17-4023-ad30-3053311c4db7/web/1_1732535053708.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1387.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012735625625</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2048489904</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 ( 5th Generation) M4 11-Inch, 256GB, WiFi, Space Black With Standard Glass </g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4b6f627d-0d29-415c-8909-57908e83e14a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/619490c5-c997-46cd-91cd-deea7da2fea9/web/1_1732537943678.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3657 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020484899044</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3032068869</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab A9 Plus Graphite 4GB RAM 64GB Wifi - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylish with a touch of cool, the galaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ features a sleek design and a smooth metal body. Enjoy samsung’s signature tablet design in graphite, silver and navy with each hue highlighting effortless charmGalaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ come with up to 8GB of RAM memory, ensuring less lag while you multi-task. Plus, the built-in 128GB storage saves all your hi-res videos, photos and files. You can expand the storage with a microSD card — up to 1TBConquer multiple tasks at once. With galaxy tab A9+, you can sketch out architectural plans and choose captivating visuals and video chat — up to three apps all on one screen without ever closing a windowTake a deep dive into a rich soundscape with speakers that provide an enveloping audio experience. Whether you're enjoying a movie or music, galaxy tab A9+ lets you fully engage in 3D sound with stunning clarity and depthKeep your information safe and sound. Store important data in the secure folder and monitor the overall security status of your device on the privacy dashboard. Make the most of your samsung galaxy experience, worry-free of security issuesSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 7040 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name GraphiteCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System AndroidTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number 13. 0Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless WirelessModel Number SM-X210NZAAMEAModel Name Tab A9 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 8 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/091c9e75-3fcc-4932-a4f7-c18aa30afc57</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/88540450-f6a5-450d-8687-a070e7fdc98b/web/1_1732533654360.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>575 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030320688695</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9254581644</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple AirPods Pro (2nd generation) With MagSafe Case (USB‑C) White</g:title>
      <g:description>The brand-new H2 chip carries out more functions than ever, using computational algorithms to deliver even smarter noise cancellation, superior three-dimensional sound, and more efficient battery life — all at onceThe chip uses powerful new adaptation algorithms to process sound more quickly, tuning audio at the precise moment you hear it. Every detail is rendered for your specific ear shape, immersing you in higher‑fidelity soundA redesigned inward-facing microphone works with voice enhancement algorithms to better recognize and articulate your voice, so it sounds more natural when you’re on phone and video callsA custom-built driver and amplifier work with the H2 chip to provide lower distortion during playback, so you’ll hear deeper bass and crisper highs — across all volume levelsFeaturing up to two times more noise cancellation than their predecessor, the H2-powered AirPods Pro are built to let you listen in peace. With control over what you hear — and don’t hear — you’ll be immersed in songs and podcasts like never beforeOverviewTransparency mode lets outside sound in, so you can hear what's going on around you. Conversation Awareness lowers media volume and enhances voices of people in front of you, all while reducing background noise to make it easier for you to engage with people nearby when wearing AirPods Pro. Up to 2x more Active Noise Cancellation than the previous-generation AirPods Pro, so you,ll hear dramatically less noise from your surrounding. Adaptive Audio dynamically blends Transparency mode and Active Noise Cancellation to deliver the best listening experience for you in any environment. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CColour Name WhiteDepartment UnisexConnection Type True WirelessAverage Battery Life 16hrs - 24hrsUsage Type Business (Call/work)Audio Jack Type-CAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WirelessEarplug Type EarbudsFeatures Active Noise Cancellation, Bluetooth, Volume Control, Voice Assistant, EarhookModel Number MTJV3ZA/A, MTJV3AM/A, MTJV3ZE/A, MTJV3ZP/A, MTJV3J/A, MTJV3LL/A, MTJV3KH/A, MTJV3HN/AModel Name Airpods Pro 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e1135adc-7672-480a-b9aa-07dd2b20e663</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d77d21b8-45a5-4ae5-9f31-0fa0e989f80a/web/1_1732533465784.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>778 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092545816444</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3827097523</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Silver - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Silver 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/687c2853-1e57-4451-8b1e-588e91428218</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d3232558-caa8-4283-a744-8551327c25c1/web/1_1732533900696.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1288 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038270975230</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2873704233</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Airpods 2nd Gen With Charging Case White</g:title>
      <g:description>AirPods deliver an unparalleled wireless headphone experiencePut them in your ears and they connect immediately, immersing you in rich, high-quality soundThey can sense when they’re in your ears and pause when you take them outTalking to your favourite personal assistant is easier than everOptical sensors and motion accelerometers work together to automatically controlling the audio experienceOverviewMore magical than ever. Now with more talk time, AirPods deliver an unparalleled wireless headphone experience. Simply take them out and they’re ready to use with all your devices. Put them in your ears and they connect immediately, immersing you in rich, high-quality sound. Just like magic. Wireless to the fullest. After a simple one-tap setup, AirPods are automatically on and always connected. Using them is just as easy. They sense when they’re in your ears and pause when you take them out. And the AirPods experience is just as amazing whether you’re using them with your iPhone, Apple Watch, iPad, or Mac. Performance you’ll want to hear. Powered by the all-new Apple H1 headphone chip, AirPods deliver a faster and more stable wireless connection to your devices — up to 2x faster when switching between active devices, and a 1. 5x faster connection time for phone calls. The H1 chip also delivers up to 30 percent lower gaming latency. So whether you’re playing games, listening to music, or enjoying podcasts, you’ll experience higher-quality sound. The power of 24‑hour battery life. AirPods deliver an industry-leading 5 hours of listening time — and now up to 3 hours of talk time — all on one charge. And they’re made to keep up with you, thanks to a charging case that holds multiple charges for more than 24 hours of listening time. Need a quick charge? Just put AirPods back in the case for 15 minutes to get up to 3 hours of listening time and 2 hours of talk time. To check the battery, simply hold the AirPods next to your iPhone. SpecificationsCharging Type Lightning PortProduct Weight 4 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type True WirelessAverage Battery Life More than 24hrsUsage Type Business (Call/work)What's In The Box AirPods, Charging Case, Lightning to USB-A Cable, DocumentationAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WiredEarplug Type EarbudsProduct Length 44. 3 mmProduct Height 53. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 21. 3 mmFeatures Voice Assistant, Travel, Gaming, Business, ErgonomicModel Number MV7N2 , MV7N2AM/A , MV7N2RU/A, MV7N2ZA/A , MV7N2ZP/A ,MV7N2ZE/A , MV7NRU/A , MV7N2TY/A , MV7N2HN/A , MV7N2ZM/A , MV7N2CH/AItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/287b45a7-6bc2-4e78-9de7-9c4892aa3652</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/935871bb-45bb-4277-8977-28aac80881df/web/1_1732537315608.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>319 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028737042339</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1511814724</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Pink - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name PinkCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Pink 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f4e59b44-75e4-48e4-91a9-2f896a62ef58</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/55f84e0d-7699-43a4-8f20-023cfc9f8260/web/1_1732535461892.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1319 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015118147240</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3627046919</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS 40mm Starlight Aluminium Case With Starlight Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Starlight Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number MR9U3QA/A , MR9V3QA/A, MR9U3LL/A, MR9U3ZP/A, MR9V3ZP/A, MR9U3SE/A, MR9V3QH/A, MR9V3LL/AModel Name MR9U3QA/A , MR9V3QA/A, MR9V3LL/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/10d79e6e-a1d3-4732-a36c-fc6847109a96</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2cb39584-79ac-4a22-8baa-2c6128c8ce94/web/1_1732537419007.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>798.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036270469193</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8309819088</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Air 2024 (6th Generation) M2 11-Inch 128GB Space Grey Wi-Fi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M2, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad AiriPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Air packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Air and an expansive 13″ iPad Air that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 7606 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space greyCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type WifiDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad AirModel Name iPad AirPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ab281dfa-328d-4a3d-b791-55bfa063a6b5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2a486c90-cebe-4c3a-a7e7-9261f4c3a429/web/1_1732537783438.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2248 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083098190884</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8837824551</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Watch 6 44 Mm GPS Smartwatch Graphite</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing BP &amp;amp; ECG on Galaxy Watch : Keep a track of your well-being by monitoring and tracking your blood pressure &amp;amp; ECG easily and more conveniently, right on your wrist. Introducing Contactless Secure Payments : make payments from your wrist with a simple Tap &amp;amp; Pay feature enabled by Samsung WalletPremium Watch : Designed with finest materials - Sapphire Crystal Glass &amp;amp; Armor Aluminum Dial. IP68 / 5ATM Water &amp;amp; Dust ResistanceOverviewAdvanced Sleep Coaching: Know your sleep with our new and improved sleep tracking technology. Plan your bedtime, detect snoring, understand and track your sleep on your wrist. Personalized HR: Create your own customized HR zones with just 10min of outdoor running. Maximize the output of your workouts with Zone alerts (Warm-up, Fat burn, Cardio etc. )SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CMaterial CombinationProduct Weight 33. 3 gColour Name GraphiteDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Product Length 44. 4 mmProduct Height 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 42. 8 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number SM-R940NZKAXMEModel Name Watch6 44 Mm, SM-R940NZKAEUE, SM-R940NZKACIS, SM-R940NZKAXME, SM-R940NZKΑΜΕΑItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6dbf364d-e414-468c-b88f-1c23baad06df</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9d104576-e94f-41c3-bfb6-cae3f2ecea51/web/1_1732538054659.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>507 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088378245513</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1466485721</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi TV A Pro 32 Inch HD Smart LED Google TV With 360° Bluetooth Remote Control Chromecast Built-In L32M8-A2ME Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPremium metallic frame with bezel-less design32" HD smart LED TV, Google TVGoogle Assistant built-in, Smart home control hub, Chromecast built-in, Supports MiracastNetflix, Prime Video and Youtube pre-installed. Thousands of apps available in Google PlaySpeaker (Sound Output) 2 × 10W, Supports Dolby Audio™, DTS-X and DTS® Virtual: X SoundOverviewThe ultra-narrow bezel design provides a high screen-to-body ratio far beyond that of standard TVs. From the instant you turn on the TV, high-resolution images in stunning colors blanket the screen for an immersive experience. Featuring an exquisite metallic frame with a unibody design, Xiaomi A Pro Series makes a real statement in any home. The 2 × 10W high-power stereo speakers fill the room with rich high and bass tones and provide an immersive sound experience. Google TV™ brings together movies, shows, and more from across your apps and subscriptions and organizes them just for you. Discover new things to watch with recommendations based on what you watch and what interests you, from across your subscriptions and content available to you. Your TV is more helpful than ever. Ask Google to find movies, stream apps, play music, and control the TV - all with your voice. Even get answers, control smart home devices, and more. Just say "Ok Google" or press the Google Assistant button on the remote to get started. Easily control your smart TV with the 360° Bluetooth remote control. The Chromecast built-in™* and Miracast allow you to continue watching what's on your smart mobile devices on a bigger screen, elevating your visual experience. The powerful quad-core A55 CPU combined with 1. 5GB RAM + 8GB ROM* offers smoother operation and more space for your favourite apps. Designed with a 2. 4GHz/5GHz Wi-Fi solution, various commonly used ports and Bluetooth 5. 0 to easily connect to different devices and adapt to more audio and video entertainment scenarios,SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 1080pInternal Memory 8 GBProduct Weight 3. 9 KGScreen Size 32 inRefresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System Google TVWhat's In The Box 60° bluetooth remote control × 1 Screws bag × 1 Stand × 2 Power cable × 1 User manual × 1 Warranty card × 1Number of Cores Quad CoreViewing Distance 1. 7 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 715. 7 mmProduct Height 423. 7 mmProduct Width/Depth 82. 5 mmFeatures Smart TV, Wi-Fi, AndroidModel Number L32M8-A2MEModel Name Xiaomi TV A Pro 32"Number of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c6ab1113-073b-4617-a4a2-3d4a8b41cee7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/95ff79f9-6d20-4afc-a490-371b9a1007a9/web/1_1731149110772.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>649 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014664857214</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1883460311</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro 40dB 3 Modes Noise Cancellation 28h Long Battery Life Black</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewUp to 40 dB Hybrid ANC The active noise cancellation can reduce up to 40dB of surrounding noise. 3 ANC modes You can switch to 3 different ANC modes in different environments, Office mode for light noise, Daily mode for outdoor noise, and Airplane mode for loud noise. 5-minutes Charge for 2 Hours Usage Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro supports fast charging, only 5 minutes charge you can use 2 hours. Never be afraid of battery off. Dual Device Connection Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro can be connected with two devices simultaneously. The devices include smartphones, tablets, PCs, and other smart devices. QCC 5151 SoC Qualcomm QCC5151 flagship SoC provides experience with robust connectivity, enhanced functionality and utilizes Low Energy technology. aptX Adaptive Qualcomm aptX Adaptive codec provides crystal clear audio performance and dynamic scalability. 11mm Dynamic Driver Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro adopts an 11mm dynamic driver and tuned by Xiaomi Sound Lap, offering you an immersive audio experience. Supports Wireless Charging Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro is compatible with Qi-certified chargers. Up to 28 hours battery life A single charge brings you up to 7 hours listening time with ANC off, and up to 28 hours when coupled with the charging case. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number BHR5114GLModel Name BHR5114GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e2c68f2d-11a6-4379-b15d-6fabfc28500d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/21be58c3-e7d7-4631-b256-223283e67b4a/web/1_1731157642829.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>309 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018834603113</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
