<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>Generic YG300 Full HD LED Projector 600 Lumens 95105 Yellow/White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsOptimal brightness levels proffer bright, lifelike colours and deep blacksHigh contrast ratio renders pictures in superior detail and clarityClocked with a wide range of inputs that ensure a clutter-free projection of high-quality imagesQuick-access lamp door reduces downtime by eliminating the need to uninstall mounted projectorCompact design makes it easily portableOverviewFull format video player: MP4, RMVB, etc. Support multi-media (music, pic, video, txt). Compact size, big wisdom: Its size is the same as a smart phone, but it has many interfaces. New generation LED light, power consumption is 10-24w. Good assistant for children education at home, also an attractive toy for kids. Uses LED light source, only 10-24W but up to 30000 hours lifespan, energy saving and environmental protection, no harm to eyesight. It is a good assistant for children Cartoon Watching and also an attractive children toys. Projector is 1280 x 800 resolution and 320 x 240p native resolution (support 1080P), can provide clear image in dark environment. Best image size 50 inches from 2 meter distance which can make you obtain best user experience1x Projector; 1x Power Plug; 1x Remote; 1x AV Cable; 1x User Manual. Notice: SEC YG300 is Not recommended for a Classroom or business presentation, needed use in a dark environment. Sleek stylish design, small and compact, mini size and only 10oz. Enjoy movie or football match after family dinner or BBQ Party at home or courtyard. Support 5V/2A portable power bank supply input( Not included). SpecificationsNumber of Charging Ports 1 PortTV HDMI Ports 1Product Weight 0. 28 KGColour Name Yellow/WhiteUsage Type HomeWhat's In The Box ProjectorsIncludes Without ScreenLight Source LampProduct Length 12. 5 cmProduct Height 4. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 5 cmProjector Brightness 1000 lmFeatures USBModel Number 95105Model Name YG300Number of USB Ports 1Number of HDMI Ports 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/49d334de-fba6-4e38-8ee9-c9d5d7564f65</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cf7bd58d-17b0-48b9-8fb4-27bfd0155242/web/1_1724398848230.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9476059396</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Digital Camera Tripod Stand With Cover Black/Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsTake control over your composition with increased camera performance and sharper images that will exceed your expectations. Extremely sharp pictures even at shorter focal lengths and in macro applicationsMaximum image quality whether you are shooting stills or video. Incredible portability and flexibilitySpecificationsProduct Weight 360 gColour Name Black/SilverSecondary Reflector NoProduct Height 104 cmFeatures Ergonomic, Travel, PersonalModel Number Pstore97Model Name Digital CameraItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/53946396-a1a1-4c63-8193-991ba76d4a99</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3fb0faa5-8364-45e5-bc4c-9767e674a052/web/1_1724663187822.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094760593964</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3969316771</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Tripod Stand With Carry Case Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAnti-skidding pads design, suitable for different kind of environmentHigh quality aluminium alloy material, firm and durableIdeal for digital camera, card camera and universal smart phone, flashlight etc. . Light, portable and easy to carrySupport 360°full rotation, convenient for you to take a photoSpecificationsProduct Weight 450 gColour Name SilverProduct Length 300 mmProduct Width/Depth 0. 66 inFeatures Ergonomic, Travel, Business, PersonalModel Number Pstore1029Model Name Tripod Camera Holder</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7d21a84e-dcdb-4cf7-9364-7ac347b77d46</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3a93e921-6ee1-4c01-8f46-10b3417101c4/web/1_1724665401447.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039693167714</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2080453634</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch 8</g:title>
      <g:description>Selling my apple watch 8 (41 mm) with originl straps and charger. Box isn't included</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fc610163-2b03-4b36-9f98-9e2ff683ae4e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/94de939e-4358-4d9f-9af9-b189f065950d/web/1_1711347180893.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020804536345</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6376375792</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Wireless WiFi USB Baby Home Security IP Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAPP monitor and control, you can check baby or older any time any where on mobiles, PC or iPad. Automatic Recording 24 hours all day, alarm recording, qudio recording and video recording. Built-in MIC and speaker for two-way talk, you can talk to your baby with super clear sound. The Infrared Night Vision will automatically start in dim light, providing clear video even in dark room. You can modify the camera user name and password, ensure safety. OverviewGeneric Digoo BB-M1 Wireless WiFi USB Baby Monitor Alarm Home Security IP Camera HD 720P Audio Netip One PieceSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number 1553668312482</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a61bc659-b9c0-4983-a2af-121ee6d67250</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/84f4d91e-5738-4c3a-82de-17ff1d5f6bbd/web/1_1724658703687.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>87.15 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063763757925</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9732708154</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic 3110 Flexible Camera Tripod Black/White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsQuick release plate for easy connecting to camera or camcorderRealizing any angle shooting, precise and efficientHigh quality material, durable and light weightSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 42 KGColour Name Black/WhiteSecondary Reflector NoProduct Length 36 cmProduct Height 7. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 8 cmFeatures BusinessModel Number XD4262700</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bb0c0e01-86b8-4276-bcc7-39a35487ce41</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/64bb8df7-169d-494b-b136-8e43f51b97b4/web/1_1724650279986.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097327081546</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8418182781</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Tripod Stand For DSLR Camera With Bag Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsErgonomically designed to offer better gripCompact and sleek for easy portabilityDurably designed for prolonged useSpecificationsColour Name Silver/Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/47746677-a13a-4223-9d41-09329ac36ab8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/397790b0-956b-4988-92f1-655af43aa476/web/1_1724656896060.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084181827816</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4086284429</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Flexible Camera Tripod Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsErgonomically designed to offer better gripCompact and sleek for easy portabilityDurably designed for prolonged useSpecificationsColour Name Silver/Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/84fc0aa7-e44e-4e58-a744-e31df1c291aa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c44d5f1e-a6c0-4afb-ad43-84d391e8d816/web/1_1724659244689.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040862844299</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2015976361</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Universal Adjustable Tripod Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsErgonomically designed to offer better gripCompact and sleek for easy portabilityDurably designed for prolonged useSpecificationsColour Name Silver/Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e5d309da-d742-48b5-ab4e-c71d10ff04ef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7834eb35-e5f8-4752-b350-695c70b4c820/web/1_1724663975777.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020159763618</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7586275105</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery E99 K3 Drone With Camera Quadcopter Fpv Profesional Rc Plane Remote Control Helicopter Dron Hd 4k Professional Gift Toys.</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewModel: K3/E99 Type: Single/Dual Camera Operation mode: remote control/APP control Frequency: 2. 4GHz Gyroscope: 6Axis Channel: 4CH Charging method: Universal USB interface Battery capacity: 3. 7V 1800mAH modular battery Flight time: about 10-15 minutes Charging time: 60 minutes Remote control distance: about 150 meters Camera mode: FPV Lens: Built-in camera Video resolution: 4K single camera/4K dual camera Speed adjustment: slow/medium/fast Product size: 25*25*6cm (expanded size) 12. 5*8*5. 5cm (folded size)SpecificationsColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Drone*1, Remote Control*1, Battery *1, Spare Wing Blades*2, USB Cable*1, Screwdriver*1, Manual *1Model Number E99 K3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/30bdbf18-7276-4e21-86a7-0dde5b58b3e0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6b79fca6-5ec2-43d7-bfeb-adb3dbf08247/web/1_1724662900267.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075862751056</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>tefeng Adjustable Tripod For iphones Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPhone bracket is adjustable and lightweightEasily change the orientation of the camera from portrait to landscape and almost any angle in between with the handy tilt motionEasy to use and carrySpecificationsColour Name Silver/BlackModel Number TF3110Model Name TF</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e3218664-e2dc-4076-b41f-35d0347c6edf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9966618e-b36f-4b5a-9b44-463f1af6181f/web/1_1724339998793.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>22.35 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8277566361</g:id>
      <g:title>Axiom DIY Acrylic Panel and Metal Arcade Case kit for 2 Player 2P Joysticks Replacement Arcade Game Machine Cabinet Controller Arcade Stick Empty Box</g:title>
      <g:description>【About Games】Pandoras 3D Box ,12000 in 1 support WIFI arcade game board with 300 3D games, support Chinese Traditional, English, Korean, Japanese, Spanis ,can download 3D games by Game classification:such as fighting games, shooting games, Stage Clear games, , puzzle games, sports games Or you can also download games by format such as MAME/N64/PS/PSP/FC/SFC/GBA/GBC/MD/PCE/DC 【HD Game Screen】It is compatible with HDMI and VGA, the resolution is 1280 x 720,support PC/PS3/4 USB joysticks online,can adjust the position of the handle，with pause,archive file, read file and play again next time;Support machine becomes gamepad mode, supports two-player online, supports any 1p position setting of the handle, and supports 4 gamepad at the same time. 【ADD 3D GAMES 】this product can support players to expand their own 3D games (Temporarily do not support 2D):(1)Prepare a TF card and choose the capacity according to the size of the game(2)Create a new folder in the root directory of the TF card with the name(roms): under the directory,create a new(game name folder),and place the game mirror under the game name Folder,for example: put Tekken 6 in TF,the complete path should be: roms/ tekken/tekken. 【About 3D Game】iso,cso,pbp,cdi,gdi,n64,c64,z64,NMI;among them,the iso of the PSX version needs to be converted to pbp. (Currently only supports game mirroring with the above suffixes,the H3 main chip only supports the expansion of PS games,and the NAOMI emulator currently only supports the 912 main chip)SpecificationsModel Name AXIUM</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7bf3cafa-daee-4c04-8219-3f9b5c0f44e5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cf02a49a-8969-4107-bab4-657fce0c8696/web/1_1724647959520.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>219 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082775663611</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4590481536</g:id>
      <g:title>IKEA LADDA Rechargeable Battery: HR03 AAA 1.2V, 750mAh pack of 4</g:title>
      <g:description>Title: IKEA LADDA Rechargeable Battery: HR03 AAA 1. 2V, 750mAhDescription:The IKEA LADDA Rechargeable Battery is an essential power solution for your everyday devices. With a capacity of 750mAh and a voltage of 1. 2V, this HR03 AAA battery is perfect for powering smaller electronics such as remote controls, cameras, and toys. Key Features:Compact Power: With a 750mAh capacity, these batteries provide reliable power for low to medium-drain devices, ensuring consistent performance. Rechargeable Convenience: Designed for multiple recharges, the LADDA battery helps reduce waste and is a cost-effective alternative to disposable batteries. Versatile Compatibility: Suitable for a wide variety of devices, making it a versatile choice for your household needs. Easy to Charge: Compatible with standard AAA battery chargers, allowing for quick and convenient recharging. Eco-Friendly Option: By choosing rechargeable batteries, you contribute to a more sustainable lifestyle, reducing environmental impact compared to single-use batteries. Opt for the IKEA LADDA Rechargeable Battery for a dependable and eco-conscious power source that keeps your devices running efficiently.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/572435c4-da1b-4e67-a377-bf9cca72ce9d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2650bf18-53d6-4f70-af2f-f2a10a3a32e6/web/1_1728379002797.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>21 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045904815367</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1283222458</g:id>
      <g:title>IKEA RABALDER Cable Tidy, White, 5 m </g:title>
      <g:description>The IKEA RABALDER Cable Tidy is a simple yet highly effective solution for organizing and managing your cables at home or in the office. This flexible cable tidy measures 5 meters in length and is designed to help you keep cords and wires neatly arranged, preventing tangling and clutter. It is especially useful for organizing cables behind desks, TV units, or workstations, providing a clean and tidy appearance. Made from durable, flexible plastic, the RABALDER can be easily cut to the desired length, allowing you to customize it to suit your specific cable management needs. The neutral white color blends seamlessly with most home and office decor, ensuring it stays discreet and unobtrusive. Key Features:5 Meter Length: Offers ample length to organize and manage multiple cables. Flexible Material: Made from durable plastic that can be easily adjusted or cut to fit your needs. Cable Protection: Prevents cords from tangling or getting damaged, prolonging their lifespan. Customizable: Can be cut to any desired length, making it versatile for various setups. Discreet Design: The white color blends with most interiors, keeping cable management unobtrusive. Easy to Install: Simple to wrap around cables, helping you declutter your workspace quickly. Lightweight and Durable: Designed for long-lasting use without adding bulk to your setup. Benefits:Clutter-Free Space: Helps keep cables neatly arranged, reducing clutter and improving organization. Custom Fit: Can be easily cut and adjusted to match your cable length and setup, offering flexibility. Extended Cable Life: Protects cables from wear and tear, reducing the risk of damage. Enhanced Safety: Reduces the risk of tripping over loose cables, making your space safer. Easy Maintenance: Keeps wires out of sight, making cleaning and maintenance around cables easier. Improved Aesthetics: Gives your home or office a cleaner, more organized look. Time-Saving: Makes it easier to identify and manage cables, saving time when making adjustments or changes.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9e8a70ae-297b-4777-b1ae-f4b8f3aad090</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cd1b24a5-c4d9-45c8-ad0b-26ab79492bff/web/1_1728379767780.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012832224585</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7724622408</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWL3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d061d717-5c79-4bc3-b886-ce79f62d51d6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/82cd081f-1a48-4c21-9e07-df33bc2c1dff/web/1_1728635592873.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077246224088</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8784905146</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ea2ccf61-abe8-4e55-a6ed-d5773472fcb8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/15d8c291-73e1-4983-b779-a165156df917/web/1_1728634708657.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087849051462</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3920937569</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Desert Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWN3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8fc687d6-aa57-48fe-9563-b769ec75d40f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/37fadd07-e9fe-4235-8911-62fd7f55ca1f/web/1_1728634401086.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6900 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039209375695</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2598489872</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - White Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN13</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e9192434-7e1b-4f2a-926b-fb99a3b8ce16</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0658d8e2-c444-493c-9ea1-970350337b17/web/1_1728635135179.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025984898726</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5588513831</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Natural Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN33</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/16ec2a38-147a-476c-87a0-83a7d82dab6d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/525f3ad0-0a16-4a62-a427-51d808cd7cbf/web/1_1728636370795.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055885138317</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7518342075</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro - 256 GB/Desert Titanium (Discounted)</g:title>
      <g:description>Description: • STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass• TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. • MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra-Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. • PRO VIDEO—Take your videos to a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. • PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. • THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. • A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. • CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. • VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4d85f19a-38e0-4215-97ac-66e9c7a85328</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3cb19aea-f5fc-455b-a394-d990f76cf54e/web/1_1728636554476.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075183420754</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2475860857</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6R3AH/A,MU793AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eac3f103-499e-40c4-8db5-941f50eb6ff5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f0b7a33a-e545-408c-8082-2716ee32483a/web/2_1728636162480.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024758608578</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9403015132</g:id>
      <g:title>IPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWJ3AE/A , MYWJ3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8d209fd4-5d9b-49cb-817c-b97db4225e79</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/53a60e40-186b-4429-8f6b-c5360273c536/web/1_1727437818532.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094030151320</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
