<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9194090757</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (256 GB) - White Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWH3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1730e5c9-fa86-42c4-a382-3b0b4d0ba1ae</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7410fc01-8fe9-4883-8f5a-0126f3cbe288/web/1_1731645944589.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091940907573</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3960748934</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Wave 200 True Wireless Earbuds Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMusic just sounds better with JBL And your day too Feel the sound with the deep bass powered by the 8mm drivers and add fun to your routineWith 5 hours in the earbuds and 15 hours in the case, the JBL Wave 200TWS don’t drop until you doNow you can take calls or listen to music with either bud (or both), with dual connect technology Choose which one to use and leave the other one in the case to save battery lifeJust a touch of the earbud is what you need to control calls, sound, your device’s voice assistant and stay in touch with your worldErgonomically shaped, the JBL Wave 200TWS fit gently and comfortably in your ears thanks to their in-ear stick form, for hours of listening pleasure They come with 3 sizes of ear tips to ensure a perfect seal for extra comfort and sound clarityOverviewAmp up your routine with the sound you love! Get powerful, JBL Deep Bass Sound and all the freedom of true wireless for up to 20 hours with the JBL Wave 200TWS. Take your world with you. Just a touch of the earbud manages your calls and music and puts you in touch with your voice assistant. And with dual connect you can use either earbud and save battery life. Ultra-light and comfortable, thanks to their ergonomic shape, the JBL Wave 200TWS are fun, ready-to-use. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number JBLW200TWSBLKModel Name JBLW200TWSBLK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/17ea4fd7-c6a1-444b-a6f7-6bc59f22ac95</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/543d1bfb-d49e-4325-baa6-8588c133b54f/web/1_1731590240346.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>162 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039607489345</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7070187331</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit Pop 3s Ultra-large 1.96" HD AMOLED Display,Fashionable Curved & Metallic Design With Bluetooth Phone Calls Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSensor :- Accelerometer sensor, Heart Rate sensor and 3-axis motion sensorNotification :- Calendar Reminder, Call Notification ,Sedentary reminders,Smartphone Apps Notifications etcWatch Functions :- Bluetooth Phone Call;Weather;Multiple Sports Modes;Sleep Monitor;Heart Rate Monitor; Mobile Phone Music Control; Mobile Phone Camera Control; Find My PhoneOverviewPop 3s Ultra-large 1. 96" (4. 9 Cm) HD AMOLED Display,Fashionable Curved &amp;amp; Metallic Design with bluetooth phone calls. Music Control, Camera Control, Find Phone, Breath Training, 12/24-hour, Stopwatch, Clock, Weather Forecast, Date Display, Dial, Cloud Multi-Dial, Custom Dial, OTA Upgrade, Multi-Language UI Interface, Multi-Language, Data Storage, All-Day Data, Call Notification, Message Reminder, Alarm Reminder, Step Goal Completion Reminder, Binding Confirmation Reminder, Low Battery Reminder, Brightness Adjustment, Vibration Adjustment, Wear Monitoring, Lift Wrist to Wake Screen, Power Saving Mode, Smart DND, Quick Settings, Female Cycle, Voice Assistant, Blood-oxygen Saturation Measurement,Monitoring of Heart Rate, Sleep and Sports DataSpecificationsMaterial SiliconeColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Smartwatch, Magnetic Charger, User ManualBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 96 inModel Number A2318Model Name A2318</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/90505906-def5-4e68-b402-82419814c8a7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/01a28b82-ad8b-466a-a1c6-3b1432b550aa/web/3_1731591402359.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>165 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070701873319</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1192673896</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit Pop 3R Smart Watch With 1.43" (3.6 Cm) HD AMOLED Display, BT Calling And AI Voice Assistance Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSensor :- Accelerometer sensor, Heart Rate sensor and 3-axis motion sensorNotification :- Calendar Reminder, Call Notification ,Sedentary reminders,Smartphone Apps Notifications etcWatch Functions :- Bluetooth Phone Call;Weather;Multiple Sports Modes;Sleep Monitor;Heart Rate Monitor; Mobile Phone Music Control; Mobile Phone Camera Control; Find My PhoneOverviewPOP 3R Smart Watch With 1. 43" (3. 6 Cm) AMOLED Display, BT Calling and AI Voice Assistance. Music Control, Camera Control, Find Phone, Breath Training, 12/24-hour, Stopwatch, Clock, Weather Forecast, Date Display, Dial, Cloud Multi-Dial, Custom Dial, OTA Upgrade, Multi-Language UI Interface, Multi-Language, Data Storage, All-Day Data, Call Notification, Message Reminder, Alarm Reminder, Step Goal Completion Reminder, Binding Confirmation Reminder, Low Battery Reminder, Brightness Adjustment, Vibration Adjustment, Wear Monitoring, Lift Wrist to Wake Screen, Power Saving Mode, Quick Settings, Female Cycle, Voice Assistant. SpecificationsMaterial SiliconeColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Smartwatch, Magnetic Charger, User ManualBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 43 inModel Number A2319Model Name A2319</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2be258af-37d7-44aa-9db6-2f766abe7955</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3c02a213-cc54-4347-8520-cc979b5fad32/web/6_1731591729596.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>165 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011926738960</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
