<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>1234714386</g:id>
      <g:title>BenQ Wireless Android-Based Smart Projector For Business EW800ST White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEW800ST can instantly turn any space into a video conferencing room without costing a fortuneGrants employees’ access to their personal cloud storage for meeting materials, enabling them to prepare for and hold meetings without laptopsExclusive driver-free wireless projection. And compatible with any device, allowing users connect and get started immediatelyEW800ST’s proprietary broadcasting system lets administrators send customized messages, such as a polite notification that meeting time is almost up, to facilitate smooth transitions between meetingsOverviewEW800ST Wireless Android-based Smart Projector for Business | 3300lm, WXGASee How Smart Projectors Benefit Your MeetingsBuilt-in video conferencing appSoftware / hardware integration for starting remote meetings immediatelyEW800ST comes embedded with TeamViewer Meeting video conferencing software that makes remote meetings straightforward and thrifty. As long as a camera is available, users can enjoy remote meetings on a large screen that makes it possible to see all participants and meeting materials clearly – an experience no other device can offer. Cloud service enables personal file access without a laptopAMS integrates most popular cloud services (Google Drive, OneDrive, and Dropbox) in one convenient interfaceAMS (Account Management Service) can sync with popular cloud storage services like Google Drive, OneDrive, and Dropbox. With just one AMS account, you can manage all your data and materials. AMS is embedded in EW800ST, offering direct access to the cloud without need for a laptop. Furthermore, EW800ST comes with WPS software that lets users open and edit Microsoft Office files. Intuitive driver-free wireless projectionJust connect and projectBenQ wireless projection offers a unique advantage over competitors, letting users mirror the screens of devices connected to the same network as the projector. This feature supports many OSes and device types. It is also compatible to connect the mobile devices which meet WPA2 standard, guaranteeing information security by safeguarding against data theft during data transmission. SpecificationsNumber of Charging Ports 2 PortTV HDMI Ports 1Product Weight 2. 6 KGDisplay Resolution 1280x800Colour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box Wireless Dongle: WDR02U Power Cord (by region) Remote Control w/ Battery (RCI023) VGA cableProjector Lamp Life 3000 to 5000 HoursIncludes Without ScreenLight Source LaserProduct Height 120 mmProduct Width/Depth 250 mmProjector Brightness 1000 lmModel Number EW800STModel Name EW800STNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/33f68799-14e7-45cd-a1f1-49364138a970</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7b218eb2-3567-4bfd-9fbc-89e39c74088d/web/1_1732020282380.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3250 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012347143869</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1868411311</g:id>
      <g:title>Canon EOS R7 (Body Only)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights32. 5MP APS-C CMOS Sensor and DIGIC X Processing Reliable and Intuitive Construction Flexible Connectivity Next-Generation Multi-Function Shoe RF-S 18-150mm f/3. 5-6. 3 IS STM LensDIGIC X Processor 2. 36m-Dot EVF and Vari-Angle Touchscreen LCDUHD 4K Video Recording Sensor-Shift Image StabilizerAutofocus and Image StabilizationAutofocus and Image Stabilization Dual Pixel CMOS AF IIOverviewCANON EOS R7 BODY The EOS R7 represents Canon's move into APS-C with the mirrorless R system. Featuring a 32. 5MP CMOS sensor and DIGIC X processing, this sleek powerhouse is capable of high-speed 30 fps shooting for sports and wildlife and features the renowned Dual Pixel CMOS AF II focusing system to keep up with and track fast-moving subjects. And, for the multimedia image-makers, 4K video is supported at up to 60p, or 30p when oversampled from a 7K area, as well as Full HD at up to 120 fps. Specifications-Colour Name Black-Camera Resolution 32. 5 MP-Model Number 5137C003AA-Model Name D. CAM EOS R7-Max Shutter Speed 30 ثانية</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c2f24b19-22a4-4022-98fc-3c085466494b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f3f797dd-3c5d-475b-9c09-474c8130f3d5/web/1_1732021748238.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Canon</g:brand>
      <g:price>4299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018684113114</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6424781003</g:id>
      <g:title>Canon EOS 90D DSLR Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsKeep up with the action، shooting at 10 fps with Intelligent Tracking and Recognition (iTR) autofocus when using the camera’s optical viewfinder. Bursts at up to 11 fps are possible in Live View mode. A 32. 5-megapixel sensor and DIGIC 8 processor work together to deliver amazing levels of detail، clarity and colour، even in low light thanks to a maximum ISO 25،600 sensitivity. An intelligent optical viewfinder gives a bright، real-time view of the world، with superimposed information that updates you on every aspect of the camera’s operation. A 220، 000-pixel RGB+IR metering sensor works with the camera’s iTR focusing system for superb subject tracking – following faces and other objects as they move around the frame. A 7. 7 cm (3. 0") Vari-Angle touchscreen makes it easier to shoot from creative angles when working in Live View mode. Just tap the screen to focus، track and shoot. Pair the camera with your smart device using Bluetooth for easy photo sharing، auto image transfer and remote camera control via Wi-Fi. OverviewFast. Versatile. Impressive. Whether capturing high-speed sporting events or simple، everyday moments، the EOS 90D camera is engineered to deliver impressive results. Equipped with an enhanced 32. 5 Megapixel CMOS (APS-C) sensor، powerful DIGIC 8 image processor and an ISO range of 100-25000 (expandable to 51200)، you'll achieve sharp، detailed images، even in low-light settings. As a DSLR the EOS 90D features a bright، clear optical viewfinder that shows the world as it really is، in real-time. Perfect for fast-moving subjects، the EOS 90D camera features a 45-point cross-type AF system and EOS iTR AF (face detection) - plus high-speed continuous shooting of up to 10 fps - raising the game for wildlife and motorsports photography enthusiasts. And with stunning uncropped 4K 30p video capability، the EOS 90D documents your travels، events and other milestones in full، wide-angle view. In this kit، the camera is paired with a very versatile EF-S 18-135mm f/3. 5-5. 6 IS USM lens، which is suitable for everything from landscapes to portraits and sport. This Intuitive DSLR is a result of a gradual evolution in design، and feels comfortable to use when shooting with large telephoto lenses and for long periods of time. Keep shooting for longer with a 1،300-shot battery life – great when you’re on location or away from home. Specifications-Product Weight 1. 96 g-Screen Size 3 in-Colour Name Black-What's In The Box DSLR-View Finder Type Combination-Sensor Type CMOS-Autofocus Yes-Product Length 28 cm-Product Height 16 cm-Product Width/Depth 22 cm-Camera Resolution 32. 5 MP-Features Wi-Fi enabled-Model Number 90D18135-Model Name 90D18135-Item Quantity 1-Inbuilt Flash Yes-Zoom Yes-Max Shutter Speed 30_1_8000_second</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/170d6335-3b6b-4777-a63e-f873fc89f7ca</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6a4202fb-8b9a-4c7f-a4bf-71328acbefd7/web/3_1732021512203.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Canon</g:brand>
      <g:price>4298 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064247810037</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2175070442</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRXQ3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU </g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRXQ3LL/A / MRXQ3ZP/A MRXQ3B/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b8031d32-d838-45fc-aa65-287d377675b2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/35a0e5c7-898a-41e7-b0a1-a5ff471c6260/web/1_1732029938700.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021750704420</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5653952008</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRXW3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name MidnightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRXW3JA/A MRXW3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/caa3c4bf-80ec-414e-ad1a-473f3e333747</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/95a5e39a-48ee-4aa7-bd2c-d2a78977d6c8/web/1_1732030228049.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056539520083</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3269570274</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXD23 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXD23LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/22e89b30-5d70-4cf5-a22a-99053128ffbc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7f754c85-84d2-475b-b953-adb1bd8b4875/web/1_1732031466728.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>6459 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032695702747</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8236619663</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWN3AE/A , MYWN3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6a28675e-f77d-4620-aa05-c38e2149767b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4e06b29f-f299-4ddf-9733-3efedcc81c44/web/1_1732031700459.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6949 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082366196634</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8104808003</g:id>
      <g:title>Canon EOS R6 Mark II Mirrorless Camera Body, Black (Upgraded EOS R6 Model)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFull-frame mirrorless camera that lets hybrid shooters master their craft40 fps, Dual pixel cmos af ii, 24. 2 megapixel, 8-stop in-body image stabilizer¹4k 60p Video, bluetooth &amp;amp; wi-fi connectivity, max iso 102,400SpecificationsColour Name BlackCamera Resolution 24. 2 MPModel Number 5666C004</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ff777181-8f6e-4178-bc62-ebae8b91de22</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6e8da593-4b10-49fc-9fff-3381b0a2d7bb/web/1_1732023585670.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Canon</g:brand>
      <g:price>7298 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081048080032</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4554496807</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWJ3AE/A , MYWJ3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2c67d794-fe6e-4913-9ddb-def94fdcb815</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/39db6e90-42e0-4ecc-a7f4-205f4318823c/web/1_1732031233236.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5540 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045544968072</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2937617344</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXCV3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name MidnightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXCV3JA/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/761444ea-25c1-4792-b316-f503c97d1064</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d564ccc9-cee4-4b91-b35b-4c8ffb86362e/web/1_1732031576389.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>6899 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029376173446</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4872057527</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MRX33 Laptop M3 Pro chip with 11‑core CPU</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 18 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRX33ZS/A / MRX33LL/A / MRX33X/A / MRX33HN/A / MRX33B/A/MRX33HN/A / MRX63B/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Pro chip with 11‑core CPU, 14‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4bfcf11e-022a-41cc-ba73-4f771c0ceff3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/db53d793-4d43-4adf-9ba4-2767f2761bc4/web/1_1732031962580.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>6999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048720575279</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8817743286</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRXU3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU Processor</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name StarlightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRXU3JA/A / MRXU3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c839f71c-1b47-42eb-8b7c-7036caee4b1b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a2abc21b-5615-444b-92b1-2bf3ac47463b/web/1_1732030467604.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088177432862</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8187956668</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 SLIM Disc + G-STORY 14" Inch</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and Portable for PS514 inch 4K(3860x2160) displayDesigned for FPS/FTS games, it could help you perform better in any gaming mode. FTG mode: Supports ultra-fast response speed. FPS mode: With Assisted aiming Cross Shapeeamlessly matching PS5's shape and aesthetic, could be closed like a laptop when not in use. Dual HDMI ports, dual 3. 5mm audio jacks. Dual built-in multimedia stereo speakers. Eye-Care technology with flicker-free backlighting and blue light filter minimizes eye fatigue. OverviewLevel up your gaming setup with the unbeatable bundle of the PS5 Slim Disc Edition and G-Story 14-Inch Monitor. This combination offers everything you need for an immersive gaming experience, whether at home or on the go. Why Choose This Bundle? This PS5 Slim Disc and G-Story Monitor bundle is the ideal solution for gamers who demand quality and portability. Whether you're gaming at home or taking your skills on the road, this combination ensures you have everything you need to play your favourite titles in stunning clarity and performance. SpecificationsProduct Weight 6. 5 KGVersion International VersionColour Name WhiteType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Language EnglishModel Number TRZ-PS5 SLIM DISC+G STORY 14INCHModel Name TRZ-PS5 SLIM DISC+G STORY 14INCH</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/53d33c6b-7d67-4686-99ba-07b2f78c9162</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3f8ac178-8be2-473b-ba2b-476f20e650fb/web/2_1732019519352.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081879566682</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5459963717</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXD43 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name MidnightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXD43LL/A MXD43X/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3dd63d39-31d4-4df8-8c91-d887c0dc37c5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1aea08aa-66bc-4e66-aea8-65fcdb2e2588/web/1_1732031863442.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>6999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054599637178</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8926070240</g:id>
      <g:title>dji Mini 3 PRO With RC(GL)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCare-free Creation - Weighing less than 249 g, Mini 3 Pro doesn't require registration in most countries and regions. The foldable and compact design also makes it easy to carry on any adventureSeriously Pro Shots - Capture your world in remarkable detail with 4K/60fps video and 48MP photos. The advanced camera system supports dual native ISO and f/1. 7 aperture for high-quality imagery, night and dayPerfect Portraits in a Tap - The redesigned DJI Mini 3 Pro offers True Vertical Shooting for portrait shots, ideal for social media. The gimbal rotates 90, so you don't have to compromise image qualitySweet Air Time - Enjoy an extended flight time of up to 34 minutes and capture and explore more of your surroundingsFly with Confidence - DJI Mini 3 Pro features tri-directional obstacle sensing and APAS 4. 0, bringing unrivaled safety to the Mini seriesCreate and Share On the Go - DJI Mini 3 Pro offers an extensive range of intelligent features including FocusTrack, True Vertical Shooting, MasterShots, Timelapse, QuickTransfer, and moreOne of the biggest improvements over the Mini 2 is the inclusion of a tri-directional obstacle avoidance system, which can avoid accidents by automatically detecting and avoiding obstacles in its flight pathAdd in a foldable design and a host of tracking and imaging modes, and you have a drone that travels easily and can accommodate both impromptu personal or professional aerial imagingOverviewCreativity is at the heart of every dream. Every idea, every groundbreaking leap that changes our world starts with the vision of talented creators. At DJI, we give these creators the tools they need to bring their ideas to life. Our platforms empower them to capture images that were once out of reach. Our flying and camera stabilization systems redefine camera placement and motion. Amazing photos and video, treasured personal memories, and high-end professional imagery are captured every day, in every corner of the world using DJI products. We do this through an unparalleled commitment to R&amp;amp;D, a culture of constant innovation and curiosity, and a focus on transforming complex technology into easy-to-use devices. Building on the ethos of “form follows function,” our products combine advanced technology with dynamic designs. Specifications-Expandable Memory Type Combination-Battery Size 3850 mAh-Product Weight 80. 5 g-Screen Size 5. 5 in-Display Resolution 3840x2160-Colour Name Grey-What's In The Box Mini 3 Pro with RC(GL)-Video Recording Resolution Type 4K-Battery Type Li-ion Polymer-Water/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust Resistant-Optical Zoom Optical Zoom-Sensor Type CMOS-Autofocus Yes-Night Vision Lens Yes-Aspect Ratio 4:3-Product Length 145 in-Product Height 62 in-Product Width/Depth 90 in-Camera Resolution 48 MP-Model Number (DJI RC)(GL)-Model Name (DJI RC)(GL)-Item Quantity 1-Inbuilt Flash no-Zoom Yes-Interchangeable Lens no-Image Stabilization Yes-Max Shutter Speed 2_to_1_8000_second-Aperture f_1_7</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8f38b6e9-e872-43c6-b7c8-86118ce7420c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/be2592c6-9625-4b4c-8720-71cf3a0ff926/web/1_1732020530116.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>DJI</g:brand>
      <g:price>3798 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089260702404</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3105576303</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iMac M3 Chip With 8 Core CPU 8 Core GPU 8GB 256GB SSD, 24-Inch 4.5K Retina Display, MQRD3 </g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewApple M3 chip with 8‑core CPU with 4 performance cores and 4 efficiency cores, 8‑core GPU, and 16‑core Neural EngineSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBScreen Size 24 inDisplay Resolution 4480x2520Colour Name PinkKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple iMacProcessor Version Number/Generation m3Number of Cores 8-CoreRAM Type DDR5Model Number MQRD3Model Name MQRD3HDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/94d55120-151a-4ca0-b673-c68ebf46ee36</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c4f97956-8294-4c0e-b757-d43414f7f8cd/web/1_1732032043458.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>7999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031055763039</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2365827142</g:id>
      <g:title>Next Level Racing NLR-S034 Go Kart Plus Simulator Cockpit</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDesigned for Go Kart style racing and general racing gamesesigned for both children and adults ranging from 3'7" – 6'7"Custom-designed Go Kart style seat with included premium fabric cover; Adjustable Seat, wheel, and pedal position to suit a wide range of usersCompatible with a wide range of entry-level to direct drive wheelsIncluded Go Kart Bumper Kit with Sticker Pack for personalization of numbers and names; Included Next Level Racing Lockable Castor Wheels for mobilityOverviewIntroducing the Next Level Racing Go Kart Plus cockpit, designed for the whole family to enjoy hours of racing fun. Whether you’re training for competitive go-karting events or creating exciting family race days, this cockpit is built to accommodate it all. This versatile cockpit is perfect for children and adults alike, offering a thrilling racing experience for all ages. With adjustable seat angle, seat distance slider, and pedal distance slider, effortlessly transition from Go Kart positioning to GT-style racing in minutes. Its compact footprint and versatile design make it perfect for family bonding and competitive training. Get ready to experience the joy of racing together with the Next Level Racing Go Kart Plus cockpit. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number 9359668000510Model Name 67050</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8a048a9b-a3b3-4ff6-8590-63e9051dae13</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bca32889-ff38-48a9-be3d-c134d5a92c28/web/1_1732021655245.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2543 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023658271424</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3670277001</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 Slim Disc Console with Extra Blue Controller and Call of Duty: Modern Warfare III Bundle</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPS5 and 2 controllers will expand your gaming experience. This is a great value set that includes a controller that comes with a PS5 unit as well as an additional blue controller and Call of Duty: Modern Warfare IIIThe included PlayStation 5 is a new PS5 model group - slim, which is designed to be a smaller model with technologies and functions that provide a gaming experienceThe Ultra HD Blu-ray disc drive is detachable and the internal SSD storage in the unit becomes 1TBPlayStation 5 Description: Play Has No Limits for new game possibilities with unleash PS5 that exceeds the limits of playSuper fast SSD dramatically improves read speed Haptic technology, adaptive trigger, and 3D audio technology deliver a dense immersive feel. And experience the new generation of amazing PlayStation titlesThe new PS5 has been reduced in volume by more than 30%, and weight by 18% and 24% compared to the previous models. There are four separate cover panels, with the top portion in a glossy look, while the bottom remains matteHarness the power of a custom CPU, GPU, and SSD with Integrated I/O that rewrite the rules of what a PlayStation console can doSpecificationsColour Name White-Blue (MW III)Connection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Language EnglishModel Number RZ384174714CModel Name RZ384174714C</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/33f3dcb1-8512-4e43-ad4e-ee74d40e02a6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d1ff7f2d-6d75-49a0-901d-511143c3a508/web/1_1732021466735.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2509 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036702770019</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5687775198</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Smart TV, Crystal UHD, 75 Inch TV Backlight T2 Lighting, With Dual Cameras, 75-85 inch</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDynamic Crystal Color4K UpscalingAirSlimOverviewSamsung 75" Crystal UHD DU8000 4K Tizen OS Smart TV (2024) 1. Dynamic Crystal Color 2. 4K Upscaling 3. Samsung Tizen OS Govee Envisual Technology: Zone-division capture scheme provides real-time color matching to enhance your visual experience Innovative Dual Camera Design: Upgraded dual camera design captures content 40% more accurately. Enhanced RGBIC Lighting: Double the light beads for more vivid and natural lighting Enhanced Music Mode: Choose between 4 modes (Energetic, Rhythm, Spectrum, Rolling) and energize your parties Unlock Home Theater Magic: Control your T2 TV Backlight using Alexa and Google AssistantSpecifications-TV HDMI Ports 2-Video Format 4K-Product Weight 20 KG-Screen Size 75 in-Refresh Rates 50 Hz-Colour Name Black-Display Type LED-Operating System Tizen-What's In The Box TV, User Manual, Power Cable, Remote Control-Viewing Distance 4. 1 m-Model Year 2024-Streaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple -Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO Max-Product Length 1676 mm-Product Height 960. 3 mm-Product Width/Depth 26. 6 mm-Model Number 75DU8000+6974316993087-Number of USB Ports 2-Number of HDMI Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/89cde606-4abe-40bb-82fd-c27991bc2025</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/94e6efa1-ee19-499f-8cec-948633be1fe7/web/1_1732021037391.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4025 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056877751989</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5308305185</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 Disc Console With Extra Red Controller And FC 24</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSony PlayStation 5 Standard Edition Disc Console with FC 24 Standard PS5 EditionThe DualSense wireless controller also includes a built-in microphone and create button, all integrated into an iconic, comfortable designEA SPORTS FC 24 is a new era for The World’s Game: 19,000+ fully licensed players, 700+ teams, and 30+ leagues playing together in the most authentic football experience ever createdEA SPORTS FC 24 is the next chapter in a more innovative future of footballSpecificationsColour Name Red / WhiteConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Language EnglishModel Number fifa24ps5disc/CFI-1218A 01/CFI-1200A 01Model Name PSKU_16482_05233012006061002384_X</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fd497273-f3e1-4f9b-9e6a-f44626a8b660</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fea96f9e-0ef6-4cb8-9b2b-833dce8a0283/web/1_1732021775698.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2575 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053083051858</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7623646438</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A06 Dual SIM Gold 4GB RAM 64GBB - Mildde East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy-A06 Dual SIM Gold 4GB RAM 64GB - Middle East VersionSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1560Colour Name GoldDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A065FZDDMEAModel Name SM-A065FZDDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/301381e9-5154-4a11-9850-b039b2ff0b4a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3381f3d9-ec37-4faf-8abb-8810fdf9b2fc/web/1_1732097460797.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>345 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0076236464381</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2501695647</g:id>
      <g:title>dji Mini 4 Pro Fly More Combo Plus (RC 2)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and Portable Lightweight, portable, and palm-sized when folded, weighing less than half a bottle of waterRegulation-Friendly For aircraft under 250 g, registration or certification is not required in most countries and regionsWide Detection Range Real-time obstacle detection effectively reduces collision risksMore Stable Hovering A pair of downward vision sensors and a more precise 3D ToF sensor facilitate more stable hoveringPost sale Warranty Support provided directly by DJI UAE Support centerSpecifications-Colour Name Grey-Style Fly More Combo Plus (DJI RC 2)-Camera Resolution 4 MP-Model Number DJI-MVM400P-C3-Model Name DJI-MVM400P-C3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/267996f6-f891-405f-8ed1-da7726c7e1c4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1375cfee-fbea-4f2c-ba21-3ab638459255/web/1_1732020735481.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>DJI</g:brand>
      <g:price>3946 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025016956479</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3917819931</g:id>
      <g:title>cmf by NOTHING Watch Pro Smartwatch With Bluetooth Calling, AMOLED Display, IP68 Water Resistant Dark Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGet reminder to drink water at set time intervalsGet reminder to stand and stretch after sitting for a certain period of timeGuidance to inhale and exhale to relax and relieve stressTrack and record sleep time and wake-uptime; monitor sleep stages awake, light sleep, deep sleep, REM and durationsTrack and record the daily average,maximum, and minimumstresslevels, and the ratio of relaxed, normal, medium, and high stresslevelsOverviewFrom running to high-intensity interval training, covering most of the daily sports. Track exercise duration (hours, minutes, seconds), calories, real-time heart rate, pace,steps, distance and more. Stay motivated by setting your exercise goals and achieve it. Resistant to water splash and sweatSpecificationsMaterial MetalBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 31. 1 gColour Name Dark GreyDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSFace/Dial Shape SquareBand Size LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 10 mmModel Number D395Model Name D395</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7670f0f8-25a8-4dd7-926e-20dee52efa98</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/91f56a16-e87b-4b7c-ba91-a9c74cb0589e/web/1_1732022714994.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>229 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039178199315</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8714613583</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2021 (9th Generation) 10.2-Inch, 64GB, WiFi, Space Gray With Facetime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe A13 Bionic chip makes everything more responsive, from messaging to web browsing to using multiple apps at onceUp to 20% faster GPU gives you the graphics performance you need. Perfect for playing immersive games and moreA more powerful Neural Engine drives machine learning–based features like Live Text in iPadOS 15The A13 Bionic chip effortlessly powers advanced apps like Adobe Fresco and ProcreateWith all-day battery life, iPad is ready to work or play for as long as you need itOverviewApple is a premium brand masquerading as a luxury one, It is one of the best- regarded brands globally, Apple's brand is valued at over $200 billion, in part because of the iPhone. But there's one thing it does that makes it more valuable than the rest, and it's something you can do too. It's almost hard to get a sense of the scale of a company like Apple From latest features to packaging the products, Apple does everything in a way that exhibits the company's uniqueness. Versatility and planning sets the company apart from the rest, making its products loved and coveted by the majority of people. Almost all the characteristics determining apple quality can be measured or classiﬁed. Consumers assess apples by its appearance (colour, size, shape, absence of defects) and then by its eating quality, although the latter may determine the willingness to buy the product again. Get the most out of the devices you love with high‑quality content and services. Award‑winning series and films, amazing music in spatial audio, world-class workouts and meditations, trusted news publications, superfun games even the ways you pay for things and they’re only on Apple. Since Apple has a large market share and is known for its versatile and fast operating system, developers prefer to launch their apps and high-end games first on iOS and then on Android. Further, iOS runs on consistent hardware, while Android comes in different iterations and versions depending on the phone. Apple is a fashion company, and in fashion companies, the role of design is style definition. When they released iOS7 in 2013, Apple signaled a major change in how UI and digital experience played into their company strategy. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPProcessor Speed 2. 65 GHzRAM Size 3 GBBattery Size 8557 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBProduct Weight 487 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 2 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name Space GrayCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2021Voice Calling Capability noOperating System Number iOS15Processor Number A13 Bionic chipFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box iPad 2021 (9th Generation)Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantFinish MetalMaximum Expandable Memory 2 TBSensor Barometer, Three‑axis Gyro, Ambient Light SensorModel Number Apple iPad 9th genModel Name iPad 2021 (9th Generation)Primary Camera (MP) 8MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/787eebb8-79b0-44f1-b326-004f6e09dded</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/030ae6ec-a048-4dd7-bc53-9aa49232ea8e/web/1_1732023281742.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087146135834</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2578347554</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Original JBL GO3 wireless Bluetooth Speaker Subwoofer Outdoor Speaker Waterproof Bass Sound Mini Speaker multiple colour</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewJBL Introducing the JBL GO 3 Bluetooth Speaker: portable, ultra-compact, with bold style and JBL Sound Pro. It combines with your style and accompanies you on the go Stream your music from your phone or tablet and enjoy up to 5 hours of music in a single charge with this Bluetooth speaker: wireless and hassle-free At the beach, pool, or even in the rain, the party never stops: the GO 3 features an IP67 certified waterproof and dustproof design Express your style: The GO 3 impresses with its modern design and expressive details. It is also available in a wide variety of colours inspired by the most current fashion Box contents: 1 x JBL GO 3 portable Bluetooth speaker, dimensions: 87. 5 x 75 x 41. 3 mm, 1 x quick start guide, 1 x safety plug, 1 x USB type C cable, blue/pinkSpecificationsColour Name BLUEProduct Length 8 cmProduct Height 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 3 cm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/906e33f9-c905-4ab5-a313-8a403e9ac5b9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/098249da-eddc-4386-a98c-89201af08600/web/1_1732022604305.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025783475548</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7013403257</g:id>
      <g:title>Canon EOS R8 Mirrorless Camera (Body Only)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA lightweight, travel-friendly, full-frame camera body, the Canon EOS R8 Mirrorless Camera offers powerful photoPairing a powerful full-frame 24. 2MP CMOS sensor and DIGIC X image processorThe R8 offers 4:2:2 10-bit shooting and up to 2-hours of video recording is now available at 29. 97 fpsFeaturing 1053 automatic AF points that cover the entire sensor areaThis phase-detection focusing system offers enhanced subject detection and trackingSpecificationsColour Name BlackVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pSensor Type CMOSCamera Resolution 24. 2 MPModel Number EOS R8Model Name Mirrorless Camera</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cae90765-a1e9-4489-b8f1-f8f25d0016be</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/47b7324e-1f36-413b-916a-ea5bc917cd51/web/1_1732022519742.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Canon</g:brand>
      <g:price>4864 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070134032574</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3140635642</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 46mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Black Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSeries 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 46 mmModel Number MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/A, MWWQ3ZP/A, MWWQ3LW/A, MWWP3ZP/AModel Name MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/A, MWWP3LW/A, MWWQ3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8fbfe226-6651-4736-8a53-a975d08a658f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eee1146a-7ab4-4053-80bb-6723ad9a33b8/web/1_1732023972032.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2100 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031406356422</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9390050945</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 46mm Rose Gold Aluminium Case With Light Blush Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSeries 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Light Blush Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 46 mmModel Number MWWT3QA/A, MWWU3QA/A, MWWT3ZP/A, MWWT3LW/A, MWWU3ZP/A, MWWU3LW/AModel Name MWWT3QA/A, MWWU3QA/A, MWWU3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fb927dbb-1e71-48ea-b715-f67f77368ce8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bf091531-adf5-4e04-b005-022852578ac4/web/1_1732023815856.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1680 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093900509452</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5609823034</g:id>
      <g:title>BenQ 4K HDR Gaming Projector TK700STi White And Brown</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights4K hdr high resolution: 3000 ANSI lumen brightness; 4K HDR-enabled; 100-inch images from 6. 5 feet (2m) away; stunning color 96% Rec. 7094K low latency: Low latency 16ms@4K/60Hz low input lag, Game Mode/Game Sound Mode to fine-tune audio and imagesPro performance: Compatible with major consoles (Sony PS4, PS5, Nintendo Switch, and Xbox Series X, Google stadia) huge, bright, sharp images and equalized audioEasy set-up: 1. 2x zoom flexible throw distances, 2D Auto vertical keystone, Picture rotation adjustment for squared imagesEndless entertainment: Google-certified android TV and google play store, with 5,000+ of the latest android apps, movies, shows, live sports, games, music, and moreOverviewBenq Tk700Sti 4K Hdr Gaming Projector | Ps5/Xbox Series X Compatible | 240Hz &amp;amp; 4Ms @ 1080P | 60Hz &amp;amp; 16Ms @ 4K | 3000 Lumens | Short Throw | 3D | Android Tv | Hdmix2 | Dlp | 5W Speaker | 2D KeystoneSpecifications-Product Weight 3. 1 KG-Screen Size 120 in-Display Resolution 3840x2160-Colour Name White And Brown-Display Type LED-Display Resolution Type UHD-What's In The Box Projector-Aspect Ratio 16:9-Projector Lamp Life 5000 Hours &amp;amp; Above-Includes Without Screen-Light Source LED-Product Length 23. 6 cm-Product Height 31. 2 cm-Product Width/Depth 11 cm-Projector Brightness 3000 lm-Model Number TK700STi-Model Name TK700STi</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/38f7ae9e-b1c8-4b24-b4cc-54575262ae22</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1d6dd5b2-3c84-4604-929c-c9497aacfc46/web/1_1732022973879.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>6347 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056098230348</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8505110942</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Blue - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Blue 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7ee2041e-4d6b-46f2-89b7-3ed92addd4e0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a7f08e64-e3ca-49db-89be-0ba3ed527246/web/1_1732023709827.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085051109421</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2702343976</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRXV3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name MidnightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRXV3JA/A /MRXV3LL/A / MRXV3X/A MRXV3ZP/A MRXV3ZS/A MRXV3B/A MRXV3HN/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1314418d-c8c1-49d2-a9e1-14f8a46cfd9c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/368e7eab-8609-4f75-b059-267320f94cc7/web/1_1732028759390.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027023439761</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2664379769</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Silver - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Silver 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/024a5688-59e1-4bfb-aab0-3f9984acfe38</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c5acbe95-5abc-47cc-a1e9-a394ce3fe499/web/1_1732023592795.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026643797695</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8366482161</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 42mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Black Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSeries 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWWE3QA/A, MWWF3QA/A,MWWF3ZP/A, MWWE3ZP/A, MWWE3LW/AModel Name MWWE3QA/A, MWWF3QA/A, MWWE3LW/A, MWWF3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5658949c-929a-4aa0-8479-1e8d9d1410c6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0099e808-9ee4-4181-9ddc-ad97dcd722f7/web/1_1732023395507.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1462 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083664821617</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6111975096</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony FX30 Digital Cinema Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights26. 1MP APS-C BSI CMOS sensorUHD 4K up to 120pCompact form designed for cage-free use10-Bit 4:2:2 XAVC S-I,16-Bit Raw OutputS-Cinetone/S-Log3/HLG, 14+ Stops DRPhase detection AF/face tracking/eye AFStandard ISO 100-32000 | Dual base ISODual CFexpress type A/SDXC card slotsUser luts and timecode sync supportOverviewThe Sony FX30 is a versatile APS-C cinema camera designed for content creators at all skill levels, offering cinematic quality and intuitive features. Its 26MP APS-C Exmor R CMOS sensor and BIONZ XR processor deliver 14+ stops of dynamic range and excellent low-light performance with Dual Base ISO (800/2500). The camera records UHD 4K at up to 60 fps with full pixel readout and can shoot 4K at 120 fps with a 1. 6x crop, plus Full HD at 240 fps for smooth slow motion. For color flexibility, the FX30 offers S-Cinetone for natural skin tones, S-Log3, and other picture profiles for enhanced dynamic range and color grading. It also supports Creative Looks and custom LUTs for monitoring and output. The camera’s Fast Hybrid AF system with 495 points provides precise focusing, including Real-Time Eye AF and Real-Time Tracking. The 5-axis in-body stabilization ensures smooth handheld shots, while Active Mode and gyro data recording help stabilize footage in post. The FX30 offers three log shooting modes—Flexible ISO, Cine EI, and Cine EI Quick—to suit various production needs. With its combination of professional features and ease of use, the FX30 is ideal for filmmakers looking to create high-quality, cinematic content. Specifications-Colour Name Black/Grey-Camera Resolution 26. 1 MP-Model Number ILME-FX30B-Model Name Sony-Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a3aff4cb-e55e-4ae0-82f1-7ac61674fb62</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1f39cdc0-9842-4f76-ba90-4c6fa5278380/web/1_1732023384119.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Sony</g:brand>
      <g:price>7285 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061119750965</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3360212115</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLY13 13.6-Inch Display: Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 8GB RAM/256GB/ English Keyboard(International version) Starlight</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies and music with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youComfortable and quiet, Magic Keyboard now has a full-height function key row for quick access to favourite controls and shortcuts. Touch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsOverviewSTRIKINGLY THIN DESIGN — The redesigned MacBook Air is more portable than ever and weighs just 2. 7 pounds. It’s the incredibly capable laptop that lets you work, play or create just about anything. Use the Apple MacBook Pro 2022 has set standards in computing thanks to its Apple M2 chip Processor. M2 is the next generation of Apple silicon. Its 8-core CPU lets you zip through everyday tasks like creating documents and presentations, or take on more intensive workflows like developing in Xcode or mixing tracks in Logic Pro. M2 features up to a 10-core GPU, resulting in a big boost in graphics performance. And its media engine lets you play and edit up to 11 streams of 4K and up to 2 streams of 8K ProRes video. Considering the amazing specifications, the Apple MacBook Pro 2022’s price is quite fair. The more unified memory (RAM) you choose, the more apps you can run simultaneously with a higher rate of performance. The 13-inch MacBook Pro can be configured with up to 24GB for more fluid multitasking and easy handling of large files. Solid-state drive (SSD) storage is the amount of space your MacBook Pro has for your documents, photos, music, videos, and other files. It delivers significant performance and speed that you’ll notice when you start up your Mac. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 5 GHzRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 1. 38 KGVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inSIM Type SIM (Standard)Display Resolution 1920x1080Screen Features Eco-FriendlyRefresh Rates 60HzMonitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name StarlightLaptop Weight 1 - 1. 4 KgDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDConnection Type USBAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableWhat's In The Box Laptop,Adapter,User ManualNumber of Cores 16-CoreWireless WirelessRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProduct Length 35 cmProduct Height 7. 35 cmProduct Width/Depth 34 cmGraphic Memory 0 GBHDD Rotation 5400 rpmFeatures Bluetooth, Business, Ergonomic, High Refresh Rate Display, PersonalModel Number MLY13, MLY13LL/A/MLY13HN/A / MLY13X/A / MLY13J/A MLY13ZP/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2Pixels Per Inch 1080x1920 pixelsHDMI Output noAdobe Flash Compatible YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fe852d8c-da2e-4af8-93fe-9c58379a163b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9c30424f-c7ca-4b2e-a30d-100d880740d9/web/1_1732024459032.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033602121156</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8980541150</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRXT3 13-inch Display</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name StarlightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRXT3LL/A / MRXT3ZP/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dbbcb76b-1b45-4c91-94b7-99525df00897</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a1f9cf7a-07fa-4bbf-ad21-301e9f8b5213/web/1_1732028624125.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3530 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089805411501</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8431350778</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Macbook Air MGN63 13" Display, Apple M1 Chip With 8-Core Processor and 7-Core Graphics</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe Apple M1 chip gives the 13. 3‑inch MacBook Air speed and power beyond beliefThe M1 chip has an 8-Core CPU with up to 2. 8x faster processing performance than the previous generationThe 8-Core GPU in the M1 delivers the most advanced integrated graphics in a personal computerWith the brilliant retina display, images take on an incredible level of detail and realismUp to 20 Hours of battery life thanks to the energy efficient new Apple M1 chipOverviewApple is a premium brand masquerading as a luxury one, It is one of the best- regarded brands globally, Apple's brand is valued at over $200 billion, in part because of the iPhone. But there's one thing it does that makes it more valuable than the rest, and it's something you can do too. It's almost hard to get a sense of the scale of a company like Apple From latest features to packaging the products, Apple does everything in a way that exhibits the company's uniqueness. Versatility and planning sets the company apart from the rest, making its products loved and coveted by the majority of people. Almost all the characteristics determining apple quality can be measured or classiﬁed. Consumers assess apples by its appearance (colour, size, shape, absence of defects) and then by its eating quality, although the latter may determine the willingness to buy the product again. Get the most out of the devices you love with high‑quality content and services. Award‑winning series and films, amazing music in spatial audio, world-class workouts and meditations, trusted news publications, superfun games even the ways you pay for things and they’re only on Apple. Since Apple has a large market share and is known for its versatile and fast operating system, developers prefer to launch their apps and high-end games first on iOS and then on Android. Further, iOS runs on consistent hardware, while Android comes in different iterations and versions depending on the phone. Apple is a fashion company, and in fashion companies, the role of design is style definition. When they released iOS7 in 2013, Apple signaled a major change in how UI and digital experience played into their company strategy. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 3. 2 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Screen Features Flat ScreenRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Space GreyDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDConnection Type HDMIAverage Battery Life 14 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirOperating System Number OS XProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableWhat's In The Box Macbook Air MGN63 13" DisplayNumber of Cores Octa CoreWireless WirelessRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 0 GBFeatures Business, Ergonomic, High Refresh Rate Display, Built In Speaker, USBModel Number MGN63,MGN63SA/A, MGN63ID/A,MGN63B/A, MGN63HN/A, Z1240009P, MGN63LL/A, MGN63ZP/A, MGN63ZS/A, MGN63ZA/A, MGN63X/A, MGN63PA/A, MGN63AB/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M1HDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot YesNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version Apple M1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/202cd038-e624-4ee5-93ef-9163a5cb7bdd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e1cf7285-a593-4392-89fe-2f4cbc25e47d/web/1_1732024165606.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2479 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084313507784</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8663153436</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLXW3 13.6-Inch Display : Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies and music with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youComfortable and quiet, Magic Keyboard now has a full-height function key row for quick access to favourite controls and shortcuts. Touch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsOverviewEnjoy super-fast speed as soon as you buy Apple MacBook Air . The responsible and durable MacBook Air's compact body is made of 100% recycled aluminum. Apple Silicon and macOS provide a high degree of built-in security to protect against malware and viruses. Macs are also designed to give you the freedom to choose what to share and how to share it. The stunning 13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display is the largest and brightest MacBook Air ever, supporting 1 billion colors. The text is crisp, and the photos and movies are brighter and more vibrant, with rich contrast and sharp details. The stunning 13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display is the largest and brightest MacBook Air ever, supporting 1 billion colors. The text is crisp, and the photos and movies are brighter and more vibrant, with rich contrast and sharp details. Stay in sync with the advanced technology by bringing home the Apple MacBook Air online. Mac is the perfect companion for other Apple devices. Read the message on your Apple Watch and reply from your Mac. Start your presentation on your Mac and rehearse on your iPhone while you're on the go. Unlock your Mac on your Apple Watch. Alternatively, you can share your entire photo album with friends across the room. So, go ahead and order the Apple MacBookSpecificationsProcessor Speed 3. 2 GHzRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 1. 24 KGVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Screen Features Eco-FriendlyRefresh Rates 60HzMonitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name Space GreyLaptop Weight 1 - 1. 4 KgDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDConnection Type USBAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableWhat's In The Box MacBook,user manualNumber of Cores 16-CoreWireless WirelessRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProduct Length 30 cmProduct Height 1. 12 cmProduct Width/Depth 21 cmGraphic Memory 0 GBFeatures Bluetooth, Compact Size, Personal, Multi-TouchModel Number MLXW3 , MLXW3ZP/A , MLXW3LL/A , MLY33LL/A . MLXW3HN/A , MLXW3X/A , MLXW3J/A , MLXW3AB/A, MLXW3PA/A / MLXW3ZA/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2Pixels Per Inch 1080x1920 pixelsHDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d770334d-60cc-4608-b9a6-e15188c6f7b1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c05b92cd-e310-475b-a139-3a9bb14f4ffb/web/1_1732028909582.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3859 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086631534367</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8120059796</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRXN3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core GPU Processor</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRXN3JA/A MRXN3LL/A MRXN3X/A / MRXN3ZP/A MRXN3ZS/A MRXN3HN/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 8-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5fe60c68-5e4e-40fc-a0a2-c75ddc121559</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fed1f3f9-bcdf-4190-9d61-30af58bbace4/web/1_1732029168029.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4200 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081200597965</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2215838150</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLXY3 13-Inch Display : Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 256GB</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies and music with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youComfortable and quiet, Magic Keyboard now has a full-height function key row for quick access to favourite controls and shortcuts. Touch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 0 GBModel Number MLXY3/MLXY3B/A/MLXY3LL/A / MLXY3X/A / MLXY3HN/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2HDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noProcessor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/303173c4-4315-42c4-8583-9ede732d0314</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d19abe92-e245-4d76-9eed-636391b31393/web/1_1732029307547.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4249 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022158381503</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3397710321</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MR7J3 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU: 14.2-inch</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MR7J3ZS/A / MR7J3X/A / MR7J3LL/A/MR7J3HN/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c2f85cf5-a4f4-41f7-bed4-61b59e962fad</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a8c53b11-d586-45ba-8061-3498d403ced9/web/1_1732030341752.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033977103214</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5250542258</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 24-inch iMac with Retina 4.5K display: Apple M3 chip with 8‑core CPU and 8‑core GPU</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsiMac now features Wi-Fi 6E, which delivers download speeds that are up to twice as fast as the previous generation, and Bluetooth 5. 3, which allows users to connect to the latest Bluetooth accessoriesWith a 1080p FaceTime camera and studio-quality mics, iMac delivers an unmatched video conferencing experience, so users can look and sound their best while taking calls from home or the officeiMac features a colour-matched keyboard, mouse, and trackpad. With the option to choose a Magic Keyboard with Touch ID,4 users can easily and securely unlock their computer, use Apple Pay, and download appsiMac features a 24-inch, 4. 5K Retina display with 11. 3 million pixels, a P3 wide colour gamut, over a billion colours, and 500 nits of brightnessSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBScreen Size 24 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name GreenKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple iMacProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 MBModel Number MQRA3ZS/A , MQRA3X/AModel Name 24-inch iMacHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot no</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e1645379-bc43-4d61-9684-7604cac24a2a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4a14ff80-f5d4-4b05-9dc1-416699448827/web/1_1732030789804.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>5290 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052505422580</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7815510182</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 24-inch iMac with Retina 4.5K display: Apple M3 chip with 8‑core CPU and 8‑core GPU</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsiMac now features Wi-Fi 6E, which delivers download speeds that are up to twice as fast as the previous generation, and Bluetooth 5. 3, which allows users to connect to the latest Bluetooth accessoriesWith a 1080p FaceTime camera and studio-quality mics, iMac delivers an unmatched video conferencing experience, so users can look and sound their best while taking calls from home or the officeiMac features a colour-matched keyboard, mouse, and trackpad. With the option to choose a Magic Keyboard with Touch ID,4 users can easily and securely unlock their computer, use Apple Pay, and download appsiMac features a 24-inch, 4. 5K Retina display with 11. 3 million pixels, a P3 wide colour gamut, over a billion colours, and 500 nits of brightnessSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBScreen Size 24 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name BlueKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple iMacProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 MBModel Number MQRC3ZS/AModel Name 24-inch iMacHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot no</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c68643c9-1f22-420a-9c65-23f597f54b5c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2acb4b2a-56df-4e59-a7f1-3168cd3fd4b3/web/1_1732031308333.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>5999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078155101828</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5672392294</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRYU3 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name MidnightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRYU3JA/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ad7169d4-1531-4992-b8b0-10562dbe22c7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6d31f7bb-deeb-47fb-be36-2245c9529d17/web/1_1732031084171.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056723922945</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7489833936</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MTL73 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. OverviewThe Apple MacBook Pro is a high-performance laptop designed for professionals and power users. With its sleek and durable aluminum build, it exudes elegance and durability. The MacBook Pro boasts a stunning Retina display with vibrant colors and sharp details, making it ideal for creative work and multimedia consumption. Powered by Apple's powerful M-series chips, the MacBook Pro delivers exceptional performance for demanding tasks, from video editing and photo manipulation to software development. The efficient architecture of these chips ensures long battery life, allowing you to work or play for extended periods without needing to recharge. The MacBook Pro is equipped with a comfortable keyboard and spacious trackpad for precise navigation. It also features a wide range of ports, including Thunderbolt 4 for fast data transfer and connection to external displays. With its combination of power, portability, and premium features, the MacBook Pro is a top choice for those seeking a high-performance laptop. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MTL73LL/A / MTL73ZS/A/MTL73X/A / MTL73ZP/A/MTL73HN/A MTL73B/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/913426bb-2a9e-4a32-add7-ada3dbd7a6f4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/75da7689-7dfe-4a0c-b55e-89df5f4336e4/web/1_1732030980203.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074898339368</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1636972015</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 ( 5th Generation) M4 11-Inch, 256GB, WiFi, Space Black With Standard Glass </g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/419b1b7f-f149-4b60-8a97-111723699c68</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/86b6830d-a2a3-4915-964c-7eb4a4d1b119/web/1_1732029043835.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016369720152</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1987615794</g:id>
      <g:title>Canon PowerShot G7 X Mark III Compact Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPortable camera for vloggers20. 1 MP, 1. 0”-type sensor, 30 fps4. 2x optical zoom, tilting LCD screen, 4K videoDIGIC 8 Image Processor &amp;amp; 2. 54cm Stacked CMOS Sensor30fps (Raw Burst Mode - One Shot AF)4K Video Recording (without crop)OverviewSuccessor to the popular PowerShot G7 X Mark II, this camera is the perfect level-up for those who wants more than just snap shots. DIGIC 8 and the 2. 54 cm Stacked CMOS Sensor provides exceptional image quality. Coupled with the f/1. 8-2. 8 lens, PowerShot G7 X Mark III performs exceptionally well in low-light conditions. PowerShot G7 X Mark III is capable of shooting 4K video recording without crop, allowing more creative approach. Stream videos shot instantaneous to YouTube through Live Streaming function. SpecificationsColour Name SilverCamera Resolution 20. 1 MPModel Number 3638C002Model Name Canon PowerShot G7 X Mark III Compact Camera, Silver</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cf8d952a-20e1-4957-bccd-e380a6b1136e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a4f42b44-e2cd-4818-98db-f96aa8a13b55/web/1_1732022712552.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Canon</g:brand>
      <g:price>5998 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019876157947</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9946843554</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWG3AE/A , MYWG3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/744cfffe-7ed2-4b7d-9f6e-e6aaaf5b099d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/348ea92a-bb0b-4aad-88b8-919c7a42b044/web/1_1732030702505.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5270 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099468435547</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5481029323</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 16 Pro 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN23AE/A , MYN23AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/90a0dc94-c9f4-4044-a243-870049ad3374</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e51f1fd1-00cc-4dff-8f3a-29bf4077d879/web/1_1732030072875.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4649 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054810293237</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5507629884</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6R3AH/A,MU793AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ad41d2ac-dd44-42c0-b6dc-a1123c9c6007</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/11b574d6-364c-41a1-a5d8-798cc5c51dcd/web/1_1732029757624.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055076298844</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8014955423</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 16 Pro 128GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYMX3AE/A , MYMX3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/57c4135b-82de-4490-b74c-b46daaae64e4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/016807e6-3f05-475b-930f-031773e6ad16/web/1_1732029498723.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4359 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080149554237</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3399761920</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy M14 4G (Sapphire Blue,4Gb,64Gb) | 50MP Triple Cam | 5000mAh Battery | Snapdragon 680 Processor | 2 Gen OS Upgrade And 4 Year Security Update | 8Gb Ram With RAM Plus</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsInterface &amp;amp; processor- Android 13 operating system having One UI 5. 1 platform with Qualcomm snapdragon 680 processor | 2. 4GHz, 1. 9GHz octa-core processorCamera - 50 mp (F1. 8) main wide angle + 2 MP (F2. 4) Macro + 2 MP (F2. 4) depth | 13MP (F2. 0) front camera | Video maximum resolution of full hd (1920 x 1080) @60fpsBattery - Get a massive 5000mAh Lithium-ion Battery (Non-removable) with C-Type fast charging (25W charging support)Display - 17. 08 centimeters (6. 7"Inch) PLS LCD display, FHD+ Resolution with 1080 x 2400 pixels , 391 PPI with 16M colors and 90Hz refresh rateOS updates &amp;amp; security- Get upto 2 generations of AndroidOS upgrades &amp;amp; 4 years of security updates with Samsung galaxy M14 4G. Includes 1 year manufacturer warranty for device and 6 months for in-box accessoriesSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 17 cmSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name blueDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Smartphone Data Cable (Type C-to-C) SIM Ejector Pin User ManualProcessor Name Qualcomm Snapdragon 660Glass Technology Gorilla GlassFlash LEDWireless 4G/3G/Wireless/BluetoothModel Year 2024Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number Samsung Galaxy M14Model Name M14 4GPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP Triple Cam</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/98efc28e-7d29-4ef1-8d6f-840a3c11eaf7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b4818894-ab52-4090-b96d-1365fdd221d8/web/1_1732097995162.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>360 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033997619207</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8732824058</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy M14 4G (Arctic Blue,4Gb,64Gb) | 50MP Triple Cam | 5000mAh Battery2 Gen. OS Upgrade And 4 Year Security Update | 8Gb Ram With Ram Plus | Snapdragon 680 Processor</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsInterface &amp;amp; processor - Android 13 operating system having one UI 5. 1 platform with Qualcomm snapdragon 680 processor | 2. 4GHz, 1. 9GHz octa-core processorCamera - 50 mp (F1. 8) main wide angle + 2 MP (F2. 4) Macro + 2 MP (F2. 4) depth | 13MP (F2. 0) front camera | Video maximum resolution of full hd (1920 x 1080) @60fpsBattery - Get a massive 5000mAh Lithium-ion Battery (Non-removable) with C-Type fast charging (25W charging support)Display - 17. 08 centimeters (6. 7"Inch) PLS LCD display, FHD+ Resolution with 1080 x 2400 pixels , 391 PPI with 16M colors and 90Hz refresh rateOS updates &amp;amp; security - Get upto 2 generations of AndroidOS Upgrades &amp;amp; 4 Years of Security Updates with Samsung Galaxy M14 4G. includes 1 year manufacturer warranty for device and 6 months for in-box accessoriesSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 17 cmSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name blueDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Smartphone Data Cable (Type C-to-C) SIM Ejector Pin User ManualProcessor Name Qualcomm Snapdragon 660Glass Technology Gorilla GlassFlash LEDWireless 4G/3G/Wireless/BluetoothModel Year 2024Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number Samsung Galaxy M14Model Name M14 4GPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP Triple Cam</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9f649ce6-1879-4d90-b549-428587b48fa1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6b20b61f-83b1-413b-a394-b0ef25dd4579/web/1_1732098509160.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>360 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087328240585</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5238454352</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A06 Dual SIM Light Blue 4G RAM 64GB - Mildde East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy-A06 Dual SIM Light Blue 4GB RAM 64GB - Middle East VersionSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1560Colour Name Light BlueDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A065FLBDMEAModel Name SM-A065FLBDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e4ef0b3a-d2f3-460b-bfbd-26a131104a21</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d9d9a3a3-3d8d-4ac1-82bb-5adfc4e6b810/web/1_1732097801782.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>348 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052384543529</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5956819206</g:id>
      <g:title>NOKIA 110 Dual SIM Midnight Blue 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewLoaded with latest featureSpecificationsCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 1 GBBattery Size 1450 mAhInternal Memory 1 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 1. 8 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 60HzColour Name Midnight BlueCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraBattery Type Lithium IonModel Year 2023Network Type 4GModel Number 110. 0Model Name 110. 0</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/990fa81b-a234-40d4-8202-42b79555548a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/693aec3d-40b7-46f3-b46d-a0ee9f617f09/web/1_1732098699172.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Nokia</g:brand>
      <g:price>100 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059568192061</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2492589912</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 4 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZKGMEA / SM-A057FZKDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/84fc0ea1-9cad-4686-b02e-802eca88ac5b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4e7f9c44-14b4-4f46-82f6-412a3c306459/web/1_1732098738289.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>360 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024925899129</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7161196687</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A06 Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 64GBB - Mildde East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy-A06 Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 64GB - Middle East VersionSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1560Colour Name BlackDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A065FZKDMEAModel Name SM-A065FZKDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f57dde05-91b0-42d1-90a5-2d55d40918da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a064e132-1357-46ff-8811-5dc4cdccd9db/web/1_1732097223811.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>345 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071611966870</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9469899442</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVGMEA / SM-A057FLVDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e6ea8aad-a73d-45ff-82c0-f7491d712e3b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/66ee9dae-abdb-408a-982d-45ff307213be/web/1_1732099980181.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>405 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094698994420</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3519006224</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi A3 Dual SIM Forest Green 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRefined and Stylish DesignSmooth 6. 71'' 90Hz Dot Drop displayMassive 5000mAh (typ) battery, and provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W chargingSecure fingerprint and AI face unlockSupports up to 1TB expandable storageOverviewThe ultra-thin design, paired with the clean flat frame, appears exquisite and stylish. Hold the phone with one hand to embrace trends and lightness. Provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W charging*. 5000mAh ultra-large battery, reducing battery life anxiety and ensuring full-day range. Powerful octa-core processor with a maximum CPU frequency of 2. 2GHz, more balanced performance, reduced lags, and more fun to enjoy. You can choose the side fingerprint or AI face to easily unlock your phone. Suitable for more unlocking scenarios, safer and more convenient. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 193 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 71 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Forest GreenDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 14Processor Number G36What's In The Box Mobile Phone | Adapter | USB Type-C Cable | SIM Eject Tool | Quick Start Guide | Safety InformationNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pNetwork Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 168 mmProduct Height 8. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 3 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number 23129RN51XModel Name Redmi A3 (4+128)Primary Camera (MP) 8+0. 08 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4bec81ee-1c59-45db-bfdc-2012848e9d3e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8cb0c7bc-e702-4b98-86dd-19c19349e0b8/web/4_1732097030749.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>299.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035190062248</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5387324289</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Silver 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name SilverOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZSGMEA / SM-A057FZSDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/802f3d80-4fb3-443e-9fdb-93e0c286fe30</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/67f45f42-66ca-460a-a63c-4202cd028800/web/1_1732098942405.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>365 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053873242893</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5995614977</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 7-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in Black, Silver and Light Green, Galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the Galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front Camera, the 2MP Depth Camera and the 50MP Wide-angle CameraEquipped with a powerful octa-core, 4/6GB of memory and 64/128GB internal storage, Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handThe 5,000mAh (typical)** battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of Super Fast Charging, Galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVDMEAModel Name SM-A057FLVDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ed88153b-508a-4b79-a75b-73e0414ff02a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/60726140-448d-46db-b0e0-5e88bc71d270/web/1_1732099815906.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>379.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059956149776</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2316687205</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FZKGMEA, SM-A055FZKDMEA, SM-A055F/DSModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4260a646-f654-4f33-87b6-60b0f43e32b1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/34a1dac3-48ac-4db5-ba86-7c4d88356e04/web/1_1732099613036.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>375 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023166872052</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4899253035</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Blue/Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZKGMEA, SM-A155F/DSNModel Name Galaxy A15Primary Camera (MP) 50+5+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3f8991b6-6219-4709-820a-8dda1fb8fc51</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/27bd7a27-96f8-4970-92f6-16f84d5d96cb/web/1_1732103960801.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>530 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048992530358</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1605764625</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor X9b Dual SIM 5G Sunrise Orange 12GB RAM 256GB - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 1. 5K Retinal Resolution / SGS 5-star Whole-device Drop Resistance Certification / 5-fold Eye Protection[12GB RAM + 25G GB Memory] Enjoy great performance &amp;amp; plenty of room for photos, movies, songs, and apps—and 20GB Super large memory(RAM Turbo)108MP Lossless Capture Camera, 108MP main Camera/ Motion Capture/ 3X lossless Zoom[Superfast 5G performance] Unleash entertainment at 5G speed with the Qualcom Snapdragon, a powerful octa-core processor with frequencies up to 2. 1GHz[Massive battery and speedy charging] Work and play nonstop with a long-lasting 5800mAh battery, then recharge quicklyOverviewA luxury look and Xtra power, Honor X9b 5G is designed to stand out with HONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 360° Anti-Drop Protection, 6. 78" Amoled+ 120Hz display. Capture incredibly clear photos and smoother videos with a 108MP+5MP+2MP camera system featuring motion capture &amp;amp; 3X lossless zoom. Honor X9b 5G is a device you will fall in love with at first touchSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5800 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 185 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 78 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Sunrise OrangeDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number Qualcomm snapdragon SM6450Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Charger, USB Type-C cable, guides, SIM toolNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 163. 6 mmProduct Height 75. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Accelerometer, Proximity SensorsModel Number ALI-NX1Model Name X9bPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bd47695b-d8f6-4f87-88cd-37f70ece09dd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4d6ed8ac-9135-4f26-a24d-fdcb1ff61530/web/1_1732103896695.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>940 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016057646252</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2748828430</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A55 Dual SIM Awesome Navy 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A55 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 32MP front camera, the 12MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 32 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 32 MP &amp;amp; AboveRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome NavyOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A556EZKVMEAModel Name SM-A556EZKVMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+12+5 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/054d670b-85ca-453e-afdb-abaaaa17127f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/81457ea8-9432-4a82-bc3a-2e7132d10819/web/1_1732104901025.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1150 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027488284302</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7830759413</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 20W USB-C 3-Pin Power Adapter White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsOffers fast and efficient charging at home, in the office or on the goYou can also pair it with iPhone 8 or later to take advantage of the fast-charging featurePower adapter is compatible with any USB‑c-enabled deviceCan be paired with the ipad pro and ipad air for optimal charging performanceThe Apple 20W USB‑C Power Adapter offers fast, efficient charging at home, in the office, or on the go. While the power adapter is compatible with any USB‑C-enabled device, Apple recommends pairing it with the iPad Pro and iPad Air for optimal charging performance. You can also pair it with iPhone 8 or later to take advantage of the fast-charging featureCharging cable sold separately. Compatibility with iPhone Models: iPhone 15 Pro iPhone 15 Pro Max iPhone 15 iPhone 15 Plus iPhone 14 Pro iPhone 14 Pro Max iPhone 14 iPhone 14 Plus iPhone 13 Pro iPhone 13 Pro Max iPhone 13 mini iPhone 13 iPhone SE (3rd generation) iPhone 12 Pro iPhone 12 Pro Max iPhone 12 mini iPhone 12 iPhone 11 Pro iPhone 11 Pro Max iPhone 11 iPhone SE (2nd generation) iPhone XS iPhone XS Max iPhone XR iPhone X iPhone 8 iPhone 8 Plus, iPad Models: iPad Pro 12. 9-inch (6th generation) iPad Pro 12. 9-inch (5th generation) iPad Pro 12. 9-inch (4th generation) iPad Pro 12. 9-inch (3rd generation) iPad Pro 12. 9-inch (2nd generation) iPad Pro 12. 9-inch (1st generation) iPad Pro 11-inch (4th generation) iPad Pro 11-inch (3rd generation) iPad Pro 11-inch (2nd generation) iPad Pro 11-inch (1st generation) iPad Pro 10. 5-inch iPad Air (5th generation) iPad Air (4th generation) iPad Air (3rd generation) iPad (10th generation) iPad (9th generation) iPad (8th generation) iPad (7th generation) iPad mini (6th generation) iPad mini (5th generation), Apple Watch Models: Apple Watch Ultra 2 Apple Watch Series 9 Apple Watch SE Apple Watch Ultra Apple Watch Series 8 Apple Watch Series 7 Apple Watch Series 6 Apple Watch Series 5 Apple Watch Series 4 Apple Watch Series 3 Apple Watch Series 2 Apple Watch Series 1 Apple Watch 1st generation. OverviewApple is a premium brand that positions itself as a luxury one. Valued over $200 billion, much of its worth comes from the iPhone. Its success lies in its attention to detail, from product design to packaging, creating a unique experience. Apple's versatility and strategic planning make its products highly desirable. Consumers assess Apple by appearance and quality, often returning for future purchases. With exclusive content, services, and a seamless ecosystem, Apple dominates the market. Developers prioritize iOS for apps and games due to its consistent hardware. Apple also sets trends in design, as seen in the significant UI shift with iOS 7 in 2013. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type WiredBrand Compatibility AppleWhat's In The Box AdapterPhone Case Material CombinationProduct Length 6. 7 cmProduct Height 8. 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 3. 5 cmWattage 20 WFeatures Plug and Play, Personal, ErgonomicModel Number MHJF3ZE/A, MHJF3B/A, MUVT3ZE/A, MUVT3ZP/A, MHJE3ZE/A, MUVT3B/A, MU7W2ZP/AItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0bd53cb2-f512-4a54-a0de-8e1a5f517c3f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/efed06ff-9768-412a-993c-cfe22866f30f/web/1_1732096823914.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078307594133</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4405707980</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 90 Dual Sim Emerald Green 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHonor 90 adopts snapdragon 7 gen 1 enhanced edition which has a maximum cpu frequency of 2. 5GhzThe honor 90 has a resolution of 2664 1200 and a ppi of 435 the actual screen has slightly less effective pixels because the referenced resolution corresponds to a standard rectangleSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 50 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 32 MP &amp;amp; AboveRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Emerald GreenDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13Processor Number Snapdragon 7 Gen 1 Accelerated EditionFast Charging YesProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number REA-NX9Model Name honor 90Primary Camera (MP) 200+12+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c66f5f9-8d17-4cea-970e-62b1760f7132</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e4e22ad1-f581-47db-a0ac-15c5ed7a93e3/web/1_1732105031628.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>1150 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044057079800</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9796165297</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Blue Black 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Blue/BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZKDMEA / SM-A156E/DSModel Name BSM-A155F/1D4NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/46ab6076-8bcb-4631-91d7-6f3d4459c920</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6316d999-c012-4b77-a7f9-85a10b016035/web/1_1732103692407.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>505 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097961652973</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9648245912</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Light Blue 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FLBDMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/1D4NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5ac4c7e7-6115-430d-b23f-d39918b83044</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d696ee8f-1552-441f-a8bb-1388bbe1082a/web/1_1732103833012.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>505 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096482459122</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5269116860</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Silver 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPremium and stylish designHigh quality cameraSmooth and fast performanceLong-lasting batteryOverviewDive into immersiveness Enjoy it all in stellar clarity. With the 6. 7-inch FHD+ display, your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless, vivid picture quality. Embracing the essentials A refined build and finish. Available in Light Green and Black Galaxy A05s brings the style in form factor. Your moments to savor and share It’s all there. Revisit your landscapes captured with the 50MP Main camera, detailed shots with the 2MP Macro camera, portraits with the 2MP Depth camera for more dimensions, and your favorite selfies with the 13MP Front camera. Equipped for superior performance Carry on doing what you love. With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor**, 4/6GB of memory and 128GB internal storage*, Galaxy A05s is equipped with the performance capacity for seamless gaming, viewing, and sharing on social media. Extend your memory with RAM Plus Galaxy A05s intelligently reads your phone usage pattern to provide extra virtual RAM* up to 6GB, allowing you to run apps smoothly and enjoy multitasking Power that keeps you going The 5,000mAh (typical)* battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W** of Super Fast Charging, Galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quickly. Go beyond the ordinary listening experience with Dolby Atmos Simply plug in your headphones and you’ll be transported to the middle of your music and movies. With Dolby Atmos, you’ll hear sound that’s full, loud and seems to surround you in the scene. Awesome experience with One UI Core Own something truly yours. Customize your Galaxy with One UI and give your phone an edgy look to match your vibes. Create a bespoke tool that assists your tasks seamlessly and makes your favorite features readily accessible. Keep your device in tip-top condition with us Enjoy peace of mind when you choose to buy a Samsung Galaxy smartphone The interactive diagnostics and optimization on the Samsung Members app makes it easy to tune up the performance of your devices, while our helpline helps you troubleshoot problems when you need the extra support. SpecificationsSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion UAE VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Micro SIMColour Name SilverCondition NewModel Number SG-SM-A057FZSHMEAModel Name Samsung Galaxy A05s</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/747c3a5d-9a41-4d4e-a58d-53019c49ed16</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/902d7a80-0aa8-45a0-ae61-6adb21d5b75d/web/1_1732103547067.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>460 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052691168606</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9822946570</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 6 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVHMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cb294923-c457-43ab-9b24-a7b3aaea794c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f21e30b2-81bf-4ae1-9429-e82eda063168/web/1_1732103367789.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098229465700</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3708479184</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 90 Dual Sim Midnight Black 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHonor 90 adopts snapdragon 7 gen 1 enhanced edition which has a maximum cpu frequency of 2. 5GhzThe honor 90 has a resolution of 2664 1200 and a ppi of 435 the actual screen has slightly less effective pixels because the referenced resolution corresponds to a standard rectangleSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 50 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 32 MP &amp;amp; AboveRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Midnight BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13Processor Number Snapdragon 7 Gen 1 Accelerated EditionFast Charging YesProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number REA-NX9Model Name honor 90Primary Camera (MP) 200+12+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/462dcc15-c90a-4370-a0cd-3ec03105113b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b5e889a4-fff0-4459-8a2a-eeda48dd11e9/web/1_1732104780874.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>1090 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037084791845</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2620169714</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Silver 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 6. 7-inch HD+ displayDesign available in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name SilverCondition NewModel Number SM-A055FD / SM-A055F / SM-A055FG / SM-A055FZSHMEAModel Name Galaxy A05</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9ec683ee-44ff-4b62-97cc-9c1924510d57</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a2423d7d-809f-4d4c-a192-97a9f3f3f011/web/1_1732102853763.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>419.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026201697146</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9303419048</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d8664959-cb13-4d6d-a1b9-b691d20619f3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4d88ae0c-95af-45b5-9ea3-92a4db3df95d/web/2_1732102578048.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>405 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093034190489</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9277948219</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Silver 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name SilverOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZSGMEA / SM-A057FZSDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fd4d0f55-3b4b-46eb-ad5b-532444751163</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9fd6c5d5-5962-42b6-8451-de69caa1808d/web/1_1732102692867.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>405 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092779482194</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9480400606</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy M15 5G (Stone Grey, 128 GB) (6 GB RAM)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights6 GB RAM | 128 GB ROM16. 51 cm (6. 5 inch) Display50MP Rear Camera6000 mAh Batteryproximity sensor ProcessorOverview16. 39 Centimeters (6. 5"Inch) Super AMOLED Display with 19. 5:9 Aspect Ratio, FHD+ Resolution with 1080 x 2340 Pixels , 399 PPI with 16M Colors and 90Hz Refresh Rate 50MP (F1. 8) Main Wide Angle Camera + 5MP (F2. 2) Ultra Wide Angle Camera + 2MP (F2. 4) Macro Angle Camera | 13MP (F2. 0) Front Camera | Video Maximum Resolution of Full HD (1920 x 1080) @30fps Latest Android 14 Operating System having One UI 6. 1 platform with MediaTek Dimensity 6100+ Processor | 2. 2GHz, 2GHz Clock Speed with Octa-Core Processor Get a massive 6000mAh Lithium-ion Battery (Non-Removable) with C-Type Super Fast Charging (25W Charging Support) Get upto 4 Generations of AndroidOS Upgrades &amp;amp; 5 Years of Security Updates with Samsung Galaxy M15. Includes 1 Year Manufacturer Warranty for Device and 6 Months for In-Box Accessories. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 212 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name GaryDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesWhat's In The Box mobile, User Manual, SIM Ejector Pin, Smartphone, Data Cable (Type C-to-C)Processor Name Octa-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080p (100fps), 1080p(30fps), 1080p(60fps), 1440P (30fps), 1440P (60fps), 4K (30fps), 720P(200fps)Wireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Sensor, Gyro Sensor, Geomagnetic Sensor, Light Sensor, Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-M156BModel Name SAMSUNG Galaxy M15 5GPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a5bf156c-16a4-4d21-a396-f45a7e99cb61</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0fadf999-de5a-4369-923a-c5a12e7a0099/web/1_1732105847805.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>549.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094804006061</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9745385672</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy M55 5G (Black, 256 GB) (8 GB RAM)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights8 GB RAM | 256 GB ROM17. 02 cm (6. 7 inch) Display50MP Rear Camera5000 mAh BatteryOverview16. 95 Centimeters (6. 7"Inch) Super AMOLED Plus Display with 19. 5:9 Aspect Ratio, FHD+ Resolution with 1080 x 2400 Pixels , 394 PPI with 16M Colors and 120Hz Refresh Rate 50MP (F1. 8) Main Wide Angle Camera + 8MP (F2. 2) Ultra Wide Angle Camera + 2MP (F2. 4) Macro Angle Camera | 50MP (F2. 4) Front Camera | Video Maximum Resolution of UltraHD 4k (3840 x 2160) @30fps Latest Android 14 Operating System having One UI 6. 1 platform with Snapdragon 7 Gen 1 Processor | 2. 4GHz, 2. 36GHz, 1. 8GHz Clock Speed with Octa-Core Processor Get a massive 5000mAh Lithium-ion Battery (Non-Removable) with C-Type Super Fast Charging (45W Charging Support) Get upto 4 Generations of AndroidOS Upgrades &amp;amp; 5 Years of Security Updates with Samsung Galaxy M55. Includes 1 Year Manufacturer Warranty for Device and 6 Months for In-Box Accessories. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 180 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Mobile, User Manual, SIM Ejector Pin, Smartphone, Data Cable (Type C-to-C)Processor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080p (100fps), 1080p(30fps), 1080p(60fps), 1440P (30fps), 1440P (60fps), 4K (30fps), 720P(200fps)Wireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Sensor, Gyro Sensor, Geomagnetic Sensor, Light Sensor, Proximity SensorModel Number SM-M556BModel Name Galaxy M55 5GPrimary Camera (MP) 50. 0 MP + 8. 0 MP + 2. 0 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b00eec29-926d-4f21-96ef-b0ea0efb5044</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/40467df2-954a-40e6-a4ad-cf95c2c99b83/web/1_1732104600385.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>980 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097453856728</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3452640591</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy F15 5G (Ash Black, 128 Gb) (6 Gb Ram)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights6 gb ram | 128 gb rom | Expandable upto 1 tb16. 51 cm (6. 5 inch) full hd+ display50MP + 5MP | 13MP front camera6000 mAh lithium ion batteryMediaTek dimensity 6100+ processorOverviewThe Samsung Galaxy F15 is a pinnacle of mobile brilliance, featuring a vibrant sAMOLED display for an immersive visual journey. Experience unmatched battery endurance, lasting up to two days, and revel in four years of hassle-free performance with a powerful MediaTek Dimensity 6100+ and up to 12 GB of RAM. Silence background sounds with noise cancellation, seamlessly share across devices, and enjoy superfast 5G speeds. Capture every detail with the 50 MP triple camera setup and have fun with the front-facing camera's creative features. Fortify your security with the Samsung Knox Vault Chipset and personalise your experience with Smart UI features. The Galaxy F15 redefines smartphone excellence in a compact and versatile package, catering to every aspect of a modern, connected lifestyle. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 217 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Ash BlackDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesWhat's In The Box Handset, Data Cable (USB Type C-to-C), Ejection Pin, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name MediaTekNumber of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassWireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 9. 3 mmProduct Height 160 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 8 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer,Fingerprint Sensor,Gyro Sensor,Geomagnetic Sensor,Light Sensor,Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-E156BLVGINS, SM-E156B/DSModel Name Samsung F15 5GPixels Per Inch 2340 x 1080 PixelPrimary Camera (MP) 50 + 5 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b0eb3046-e0bd-4ac3-847b-045f56e1d3f9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0e155ac2-3a1a-4e7b-bc94-d8b13621a38c/web/2_1732106922083.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>580 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034526405919</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2456225817</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Dual SIM Titanium Yellow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe Samsung Galaxy S24 is universally use the new Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 across the world. The Galaxy S24 have AI-optimized main camera photos. Night mode is also better. Nightography Zoom will bring brighter nighttime photos with the zoom camerasThe Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra comes with emergency texting via satellite support over the 3GPP standard. OverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 8 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Titanium YellowOperating System AndroidNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number S24 Ultra Titanium Yellow 12/512 International VersionModel Name S24 Ultra Titanium Yellow 12/512 International VersionPrimary Camera (MP) 200+10+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ddad3097-7d0e-4c1d-8482-edf13a661947</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1c0ac7bf-5172-4090-ba0b-ef5a9c7af3d9/web/1_1732105875393.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3650 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024562258174</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1034503083</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5 Single Sim + eSim Phantom Black 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung Pay may not workOverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMColour Name BlackDisplay Type Foldable Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number SM8550-AC Snapdragon 8 Gen 2Fast Charging YesProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Z Fold 5Model Name Z Fold 5Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dcb21555-466d-4ad5-87ee-a6971b15bf3c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c339e456-39aa-4abe-b085-3e3c7b1cfa28/web/1_1732105439755.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3400 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010345030839</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9508984962</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Blue/Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE -International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Blue/BlackOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 4GCondition NewModel Number Galaxy A15Model Name Galaxy A15</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7227d82e-87ed-455b-bc90-fe523c152e5b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ff1342a8-8fc7-4cad-b3d3-dba78dd25539/web/1_1732105980236.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>550 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095089849626</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8994424190</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5 Dual SIM Cream 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung Pay may not workOverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4235 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 3 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name CreamDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System AndroidFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 4K Ultra HDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Digital Compass, gyroscopeModel Number BSM-F946BE/2D/SM-F946B/DS/ SM-F946NZEAKOOModel Name SM-F946BZEDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0a25a50a-3d45-49c5-af26-d30127a3955d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0dc7ab76-e7c5-4ad4-a0bc-48f096ff1738/web/1_1732105579189.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3400 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089944241908</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8728885137</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Dual SIM Titanium Black 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe Samsung Galaxy S24 is universally use the new Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 across the world. The Galaxy S24 have AI-optimized main camera photos. Night mode is also better. Nightography Zoom will bring brighter nighttime photos with the zoom camerasThe Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra comes with emergency texting via satellite support over the 3GPP standard. OverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 8 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Titanium BlackOperating System AndroidNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number S24 Ultra Titanium Black 12/512 International VersionModel Name S24 Ultra Titanium Black 12/512 International VersionPrimary Camera (MP) 200+10+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e1c09fde-0d40-4d40-8ff5-fe1137f73fdf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6f21315a-25a7-4697-a496-505620d98051/web/1_1732105722224.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3649 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087288851371</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4088929878</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Dual SIM Pink 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b9dde0ee-1edc-4ad0-98e4-d6e0c0d5e715</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7c0d8431-701d-4239-aaf4-6f35ec1774c2/web/1_1732107171339.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040889298785</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6528965487</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Light Blue 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FLBGMEAModel Name Galaxy A15Primary Camera (MP) 50+5+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a5d35f33-5f5d-4e18-841b-f746c9dfb90a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7326d5cf-8ac0-4d38-b0c0-f92ca8d936eb/web/1_1732104137569.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>530 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065289654870</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4511676965</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Dual SIM Black 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldables. Design: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screen. Durability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative FlexHinge. Gaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specs. Battery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient display. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/74d4ccd9-23e9-4e80-b0b7-731c11171a83</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f3280e82-855e-4bcd-85eb-d4d9c599990d/web/1_1732106997464.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4350 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045116769656</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2646707410</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5 Dual SIM Icy Blue 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung Pay may not workOverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4235 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 3 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Icy BlueDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System AndroidFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 4K Ultra HDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Digital Compass, gyroscopeModel Number BSM-F946BE/2D / SM-F946B/DS/ SM-F946NLBAKOOModel Name SM-F946BLBDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ab6df135-a54c-410f-93b7-3cb128440fd3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/52cf1b23-eaf9-442d-a914-eb6a9cc3743e/web/1_1732105205376.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3399.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026467074101</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9509058513</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Dual SIM Silver shadow 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c38d73ab-0314-457c-81b3-94c1e8f6420f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/df270314-5892-4899-8acb-f7a3f16ab8c8/web/1_1732106926206.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4350 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095090585131</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5882908324</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy M15 Dual Sim Blue/ Celestial Blue 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights6 GB RAM | 128 GB ROM16. 51 cm (6. 5 inch) Display50MP Rear Camera6000 mAh Batteryproximity sensor ProcessorOverview16. 39 Centimeters (6. 5"Inch) Super AMOLED Display with 19. 5:9 Aspect Ratio, FHD+ Resolution with 1080 x 2340 Pixels , 399 PPI with 16M Colors and 90Hz Refresh Rate 50MP (F1. 8) Main Wide Angle Camera + 5MP (F2. 2) Ultra Wide Angle Camera + 2MP (F2. 4) Macro Angle Camera | 13MP (F2. 0) Front Camera | Video Maximum Resolution of Full HD (1920 x 1080) @30fps Latest Android 14 Operating System having One UI 6. 1 platform with MediaTek Dimensity 6100+ Processor | 2. 2GHz, 2GHz Clock Speed with Octa-Core Processor Get a massive 6000mAh Lithium-ion Battery (Non-Removable) with C-Type Super Fast Charging (25W Charging Support) Get upto 4 Generations of AndroidOS Upgrades &amp;amp; 5 Years of Security Updates with Samsung Galaxy M15. Includes 1 Year Manufacturer Warranty for Device. SpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BLUEDisplay Type FHDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidProcessor Number 2. 2 GHz + 2. 0 GHz Octa Core ProcessorNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name Octa Core ProcessorFlash LEDCondition NewModel Number SM-M156B/DSModel Name M15-5GPrimary Camera (MP) 50</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5b0f8a2a-183a-482f-91d0-159f0f2a3ca4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/65a6a833-74c6-48db-87b0-b26cf3ca3f71/web/4_1732106249325.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>559.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058829083247</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
