<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>3815392767</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS 44mm Silver Aluminium Case With Winter Blue Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Winter Blue Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number MREF3QA/A, MREF3LL/A, MREF3QH/AModel Name MREF3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/85f362b1-f78d-4a50-be58-22dad7bff7e2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/87e6c4c7-090f-404c-96a3-6f552506dba7/web/1_1733295582195.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>938.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038153927677</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
