<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>1126369239</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban Smart Glasses Wayfarer Large Transitions Matte Black / G15 Green</g:title>
      <g:description>Ray-Ban Style with Meta Technology Iconic style, cutting-edge technology and light-weight form unite in a range of frames designed for living in the moment while expressing yourself to the maxVersatile Lens Options High performance lenses are available in sun, polarized or Transitions® lenses. All lenses offer advanced clarity, comfort, and 100% UVA &amp;amp; UVB protection. Prescription lens compatibleBuilt-in HD Camera Capture high-quality photos and videos with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic systemMeta AI Voice Control Spark creativity, get information and control features with your voice—just ask Meta AI so you don’t miss a beatOpen-Ear Audio Discreet open-ear speakers let you enjoy rich audio quality, music and calls, while keeping you connected to the world around youOverviewMeet the next generation of smart glasses. The Ray-Ban Meta collection combines iconic design with cutting-edge technology. Capture life's best moments with an upgraded 12MP camera and five-mic system. Livestream your view of life’s best moments to Instagram and Facebook. Stay connected with hands-free calls and messages and listen to your favorite tracks through built-in speakers. Because no one sees the world like you do, express yourself with the most unique perspective there is - yours. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Matte Black / G15 GreenModel Number RW4008Model Name Meta Rayban AR Glasses Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b17879fd-d89a-44a1-94c9-78f6c55ea8a7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7ab99ba4-5ca4-4f58-bda3-44ff341c9d9a/web/1_1729574400227.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1838.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011263692390</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5888033060</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Marble Grey 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Easy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Marble GreyDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/096bf27c-3da5-49b0-a22a-706165ed6443</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6df2ebac-431f-4165-a327-3d8247214823/web/1_1729572432671.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2470 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058880330601</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5158303277</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Pal Digital Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>Pocket-friendly design in five exciting colorsWide-angle lens for more expansive and creative shotsMulti-use detachable ring for a better hold, remote shooting, and a viewfinderBluetooth transfer for easy image sharing and editing. Lithium-ion battery with USB Type-C chargingInternal memory and microSD/micro SDHC card storage optionsBluetooth TransferSmartphone App comes with 18 filtersOverviewThe one and only Instax Pal, a super small digital camera, eager to capture small spontaneous moments, helping to make them feel powerful. Then, when you are ready for the big reveal, transfer your images (Pal can store 50 maximum) to your smartphone via Bluetooth. Select the camera roll on the Instax Pal app to transfer, add one of 18 filters, text or decorate with stickers, you can even select the size of your mini, square, wide, film before printing images via your Instax Link printer. SpecificationsProduct Weight 41 gColour Name WhiteProduct Length 4. 23 cmProduct Height 4. 43 cmProduct Width/Depth 4. 3 cmFeatures Removable Memory CardModel Number Instax PalItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/57b84ed2-5379-4688-9663-d39b6eea0c02</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/60736548-15b0-4fbd-8719-1df1ab71993a/web/1_1729571932382.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>448.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051583032773</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6575892205</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban Wearable x Skyler RW4010 601/MF-52 / Clear to Cerulean Blue Photochromic Lenses Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Camera Capture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban Meta Skyler smart glasses are designed to unlock new possibilities in how you see the world. The lightweight frame is integrated with wearable tech, so you can listen, call, capture and livestream without disconnecting from what’s happening around you. Drawing on our 60s archive and the Golden Age of air travel, the Skyler shape is inspired by an era of iconic jet-set style. Its wider front and gentle curves are designed to suit most faces. SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 5 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 150 mmProduct Height 41. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 52. 2 mmModel Number RW4010BK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d407b45e-ca38-4bc6-a3c9-015864f90d13</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/79c48829-f16b-4bbf-8b3c-55eae985c920/web/1_1729573895200.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1849 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065758922059</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3428515027</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Wearable x headliner RW4009 601/9A 50 Polar G15 Green Shiny Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Capture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban | Meta Headliner With Ray-Ban Meta Headliner smart glasses you can express yourself with the most unique perspective there is – yours. Integrated with AI-enhanced wearable tech, the lightweight frame enables you to listen, call, capture and livestream, all while staying present in the moment. The Headliner panthos shape is a hybrid of the Wayfarer and the Round, bringing together the best of two icons. SpecificationsColour Name Shiny BlackStorage Capacity 32 GBModel Number RW4009Model Name RW4009Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/33f9942a-d41b-4a6a-a500-3d176282955e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6bb3877e-82b7-468c-b79e-f259a3033d04/web/1_1729573646797.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1890 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034285150273</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1406118086</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e4359b62-f6db-4684-92de-3bc3019fefc6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ff1c7769-15f3-4694-84f2-2925b0b3784c/web/1_1729573178769.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>7799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014061180861</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7362358657</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban Meta Wayfarer RW4006 601ST350 - Polar Gradient Graphite</g:title>
      <g:description>Ai Technology - Spark your creativity, get information, and control your glasses just by saying “Hey Meta”2. Ask Meta AI3 to get what you need and never miss a beatAudio - Seamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. thanks to improved directional audioControls - Unlock a range of hands-free possibilities with voice command2 – call and message, capture content, and manage media settings with your phone in your pocketCharging Case - Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to eight more charges on the go4 – means you can focus on your day without interruptionOverviewExperience the intersection of style and performance with Ray-Ban RAY-BAN | META WAYFARER. These square-shaped glasses feature a matte black frame that offers a sleek and modern look. The polarized lenses, in graphite color with gradient treatment, provide excellent protection against glare and enhance your vision. The gradient transition from top to bottom adds a touch of elegance to these shades. SpecificationsColour Name Polar Gradient GraphiteModel Number RW4006Model Name RW4006</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4cf1617e-7c25-4af3-b703-4d28e68fe959</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3d19f589-9609-4318-b632-2c5b8a9157f0/web/1_1729574620942.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073623586572</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2351059045</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 MAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 InSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber Of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8d60a8e0-af22-4d4d-a198-9c9bc143009e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b373297d-d6d1-4e5c-b801-3001d30788d5/web/1_1729584640250.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023510590458</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2010550403</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Black Titanium Case With Black Ocean Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFeaturing a stunning, new black titanium case, Apple Watch Ultra 2 is the ultimate sports and adventure watch. It has all the connectivity, health and safety features for the every day. And it takes training further with the most accurate GPS in a sports watchUltra 2 is built for extremes. Now available in black titanium, the 49 mm case is designed for the toughest environments, and it’s certified to EN13319, the internationally recognised standard for diving accessoriesAction on the spot. The customisable Action button gives you precise control over starting a workout, marking a segment or moving on to the next intervalA battery made for the long run. Wherever you find yourself, the last thing you want to worry about is your battery. Ultra 2 is engineered to perform at peak conditions longer, so you can perform at yoursApple Watch Ultra 2 is the perfect partner whether you’re riding indoors, road cycling, mountain biking or commuting. From Bluetooth-enabled accessories to metrics to seeing them easily while you’re riding, you’re always ready to rollOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Ocean BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 49 MmModel Number MX4P3QA/AModel Name MX4P3QA/A, MX4P3LW/A, MX4P3ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b2894516-597d-4433-9030-5303ddde47d5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5b351dd0-8bcf-4e58-b344-b6ac8ce812df/web/1_1729585063851.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020105504036</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3757346679</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas 4 Way Extension Socket 13A - Extension Strip With Led Indicators | Child Safe |Extra Long Cord with Over Current Protected | Ideal For All Electronic Devices White/Orange 35.2x13.4x3.6cm</g:title>
      <g:description>This Geepas 4 Way Extension Socket/Strip is damage-resistant and fireproof housing protects circuits from fire, impact or rust, and prevents dents and scratches. The built-in power indicator light makes it easy to know its ON/OFF mode. Compatible for connecting various devices like washing machines, Iron boxes, TV, Hair Dryer, Mobile, Drill machines, Printer, Computer, Refrigerator, Vacuum cleaners and more. 1. PREMIUM PROTECTION FOR YOUR ELECTRONICS -The Geepas strip features high-quality construction and a durable design with damage-resistant housing that protects circuits from fire, impact, and rust. Three protected AC outlets make this surge protection strip an ideal solution for home offices, media rooms, and other areas where multiple devices need to be connected. 2. 750 DEGREE FLAME RETARDANT MATERIAL - Built with durable material which is fireproof ABS plastic and has a high melting and heating point, protecting your connected devices. The material is 750 degree Celsius Flame Retardant. 3. ERGONOMIC DESIGN -This extension strip has 4 plugs that are angled so it does not block the other outlet. This keeps it free for use with additional items. The size of this socket is 35. 2x13. 4x3. 6cm. 4. 3 METER POWER CORD - Along with its slim, sleek design that effortlessly slides into narrow spaces, the three-outlet, power strip provides a 3-meter extra long power cord to prevent a tripping hazard and to minimize clutter. 'SpecificationsProduct Weight 560 gColour Name White/OrangeModel Number GES58012Model Name GES58012Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/52525667-d050-4580-80b3-d1f7d7b7f705</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ab58eeea-667a-4174-8d56-468caba703cf/web/1_1729583987115.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>31 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037573466797</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3757120709</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLY13 13.6-Inch Display: Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 8GB RAM/256GB/ English Keyboard(International version) Starlight</g:title>
      <g:description>STRIKINGLY THIN DESIGN — The redesigned MacBook Air is more portable than ever and weighs just 2. 7 pounds. It’s the incredibly capable laptop that lets you work, play or create just about anything. Use the Apple MacBook Pro 2022 has set standards in computing thanks to its Apple M2 chip Processor. M2 is the next generation of Apple silicon. Its 8-core CPU lets you zip through everyday tasks like creating documents and presentations, or take on more intensive workflows like developing in Xcode or mixing tracks in Logic Pro. M2 features up to a 10-core GPU, resulting in a big boost in graphics performance. And its media engine lets you play and edit up to 11 streams of 4K and up to 2 streams of 8K ProRes video. Considering the amazing specifications, the Apple MacBook Pro 2022’s price is quite fair. The more unified memory (RAM) you choose, the more apps you can run simultaneously with a higher rate of performance. The 13-inch MacBook Pro can be configured with up to 24GB for more fluid multitasking and easy handling of large files. Solid-state drive (SSD) storage is the amount of space your MacBook Pro has for your documents, photos, music, videos, and other files. It delivers significant performance and speed that you’ll notice when you start up your Mac. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 5 GHzRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 1. 38 KGVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inSIM Type SIM (Standard)Display Resolution 1920x1080Screen Features Eco-FriendlyRefresh Rates 60HzMonitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name StarlightLaptop Weight 1 - 1. 4 KgDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDConnection Type USBAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableWhat's In The Box Laptop,Adapter,User ManualNumber of Cores 16-CoreWireless WirelessRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProduct Length 35 cmProduct Height 7. 35 cmProduct Width/Depth 34 cmGraphic Memory 0 GBHDD Rotation 5400 rpmFeatures Bluetooth, Business, Ergonomic, High Refresh Rate Display, PersonalModel Number MLY13, MLY13LL/A/MLY13HN/A / MLY13X/A / MLY13J/A MLY13ZP/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2Pixels Per Inch 1080x1920 pixelsHDMI Output noAdobe Flash Compatible YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5fdc7924-b249-41a6-9308-fdbfbc6fc6d5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4ed2f49f-9ec3-49d5-b7f5-c05bf779e5e2/web/1_1729578199279.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3345 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037571207095</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8709785830</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Air 2024 (6th Generation) M2 11-Inch 256GB Blue Wi-Fi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M2, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad AiriPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Air packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Air and an expansive 13″ iPad Air that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 7606 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 InPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type ESIMConnection Type WifiDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System IOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone FlashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof And Dust ProofModel Number IPad AirModel Name IPad AirPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d96be9b9-ae8d-42b3-b108-ab7f5f99986c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/55a843df-9be5-49f6-a1ee-1e6bbbd8807b/web/1_1729585931449.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087097858301</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4778173707</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Mini 40 Instant Film Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>Automatic Exposure- Mini 40 automatically adjusts to surrounding brightnessSelfie Mode- simply pull out the lens and start taking selfiesSelfie Mode also captures close up shots clearly, Close up range- 30 to 50 cmsSuperior Design- high quality texture and premium silver accentsFilm Size- 62 mm × 46 mmFor a very large company, Fujifilm has retained a culture of innovation that has seen it through good times and badOverviewDigital cameras, lens, accessories film instant and single-use cameras and instant film; binoculars and sports optics; skin care. For a very large company, Fujifilm has retained a culture of innovation that has seen it through good times and bad. Think Fujifilm, think Green, sustainability, innovation, quality, fun, enrichment, and humility. This brand stands for innovation, quality, and humility. In fact, for such a big company with so many accomplishments, Fujifilm is low key. Despite an impressive record of innovation, commitment to sustainability, diversification, few people know of the company’s enormous accomplishments across so many spheres of business spanning the entire globe. Without fanfare, Fuji builds communities around its various products featuring stories of active users or opportunities to share information such as in its online Wonder Shop creative community or communities for its digital camera series in which enthusiasts can share , learn about anything, and even have their photography featured. The Fujifilm customer is not about flash, but substance. People buy Fujifilm for the features, the value, and the innovation, not to make a statement. The Fujifilm brand is smart, practical, innovative, individualistic. The company’s philosophy, it says, is based on the recognition that our mission…is to significantly contribute to the realization of a society in which all people across the world can lead lives that are abundant in spiritual as well as material wealth and with a sense of fulfillment and satisfaction. SpecificationsProduct Weight 330 gColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Instant CameraBattery Type Li-ion PolymerCamera Zoom Type DigitalProduct Length 104 mmProduct Height 121 mmProduct Width/Depth 65 mmCamera Resolution 2 MPModel Number Mini40Model Name Mini40Item Quantity 1Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a8d2e62d-49c3-4d54-8bd9-8656ffc7a9d1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d1452eca-8bbe-4185-bf41-193e2c15dcae/web/1_1729575277466.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047781737077</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8031590243</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLY33 13.6-Inch Display : Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 256GB SSD, English Keyboard(International version) Midnight</g:title>
      <g:description>Your efficiency levels will be on point as the Apple MacBook Air 2022 features a new look loaded with so many specifications. It blends functionality with style packing in an awesome look with efficient performance. The macOS Big Sur operating system and powerful Processor help you perform your regular activities along with fun games. It has a powerful storage capacity and efficient RAM which lets you store a huge amount of important data and enjoy lag-free operation respectively. The 13. 3-inch Retina display allows you to enjoy watching videos and playing games a more enjoyable experience. The MacBook has set standards in computing thanks to its Apple M2 chip Processor. It has an 8-Core CPU with 4 perform­ance cores and 4 efficiency cores, 8-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The processor variant is Big Sur. The superbly fast processor takes your productivity, creativity, and gaming to a whole new level and never lets you slow down so that the quality and quantity of your work are never compromised. The 8GB RAM (Unified Memory) makes sure you can multitask between different tabs providing you with lightning-fast responsiveness for an amazing user experience. It gives you a delightful gaming experience. This MacBook is full of amazing specifications. The Apple MacBook Air 2020’s price is quite a bargain, making this an affordable buy. With the huge amount of workload and data involved in today’s world, it may get difficult at times to keep all data safe for current or future use stored due to average storage capacities. It comes with a serious storage capacity which helps you to save your contents. It has 256GB SSD to make it more efficient and productive which lets you store your important official data and videos, songs, and photos for your leisure. Play like a pro and watch movies on this laptop for experiencing first-class audio and visual experience where the quality of your entertainment is not compromised. Enjoy watching videos and viewing photos like never before with the 13. 3-inch (diagonal) LED-backlit display with IPS technology which ensures you never miss out on a detail. The resolution is 2560 x 1600 pixels native resolution at 227 pixels per inch with support for millions of colors. This MacBook is an extremely convenient choice for modern tech-oriented people. Built-in 49. 9-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 3. 2 GHzRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 1. 29 KGVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inSIM Type SIM (Standard)Display Resolution 1920x1080Screen Features Eco-FriendlyRefresh Rates 60HzMonitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name MidnightLaptop Weight 1 - 1. 4 KgDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDConnection Type USBAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableWhat's In The Box ‎‎Laptop, Adapter, User Guide, ManualsNumber of Cores 16-CoreWireless WirelessRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProduct Length 21 cmProduct Height 1. 09 cmProduct Width/Depth 30. 41 cmGraphic Memory 0 GBHDD Rotation 5400 rpmFeatures Bluetooth, Compact Size, High Refresh Rate Display, Ergonomic, PersonalModel Number MLY33LL/A MLY33PA/A MLY33ZP/A MLY33ZA/A / MLY33HN/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2Pixels Per Inch 1080x1920 pixelsHDMI Output noAdobe Flash Compatible YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noNumber of HDMI Ports 2Processor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a97887e8-c0e4-4b94-af43-997629186a45</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6bd4389c-9473-4d0e-b654-a6f8507d772d/web/1_1729576014656.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3390 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080315902435</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1614543907</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Pastel Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 GColour Name Pastel BlueProduct Length 10. 41 CmProduct Height 12. 19 CmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 CmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/524f324d-ec56-4f6f-96d0-39516a74393a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/77b5445b-8562-4f3b-9e71-b6bf198cf8bc/web/1_1729586512445.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016145439070</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4481048245</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 GVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version IOS 18Operating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber Of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone FlashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 MmProduct Height 163 MmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 MmModel Number MYWJ3AE/A , MYWJ3AH/AModel Name IPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ee7e15cf-a75a-4e2f-a599-d37bf0444b25</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0500d21c-481b-4ab2-9c69-45b58fa1546e/web/1_1729588226863.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5200 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044810482458</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9521389827</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 GVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version IOS 18Operating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber Of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone FlashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 MmProduct Height 163 MmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 MmModel Number MYWH3AE/A , MYWH3AH/AModel Name IPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a3010d4b-7f56-4500-8e89-f9fcd03cef35</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d11a6315-f188-4573-b690-2b05f3a2d0c3/web/1_1729588407568.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5200 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095213898278</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3688499585</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray Ban Wayfarer RW4006 Shiny Black Frames With G15 Green Classic Lenses Direct To Social 12MP Camera Open Ear Audio Five-Mic System AI Voice Control</g:title>
      <g:description>Ray-ban | meta wayfarer ; Shiny black frames with G15 Green classic lenses. ;The latest in wearable tech with iconic Ray-Ban style. ;Try Classic Ray-Ban lenses with a uniform tint for consistent shade and a timeless aesthetic. ;A sun lens for outdoorDesigned for living in the moment; An icon of style from Hollywood to hip-hop, the Wayfarer never stands still. ;Embraced by the next generation of culture makers, its journey continues with AI-enhanced wearable tech. ;Listen, call, capture and livesDirect to social ;Choose to livestream directly from your glasses to Instagram and Facebook without missing the moment. ;Seamlessly switch between your glasses and phone cameras while sharing your unique POV. ;Livestream up to 30 mins12MP camera; Capture what you see and hear with a new ultra-wide 12MP camera and five-mic system. ;Take high-quality photos and immersive videos, or live stream it all on Facebook and Instagram. ;Rest assured, your media will never be posted or shareOpen-ear audio; Discreet open-ear speakers and five built-in microphones let you seamlessly switch between music and calls, while still allowing you to hear the ambient sound of your surroundingsMeta AI voice controlSpark creativity, get information and control features with your voice—just ask Meta AI so you don’t miss a beatSo if you're out grilling with a group of friends, you can ask: “Hey Meta—I’m grilling scallops, corn on the cob, and burgers—how long should I cook each of them?” “Hey Meta—what salad goes well with thatOr if you find yourself in a messy situation while finger painting with a toddler, you can ask: “Hey Meta—how do I wash finger paint off walls?” “Hey Meta—send a photo to Grandpa on WhatsAppWith voice control you can take photos/videos, make calls, send messages and more—it all starts with “Hey Meta. ”OverviewToggle between your phone and glasses camera when you videocall or livestream(1), so that everyone can experience your unique view of the world. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Everything is for your ears only, thanks to improved directional audio. SpecificationsModel Number RW4006Model Name RW4006</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/90e7c22d-9485-4de3-814a-183ebd788ffa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3436004e-0b2a-457f-b968-a8df21bec0d5/web/1_1729574833385.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1615.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036884995859</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8106316573</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban Wearable x Skyler RW4010 670013-52 Chalky Grey / Cinnamon Lenses Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>Camera Capture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban Meta Skyler smart glasses are designed to unlock new possibilities in how you see the world. The lightweight frame is integrated with wearable tech, so you can listen, call, capture and livestream without disconnecting from what’s happening around you. Drawing on our 60s archive and the Golden Age of air travel, the Skyler shape is inspired by an era of iconic jet-set style. Its wider front and gentle curves are designed to suit most faces. SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 5 KGColour Name PinkProduct Length 150 mmProduct Height 41. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 52. 2 mmModel Number RW4010PK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4be3a9e4-13b8-4af9-9842-e375ef23b7a5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4e438450-2f79-45cf-bf34-db8f88ddb171/web/1_1729575455918.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1698.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081063165738</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3565302466</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 512GB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/26c9dfa9-837b-4fa1-ab10-52b76c6b8484</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/371e7b0f-0aa9-439f-9d5a-805a211a2acd/web/1_1729578396655.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5453.55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035653024660</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6921096176</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 GPS + Cellular, 49mm Titanium Case With Blue Ocean Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhonePrecision dual‑frequency GPS, Cellular connectivity, Family Setup, Pair multiple watches with one iPhoneEmergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash Detection SirenUp to 36 hours. Up to 72 hours in Low Power Mode. Fast chargingBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewApple’s brightest Always-On Retina display is easy to see, even in harsh sunlight. More room for adding complications to customize your watch face and enough space to view six metrics at once. Made for recreational water sports, scuba, and free diving for descents to 40 meters. The Depth app shows the time, current depth, water temperature, duration under water, and maximum depth you’ve reached. The Oceanic+ app puts a dive computer on your wrist. Ocean Band is light and flexible, with a titanium buckle and adjustable loop for a secure fit even during high-speed water sports. The Compass app delivers helpful views and details like elevation, incline, longitude, and latitude. See the last place where you had cellular reception. Mark your location with Compass Waypoints. Backtrack uses GPS to map where you’ve been so you can retrace your steps. Alpine Loop is an extremely rugged and secure band to meet the needs of all outdoor adventurers. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Blue Ocean BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MREG3AE/A, MRF73ZA/A , MREG32P/A, MREG3ZP/A, MREG3LL/A, MREG3LW/A, MREG3J/AModel Name MREG3AE/A, MREG3VC/A, MREG3NF/A, MREG3B/A, MREG3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9a453e96-00f5-4c1b-bf1e-87b012d97357</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/300e689b-a003-423e-9420-c4355baaab68/web/1_1729577900375.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2852.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069210961761</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4815246680</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Mini Evo Instant Photo Kit (Black)</g:title>
      <g:description>100 Different Expressions Stunning, evocative, dynamic. Interesting, striking, surprising. With 10 lens effects and 10 film effects, you can create the exact vision you have in mind. Experiment with the vividness, go retro, add softness to the focusDesign Focused With a luxurious design and razor-sharp finish, the mini Evo boasts an analogue look and feel and even features a traditional film camera lever to print your photos. And, thanks to the built-in selfie mirror,Smartphone Printer_x000D_ Sometimes the shots you are most proud of are hidden in the depths of your camera roll. Adjust the crop, rotate, tweak the brightness, contrast and saturation, add a filter and then print your mini masterpieceSave Images_x000D_ Captured your pièce de resistance? It’s good to share. That’s why the mini Evo turns your smartphone into your very own print gallery, saving every single printed image in a handy digital format. Leaving you to get posting _x000D_Remote Shooting Keep your eye on the shot and go hands-free. Simply connect your smartphone to your mini Evo and hey presto, you’ve now got a remote shutter button. Spot on for group photos, arty portrait setups, even trickier wildlife shots. OverviewThe instax mini Evo is our most expressive camera yet. We believe that everyone has their own unique perspectives, and with 10 lens options and 10 film effects, the mini Evo gives you 100 different ways to express yourself through the images you capture and print. Combining traditional analogue design with the controls and convenience of digital devices, the mini Evo is a hybrid instant camera and smartphone printer in one. Creativity is paramount. That’s why the mini Evo brings endless possibilities to your fingertips, leaving you to express your unique point of view and share life’s beautiful nuances. SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 28 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 3. 6 cmProduct Height 8. 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 12. 3 cmModel Number 84481</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/118e84c7-8938-491c-a30a-47fe6cada52a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/16b5f872-77a8-4356-9c12-68f42cc0c04a/web/1_1729577803092.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>995 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048152466800</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7949557357</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Mini Evo Instant Photo Kit (Black)</g:title>
      <g:description>100 Different Expressions Stunning, evocative, dynamic. Interesting, striking, surprising. With 10 lens effects and 10 film effects, you can create the exact vision you have in mind. Experiment with the vividness, go retro, add softness to the focusDesign Focused With a luxurious design and razor-sharp finish, the mini Evo boasts an analogue look and feel and even features a traditional film camera lever to print your photos. And, thanks to the built-in selfie mirror,Smartphone Printer_x000D_ Sometimes the shots you are most proud of are hidden in the depths of your camera roll. Adjust the crop, rotate, tweak the brightness, contrast and saturation, add a filter and then print your mini masterpieceSave Images_x000D_ Captured your pièce de resistance? It’s good to share. That’s why the mini Evo turns your smartphone into your very own print gallery, saving every single printed image in a handy digital format. Leaving you to get posting _x000D_Remote Shooting Keep your eye on the shot and go hands-free. Simply connect your smartphone to your mini Evo and hey presto, you’ve now got a remote shutter button. Spot on for group photos, arty portrait setups, even trickier wildlife shots. OverviewThe instax mini Evo is our most expressive camera yet. We believe that everyone has their own unique perspectives, and with 10 lens options and 10 film effects, the mini Evo gives you 100 different ways to express yourself through the images you capture and print. Combining traditional analogue design with the controls and convenience of digital devices, the mini Evo is a hybrid instant camera and smartphone printer in one. Creativity is paramount. That’s why the mini Evo brings endless possibilities to your fingertips, leaving you to express your unique point of view and share life’s beautiful nuances. SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 28 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 3. 6 cmProduct Height 8. 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 12. 3 cmModel Number 84481</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b54b644-358a-4e0f-950d-b6ac02a2a995</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/534ec70c-04ce-4f17-9d86-9c26bd29e8ca/web/1_1729577367349.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>995 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079495573573</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1833662009</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b16856fd-747a-452e-a530-f2d6b96d643a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/03183d29-d013-491c-bc6d-da501fe53813/web/1_1729587845899.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018336620090</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7066130021</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Single+ESIM Titanium Gray 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The legacy of Galaxy Note is alive and well. Write, tap, and navigate with the precision your fingers wish they had on the new, flat displayCapture stunning details with the most megapixels on a smartphone and AI processing. The enhanced ProVisual Engine recognises objects - improving colour tone, reducing noise, and bringing out detailWith 1. 6x larger pixels and a wider Tele OIS, photos and videos are brighter and more stable, making even distant subjects clearly stunning from sunup to sundown and everything in betweenSpace Zoom puts you in the middle of the action, even at night. With 1. 6x larger pixels and a wider Tele OIS, photos and videos are brighter and more stable — making even distant subjects clearly stunningWith massive capacity and greater energy efficiency, ultra's battery gives you extra life when it matters most you know, like the epic boss battle you've been gearing up forOverviewBehold the Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra smartphone, an exceptional amalgamation of incredible technology and superior sophistication. Whether you're typing up a storm or jotting something down, Note Assist makes a long story shortSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 8 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 3168x1440Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Titanium GrayDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature QuadFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24 UltraModel Name Galaxy S24 Ultra</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c909eb04-7ca8-46e7-b1a0-ed6ecbd2aa7d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c5438586-1684-4a87-8569-77ed4300ec43/web/3_1729587546118.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3190 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070661300214</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8002064608</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Rechargeable Portable Speaker, Portable Handle with 1500 MAH Huge Battery| TWS Connection & Compatible with BT/ USB/ AUX/ FM/ Micro SD | Ideal for Home, Hotels, Trips & Outdoor Use GMS11187 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>MULTIPLE CONNECTIVITY - Wireless PA speakers have built-in Bluetooth for wireless audio streaming There are 4 modes available It is used as a karaoke machine, music player, PA system, FM radio, etc The portable speaker karaoke PA system is equipped with a USB flash drive and SD card reader so it can serve as an MP3 player, 35mm AUX input and mic/guitar inputFLASHING DJ LIGHTS: The LED light of this Geepas PA speaker changes with the music playing, which can create a colourful and joyful effect The body design of the audio system is highly mechanical and can satisfy your rhythm at karaoke You will carefully notice that you have the rhythm pattern of a deformed robotPORTABLE &amp;amp; EASY TO USE - The portable karaoke speaker with 2 flexible wheels on the bottom has a medium-sized, light and wear-resistant hard shell and is easy to move The speaker has a short handle which is suitable for people of all walks of life It is suitable for family reunions, indoor gatherings, classroom teaching, public speaking, and small stage performancesPOWERFUL RECHARGEABLE BATTERY：The rechargeable party speaker has a built-in 3. 7V / 1500mAh high-capacity lithium-ion battery, which can play music for few long hours continuouslyThis Bluetooth speaker has a built-in amplifier that can stream music to your instrumentsThe portable speaker karaoke PA system is equipped with a USB flash drive and SD card reader so it can serve as an MP3 player, 3. 5mm AUX input, and mic/guitar inputOverviewWireless PA speakers have built-in Bluetooth for wireless audio streaming There are 4 modes available It is used as a karaoke machine, music player, PA system, FM radio, etc The portable speaker karaoke PA system is equipped with a USB flash drive and SD card reader so it can serve as an MP3 player, 35mm AUX input and mic/guitar input The LED light of this Geepas PA speaker changes with the music playing, which can create a colourful and joyful effect The body design of the audio system is highly mechanical and can satisfy your rhythm at karaoke You will carefully notice that you have the rhythm pattern of a deformed robot The portable karaoke speaker with 2 flexible wheels on the bottom has a medium-sized, light and wear-resistant hard shell and is easy to move The speaker has a short handle which is suitable for people of all walks of life It is suitable for family reunions, indoor gatherings, classroom teaching, public speaking, and small stage performancesSpecificationsProduct Weight 2. 14 KGColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Warranty Card &amp;amp; User manualProduct Length 41. 3 cmProduct Height 18. 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 21. 3 cmWattage 25000 WFeatures Amplifier, Compact Size, USB, Smart, WirelessModel Number GMS11187Model Name Geepas GMS11187Number of HDMI Ports 0</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/232652ad-9deb-4b2a-87fc-92da24d2bb0e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c4dfd530-c86b-4097-b67d-9ce1f2913de2/web/1_1729586612466.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080020646082</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7035136726</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas 32 Inch Frameless HD Smart LED TV With Remote Control, HDMI And USB Ports, Head Phone Jack, PC Audio In ,Wi-Fi, Android 14.0 With E-Share,YouTube Etc GLED3202SCHD Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Good video quality: This geepas 32 inch smart LED tv allows you to experience detail and color definitionDisplay: 32 Inch; aspect ratio: 16:9; resolution: 1366x768; response time: 6. 5msHigh-quality sound: With HQ, a superior audio experience is delivered. The sound is intelligently optimized according to audio content or customized to personal taste insteadWide viewing angle 176 H X 176 W: Enjoy the same consistency and clarity from almost any viewing angle. Sit in any corner of the room, and you will experience the same quality. This resolution provides an expansive entertainment experienceConnectivity: AV IN, USB, HDMI, headphone jack, coaxial maximum audio output 2x8wVideo system: PAL, SECAM, NTSCThe package includes a remote controlPower consumption operation ≤60 W; power consumption standby ≤ 0. 50 W; power requirement: AC 100-240V 50/60 HzOverview"Delivers a picture that is smooth and clear, full of rich colors and detailed contrast. Enjoy unmatched clarity and crispness with the Geepas 32"" Smart LED TV. An immersive experience with a captivating visual and audio experience as real as possible with a high-quality display A device engineered to offer high speed, quality performance, and other stunning details. You can now quickly access the contents and control them with a remote control. For a truly remarkable viewing experience, picture quality is enhanced by an advanced 176x176 viewing angle and wide color enhancement. It optimizes every scene for splendid expression. It is engineered with the latest technology to produce high speed, quality performance, and stunning details. It has an impressive, frameless design and will elevate your interior style and ambience. You can watch your favorite movies, shows, and much more. Android 12. 0 provides a wide range of entertainment options. The sound is intelligently optimized according to audio content or customized to your personal taste with effects and stereo sound quality. With HDMI and USB ports that allow for a physical connection, the TV makes it simple to connect. Furthermore, these ports allow for multiple input and output options. This TV is full HD compatible, so you can enjoy HD movies and TV shows. Using the remote control, you can switch between watching your favorite movies, shows, and much more all in one place without leaving your seat. The package includes a remote control. The LED TV uses eco-efficiency technology to offer you a wonderful theatrical experience while being light in your pocket. "SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 720pRAM Size 1 GBInternal Memory 8 GBProduct Weight 8 KGScreen Size 32 inRefresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box 1 x Television, 2 x BaseProcessor Name Cortex-A53Number of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR2Viewing Distance 1. 7 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 32 cmProduct Height 70. 84 cmProduct Width/Depth 39. 85 cmFeatures Android, USB, HDMIModel Number GLED3202SCHDModel Name GLED3202SEHDNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 2Processor Version A55 Quad Core</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/246a3459-376d-450b-8e54-721292d1d71b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ae7b2577-580f-4507-be67-876cf7116510/web/1_1729581101251.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>375 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070351367268</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7865302736</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWL3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cf203241-319b-4e19-9e77-2e44654d4e2c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fbce0527-6fa7-4aaa-980c-1902fdbfed21/web/1_1729588684454.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6948.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078653027361</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7320805426</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro - 256 GB/Desert Titanium (Discounted)</g:title>
      <g:description>Description: • STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass• TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. • MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra-Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. • PRO VIDEO—Take your videos to a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. • PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. • THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. • A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. • CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. • VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3db1c1b3-7544-4825-b7d2-48fab2b0117b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/83378a1e-9b96-4f37-b534-9fc45220711e/web/1_1729594173772.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073208054267</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
