<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>1906876426</g:id>
      <g:title>Panasonic Portable FM/AM Radio With Tuner RF-2400D Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFeatures a universal design for easy viewing and a new tuner for easy and stable tuningOperates with either an ac adaptor or battery, so it can be easily used in the living roomAFC function expands the AM radio reception range and simplifies tuningEliminates the need for exact tuning precision by automatically selecting the nearest stationFluorescent pointer provides comfortable viewing in the darkSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number RF-2400D</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b02b3edc-00dd-4272-8500-cea06bc7a61f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6fa964bf-c1ce-4df3-be92-5daf9568b8f0/web/1_1731419808420.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>105 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019068764267</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7890980526</g:id>
      <g:title>Mikrotik hAP Lite TC Wireless Router White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe home access point lite (hAP lite) is an ideal little device for your apartment, house or officeSupports button triggered WPS, for the convenience of not typing a complicated password when somebody wants to have wireless internet access, and can also be told to change to cAP mode and join a CAPsMAN centrally managed network by the push of a buttonDevice runs RouterOS with all the features, bandwidth shaping, firewall, user access control and many othersThe hAP lite is equipped with a powerful 650MHz CPU, 32MB RAM, dual chain 2. 4GHz onboard wireless and four Fast Ethernet ports and a RouterOS L4 licenseWireless 2. 4 GHz max data rate is 300 Mbit/sSpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableModel Number RB941-2nD-TC</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9fb41a01-28bb-46e0-8b55-14c9ff8e717e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4570d52a-9e06-4c06-bb5d-49918d76fb46/web/1_1731419395155.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>105 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078909805262</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8741994576</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee Smart E27 Color Light Bulb</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsConnect with either 2. 4 Ghz Wi-Fi or Bluetooth, Controllable with voice assistant or via app control, Dimmable RGBWW with over 16 million colors, 2700-6500K, 1200 Lumens, 12W-85WThis E27 socket has a power consumption of 9W and a lifetime of 25000 hours. The light has a size of 6. 5x6. 5x13 cm and can be dimmed via app. This RGBWW LED type provides up to 1200 lumens and can be adjusted between 2700K and 6500K. The light can be controlled via the Govee Home App, Siri, Google Assistant or Alexa and works with iOS and Android. SpecificationsColour Name MulticolorWhat's In The Box Gaming LED LightsType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number 6974316992745Model Name 60906</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6ea6191d-51f7-413b-ba79-56a81629f027</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/acce88ef-97b0-43c9-ba4a-e6b7154305d9/web/1_1731426701128.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>114 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087419945764</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7949459030</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Tune 510Bt Wireless On-Ear Headphones</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMulti-point connections. Hands-free calls. lightweight comfortable and foldable design. up to 40H battery life andspeed charge. Unique and fashionable designJBL PURE BASE SOUND: Packed with 32mm Dynamic drivers, the JBL Tune 510BT features the renowned JBL Pure Bass sound, which can be found in the most famous venues all around the worldQUICK CHARGING: With its superior USB Type-C charging cable, a quick 5 min recharge of your Tune 510BT provides you with playtime upto 2 Hours while in a span of 2 hours, get your headphones completely charged upDUAL PAIRING: The Multi Point Connectivity (Dual Pairing) on Tune 510BT allows youto effortlessly switch between 2 Bluetooth devices. Its a smooth transition when you have to receive a call on your mobile phone call while you are watching a video on your tabUPTO 40 HOURS PLAYTIME: Designed for long playhours, the Tune 510BT allows you to Listen wirelessly upto 40 hours non-stop under optimal audio settingsVOICE ASSISTANT INTEGRATION: Siri or Hey Google is just a button away: activate the voice assistant of your device by pushing the multi-function button on the earcupHANDS FREE CALLS: The button controls on the earcup of Tune 510BT, allows you to easily control your sound and manage your calls from your headphonesOverviewThe JBL Tune 510BT headphones let you stream powerful JBL Pure Bass sound with no strings attached. Easy to use, these headphones provide up to 40 hours of pure pleasure and an extra 2 hours of battery with just 5 minutes of power with the USB-C charging cable. And if a call comes in while you are watching a video on another device, the JBL Tune 510BT seamlessly switches to your mobile. Bluetooth 5. 0 enabled and designed to be comfortable, the JBL Tune 510BT headphones also allow you to connect to Siri or Google without using your mobile device. Available in multiple fresh colors and foldable for easy portability, the JBL Tune 510BT headphones are a grab ‘n go solution that helps you to inject music into every aspect of your busy life. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 450 mAhProduct Weight 160 gColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessAverage Battery Life 11hrs - 16hrsUsage Type BusinessWhat's In The Box Wireless HeadphonesAudio Headphone Type On-EarCharging Case Type WiredEarplug Type CanalphonesProduct Length 27 cmProduct Height 26 cmProduct Width/Depth 23 cmFeatures Bluetooth, Voice Assistant, Neckband, Volume Control, Tangle-free CordModel Number JBL-T510BTBK / JBLT510BTBLKEU / JBLT510BTBLKModel Name T510Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d54037eb-ed06-4af9-a83d-538e2480c082</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/31fdebd2-45fd-460c-ba06-97434feb0364/web/1_1731430201155.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>122 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079494590304</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8278787433</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Tune 510Bt Wireless On-Ear Headphones</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHands-free calls. lightweight comfortable and foldable design. up to 40H battery life and speed charge. The tune 510 wireless headphones feature JBL pure bass sound which can be found in the most famous venues all around the worldSiri or hey google is just a button away activate the voice assistant of your device by pushing the multifunction button designed for long play hours the tune 510 allows you to listen wirelessly upto 40 hours non stop under optimal audio settingsThe tune 510 wireless headphones feature JBL pure bass sound which can be found in the most famous venues all around the worldOverviewThe JBL Tune 510BT headphones let you stream powerful JBL Pure Bass sound with no strings attached. Easy to use, these headphones provide up to 40 hours of pure pleasure and an extra 2 hours of battery with just 5 minutes of power with the USB-C charging cable. And if a call comes in while you are watching a video on another device, the JBL Tune 510BT seamlessly switches to your mobile. Bluetooth 5. 0 enabled and designed to be comfortable, the JBL Tune 510BT headphones also allow you to connect to Siri or Google without using your mobile device. Available in multiple fresh colors and foldable for easy portability, the JBL Tune 510BT headphones are a grab ‘n go solution that helps you to inject music into every aspect of your busy life. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 450 mAhProduct Weight 143 gColour Name BlueConnection Type WirelessAverage Battery Life More than 24hrsUsage Type Sports &amp;amp; FitnessWhat's In The Box Wireless headphones, manualAudio Headphone Type On-EarCharging Case Type WiredProduct Length 8. 07 inProduct Height 1. 89 inProduct Width/Depth 8. 77 inFeatures Bluetooth, Foldable, Voice Assistant, Water Resistant, Volume ControlModel Number JBL-T510BTBLUModel Name T510Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/889df716-c3bf-442e-96c8-3b1f113fca0b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3633a42b-edb1-4ac7-a7fa-341254ffb8f8/web/1_1731430076471.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>122 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082787874333</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3379094297</g:id>
      <g:title>Nintendo Switch Pro Controller - Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPro Controller is larger than the Switch's included Joy-Con controllers, even when they're placed in their Grip accessoryController also has a more traditional layout, most notably with its full d-pad, which is important for games that require digital precisionIncludes motion controls, HD rumble, built-in NFC for amiibo functionality, and moreFight faster and smarter with new and returning techniques, like the perfect shield and directional air dodgeSpecificationsConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box Motion controls, HD rumble, built-in amiibo functionalityProduct Length 6. 7 cmProduct Height 15. 4 cmProduct Width/Depth 15. 8 cmModel Number HACAFSSKAModel Name HACAFSSKA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dc5a1954-15e5-4c1e-b8d4-963615e57ee3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/33548144-ec71-466b-b69b-8926ec620110/web/1_1731496641482.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>130 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033790942977</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8962133464</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Tune 510Bt Wireless On-Ear Headphones </g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsIt features the renowned JBL Pure Bass sound, which can be found in the most famous venues all around the world. Wirelessly stream high-quality sound from your smartphone without messy cords. For long-lasting fun, listen wirelessly for 40 hours and recharge the battery in as little as 2 hours with the convenient Type-C USB cable. A quick 5-minute recharge gives you 2 additional hours of music. Easily control your sound and manage your calls your headphones with the convenient buttons on the ear cup hands free calls the button controls on the earcup of tune 510 allows you to easily control your sound and manage your calls from your headphonesSiri or hey google is just a button away activate the voice assistant of your device by pushing the multinfunction button designed for long playhours the tune 510 allows you to listen wirelessly upto 40 hours non stop under optimal audio settingsThe tune 510 wireless headphones feature renowned jbl pure bass sound which can be found in the most famous venues all around the worldWith wireless bluetooth 5. 0 streaming, you can stream wirelessly your device and even switch between two devices so that you don't miss a callOverviewJbl tune 510 the jbl tune 510 headphones let you stream powerful jbl pure bass sound with no strings attached. Easy to use, with up to 40 hours of battery life and speed charge, they are super lightweight and comfortable. Grab them and fill your day with music. listen for longer. up to 40h battery life and speed charge (5mins = 2h) for long-lasting fun, listen wirelessly for 40 hours and recharge the battery in as little as 2 hours with the convenient type-c usb cable. A quick 5-minute recharge gives you 2 additional hours of music. jbl pure bass sound these wireless headphones feature the renowned jbl pure bass sound, which can be found in the most famous venues all around the world. Wirelessly stream this high-quality sound your smartphone without messy cords. wirelessly stream high-quality sound from your smartphone without messy cords. available in multiple fresh colors and foldable for easy portability, the jbl tune 510bt headphones are a grab ‘n go solution that helps you to inject music into every aspect of your busy life. these wireless headphones feature the renowned jbl pure bass sound, which can be found in the most famous venues all around the world. Wirelessly stream this high-quality sound from your smartphone without messy cords. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 450 mAhProduct Weight 143 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessAverage Battery Life More than 24hrsUsage Type Sports &amp;amp; FitnessWhat's In The Box Wireless headphones, manualAudio Headphone Type On-EarCharging Case Type WiredProduct Length 8. 07 inProduct Height 1. 89 inProduct Width/Depth 8. 77 inFeatures Bluetooth, Foldable, Voice Assistant, Water Resistant, Volume ControlModel Number JBLT510BTWHTModel Name JBLT510BTWHTItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9697e009-1447-4ae5-ac56-03e4c2479695</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9f85e99a-46a3-4b54-a31f-bb81307aef18/web/1_1731498361159.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>125 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089621334640</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3006315383</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Tune 510Bt Wireless On-Ear Headphones</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMulti-point connectionsHands-free callslightweight comfortable and foldable designup to 40H battery life andspeed chargeUnique and fashionable designMade of high quality materialsOverviewThe JBL Tune 510BT headphones let you stream powerful JBL Pure Bass sound with no strings attached. Easy to use, these headphones provide up to 40 hours of pure pleasure and an extra 2 hours of battery with just 5 minutes of power with the USB-C charging cable. And if a call comes in while you are watching a video on another device, the JBL Tune 510BT seamlessly switches to your mobile. Bluetooth 5. 0 enabled and designed to be comfortable, the JBL Tune 510BT headphones also allow you to connect to Siri or Google without using your mobile device. Available in multiple fresh colors and foldable for easy portability, the JBL Tune 510BT headphones are a grab ‘n go solution that helps you to inject music into every aspect of your busy life. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 450 mAhProduct Weight 158. 7 gColour Name RoseConnection Type WirelessAverage Battery Life 11hrs - 16hrsUsage Type BusinessWhat's In The Box HeadphoneAudio Headphone Type Over-EarCharging Case Type WiredProduct Length 22. 3 cmProduct Height 22. 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 4. 8 cmFeatures Bluetooth, Voice Assistant, Volume ControlModel Number JBL-T510BTRSModel Name T510Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ec6a98f0-7025-4a67-a9b4-a126d5ad0cfd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eedd6207-48b7-4d46-9efd-452f5a921b67/web/3_1731498448528.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>126.85 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030063153832</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1072873220</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL GO 3 Portable Bluetooth Speaker Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltimate JBL Pro Sound: Enjoy signature JBL bass without any distortion. Port-anywhere: Feather light, ultra-portable grab-and-go designIP67 water-resistant and dust-resistant, Engineered to withstand splashes and sand. Quick-Connect: Experience your music and movies without any laggingMega Playtime: One single charge = upto 5 Hour battery backup under optimum audio settings. USB Type C charging. Charging time 2. 5hrsAnti-shine colour palette: Available in vibrant pure matte colors to help you make a statement anywhereThe compact JBL Go 3 packs quite a punch when it comes to its crystal-clear sound. Enjoy signature JBL bass at 4. 2W RMS without any distortion, no matter the audio range. Fusing the best of style and substance the Go 3 makes its mark with its edgy design, colorful fabrics, and expressive detailsOverviewJBL is a popular brand for home music aficionados, its brand is based on its role powering the sound of the world’s top musicians, athletes, and venues for more than seven decades. That said, JBL has a down-to-earth customer experience that focuses on helping people find the information they need about each product as well as complete support and specifications. An active Youtube and online community provide an array of answers to questions about its products. The love of music and appreciation for sound quality spans all age and demographic groups, bound only by one’s financial means or living situation, so the usual demographic rules do not apply to the JBL brand. While the obvious customer for JBL’s brand is in the higher income, people of all means make a stretch for brands they love. JBL has an active co-marketing strategy including programs with the Hard Rock Cafe the New York Yankees, Grammy’s and a Brand Ambassador program that includes an eclectic collection of leaders across the music, entertainment, arts and sports spectrum. Speakers, portable Bluetooth, home, party, smart, kids, car audio, marine, and professional; Headphones, wireless, in ear, over ear, sports, noise-cancelling, kids. JBL also has a complete line for professionals and venues. JBL serves the consumer home and professional market. The professional market includes studios, installed/tour/portable sound, cars, music production, DJ, cinema markets, etcSpecificationsProduct Weight 980 gColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box Portable Bluetooth SpeakersProduct Height 4 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 9 cmFeatures Lithium PolymerModel Number JBLGO3BLKModel Name JBLGO3BLKItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6da21f7a-1805-4a9b-94e2-56905e0e7efe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6e01baad-a09f-4dc1-a237-a9e36ccbe2e2/web/1_1731498644258.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>135 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010728732206</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3010429235</g:id>
      <g:title>Nintendo Switch Controller Splatoon 3 Edition</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsTake your game sessions up a notch with the Nintendo Switch Pro ControllerThis controller includes many of the features found in the Joy-Con controllers: Motion controls, HD rumble, built-in amiibo functionality and morePlay anyone, any time, anywhere with the Nintendo Switch Pro-ControllerCompatible with the Nintendo Switch onlySpecificationsColour Name Splatoon 3Type of Console Software Nintendo SwitchModel Number HAC-A-FSSKT-MSEModel Name HAC-A-FSSKT-MSE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/02982262-ca32-44c0-9a3c-72579122af53</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3b5b8822-53f8-45c7-8f5d-ea5d2b9a3cda/web/1_1731502018451.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>129 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030104292353</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
