<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>4785529343</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery Drone With 4K Camera For Adults Children RC Quadcopter With Four Way Obstacle Avoidance Follow Me Fly Altitude Hold My Ball</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsColour Name BlackVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pCamera Resolution 1080 MPModel Number H8Model Name H8 RC Mini Drone</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c6d61155-6362-49f0-b5af-914212fb79c0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/67603fd0-c48a-4cc8-88fe-55eeeb994b90/web/1_1724238210490.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047855293430</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>Docooler YG300 Portable QVGA LED 400 Lumens Projector With Remote Control YG300 White/Yellow</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAdopts LCD technology with more than 30000 hours of LED lifespanHigh quality multi-chip-coated optical glass lens provides better color reproduction, better transmittance and better temperature resistanceKeeps projection image in focus and color fidelity, much better than plastic lensGives you a clear frame and a projection size of up to 130 inches, you can also select the optimal size of image by adjusting the distance to obtain the best using experienceEquipped with dual built-in speaker that lets you enjoy audio from your videosThe device supports variety of videos, pictures and music formats. Also, its quality lumens helps you get high-definition and bright imagesIt will bring in the convenienence and unexpected great experiences in your daily life &amp;amp; work. Its Technology has 30000 hours of LED lifespan. Owing this portable projector lets you carry all your favorite movies and songs in your pocketIt is equipped with HD, USB, AV, Headphone jack and TF card slot, which makes it easy to connect with Laptop, PC, Smartphone, USB disk, TF Card, etcOverviewComes in compact portable size that is easy to operate and lasts long. The device supports variety of videos, pictures and music formats. Also, its quality lumens helps you get high-definition and bright images. It will bring in the convenienence and unexpected great experiences in your daily life &amp;amp; work. Its Technology has 30000 hours of LED lifespan. Owing this portable projector lets you carry all your favorite movies and songs in your pocket. Not only this, with this projector you can create and present impressive business presentation anytime, anywhere. Since it gives you a clear frame and a projection size, you also can select the optimal size of image by adjusting the distance to obtain the best experience. It is equipped with HD, USB, AV, Headphone jack and TF card slot, which makes it easy to connect with Laptop, PC, Smartphone, USB disk, TF Card, etc. Color Gamut: 100%NTS, Standard Interfaces: 1 x HD Port x AV Port x 3. 5 mm Earphone Port x Standard USB Port x TF Card Slot x Power Input port, Power Consumption: 24 W, Power Supply: 100~240V, 50/60Hz; Output: 12V / 1. 5ASpecificationsVideo Format 720pProduct Weight 245 gColour Name White/YellowUsage Type PersonalWhat's In The Box 1x Projector, 1x Remote ControllerAudio Jack No Audio JackIncludes Without ScreenProduct Length 4. 5 cmProduct Height 13 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 5 cmProjector Brightness 1000 lmModel Number YG300Model Name YG300</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/76776a1e-6046-4057-8a46-83805d1dc7e8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b67b3e96-63ae-43cc-a297-db77381b4acf/web/1_1724329034104.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Camera Stand Tripod Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAllows you to capture shake-free videos or photos with your smart phoneLegs with clip locks make set up quick and easy change. Lightweight tripod that doesn't t take up much roomThe rubber grips accommodate many phone sizes and once mounted into the spring-loaded holder the mini video tripod can easily beEasy to set up and store (just needs a few seconds)SpecificationsProduct Weight 450 gColour Name SilverProduct Length 35 cmProduct Width/Depth 0. 66 inFeatures Ergonomic, Travel, Business, PersonalModel Number Pstore1051Model Name Tripod Camera Holder</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/34ed9723-ea49-49a8-8d6e-8df301318a15</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e4411a6c-ee6e-475a-b1d0-ff5eba6c5343/web/2_1724318710330.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>21 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>YG-300 QVGA LED Projector 300 White/Yellow</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHigh-permeability lens increases light transmittance for immersive visualsHigh contrast ratio renders pictures in superior detail and clarity30,000 hours of lamp life accounts for a prolonged usageFeatures composite HDMI, AV and USB interfaces for you to play files directly from a source deviceComes with a reduced-noise fan which can lower the noise by halfSpecificationsProduct Weight 290 gColour Name White/YellowIncludes Without ScreenProduct Length 12. 5 cmProduct Height 4. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 5 cmProjector Brightness 1000 lmModel Number 300</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e82c49a2-adfb-413d-8cda-adbc7e997766</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eb0a2277-1bee-4bef-8145-1584dd4bec24/web/1_1724331253875.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Portable Monopod Tripod With Carry Bag Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsErgonomically designed to offer better gripCompact and sleek for easy portabilityDurably designed for prolonged useSpecificationsColour Name Silver/Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4be35023-baf2-4f31-9a2a-d8530912ddfd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/29bff2b7-fbf8-46e7-bd20-e1c5a62433b0/web/1_1724332790114.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>22.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1523348474</g:id>
      <g:title>PHLGHT LCD Mini Projector YG300 Basic Multicolour</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBright rooms are no match for this projector – this powerful yet affordable model delivers exceptionally bright yet colourful images with clear detailsIt utilises Epson’s renowned 3LCD technology, which produces an equally high White and Colour Light OutputDurable and affordable, this model's long-lasting lamp light source means you'll be able to project your content every day for six yearsPortable and quick to set up: Easy to position with keystone sliderSo smart and lightweight you can put it in your pocket or bag and travel with it multiple compatible devicesOverviewThe projector features a lamp that produces bright light to display and clarify the image details as closely as possible, an ideal resolution for viewing content, all you have to do is adjust the clarity in relation to the distance and the size of the display to enjoy unparalleled viewing. Portable projector is usually used for presentations and data show. Its small portable size enables you to take it with your bag, whether to display content to students in schools, universities and institutes, or at companies and inform employees about everything new through a suitable display. The projector comes with multiple plug and play ports, with the ability to play via multimedia audio and video together. Playing and viewing content is no longer easier than it appears now, all you have to do is connect the device and adjust the contrast of the image simply without much effort. SpecificationsNumber of Charging Ports 1 PortTV HDMI Ports 1Product Weight 484 gScreen Size 55 inDisplay Resolution 1440x1080Colour Name MulticolourDisplay Type LCDDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Windows 10Usage Type EducationalWhat's In The Box LCD Mini Projector</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cb6d9e1c-18b8-49e7-beca-a33cf90da763</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/51c12f90-785e-4d1b-aece-1365644aa36d/web/1_1724820296398.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>110 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015233484749</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Professional Camera Tripod Mount Stand Silver/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFeatures a pan-tilt-swivel head and removable mounting plateLightweight tripod stand with mobile HolderUltra compact, sturdy and durableNon-slip rubber feet for ideal useBuilt in level and quick level lockBest quality construction ensures a lasting useWe assure the authenticity and quality of our productsMade with premium quality material ensuring it's longevity and durabilityProfessional Camera Tripod Mount Stand. Features a pan-tilt-swivel head and removable mounting plateCompatible with most video cameras, digital cameras, still cameras, GoPro devices and smartphonesOverview Professional Camera Tripod Mount Stand. Features a pan-tilt-swivel head and removable mounting plate. Lightweight tripod stand with mobile Holder. Ultra compact, sturdy and durable. Non-slip rubber feet for ideal use. Built in level and quick level lock. Premium finish light weight professional tripod with adjustable height, multi level locking and steady rubberized legs. Compatible with most video cameras, digital cameras, still cameras, GoPro devices and smartphones. SpecificationsCharging Type Micro USBProduct Weight 450 gColour Name Silver/BlackConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box Complete Tripod UnitsCamera Lens Adjustment ManualCamera Flash Adjustment Manual AdjustmentSecondary Reflector NoProduct Length 6. 6 cmProduct Height 15. 2 cmProduct Width/Depth 19. 8 cmFeatures Business, Mechanical, Personal, Travel, Spill ResistantModel Number BTX-5Model Name BTX-5Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1850ec1b-ca20-46dc-b638-e0d495d3fb46</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/963701c3-6961-4ab3-803b-93110f877afc/web/1_1724257086716.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3184003887</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery Mini Photo Printer, Portable Thermal Printer For Android Or IOS APP, Inkless Printer Gift For Friends, Used In Home, Office, Study, Work</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMultifunctional thermal printer, support photo printing, label printing, card printing, document printing, web printing, perfect for study or daily work. BLE4. 0 BT wireless connection, just download the APP and connect, easy and quick; 200 DPI resolution, ensuring clear printing quality. One-button printing, quick and convenient; no ink needed, energy-saving and environmentally-friendly. Built-in 1000mAh large capacity rechargeable lithium battery, the stand-by time is very long, no trouble of low battery and frequent charging. Compact size and light weight, convenient for carrying; cute cat appearance design, a nice birthday gift or festival gift for boys and girls. SpecificationsColour Name Pink</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f732b56a-0062-4363-9286-8e50c3749f06</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/797f3663-b786-4f8f-b763-27df308aa3d4/web/1_1724765954890.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031840038878</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5342792939</g:id>
      <g:title>VISEART Sheer Velvet Pressed Powder Cream</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights Provides skin with an overall healthy glow and brightens your complexion Helps prepare a flawless base for a perfect makeup look Covers facial blemishes, dark circles and skin spots effortlessly Overview The highly pigmented formula of the Viseart Sheer Velvet Pressed Powder creates a medium to full-coverage and durably sets makeup for a long-lasting wear. Its lightweight texture blends perfectly into the skin for a shine-free, pore-less, photo-filter finish. Marketing Claim: Free of parabens, fragrance, sulfates, phthalates and mineral oil. Specifications Colour Name Cream Department Women Finish Sheer Target Skin Type Normal UV Protection High SPF Formation Powder Skin Tone Medium Skin Coverage Medium Model Number VVP103 Model Name VVP103</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/44ae6217-3fb3-4c53-ba04-dada3a0464d3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bdd2af69-06f8-44cd-92d1-a2155cad3224/web/1_1717410235444.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>VISEART</g:brand>
      <g:price>72 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053427929393</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8324987613</g:id>
      <g:title>VISEART Sheer Velvet Pressed Powder Cream</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights Provides skin with an overall healthy glow and brightens your complexion Helps prepare a flawless base for a perfect makeup look Covers facial blemishes, dark circles and skin spots effortlessly Overview The highly pigmented formula of the Viseart Sheer Velvet Pressed Powder creates a medium to full-coverage and durably sets makeup for a long-lasting wear. Its lightweight texture blends perfectly into the skin for a shine-free, pore-less, photo-filter finish. Marketing Claim: Free of parabens, fragrance, sulfates, phthalates and mineral oil. Specifications Colour Name Cream Department Women Finish Sheer Target Skin Type Normal UV Protection High SPF Formation Powder Skin Tone Medium Skin Coverage Medium Model Number VVP103 Model Name VVP103</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cba3cca4-5e5e-4f76-b33e-61c8be8ce353</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76423039-f96d-4387-9aab-a17d3403adc9/web/1_1717410325219.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>VISEART</g:brand>
      <g:price>72 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083249876131</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id></g:id>
      <g:title>Generic JF-3110 28-65cm Aluminum Alloy Tripod Portable Lightweight Travel 3-sections Stand w/Phone Holder 1/4inch Screw Hole for Projector Smart Phone Camera White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFeatures: 3-sections tripod, height adjustable from 28-65cm, with 3 legs, stable and safe. Constructed by high quality aluminum alloy, anti-rust and waterproof. Rotate the tripod head pan &amp;amp; tilt axis to find the best shooting or projecting angle. Use the rocker to shake the shaft, move stably and smoothly, stop it whenever you want. Suitable for multiple occasions, such as broadcastingSUITABLE FOR MULTIPLE OCCASIONS, SUCH AS BROADCASTING, TAKING PHOTOS, WATCHING MOVIES. MATERIAL: ALUMINUM ALLOYPAYLOAD: 2KG TRIPOD LEG DIAMETER: 1. 1CM HEIGHT RANGE: 28-65CM / 11. 02-25. 5IN ITEM WEIGHT: 320G / 11. 28OZ PACKAGE SIZE: 29 * 8. 5 * 8. 5CM / 11. 41 * 3. 34 * 3. 34IN PACKAGE WEIGHT: 370G / 13. 05OZ1 * TRIPOD 1 * STORAGE BAG 1 * MOBILE PHONE HOLDERSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number S14520a-59Model Name Tripod Portable Lightweight Travel 3-sectionsItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cf9708fd-32d8-4051-ad1b-e739db0dc4bb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/68cfe1e3-a76c-477e-8627-c8364807d82e/web/1_1724336463801.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>22.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0000000000000</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
