<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9569826239</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS + Cellular 42mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Ink Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSeries 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Ink Sport LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 MmModel Number MWX83QA/AModel Name MWX83QA/A, MWX83ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f33e89dd-50e4-4e13-a18e-a27dfd55315d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ef758824-7ce2-489c-8683-708d0892ef81/web/1_1730983321111.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2014 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095698262397</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8587650394</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 GPS + Cellular, 49mm Titanium Case With Medium (Band fits 145–190mm wrists.) Olive Alpine Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCarbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app. ECG app. High and low heart rate notifications. Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash Detection SirenUp to 36 hours. Up to 72 hours in Low Power Mode. Fast chargingPrecision dual‑frequency GPS, Cellular connectivity, Family Setup, Pair multiple watches with one iPhoneBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewApple’s brightest Always-On Retina display is easy to see, even in harsh sunlight. More room for adding complications to customize your watch face and enough space to view six metrics at once. Made for recreational water sports, scuba, and free diving for descents to 40 meters. The Depth app shows the time, current depth, water temperature, duration under water, and maximum depth you’ve reached. The Oceanic+ app puts a dive computer on your wrist. Ocean Band is light and flexible, with a titanium buckle and adjustable loop for a secure fit even during high-speed water sports. The Compass app delivers helpful views and details like elevation, incline, longitude, and latitude. See the last place where you had cellular reception. Mark your location with Compass Waypoints. Backtrack uses GPS to map where you’ve been so you can retrace your steps. Alpine Loop is an extremely rugged and secure band to meet the needs of all outdoor adventurers. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Olive Alpine LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size Small/MediumSmartwatch Dial Size 49 MmModel Number MREX3AE/AModel Name MREY3AE/A, MREY3LL/A, MREY3ZP/A, MREY3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7322b0f9-ef89-452b-a4ff-3e6be12f5bc2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c21a1b34-af9e-47c1-a83b-bc882ade247a/web/1_1730983471050.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2830 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085876503947</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8554963461</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Gen) 10.9 inch Blue 64GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 InPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System IOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number IPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber Of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number IPad (2022) Blue 64GB 5GModel Name IPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c7a057f-2846-4f94-951f-15f4da1c53fd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8b897ac1-de92-4229-8e8b-8c8b231600b6/web/1_1730983164213.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1630 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085549634619</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8366087543</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2021 (6th Generation) 8.3inch, 64GB, WiFi, 5G, Space Gray with Facetime - International version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAll-screen design with a stunning 21. 08-centimetre (8. 3-inch) Liquid Retina display with wide colour, True Tone and 500 nits of brightnessTouch ID integrated into the top button for fast, easy and secure authenticationEnjoy incredible performance and all-day battery life with the A15 Bionic chipUse the 12MP Ultra Wide front camera with Centre Stage for more natural video callsWi-Fi 6. Experience high internet speeds with the fastest Wi-Fi availableSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPProcessor Speed 2. 93 GHzRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5124 MAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 InPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space GrayCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System IOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2021Voice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A15 BionicNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name AppleNumber Of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraModel Number Apple IPad Mini 6th GenModel Name IPad Mini 2021 (6th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6f41b19e-a012-4cf3-88e6-031bfc048ca4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a91f472a-075a-4f34-a69e-ef9c94f2dade/web/1_1730983671850.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2215 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083660875430</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3516646819</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 GVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version IOS 18Operating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber Of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone FlashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 MmProduct Height 163 MmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 MmModel Number IPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name IPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5f540fb6-26f0-4b85-a000-2bf8636e0ff8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/942cec05-be8b-4d85-a1b4-fddb3c15eb4c/web/1_1730981571828.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035166468197</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3143530754</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Onyx Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEasy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Onyx BlackDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber Of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital CompassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 Mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b856d5d-a47e-41b7-9d88-1edb737ea928</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0581edb2-c147-48a9-a2d8-7e8a0abc24b9/web/1_1730983925005.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2390 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031435307549</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7434708333</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 MAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 GVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version IOS 18Operating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber Of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone FlashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 MmProduct Height 163 MmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 MmModel Number IPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name IPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c644e291-f1bc-4c53-9a86-3fd1365104f5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f45bea77-0b92-4841-88f0-eef33797d32c/web/1_1730981053215.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5949 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074347083330</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1258641134</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 MAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 GVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version IOS 18Operating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber Of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone FlashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 MmProduct Height 163 MmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 MmModel Number IPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name IPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2e0dac8c-c524-43df-ad1a-e2b306f5b432</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e1a174ae-e9b3-4a47-a674-24094e85d09e/web/1_1730982685923.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012586411347</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6639745102</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 MAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 GVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 InSIM Type Nano + ESIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version IOS 18Operating System IOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber Of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone FlashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 MmProduct Height 163 MmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 MmModel Number IPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name IPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/201e2d0d-8dea-4430-bbe0-332ff666fcac</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d2dad27c-977d-4029-ba3a-d5d49be8d6bb/web/1_1730980721056.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066397451023</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1379050073</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 1TB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 16 GBBattery Size 8000 MAhInternal Memory 1024 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 InPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type ESIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System IOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 Inches &amp;amp; AboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone FlashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof And Dust ProofModel Number IPad ProModel Name IPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/29010297-7b61-448c-b511-0af4bef02761</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6cd05175-e33b-4ec4-af5b-bfd3583478d0/web/1_1730982896742.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>6026 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013790500735</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
