<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>1289959462</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Single+eSIM Titanium Violet 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe legacy of Galaxy Note is alive and well. Write, tap, and navigate with the precision your fingers wish they had on the new, flat displayCapture stunning details with the most megapixels on a smartphone and AI processing. The enhanced ProVisual Engine recognises objects - improving colour tone, reducing noise, and bringing out detailWith 1. 6x larger pixels and a wider Tele OIS, photos and videos are brighter and more stable, making even distant subjects clearly stunning from sunup to sundown and everything in betweenSpace Zoom puts you in the middle of the action, even at night. With 1. 6x larger pixels and a wider Tele OIS, photos and videos are brighter and more stable — making even distant subjects clearly stunningWith massive capacity and greater energy efficiency, ultra's battery gives you extra life when it matters most you know, like the epic boss battle you've been gearing up forOverviewBehold the Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra smartphone, an exceptional amalgamation of incredible technology and superior sophistication. Whether you're typing up a storm or jotting something down, Note Assist makes a long story shortSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 8 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 3168x1440Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Titanium VioletDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature QuadFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24 UltraModel Name Galaxy S24 UltraPrimary Camera (MP) 200+50+12+10 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8f3fdc68-208a-4bf6-99ae-367647879bd9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3e25219e-9582-4093-8dc2-dc376799da05/web/1_1732186436220.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3290 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012899594621</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4219673045</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 ( 5th Generation) M4 11-Inch, 256GB, 5G, Silver With Standard Glass</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9d1886a3-9893-47d9-ae22-7dfb96064268</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1dcc4c13-9d8e-44c7-8a7d-6dcc69c56538/web/1_1732187256713.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4515.15 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042196730453</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9368461942</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 ( 5th Generation) M4 11-Inch, 512GB, 5G, Silver With Standard Glass</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/56f4bf90-cef8-4696-b451-acd86c846608</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0ca7abf7-de0d-46a0-ba31-332bf3f04a58/web/1_1732188524435.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093684619422</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4017335029</g:id>
      <g:title>Green Lion 360 Carsaca Plus Case with Normal HD Glass - Light Green</g:title>
      <g:description>Green Lion 360 Carsaca Plus Case with Normal HD Glass - Light Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e5e81d92-d725-4f23-bf82-55a4637b3429</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/44d239ea-712e-4188-a209-457a8a0c3a90/web/1_1732186755054.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040173350298</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7574568459</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 256GB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7162b39e-354a-42f6-bc6a-01c5de43c1e3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1aebd2d3-5313-4f7f-bb68-f69eb1138bf6/web/1_1732187555648.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075745684594</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2838302365</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d49be953-6e65-4653-aa22-901ea7080ecf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/54b8373b-3e7f-466d-83fe-9863ce9d162e/web/1_1732187728937.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4849 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028383023652</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8956048262</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/96e1811a-0390-42db-a847-e20531dd2174</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/56d7410e-6214-4094-be79-8f79d693e286/web/1_1732187792089.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4899 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089560482624</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5988585844</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d8a88d95-f55c-4bec-8ac5-38bbe5ec130b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/193207f1-2981-4372-beef-a02ab51aeb8a/web/1_1732188739280.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059885858442</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3723094870</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MTL83 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU: 14.2-inch</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 1 TBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MTL83LL/A / MTL83X/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6e2bfa90-27c5-4b9d-abc3-3a4ff364630b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/85c26c7c-7146-4925-9fdc-95046d8b5a82/web/1_1732189090540.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5990 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037230948703</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6578851358</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver shadow 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 1024 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/29550722-f66b-4558-bddd-e1dcd64d3653</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4275c144-3e2f-4007-b0ff-070917d0992b/web/1_1732189176757.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>6099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065788513586</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9501200765</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Blossom Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Blossom PinkProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9033f26b-786e-49da-9c62-13fd7245c216</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/412a86e4-4862-4fa2-8f09-770989da35af/web/1_1732112802423.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>285 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095012007659</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9306680001</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a11f1586-b279-4c29-b7e9-f6badd00d66b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d5178099-793e-494b-a81c-5193cba6cb74/web/1_1732192760093.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093066800011</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1362040968</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MRX33 Laptop M3 Pro chip with 11‑core CPU, 14‑core GPU: 14.2-inch</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 18 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRX33ZS/A / MRX33LL/A / MRX33X/A / MRX33HN/A / MRX33B/A/MRX33HN/A / MRX63B/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Pro chip with 11‑core CPU, 14‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ab52200f-2f63-409f-ba2d-a4e5a1483392</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a68057bb-747a-4852-8ab8-7061fb8de992/web/1_1732193200029.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>7099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013620409689</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3093856170</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/28772f37-e4be-4b4e-b7ca-98b9bb8148a0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d5b25149-1822-43db-976f-a568023141ba/web/1_1732192862457.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030938561700</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3444246855</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/53e4bf9c-89e1-4f6b-a46c-16643683ec48</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cc17a027-c46f-424b-a904-4b2d20928bf5/web/1_1732192972799.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034442468555</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8610749987</g:id>
      <g:title>Microsoft Surface Pro Edition Copilot+ PC 13 Inch OLED Display, Snapdragon X Elite Processor</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEngineered For Maximum Performance: Breeze through demanding multi-tasking and elevate your productivity, creativity, and entertainment experience! Microsoft Surface Pro (11th Edition) features the game-changing Snapdragon X Elite, one of the smartest and most efficient processors for Windows in its class. It also boasts 16GB LPDDR5X RAM with 3. 4 GHz max multithread frequency, offering supercharged performance, seamless responsiveness, stunning graphics, and low power consumption. AI Powerhouse: Unleash your full potential with the Snapdragon X Elite, featuring a Qualcomm AI Engine with an integrated Hexagon NPU to boost your creativity, elevate your video calls, fortify your security, and streamline your productivity. With blazing-fast speeds, Snapdragon X Elite can run generative AI LLM models over 13B parameters on-device. Plus, it supports Windows Studio Effects and various AI-accelerated applications to unlock endless possibilities. Smart &amp;amp; User-Friendly: Take advantage of next-level intelligence and convenience. Connect, stream, download, and sync efficiently with lightning-fast Wi-Fi 71 and HBS Multi-Link support. You can also enjoy smooth transitions between devices with Snapdragon Seamless, bask in incredible audio with the Snapdragon Sound™ Technology Suite, and get robust security with Qualcomm Secure Processing Unit – all designed to transform your user experience. Innovative Flexibility: Engineered to revolutionise your workflow, the Surface Pro perfectly merges the power of a laptop and the versatility of a tablet, all in one unit. Transform your device according to your needs, thanks to its iconic 165-degree fluid kickstand design and seamless compatibility with the Surface Pro Flex Keyboard (sold separately)2. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 3. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 2880x1920Colour Name DuneKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type PixelSenseDisplay Resolution Type QHDConnection Type HDMIAverage Battery Life 14 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version Windows 11 HomeOperating System WindowsUsage Type BusinessModel Series Microsoft Surface ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 12-CoreRAM Type DDR5External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number ZIB-00046Model Name Surface Pro 11 Copilot+ PCHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot YesNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version Qualcomm Snapdragon X Elite</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/73ece0be-13d4-479e-a75e-ff624b1cf125</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9556469c-9deb-4cae-ad31-6853f30ff5f0/web/1_1732193390720.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Microsoft</g:brand>
      <g:price>7285 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086107499879</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3547599967</g:id>
      <g:title>Dell G15 5511</g:title>
      <g:description>Selling my Dell laptop i5-11400H24 GB DDR4 RAMRTX 3050 4GB v-Ram2500 SSD NVMe storage 1920x1080 120 Hz display</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dce418fb-4e1b-4f75-8d16-891cdd218f5e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/18f99468-37c3-48d0-97a9-e95c677201f2/web/image_picker_E3637811-0DC4-4D5D-9673-C67094CE220E-8341-00000472B5DBC2AE.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Dell</g:brand>
      <g:price>3100 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035475999672</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7008259901</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max Physical Dual SIM 256GB Desert Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dd0352fd-efe1-43b6-88fb-f87c61680f6e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7796d611-262d-46e7-9c4e-39c451ac8f2e/web/1_1732107324515.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5050 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070082599013</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6650759263</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy F15 5G (Jazzy Green, 128 Gb) (6 Gb Ram)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights6 gb ram | 128 gb rom | Expandable upto 1 tb16. 51 cm (6. 5 inch) full hd+ display50MP + 5MP | 13MP front camera6000 mAh lithium ion batteryMediaTek dimensity 6100+ processorOverviewThe Samsung Galaxy F15 is a pinnacle of mobile brilliance, featuring a vibrant sAMOLED display for an immersive visual journey. Experience unmatched battery endurance, lasting up to two days, and revel in four years of hassle-free performance with a powerful MediaTek Dimensity 6100+ and up to 12 GB of RAM. Silence background sounds with noise cancellation, seamlessly share across devices, and enjoy superfast 5G speeds. Capture every detail with the 50 MP triple camera setup and have fun with the front-facing camera's creative features. Fortify your security with the Samsung Knox Vault Chipset and personalise your experience with Smart UI features. The Galaxy F15 redefines smartphone excellence in a compact and versatile package, catering to every aspect of a modern, connected lifestyle. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 217 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Jazzy GreenDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesWhat's In The Box Handset, Data Cable (USB Type C-to-C), Ejection Pin, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name MediaTekNumber of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassWireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 9. 3 mmProduct Height 160 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 8 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer,Fingerprint Sensor,Gyro Sensor,Geomagnetic Sensor,Light Sensor,Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-E156BLVGINSModel Name Samsung F15 5GPixels Per Inch 2340 x 1080 PixelPrimary Camera (MP) 50 + 5 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e552756c-f4ce-4204-9dbe-f9649500c117</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/79d56c37-9337-4551-b8fc-0f139b7ed705/web/1_1732106785739.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>569.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066507592639</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4902823409</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/54ea1db9-2812-45da-aa39-7f3cae5211c6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/48ab62c8-3312-4885-b282-91646856bbc9/web/1_1732107833082.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5300 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049028234097</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6557781231</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea CM822 8-Inch Smart Kids Tablet Single SIM 6GB RAM 256GB 5G Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThis 8"Inch WVGA Capacitive IPS touch screen LCD of CM822 android tab provides consistent and accurate colors from all viewing angles. Support 5. 0MP back camera and 2. 0MP front camera to take pictures or make video calls with powerful. Quad core processor provides an overall lag-free performanceOverviewThe C idea CM822 is a budget friendly tablet that will fit nicely in anyone's arms. It features a 8" WVGA IPS LCD screen. It has a TF card slot which allows you to expand the memory with up to an additional 64GB. The C idea CM822 features with a 2MP front camera and 5MP rear camera (Kids Version). SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPRAM Size 6 GBInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 319 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 8 inDisplay Resolution 800x1280Primary Camera Resolution 5 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type SIM (Standard)Connection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System Version Android 12Operating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 2 - 4. 9 MPVoice Calling Capability YesWhat's In The Box Android Tablet*1, UK Charger*1, Type-C cable*1, Screen Protector *1,Book Cover*1,OTG*1, Kids Watch*1,Touch Pen*1, TWS Bluetooth Headset*1,Colour Marker*6,Random Cartoon stickers*1,Sand painting*1,Key Ring*1,Finger Buckle*1 User Manual*1Network Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDBattery Type Lithium PolymerFinish PlasticProduct Length 206. 2 mmProduct Height 9. 2 mmProduct Width/Depth 129 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM822Model Name Kids TabletPrimary Camera (MP) 5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6fb275f0-5148-46be-b4ca-640f28c1fba1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a939d212-c2e5-4d9e-bfca-f1660c120e35/web/1_1732108411501.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>165 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065577812319</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5455855559</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Mini 99 Instant Film Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFive levels of brightnessProgrammed electronic shutterFill-in flash, Red-eye removal, Automatic Flash or Flash offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashClassic Finish designinstant camera draped effortlessly over your shoulderSelf-timer featureOverviewThe classic camera styling, The stunning tactile matte black finish, the sleek dials and buttons, every surface, edge and corner of this analog instant camera has been crafted to perfection. Turn the lens dial to power up your camera. Stop at Landscape Mode for distances, Macro for stunning close-ups or Standard Mode for everything in between. Digital cameras, lens, accessories film instant and single-use cameras and instant film; binoculars and sports optics; skin care. For a very large company, Fujifilm has retained a culture of innovation that has seen it through good times and bad. Think Fujifilm, think Green, sustainability, innovation, quality, fun, enrichment, and humility. This brand stands for innovation, quality, and humility. In fact, for such a big company with so many accomplishments, Fujifilm is low key. Despite an impressive record of innovation, commitment to sustainability, diversification, few people know of the company’s enormous accomplishments across so many spheres of business spanning the entire globe. Without fanfare, Fuji builds communities around its various products featuring stories of active users or opportunities to share information such as in its online Wonder Shop creative community or communities for its digital camera series in which enthusiasts can share , learn about anything, and even have their photography featured. The Fujifilm customer is not about flash, but substance. People buy Fujifilm for the features, the value, and the innovation, not to make a statement. The Fujifilm brand is smart, practical, innovative, individualistic. The company’s philosophy, it says, is based on the recognition that our mission…is to significantly contribute to the realization of a society in which all people across the world can lead lives that are abundant in spiritual as well as material wealth and with a sense of fulfillment and satisfaction. SpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number Instax Mini 99Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f91721ae-cde6-43c0-9ca8-aea25aceb3a2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/510ccc35-596c-4ee8-9970-da5573f4642a/web/1_1732115895164.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>807 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054558555598</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4031370225</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Amp Best Ever Wireless Amplifier AMPG1AU1BLK / AMPG1UK1BLK Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPower Everything - The versatile amplifier for powering all your entertainmentUpgrade your wired speakers - Connect everything from your turntable and stereo to your wired speakers to enjoy vinyl, CDs, stored audio files, and streaming You can even power outdoor speakers and expand your Sonos system to the gardenAmplify your TV experience - Enjoy stereo sound for shows, films, and video games when you connect Amp to your speakers and TV Wirelessly add a pair of Sonos One surrounds for an immersive home theatre experienceDesigned to keep cool - The rack-mountable design features a specially developed heatsink for optimised airflow and heat managementCreate an invisible sound system - Get brilliant sound without compromising space or design with Sonos Architectural by Sonance, a collection of in-ceiling, in-wall, and outdoor speakers optimised for AmpSpecificationsProduct Weight 2. 1 KGColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Sonos Amp, Sonos banana plugs (2), AC power cord, Quickstart Guide, and Legal BookletProduct Length 217 mmProduct Height 64 mmProduct Width/Depth 217 mmFeatures Internet, Wireless, SmartModel Number AMPG1AU1BLK / AMPG1UK1BLKModel Name Sonos Amp BlackNumber of HDMI Ports 0</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d6900515-9f3f-4d26-a40d-8f935297bbfe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9f737a39-6e07-43ef-97c8-6409e87f62da/web/1_1732121462488.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2899.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040313702253</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2921852150</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5 Dual SIM Phantom Black 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung Pay may not workOverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4235 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 3 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Phantom BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System AndroidFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 4K Ultra HDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Digital Compass, gyroscopeModel Number BSM-F946BE/2D / SM-F946B/DS / SM-F946NLBAKOOModel Name SM-F946BZKDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ba832abd-7e05-4e2f-9b95-2a691fd3f39a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/72f5b69c-c4db-4cbf-8262-d2e37e88da01/web/1_1732105323881.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3400 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029218521503</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4969944101</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy M15 5G (Blue Topaz, 128 GB) (6 GB RAM)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights6 GB RAM | 128 GB ROM16. 51 cm (6. 5 inch) Display50MP Rear Camera6000 mAh Batteryproximity sensor ProcessorOverview16. 39 Centimeters (6. 5"Inch) Super AMOLED Display with 19. 5:9 Aspect Ratio, FHD+ Resolution with 1080 x 2340 Pixels , 399 PPI with 16M Colors and 90Hz Refresh Rate 50MP (F1. 8) Main Wide Angle Camera + 5MP (F2. 2) Ultra Wide Angle Camera + 2MP (F2. 4) Macro Angle Camera | 13MP (F2. 0) Front Camera | Video Maximum Resolution of Full HD (1920 x 1080) @30fps Latest Android 14 Operating System having One UI 6. 1 platform with MediaTek Dimensity 6100+ Processor | 2. 2GHz, 2GHz Clock Speed with Octa-Core Processor Get a massive 6000mAh Lithium-ion Battery (Non-Removable) with C-Type Super Fast Charging (25W Charging Support) Get upto 4 Generations of AndroidOS Upgrades &amp;amp; 5 Years of Security Updates with Samsung Galaxy M15. Includes 1 Year Manufacturer Warranty for Device and 6 Months for In-Box Accessories. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 212 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name blueDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesWhat's In The Box mobile, User Manual, SIM Ejector Pin, Smartphone, Data Cable (Type C-to-C)Processor Name Octa-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080p (100fps), 1080p(30fps), 1080p(60fps), 1440P (30fps), 1440P (60fps), 4K (30fps), 720P(200fps)Wireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Sensor, Gyro Sensor, Geomagnetic Sensor, Light Sensor, Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-M156BModel Name SAMSUNG Galaxy M15 5GPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cec2e05c-958f-48c2-970b-69f07ad5e7df</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8ab70287-660b-4875-89a5-fbfb863a0b9d/web/1_1732106106354.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>554.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049699441015</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4388784881</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban Wearable x Skyler RW4010 601/MF-52 / Clear to Cerulean Blue Photochromic Lenses Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCamera Capture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban Meta Skyler smart glasses are designed to unlock new possibilities in how you see the world. The lightweight frame is integrated with wearable tech, so you can listen, call, capture and livestream without disconnecting from what’s happening around you. Drawing on our 60s archive and the Golden Age of air travel, the Skyler shape is inspired by an era of iconic jet-set style. Its wider front and gentle curves are designed to suit most faces. SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 5 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 150 mmProduct Height 41. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 52. 2 mmModel Number RW4010BK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/41c1ac22-2404-47f7-b297-ea4fea7bde85</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7386a785-84c2-4f46-baab-14958260bf9d/web/1_1732118866517.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1703.60 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043887848815</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5196293291</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea CM822 8-Inch Smart Kids Tablet Single SIM 6GB RAM 256GB 5G Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThis 8"Inch WVGA Capacitive IPS touch screen LCD of CM822 android tab provides consistent and accurate colors from all viewing angles. Support 5. 0MP back camera and 2. 0MP front camera to take pictures or make video calls with powerful. Quad core processor provides an overall lag-free performanceOverviewThe C idea CM822 is a budget friendly tablet that will fit nicely in anyone's arms. It features a 8" WVGA IPS LCD screen. It has a TF card slot which allows you to expand the memory with up to an additional 64GB. The C idea CM822 features with a 2MP front camera and 5MP rear camera (Kids Version). SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPRAM Size 6 GBInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 319 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 8 inDisplay Resolution 800x1280Primary Camera Resolution 5 MPColour Name BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System Version Android 12Operating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 2 - 4. 9 MPVoice Calling Capability YesWhat's In The Box Android Tablet*1, UK Charger*1, Type-C cable*1, Screen Protector *1,Book Cover*1,OTG*1, Kids Watch*1,Touch Pen*1, TWS Bluetooth Headset*1,Colour Marker*6,Random Cartoon stickers*1,Sand painting*1,Key Ring*1,Finger Buckle*1 User Manual*1Network Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDBattery Type Lithium PolymerFinish PlasticProduct Length 206. 2 mmProduct Height 9. 2 mmProduct Width/Depth 129 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM822Model Name Kids TabletPrimary Camera (MP) 5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cd18611d-21eb-48dd-8e27-3f80e4f15f4c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/31f374fb-2170-4d80-9c4c-936a9099600d/web/1_1732108060374.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>160 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051962932915</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9579353894</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray Ban Wayfarer RW4006 Shiny Black Frames With G15 Green Classic Lenses Direct To Social 12MP</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRay-ban | meta wayfarer ; Shiny black frames with G15 Green classic lenses. ;The latest in wearable tech with iconic Ray-Ban style. ;Try Classic Ray-Ban lenses with a uniform tint for consistent shade and a timeless aesthetic. ;A sun lens for outdoorDesigned for living in the moment; An icon of style from Hollywood to hip-hop, the Wayfarer never stands still. ;Embraced by the next generation of culture makers, its journey continues with AI-enhanced wearable tech. ;Listen, call, capture and livesDirect to social ;Choose to livestream directly from your glasses to Instagram and Facebook without missing the moment. ;Seamlessly switch between your glasses and phone cameras while sharing your unique POV. ;Livestream up to 30 mins12MP camera; Capture what you see and hear with a new ultra-wide 12MP camera and five-mic system. ;Take high-quality photos and immersive videos, or live stream it all on Facebook and Instagram. ;Rest assured, your media will never be posted or shareOpen-ear audio; Discreet open-ear speakers and five built-in microphones let you seamlessly switch between music and calls, while still allowing you to hear the ambient sound of your surroundingsMeta AI voice controlSpark creativity, get information and control features with your voice—just ask Meta AI so you don’t miss a beatSo if you're out grilling with a group of friends, you can ask: “Hey Meta—I’m grilling scallops, corn on the cob, and burgers—how long should I cook each of them?” “Hey Meta—what salad goes well with thatOr if you find yourself in a messy situation while finger painting with a toddler, you can ask: “Hey Meta—how do I wash finger paint off walls?” “Hey Meta—send a photo to Grandpa on WhatsAppWith voice control you can take photos/videos, make calls, send messages and more—it all starts with “Hey Meta. ”OverviewToggle between your phone and glasses camera when you videocall or livestream(1), so that everyone can experience your unique view of the world. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Everything is for your ears only, thanks to improved directional audio. SpecificationsModel Number RW4006Model Name RW4006</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/79350f87-d4e2-4889-861f-1065c0282dda</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8ac33d1f-db5a-43c1-b117-4dab818ef146/web/3_1732117966833.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1525.15 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095793538946</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4866270974</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 GPS + Cellular, 49mm Titanium Case With Medium (Band fits 145–190mm wrists.)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCarbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app. ECG app. High and low heart rate notifications. Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash Detection SirenUp to 36 hours. Up to 72 hours in Low Power Mode. Fast chargingPrecision dual‑frequency GPS, Cellular connectivity, Family Setup, Pair multiple watches with one iPhoneBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewApple’s brightest Always-On Retina display is easy to see, even in harsh sunlight. More room for adding complications to customize your watch face and enough space to view six metrics at once. Made for recreational water sports, scuba, and free diving for descents to 40 meters. The Depth app shows the time, current depth, water temperature, duration under water, and maximum depth you’ve reached. The Oceanic+ app puts a dive computer on your wrist. Ocean Band is light and flexible, with a titanium buckle and adjustable loop for a secure fit even during high-speed water sports. The Compass app delivers helpful views and details like elevation, incline, longitude, and latitude. See the last place where you had cellular reception. Mark your location with Compass Waypoints. Backtrack uses GPS to map where you’ve been so you can retrace your steps. Alpine Loop is an extremely rugged and secure band to meet the needs of all outdoor adventurers. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Olive Alpine LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size Small/MediumSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MREX3AE/AModel Name MREY3AE/A, MREY3LL/A, MREY3ZP/A, MREY3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7443945a-873e-4ca8-ae96-e77c7989326d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5e7ab3d5-8003-4e78-9f79-90c00679f3e0/web/1_1732121348546.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2812.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048662709749</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8895020931</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2021 (6th Generation) 8.3inch, 64GB, WiFi, 5G, Space Gray with Facetime</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAll-screen design with a stunning 21. 08-centimetre (8. 3-inch) Liquid Retina display with wide colour, True Tone and 500 nits of brightnessTouch ID integrated into the top button for fast, easy and secure authenticationEnjoy incredible performance and all-day battery life with the A15 Bionic chipUse the 12MP Ultra Wide front camera with Centre Stage for more natural video callsWi-Fi 6. Experience high internet speeds with the fastest Wi-Fi availableSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPProcessor Speed 2. 93 GHzRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5124 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space GrayCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2021Voice Calling Capability yesProcessor Number A15 BionicNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraModel Number Apple iPad Mini 6th GenModel Name iPad Mini 2021 (6th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d0220402-46bf-44d0-909a-3c7db951cf45</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c2914e8b-0dd5-40a2-babc-1c231fca805a/web/1_1732120352992.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088950209315</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2306537837</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Ice Blue 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome Ice BlueOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356ELBVMEA, SM-A356E/DSModel Name SM-A356ELBVMEA, SM-A356E/DSPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0acdf105-eb83-460b-ba99-c77f1d2f240e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a330a1a5-90a9-4225-949c-dad5067f86f0/web/1_1732110878954.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>935 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023065378372</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1067869925</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 200 LITE Starry Blue Dual SIM 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights108MP rear camera, portrait in the spotlightHonor 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your handExtra-large AMOLED view, boundless with brightness and clarityOverviewThe Portrait Master 108MP &amp;amp; 50MP Glorious Portrait Risk-free Dimming AMOLED Display Lightweight Drop-resistant Design 108MP Rear Camera, Portrait in the Spotlight 50MP Light-sensitive Selfie, Fantastic group photo Ultra-slim in Shape, Crafted in Style Drop-Proof, Trust Enhanced Risk-Free Dimming Eye-Care Display 256GB Ultra-large Storage Dynamic in Design, Elegant in Heart HONOR 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, Exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your hand. 6. 78mm Thickness 166g Weight Selfie Light 50MP Front Camera 108MP Main Camera f/1. 75 aperture Marco Camera f/2. 4 aperture Wide &amp;amp; Depth Camera f/2. 2 aperture AI Wide-angle Selfie 78° FOV mode works while taking selfies, and switches to 90° FOV mode whlie taking groupfies. Multi-focal Portrait, the Art of Boken The Rear camera features three focal choices, each showing a side of your unique charm. 108MP image,Uncompromising Clarity The 108MP HD Rear camera can capture the excitement of your life clearly and vividly. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4500 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Colour Name Starry BlueDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number 6080Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek DimensityNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number LLY-NX1Model Name HONOR 200 LITEPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4dff1f59-2f5b-41a5-b59c-a428b112f1cb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/869cfa21-d359-4315-89e2-5d9ff4b850b4/web/1_1732109971789.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>810 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010678699253</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5414139822</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A04e Dual SIM Light Blue 3GB RAM 32GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights720 x 1600 (HD+) PLS LCD Display13 MP Rear Camera with Digital Zoom Up To 10xand 5 MP Front CameraNano-SIM (4FF), MicroSD Upto 1TB and USB Type-C ChargerAccelerometer,Light Sensor,Proximity SensorSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 3 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 32 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEModel Year 2022Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1000 GBModel Number SM-A042FLBDMEA / SM-A042F/DSModel Name Galaxy A04ePrimary Camera (MP) 13+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/162ef352-656a-4914-a898-ccd0852c5b24</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bf0f4972-b35b-43c1-a45c-615524771329/web/1_1732109230605.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>275 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054141398229</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5070401699</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy F15 5G (Groovy Violet, 128 Gb) (6 Gb Ram)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights6 gb ram | 128 gb rom | Expandable upto 1 tb16. 51 cm (6. 5 inch) full hd+ display50MP + 5MP | 13MP front camera6000 mAh lithium ion batteryMediaTek dimensity 6100+ processorOverviewThe Samsung Galaxy F15 is a pinnacle of mobile brilliance, featuring a vibrant sAMOLED display for an immersive visual journey. Experience unmatched battery endurance, lasting up to two days, and revel in four years of hassle-free performance with a powerful MediaTek Dimensity 6100+ and up to 12 GB of RAM. Silence background sounds with noise cancellation, seamlessly share across devices, and enjoy superfast 5G speeds. Capture every detail with the 50 MP triple camera setup and have fun with the front-facing camera's creative features. Fortify your security with the Samsung Knox Vault Chipset and personalise your experience with Smart UI features. The Galaxy F15 redefines smartphone excellence in a compact and versatile package, catering to every aspect of a modern, connected lifestyle. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 6000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Groovy VioletDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesWhat's In The Box Handset, Data Cable (USB Type C-to-C), Ejection Pin, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name MediaTekNumber of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassWireless 5GFinish GlassModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer,Fingerprint Sensor,Gyro Sensor,Geomagnetic Sensor,Light Sensor,Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-E156BLVGINS, SM-E156B/DSModel Name Samsung F15 %GPixels Per Inch 2340 x 1080 PixelPrimary Camera (MP) 50 + 5 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eb5b7459-d2a9-4361-9448-a68db386f004</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d17ef9d4-af3c-42ee-a892-5a607a2514b4/web/1_1732106620396.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>569.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050704016999</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7165323199</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea CM822 8-Inch Smart Kids Tablet Single SIM 6GB RAM 256GB 5G Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThis 8"Inch WVGA Capacitive IPS touch screen LCD of CM822 android tab provides consistent and accurate colors from all viewing angles. Support 5. 0MP back camera and 2. 0MP front camera to take pictures or make video calls with powerful. Quad core processor provides an overall lag-free performanceOverviewThe C idea CM822 is a budget friendly tablet that will fit nicely in anyone's arms. It features a 8" WVGA IPS LCD screen. It has a TF card slot which allows you to expand the memory with up to an additional 64GB. The C idea CM822 features with a 2MP front camera and 5MP rear camera (Kids Version). SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPRAM Size 6 GBInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 319 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 8 inDisplay Resolution 800x1280Primary Camera Resolution 5 MPColour Name RedCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Micro SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System Version Android 12Operating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 2 - 4. 9 MPVoice Calling Capability YesWhat's In The Box Android Tablet*1, UK Charger*1, Type-C cable*1, Screen Protector *1,Book Cover*1,OTG*1, Kids Watch*1,Touch Pen*1, TWS Bluetooth Headset*1,Colour Marker*6,Random Cartoon stickers*1,Sand painting*1,Key Ring*1,Finger Buckle*1 User Manual*1Network Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDBattery Type Lithium PolymerFinish PlasticProduct Length 206. 2 mmProduct Height 9. 2 mmProduct Width/Depth 129 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM822Model Name Kids TabletPrimary Camera (MP) 5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4208a21d-a600-4e28-a712-55c3d1d4ed55</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/acc60baf-bc39-4a8c-9b4e-601dd12d01f7/web/1_1732108247824.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>165 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071653231998</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9776990998</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Dual SIM Titanium Violet 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe Samsung Galaxy S24 is universally use the new Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 across the world. The Galaxy S24 have AI-optimized main camera photos. Night mode is also better. Nightography Zoom will bring brighter nighttime photos with the zoom camerasThe Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra comes with emergency texting via satellite support over the 3GPP standard. OverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 8 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Titanium VioletOperating System AndroidNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number S24 Ultra Titanium Violet 12/512 International VersionModel Name S24 Ultra Titanium Violet 12/512 International VersionPrimary Camera (MP) 200+10+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/13d14494-fa06-41cd-85fa-326159003dd5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b13a461c-4694-4488-ba82-a588721b6eb3/web/1_1732106631615.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3650 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097769909989</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6589124673</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Dual SIM Pink 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b1c84944-063f-4df5-b146-86c9ddc98169</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ed795298-f905-43e3-bcf7-a215a6dc6362/web/1_1732106747542.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4250 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065891246739</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6113840651</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Dual SIM Navy 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name NavyDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f0f606e3-199c-49ba-a3d8-6e7c5e603333</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/db8b4d08-5336-4610-9f37-141006dd5b96/web/1_1732106826724.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4250 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061138406515</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7100296203</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Dual SIM Silver shadow 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 1024 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/29993314-c9a8-46be-9021-f5490ecb645f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/583b0f63-39b9-43b8-b2bf-f1f06b033ba2/web/1_1732107962743.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>5564.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071002962030</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1351581043</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 4G -International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Blue/BlackModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number Galaxy A15Model Name Galaxy A15</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6aa4fd1a-994d-463d-8d5f-af774565ad4b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ec92f139-38be-4ecb-9f70-eae5a6c30fd1/web/1_1732107949067.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>640 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013515810439</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4694680016</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Light Blue 8GB RAM 256GB 4G -International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A15 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A15 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Light BlueNetwork Frequency Band LTEModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number Galaxy A15Model Name Galaxy A15</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c0d819a0-965d-42d0-a1a7-6508f098e1f1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/247bb5f7-f342-4bf2-915b-70adb6f26e47/web/1_1732108117432.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>645 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0046946800168</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4617276392</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi A3 Dual SIM Midnight Black 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRefined and Stylish DesignSmooth 6. 71'' 90Hz Dot Drop displayMassive 5000mAh (typ) battery, and provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W chargingSecure fingerprint and AI face unlockSupports up to 1TB expandable storageOverviewThe ultra-thin design, paired with the clean flat frame, appears exquisite and stylish. Hold the phone with one hand to embrace trends and lightness. Provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W charging*. 5000mAh ultra-large battery, reducing battery life anxiety and ensuring full-day range. Powerful octa-core processor with a maximum CPU frequency of 2. 2GHz, more balanced performance, reduced lags, and more fun to enjoy. You can choose the side fingerprint or AI face to easily unlock your phone. Suitable for more unlocking scenarios, safer and more convenient. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 71 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Midnight BlackDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 14Processor Number G36What's In The Box Mobile Phone | Adapter | USB Type-C Cable | SIM Eject Tool | Quick Start Guide | Safety InformationNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pNetwork Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 168 mmProduct Height 8. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 3 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number 23129RN51XModel Name Redmi A3 (4+128)Primary Camera (MP) 8+0. 08 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/89ecb0e2-1ac2-4ad9-be17-1d13afa9b7ec</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b8d880f3-b2cf-41b9-8707-c632482a8ac3/web/1_1732108475607.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>295 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0046172763923</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1087136569</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Blue Black 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Blue BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZKDMEA, SM-A256E/DSNModel Name BSM-A256E/1D6NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/af1c68d5-489f-490c-8224-1822733764ae</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f08e6c91-5bb6-44b6-9139-d862898e998c/web/1_1732108875192.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>670 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010871365696</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8607773838</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Light Blue 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FLBIMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/86161ddd-ad5a-45b2-bd0d-6b497077027d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/36951706-2b46-4d83-b52f-4ca9b5c17802/web/1_1732108422156.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>645 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086077738381</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2857009082</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea Smart Android Tablet</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThis 8"Inch WVGA Capacitive IPS touch screen LCD of CM815 android tab provides consistent and accurate colors from all viewing angles. Afixed a tempered glass on tablet screen for durable. In this tablet uses the Android 12. 0 operating system. Powerful and energy-efficient Quad-core processor,which has a more energy-efficient operation method and faster processing speed than previous generations of systems and chips. The tablet has 5MP front + 8MP rear cameras to record the beautiful pictures in life, also allows you to use smooth video chat and Zoom App by calling. This 8'' tablet is very light, and can be held in one hand. Tablet PC comes with an extra case that protects it well. Protect the tablet from scratches, drops, shocks, etc. In this leather case has folding feature to make stand keep on table. OverviewCidea Cm815 WVGA Capacitive IPS Touch Screen LCD 1080p Full HD, Lithium Polymer battery allowing you to enjoy reading, watching TV shows, surfing the web, playing light games and more, providing over 4 to 5 hours of mixed use. It also has an TF card slot that can be plugged into 64GB of expanded memory, can more store lots of music, pictures, videos. In this device have only one SIM card slot, and therefore, can only have one mobile network service active at a time. The compact and thin body can be easily put into a pocket backpack and carry it with you, suitable for any scene such as travel, business, home, and outdoor. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPRAM Size 6 GBInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 324 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 8 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name PurpleCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Micro SIMDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 12. 0What's In The Box Android Tablet*1, UK Charger*1, USB to Type-C cable*1,OTG*1, Kids Watch*1,Touch Pen*1,Bluetooth Wireless Earbuds*1,Key Ring*1, User Manual*1, Warranty card*1 , Screen Protector*1, Flip Case Cover*1Network Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pBattery Type Lithium PolymerFinish PlasticProduct Length 20. 6 cmProduct Height 1. 08 cmProduct Width/Depth 12. 3 cmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM815Model Name C idea CM SeriesPrimary Camera (MP) 8. 0</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a3fc915a-029a-4386-89a3-61b8343af526</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/74bfbc22-de96-41ea-a11e-d7c60b71da9e/web/1_1732108802170.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>170 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028570090825</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8643080927</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro Dual SIM Forest Green 8GB RAM 256GB - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS120Hz FHD+ amoled displayImmersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels67W turbo charging with 5000mAh typ batteryMediaTek helio G99-ultraOverviewUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS |120Hz FHD+AMOLED display | Immersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels | 67W turbo charging with 5000mAh (typ) batterySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 187 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 67 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Forest GreenDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 13Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number 7th_generation_intel_kaby_lake_7y30_processor 4nmFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile Phone/ Adapter/ USB Type-C Cable/ SIM Eject Tool/ Protective Case/ Quick Start Guide/ Warranty Card/ Safety informationNetwork Frequency Band LTENumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleCondition NewProduct Length 161. 1 mmProduct Height 74. 95 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 256 GBSensor Proximity Sensors, ambient_light_sensor, AccelerometerModel Number 23117RA68GModel Name Redmi Note 13 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 200MP+8MP+2MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6419bf3e-2293-4083-ba56-08bd357847ee</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5cb12bce-6823-4f57-8864-620964390b4f/web/1_1732109127141.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086430809277</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4059132785</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea 5G Android Tablet CM813 Pro </g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights• C idea 8" inch tablet is thin and light, making it portable for anywhere use. This WVGA IPS screen makes your images more crisp and delicate. It enables you to view pictures and videos with the high definition visual enjoyment. • The CM513 Pro Pro smart tab has a powerful Quad Core CPU can run many applications faster and smoother. • With 5MP back camera and 2MP front camera, you can get high quality pictures anytime and anywhere. OverviewC idea 8" Android Smart Tablet CM813 Pro is your gateway to the internet. It offers a High Quality IPS Touch Screen that is easy to navigate. The Quad Core Processor enables you to open apps and programs on the go. The 2. 0 MP Front and 5. 0 MP Back camera capture every precious moment. The 6GB RAM and 256GB ROM store all your important documents and photos. The TF Card upto 64GB is expandable. The 5G LTE, WIFI, Bluetooth enables seamless connectivity. The ZOOM Supported Camera captures the smallest of details with perfect clarity. ●Item : 8" Smart Tablet PC ●Brand: C idea ●Model : CM813 Pro Specification: •Network : 5G LTE/Wifi •Display : 8" inch WVGA Capacitive IPS Touch Screen(600*1024) •Operating System : Android •CPU: MTK •Chipset : Quad Core •Flash+Ram : 256GB+6GB •Expandable Memory : Up to 64GB •Support Zoom : Yes •Camera : Front - 2MP Back - 5MP •Flash Light: Yes •Wi-Fi Support : Yes •Bluetooth Connect : Yes •Face Recognition : Yes •Power Input : 5V/2A •Dimension : 10. 8mm Slim BodySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPRAM Size 6 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8 inDisplay Resolution 1024x600Primary Camera Resolution 5 MPColour Name GreyCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 2 - 4. 9 MPModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTENumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraFlash LEDBattery Type Lithium PolymerProduct Length 12. 6 cmProduct Height 1. 08 cmProduct Width/Depth 21. 1 cmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM813 ProModel Name C idea CM Series</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b4899361-d446-4b42-8783-ea9cb9dcf6a7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5748e614-a67a-4567-bb3a-9ba02f98555b/web/1_1732109298211.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>179.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040591327858</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2852515165</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 9A Dual Sim Lake Green 4GB RAM 64GB 4G - Chinese Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAndroid 10, MIUI 12MediaTek MT6762G Helio G25 (12 nm)microSDXC (dedicated slot)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Chinese VersionScreen Size 6. 53 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Lake GreenDisplay Type IPS LCDOperating System AndroidProcessor Number MT6762GNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDModel Year 2020Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number 9AModel Name Redmi 9APrimary Camera (MP) 13 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f327c2e2-2740-498f-bcb3-49235ec843d1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d495024d-884a-46bb-a5d1-3a46fc459266/web/1_1732109364769.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>269.35 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028525151656</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7719905831</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Blue BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZKHMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b25c1a74-6f43-4ea1-9e96-b7da7bd6f2e5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2b8b02a5-a7b9-4f0c-bbe0-057e946c0b5a/web/1_1732109676304.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>745 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077199058310</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7859361151</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 10A Dual Sim Charcoal Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G - Chinese Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAndroid 11, MIUI 12. 5Fingerprint (rear-mounted), accelerometer, proximityMediaTek MT6762G Helio G25 (12 nm)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Chinese VersionScreen Size 6. 53 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Charcoal BlackDisplay Type IPS LCDOperating System AndroidProcessor Number MediaTek MT6762G Helio G25 (12 nm)Network Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDModel Year 2022Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number RM10A-4G-64GB4GB-BLKModel Name Redmi 10APrimary Camera (MP) 13 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5d600c4c-d38c-4fb0-acae-526c139ca6f3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aa1c97d4-89df-46ec-903c-15daf396a032/web/1_1732109592907.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>250.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078593611514</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8972019684</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 200 LITE Cyan Lake Dual SIM 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights108MP rear camera, portrait in the spotlightHonor 200 lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your handExtra-large AMOLED view, boundless with brightness and clarityOverviewThe Portrait Master 108MP &amp;amp; 50MP Glorious Portrait Risk-free Dimming AMOLED Display Lightweight Drop-resistant Design 108MP Rear Camera, Portrait in the Spotlight 50MP Light-sensitive Selfie, Fantastic group photo Ultra-slim in Shape, Crafted in Style Drop-Proof, Trust Enhanced Risk-Free Dimming Eye-Care Display 256GB Ultra-large Storage Dynamic in Design, Elegant in Heart HONOR 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, Exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your hand. 6. 78mm Thickness 166g Weight Selfie Light 50MP Front Camera 108MP Main Camera f/1. 75 aperture Marco Camera f/2. 4 aperture Wide &amp;amp; Depth Camera f/2. 2 aperture AI Wide-angle Selfie 78° FOV mode works while taking selfies, and switches to 90° FOV mode whlie taking groupfies. Multi-focal Portrait, the Art of Boken The Rear camera features three focal choices, each showing a side of your unique charm. 108MP image,Uncompromising Clarity The 108MP HD Rear camera can capture the excitement of your life clearly and vividly. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4500 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Colour Name Cyan LakeDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number 6080Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek DimensityNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number LL-NX1 , LLY - NX1Model Name HONOR 200 LITEPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/00a07989-777a-4a48-bf0b-fe15125b762a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aaf413fe-b884-47c5-a9db-f37898297647/web/1_1732110087181.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>810 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089720196842</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9719755744</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Ice Blue 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome Ice BlueOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356ELBPMEA, SM-A356E/DSModel Name SM-A356ELBPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9798c33b-a356-48bb-b10d-f5f41428c58b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5db893da-684f-4362-876b-20789d81059b/web/1_1732110228755.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>825 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097197557448</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8826472695</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor X9b Dual SIM 5G Sunrise Orange 12GB RAM 256GB - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 1. 5K Retinal Resolution / SGS 5-star Whole-device Drop Resistance Certification / 5-fold Eye Protection[12GB RAM + 25G GB Memory] Enjoy great performance &amp;amp; plenty of room for photos, movies, songs, and apps—and 20GB Super large memory(RAM Turbo)108MP Lossless Capture Camera, 108MP main Camera/ Motion Capture/ 3X lossless Zoom[Superfast 5G performance] Unleash entertainment at 5G speed with the Qualcom Snapdragon, a powerful octa-core processor with frequencies up to 2. 1GHz[Massive battery and speedy charging] Work and play nonstop with a long-lasting 5800mAh battery, then recharge quicklyOverviewA luxury look and Xtra power, Honor X9b 5G is designed to stand out with HONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 360° Anti-Drop Protection, 6. 78" Amoled+ 120Hz display. Capture incredibly clear photos and smoother videos with a 108MP+5MP+2MP camera system featuring motion capture &amp;amp; 3X lossless zoom. Honor X9b 5G is a device you will fall in love with at first touchSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5800 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 185 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 78 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Sunrise OrangeDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number Qualcomm snapdragon SM6450Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Charger, USB Type-C cable, guides, SIM toolNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 163. 6 mmProduct Height 75. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Accelerometer, Proximity SensorsModel Number ALI-NX1Model Name X9bPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b4316e25-ede7-48b1-a836-96daf435eef8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/21c08448-af7d-4e48-935f-88af8c13ee3a/web/1_1732111047324.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>940 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088264726959</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4024038048</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Mini Instant Film Stone Gray Border, 10 Shot Pack, Suitable For All Instax</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsProduce instant credit card sized photos, print size 54 (W) x 86 (H) mm image size 46 (W) x 62 (H) mmSuitable for all instax mini series cameras, mini SHARE and Link printers and LiPlay and EVO Hybrid camera/smartphone printerUses real film technology, with vibrant colour reproduction for years and yearsFas picture development ISO 800 film with borderCartridge contains 10 shotsOverviewmini film with coloured borders. Each pack contains 10 shots of high quality credit-card sized photos that you can fit into a purse, wallet, or mini photo frame. Incredibly sharp pictures thanks to the high-speed ISO 800 film made for the instax mini- series cameras and smartphone printers. Recognised for its high quality colour reproduction, this instax mini film has a glossy finish, simple to use and easy to load with a print size 54 x 86 mm, image size 46 x 63 mm. SpecificationsColour Name grayModel Number 16754043</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/87743ad1-5100-4bb0-a7c2-4d2d66aa5e0d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/66c5e27d-7b3b-496b-8789-e95ce04979e6/web/1_1732112313509.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040240380487</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6235260464</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 90 Lite Dual Sim Midnight Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights100 MP ultra camera, 6. 7 inch edgeless eye comfort displayLight, slim and long lasting 4500mAh8GB + 256GB large storageOverviewLight, slim &amp;amp; long lasting 4500 mAh, 100 mp masterpiece just a snap away, large storage, edgeless eyecomfort display, honor 90 lite midnight blackSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 1 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4500 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 179 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Midnight BlackDisplay Type LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System AndroidOperating System Number 13Processor Number 6020Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name MediaTek DimensityNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology SapphirePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1920x1080pAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GProduct Length 162. 9 mmProduct Height 7. 48 mmProduct Width/Depth 74. 5 mmSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Digital Compass, gyroscopeModel Number CRT-NX1Model Name Cartier-N31EPrimary Camera (MP) 100+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/16d071cf-b1e2-4f13-b07b-5b336a74a0b2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/63dd4c9e-e1da-462e-bce1-a2e7cfe1d4fc/web/1_1732111164341.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>650 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062352604640</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4087827225</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Lilac 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome LilacOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356ELVPMEAModel Name SM-A356ELVPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/752b1c17-9296-4e69-a700-3eecc8c94fbf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/189a4705-70fb-46f8-9736-b329c5910e44/web/1_1732110638434.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>825 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040878272253</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4547602440</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Mint Green</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Mint GreenProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/171345bd-a3d5-4e15-869c-4784fab4adf8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fe02f396-2fb0-4bf8-8b8f-713549d1723e/web/1_1732112593989.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>274.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045476024402</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5977180854</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Pal Digital Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPocket-friendly design in five exciting colorsWide-angle lens for more expansive and creative shotsMulti-use detachable ring for a better hold, remote shooting, and a viewfinderBluetooth transfer for easy image sharing and editing. Lithium-ion battery with USB Type-C chargingLithium-ion battery with USB Type-C chargingBluetooth TransferSmartphone App comes with 18 filtersOverviewThe one and only Instax Pal, a super small digital camera, eager to capture small spontaneous moments, helping to make them feel powerful. Then, when you are ready for the big reveal, transfer your images (Pal can store 50 maximum) to your smartphone via Bluetooth. Select the camera roll on the Instax Pal app to transfer, add one of 18 filters, text or decorate with stickers, you can even select the size of your mini, square, wide, film before printing images via your Instax Link printer. SpecificationsColour Name GreenModel Number Instax Pal</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/75fe6256-43ef-4527-8c19-9c455ddcb1ca</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/44b9eb58-27e1-4ddf-ad82-8b87ae8dd5e3/web/1_1732113418920.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>375 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059771808544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4468643162</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Pal Digital Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPocket-friendly design in five exciting colorsWide-angle lens for more expansive and creative shotsMulti-use detachable ring for a better hold, remote shooting, and a viewfinderBluetooth transfer for easy image sharing and editing. Lithium-ion battery with USB Type-C chargingInternal memory and microSD/micro SDHC card storage optionsBluetooth TransferSmartphone App comes with 18 filtersOverviewThe one and only Instax Pal, a super small digital camera, eager to capture small spontaneous moments, helping to make them feel powerful. Then, when you are ready for the big reveal, transfer your images (Pal can store 50 maximum) to your smartphone via Bluetooth. Select the camera roll on the Instax Pal app to transfer, add one of 18 filters, text or decorate with stickers, you can even select the size of your mini, square, wide, film before printing images via your Instax Link printer. SpecificationsProduct Weight 41 gColour Name WhiteProduct Length 4. 23 cmProduct Height 4. 43 cmProduct Width/Depth 4. 3 cmFeatures Removable Memory CardModel Number Instax PalItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/03096185-26a1-4e08-980e-5f89d6efe986</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e45f625e-39e5-4d82-ad67-21ddb852fb40/web/1_1732113499523.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>375 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044686431628</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9469536486</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Mini 40 Instant Film Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAutomatic Exposure- Mini 40 automatically adjusts to surrounding brightnessSelfie Mode- simply pull out the lens and start taking selfiesSelfie Mode also captures close up shots clearly, Close up range- 30 to 50 cmsSuperior Design- high quality texture and premium silver accentsFilm Size- 62 mm × 46 mmFor a very large company, Fujifilm has retained a culture of innovation that has seen it through good times and badOverviewDigital cameras, lens, accessories film instant and single-use cameras and instant film; binoculars and sports optics; skin care. For a very large company, Fujifilm has retained a culture of innovation that has seen it through good times and bad. Think Fujifilm, think Green, sustainability, innovation, quality, fun, enrichment, and humility. This brand stands for innovation, quality, and humility. In fact, for such a big company with so many accomplishments, Fujifilm is low key. Despite an impressive record of innovation, commitment to sustainability, diversification, few people know of the company’s enormous accomplishments across so many spheres of business spanning the entire globe. Without fanfare, Fuji builds communities around its various products featuring stories of active users or opportunities to share information such as in its online Wonder Shop creative community or communities for its digital camera series in which enthusiasts can share , learn about anything, and even have their photography featured. The Fujifilm customer is not about flash, but substance. People buy Fujifilm for the features, the value, and the innovation, not to make a statement. The Fujifilm brand is smart, practical, innovative, individualistic. The company’s philosophy, it says, is based on the recognition that our mission…is to significantly contribute to the realization of a society in which all people across the world can lead lives that are abundant in spiritual as well as material wealth and with a sense of fulfillment and satisfaction. SpecificationsProduct Weight 330 gColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Instant CameraBattery Type Li-ion PolymerCamera Zoom Type DigitalProduct Length 104 mmProduct Height 121 mmProduct Width/Depth 65 mmCamera Resolution 2 MPModel Number Mini40Model Name Mini40Item Quantity 1Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4596968a-670c-41c7-963a-8672539019fe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3b485a34-beb4-43f4-80de-38ca3eda2558/web/1_1732113986910.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>468.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094695364868</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1764104206</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Beam (Gen 2) Smart Soundbar BEAM2AU1 / BEAM2UK1 White</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights3D Audio with Dolby AtmosHDMI eARC CompatibilityNFC Capabilities, Night Sound, Trueplay, In-built MicrophoneSpecificationsProduct Weight 2. 8 gColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box Sonos Beam (Gen 2), Power Cable, 1x HDMI Cable (4. 9 ft/1. 5 m), 1x Optical Audio Adapter, DocumentationProduct Length 65. 1 cmProduct Height 10 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 9 cmFeatures SmartModel Number BEAM2AU1 / BEAM2UK1Model Name BEAM2AU1Number of HDMI Ports 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8a0b1fb9-3946-4fec-a9eb-f1eacaa626eb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/17739f05-ab77-4473-b204-11a530f87200/web/1_1732120011551.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2088 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017641042061</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2998180465</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban Meta Wayfarer RW4008 670683 53 - Shiny Caramel Polar Brown</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRay-Ban Style with Meta Technology Iconic style, cutting-edge technology and light-weight form unite in a range of frames designed for living in the moment while expressing yourself to the max. Versatile Lens Options High performance lenses are available in sun, polarized or Transitions® lenses. All lenses offer advanced clarity, comfort, and 100% UVA &amp;amp; UVB protection. Prescription lens compatible. Built-in HD Camera Capture high-quality photos and videos with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Meta AI Voice Control Spark creativity, get information and control features with your voice—just ask Meta AI so you don’t miss a beat. *Open-Ear Audio Discreet open-ear speakers let you enjoy rich audio quality, music and calls, while keeping you connected to the world around you. OverviewMeet the next generation of smart glasses. The Ray-Ban Meta collection combines iconic design with cutting-edge technology. Capture life's best moments with an upgraded 12MP camera and five-mic system. Livestream your view of life’s best moments to Instagram and Facebook. Stay connected with hands-free calls and messages and listen to your favorite tracks through built-in speakers. Because no one sees the world like you do, express yourself with the most unique perspective there is - yours. SpecificationsColour Name Shiny Caramel Polar BrownModel Number RW4008Model Name RW4008</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cbdf73a6-222e-4f34-8e5e-0802eb4feb5c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/db486535-6637-4df2-bfc4-c59558391172/web/1_1732118488171.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1625 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029981804650</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9336045552</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Yellow 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name YellowOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZYHMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6d022ef9-81cb-4c07-bb43-ecbcc0c6c09c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c2577514-56b8-452e-8eb4-d1b706ecf66d/web/1_1732109536979.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>735 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093360455528</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2563890837</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Mini Plain Film 80 pack</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCapture life's moments instantly with this pack of 80 Fujifilm Instax Mini Plain Film, tailored for all Instax mini cameras and the Instax SHARE SP-2 Smartphone Printer. *Contains 80 sheets. - Abundant supply for all your photographic adventures. - *High-quality prints. - Delivers stunning instant photos that fit perfectly in wallets or frames. - *Professional-grade technology. Ensures vivid colours and sharp details in every shot. - *Hi-Speed ISO 800. - Captures images in vibrant colour with exquisite grain quality. - *Universal compatibility. - Perfect match for Fujifilm Instax Mini Cameras and SHARE SP-2 Printers. Vivid memories in instant clarity Engineered with Hi-Speed ISO 800 film, it captures your moments in brilliant colour and remarkable detail. Each shot is a celebration of vibrant hues and clearcrisp images,Instant satisfaction, lasting impressions Gone are the days of waiting for photos to develop. Fujifilm's cutting-edge film technology prints your pictures in seconds, offering you instant gratification without compromising on quality. OverviewInstax Mini Film is for all Instax mini cameras. It offers stunning instant pictures that you can fit into a purse, wallet or mini photo frame. Compatible with all FUJIFILM Instax Mini Cameras &amp;amp; Instax SHARE SP-2 Smartphone Printers. SpecificationsColour Name whiteModel Number 85433</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/83396ddb-1a30-4611-a163-725d9f92d267</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5bf85427-8fa1-4638-b799-736e09c04c7c/web/1_1732112907826.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>315 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025638908375</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7205770136</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Move - Portable Speaker Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGet brilliant sound anywhere with the weatherproof and drop-resistant Move. Control with your voice, the Sonos app, and Apple AirPlay 2 at home, and stream via Bluetooth when WiFi isn't available. Enjoy surprisingly rich bass, a wide soundstage, and automatic Trueplay tuning, which continually adapts the sound for where you are and what you’re listening to. Get brilliant sound anywhere with the weatherproof and drop-resistant Move. The Google Assistant and Amazon Alexa are built right in so on WiFi you can play music, check news, set alarms, get your questions answered, and more, completely hands free. Stream over WiFi and connect Move to the rest of your Sonos system at home. Switch to Bluetooth when you're offline. With an IP56 rating, Move stands up to humidity, rain, snow, dust, salt spray, UV rays, and extreme heat and cold. Enjoy thousands of stations, including live radio and exclusive programming, on your system through the Sonos app. Get up to 11 hours of battery life. Set the speaker on the included indoor charging base for quick power whilst you listen, and get power wherever you need it with an additional charging base. OverviewListen AnywhereThe durable, battery-powered smart speaker for outdoor and indoor listening. Get brilliant sound anywhere with the weatherproof and drop-resistant Move. Control with your voice, the Sonos app, and Apple AirPlay 2 at home, and stream via Bluetooth when WiFi isn't available. Finely tuned to your surroundingsEnjoy surprisingly rich bass, a wide soundstage, and automatic Trueplay tuning, which continually adapts the sound for where you are and what you’re listening to. Voice ControlThe Google Assistant and Amazon Alexa are built right in so on WiFi you can play music, check news, set alarms, get your questions answered, and more, completely hands free. WiFi and BluetoothStream over WiFi and connect Move to the rest of your Sonos system at home. Switch to Bluetooth when you're offline. Weather-resistantWith an IP56 rating, Move stands up to humidity, rain, snow, dust, salt spray, UV rays, and extreme heat and cold. Simple rechargingGet up to 11 hours of battery life. Set the speaker on the included indoor charging base for quick power whilst you listen, and get power wherever you need it with an additional charging base. Introducing Sonos RadioEnjoy thousands of stations, including live radio and exclusive programming, on your system through the Sonos app. SpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number MOVE1UK1BLKModel Name MOVE1UK1BLK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7535ac67-5ec4-4c2d-bb97-26a456393c6d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2cf6270a-4f8b-4a8e-83bc-1d77641aa247/web/1_1732117806138.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1465 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0072057701360</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6095907420</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban Meta Wayfarer RW4006 601ST350 - Polar Gradient Graphite</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAi Technology - Spark your creativity, get information, and control your glasses just by saying “Hey Meta”2. Ask Meta AI3 to get what you need and never miss a beatAudio - Seamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. thanks to improved directional audioControls - Unlock a range of hands-free possibilities with voice command2 – call and message, capture content, and manage media settings with your phone in your pocketCharging Case - Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to eight more charges on the go4 – means you can focus on your day without interruptionOverviewExperience the intersection of style and performance with Ray-Ban RAY-BAN | META WAYFARER. These square-shaped glasses feature a matte black frame that offers a sleek and modern look. The polarized lenses, in graphite color with gradient treatment, provide excellent protection against glare and enhance your vision. The gradient transition from top to bottom adds a touch of elegance to these shades. SpecificationsColour Name Polar Gradient GraphiteModel Number RW4006Model Name RW4006</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/12f27a55-e02a-4266-9e3b-fec9089a77e3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5c523ca6-911d-4e20-98e9-c209d152b8b1/web/1_1732118412796.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1610.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060959074200</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6980676540</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban Wearable x Skyler RW4010 670013-52 Chalky Grey / Cinnamon Lenses Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCamera Capture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban Meta Skyler smart glasses are designed to unlock new possibilities in how you see the world. The lightweight frame is integrated with wearable tech, so you can listen, call, capture and livestream without disconnecting from what’s happening around you. Drawing on our 60s archive and the Golden Age of air travel, the Skyler shape is inspired by an era of iconic jet-set style. Its wider front and gentle curves are designed to suit most faces. SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 5 KGColour Name PinkProduct Length 150 mmProduct Height 41. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 52. 2 mmModel Number RW4010PK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4db0da39-7413-4d80-afee-324fddd6d2a4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5ce04371-549a-4cac-a813-64cc09ea9bff/web/1_1732118305194.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069806765407</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8894599986</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Ray-Ban - Smart Glasses - Headliner -F/L Polar Dusty Red RW4009 Shiny Jeans</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCapture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban | Meta Headliner With Ray-Ban Meta Headliner smart glasses you can express yourself with the most unique perspective there is – yours. Integrated with AI-enhanced wearable tech, the lightweight frame enables you to listen, call, capture and livestream, all while staying present in the moment. The Headliner panthos shape is a hybrid of the Wayfarer and the Round, bringing together the best of two icons. SpecificationsColour Name Shiny JeansStorage Capacity 32 GBModel Number RW4009Model Name RW4009Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c8dec49b-5ea2-42fd-9ae0-61b45a65b9f3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1fd03f2d-c4d4-4e9a-8610-653c62bb42b7/web/1_1732118664481.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1649 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088945999863</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7414374467</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS + Cellular 42mm Silver Aluminium Case With Denim Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSeries 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Denim Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWX33QA/A, MWX43QA/AModel Name MWX33QA/A, MWX43QA/A, MWX33ZP/A, MWX33LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/256b3053-4393-480f-b728-acd79d3f3323</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c6fb6f77-bc34-45f1-9e70-f88d9120c27f/web/1_1732118578829.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1645 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074143744671</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6336652489</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Wearable x headliner RW4009 601/9A 50 Polar G15 Green Shiny Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCapture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban | Meta Headliner With Ray-Ban Meta Headliner smart glasses you can express yourself with the most unique perspective there is – yours. Integrated with AI-enhanced wearable tech, the lightweight frame enables you to listen, call, capture and livestream, all while staying present in the moment. The Headliner panthos shape is a hybrid of the Wayfarer and the Round, bringing together the best of two icons. SpecificationsColour Name Shiny BlackStorage Capacity 32 GBModel Number RW4009Model Name RW4009Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1eb0856b-aba9-473d-abd3-4b556dbc1611</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6ad10f93-7336-4306-9193-c43dad7ecaed/web/1_1732118754579.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063366524894</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1333130046</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Mini Evo Instant Photo Kit (Black)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights100 Different Expressions Stunning, evocative, dynamic. Interesting, striking, surprising. With 10 lens effects and 10 film effects, you can create the exact vision you have in mind. Experiment with the vividness, go retro, add softness to the focusDesign Focused With a luxurious design and razor-sharp finish, the mini Evo boasts an analogue look and feel and even features a traditional film camera lever to print your photos. And, thanks to the built-in selfie mirror,Smartphone Printer_x000D_ Sometimes the shots you are most proud of are hidden in the depths of your camera roll. Adjust the crop, rotate, tweak the brightness, contrast and saturation, add a filter and then print your mini masterpieceSave Images_x000D_ Captured your pièce de resistance? It’s good to share. That’s why the mini Evo turns your smartphone into your very own print gallery, saving every single printed image in a handy digital format. Leaving you to get posting _x000D_Remote Shooting Keep your eye on the shot and go hands-free. Simply connect your smartphone to your mini Evo and hey presto, you’ve now got a remote shutter button. Spot on for group photos, arty portrait setups, even trickier wildlife shots. OverviewThe instax mini Evo is our most expressive camera yet. We believe that everyone has their own unique perspectives, and with 10 lens options and 10 film effects, the mini Evo gives you 100 different ways to express yourself through the images you capture and print. Combining traditional analogue design with the controls and convenience of digital devices, the mini Evo is a hybrid instant camera and smartphone printer in one. Creativity is paramount. That’s why the mini Evo brings endless possibilities to your fingertips, leaving you to express your unique point of view and share life’s beautiful nuances. SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 28 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 3. 6 cmProduct Height 8. 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 12. 3 cmModel Number 84481</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0af3d7f7-b521-4d28-b279-da5e14045716</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9e57327d-9647-43ce-ab80-be045fe9199e/web/1_1732117144786.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>995 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013331300466</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4855331449</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Beam (Gen 2) Smart Soundbar BEAM2UK1BLK Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights3D Audio with Dolby AtmosHDMI eARC CompatibilityNFC Capabilities, Night Sound, Trueplay, In-built MicrophoneSpecificationsProduct Weight 2. 8 gColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Sonos Beam (Gen 2), Power Cable, 1x HDMI Cable (4. 9 ft/1. 5 m), 1x Optical Audio Adapter, DocumentationProduct Height 69 cmProduct Width/Depth 651 cmFeatures SmartModel Number BEAM2UK1BLKModel Name BEAM2AU1BLKNumber of HDMI Ports 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6c055326-1440-403c-bd62-ad9bb5781470</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fb4f0631-5434-454d-ad8a-560475aa6881/web/1_1732119932618.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2013.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048553314496</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6360211486</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Marble Grey 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEasy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Marble GreyDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f25202b8-e216-4866-a320-22d3cca5b0fc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/606c6541-d001-4f7e-a314-9c0342e69e80/web/1_1732120858021.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2470 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063602114865</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7424039352</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Onyx Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEasy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Onyx BlackDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9de7b199-d75c-4344-bb6e-5333b0202f8d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9368af02-d3b7-4b12-b478-d261425919b5/web/1_1732120481564.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2390 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074240393529</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3443166574</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Cobalt Violet, 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEasy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Cobalt VioletDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c2822202-bcd7-4de1-b75f-b1e0a49ef77a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c8f9d775-63ed-4adc-8499-2dff0065cda3/web/1_1732120762825.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2449 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034431665743</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8595291333</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Clay White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. The instax mini 12 instant camera is the updated version that comes in 5 amazing pastel shades with great auto exposure and selfie mode with simple operations. Get your instant memories and selfies and brighten up your world with a handy version of the mini-series Featuring programmed electronic shutter speed, flash brightness, and automatic adjustments to ambient light, the FUJIFILM Instax Mini 12 Instant Camera ensures bright and well-exposed photos effortlessly. Thus, you can say goodbye to underexposed or overexposed shots, as it optimises settings based on the surrounding light conditions, allowing you to capture stunning images wherever and whenever inspiration strikes. Boasting a built-in selfie mirror, this instant camera takes your selfie game to the next level. Plus, with automatic flash adjustment, you'll always get well-lit selfies without any hassle. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Clay WhiteProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f20f5a41-54bc-4553-a93b-4f169edeb82b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c02956e3-22f1-4002-8d81-fb62f42093b4/web/1_1732112688319.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>280.85 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085952913332</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7165307747</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro Dual SIM Midnight Black 8GB RAM 256GB - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS120Hz FHD+ amoled displayImmersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels67W turbo charging with 5000mAh typ batteryMediaTek helio G99-ultraOverviewUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS |120Hz FHD+AMOLED display | Immersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels | 67W turbo charging with 5000mAh (typ) batterySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 187 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 67 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Midnight BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 13Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number 7th_generation_intel_kaby_lake_7y30_processor 4nmFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile Phone/ Adapter/ USB Type-C Cable/ SIM Eject Tool/ Protective Case/ Quick Start Guide/ Warranty Card/ Safety informationNetwork Frequency Band LTENumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleCondition NewProduct Length 161. 1 mmProduct Height 74. 95 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 256 GBSensor Proximity Sensors, ambient_light_sensor, AccelerometerModel Number 23117RA68G , 2312DRA50GModel Name Note 13 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 200MP+8MP+2MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/27e0d0f8-4406-473b-9cee-b33015b0a95b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c9588006-2414-45a6-ba15-f3bc226d402d/web/1_1732109410315.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071653077473</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3482050318</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Era 300 UK E30G1UK1BLKR2/E30G1AU1BLKR2 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsWith next-level audio that hits from every direction, era 300 doesn’t just surround you, it puts you inside your musicConnect to all your content and devices using wifi, bluetooth, and 3. 5 mm line inImmerse yourself in an unrivaled dolby atmos experience when you pair two with arc or beam gen 2OverviewFeel sound all around. Spatial audio like only Sonos can do spatial audio. Introducing Era 300. SpecificationsProduct Weight 4. 47 KGColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Power CableProduct Length 169 mmProduct Height 189 mmProduct Width/Depth 260 mmFeatures Wireless, Bluetooth, Compact Size, Ethernet (LAN), SmartModel Number E30G1UK1BLKR2/E30G1AU1BLKR2Model Name Sonos Era 300 UK (Black)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/475de929-c7ad-47aa-9768-47cd475dbbaa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0592706c-3d08-4517-9a70-7972f5efde4f/web/1_1732119438019.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1849 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034820503182</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2132121611</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Dual SIM Silver shadow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/54527232-e68f-43c8-ac79-684625c5dc3c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a883b541-ffe0-4e93-b80f-a4ac83ee91d0/web/1_1732107084246.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021321216116</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2232111112</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Buds 3 Pro Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDual AMP ~ Crystal Sound ~ The Blade LightsAI Technology Support ~ Pinch Control &amp;amp; Swip360 Audio Recording ~ Super Clear CallAmbient Sound - 3 Mic VPUDynamic Noise adjustmentOverviewSamsung Galaxy Buds 3 ProSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 53 mAhColour Name SilverDepartment Adult UnisexConnection Type True WirelessAverage Battery Life Less than 8 hrsWhat's In The Box Buds &amp;amp; Charger caseAudio Jack Type-CAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WiredEarplug Type EarbudsModel Number SM-R630NZAAMEA, SM-R630</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/114cf2fe-f011-409d-afe9-a5ccf7010331</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b65898eb-f5a4-424e-bcdc-917af94d0575/web/1_1732106372871.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>560 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022321111128</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1405115989</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Silver 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name SilverOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FZSDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dd1dec5b-b1df-4228-ab3f-119895d52b50</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3921b822-f91b-4755-bd74-8416663788a5/web/1_1732108732985.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>290 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014051159891</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9768971081</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro Dual SIM Lavender Purple 8GB RAM 256GB - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS120Hz FHD+ amoled displayImmersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels67W turbo charging with 5000mAh typ batteryMediaTek helio G99-ultraOverviewRedmi Note 13 Pro Dual SIM Purple 8GB RAM 256GB - Global VersionSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 187 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 67 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Lavender PurpleDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 13Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number 7th_generation_intel_kaby_lake_7y30_processor 4nmFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile Phone/ Adapter/ USB Type-C Cable/ SIM Eject Tool/ Protective Case/ Quick Start Guide/ Warranty Card/ Safety informationNetwork Frequency Band LTENumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleCondition NewProduct Length 161. 1 mmProduct Height 74. 95 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 256 GBSensor Proximity Sensors, ambient_light_sensor, AccelerometerModel Number 23117RA68GModel Name Note 13 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 200+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d667bb1f-a22f-4fdc-bee1-8deb458be9e3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/80c63714-2926-4130-97ca-ce5969a2d04d/web/1_1732109273685.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097689710818</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2611262262</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FZKDMEA / SM-A055FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4892da3c-9145-4037-9e26-23f6d10e9880</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d55cb5bf-c89c-4c0c-a601-ee7294d25179/web/1_1732108618466.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>293 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026112622626</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9388126062</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Blue/BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZKIMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/67cc5e7d-f67d-45e6-9b75-e1ccfc796811</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6f8e6e9d-561e-4702-af3c-34c6b4425eae/web/1_1732107499904.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>635 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093881260625</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6836128799</g:id>
      <g:title>JVC Portable Bluetooth Party speaker with wireless mic and remote control XS-N4112PB black</g:title>
      <g:description>Output Power of 40W with PMPO 800WBluetooth ConnectivityAux Input for easy sound playUSB Input portTF/SD InputOverview-Huge sound, dazzling lights and unbelievable power set this speaker apart from the crowd. -The JVC XS-N4112PB packs a full party into a transportable sound machine like no other. -Turn up your favorite playlists anywhere, from get-togethers at home to dance parties . - Bring big party vibes with 800 watts PMPO of JVC Sound -Plug in and keep the fun going all nightSpecificationsProduct Weight 5 KGColour Name blackWhat's In The Box WIRELESS MIC , REMOTE CONTROL , SPEAKER UNITProduct Length 240 mmProduct Height 590 mmProduct Width/Depth 200 mmModel Number XS-N4112PB</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/52947f0b-00e0-4157-ba1b-f1b0db90089e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6491ce7f-49ab-4c97-b43f-038fbe2f20a0/web/1_1732171104655.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>275 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068361287997</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7240516076</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Sub Gen 3 The Wireless Subwoofer For Deep Bass SUBG3AU1BLK Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsExperience the best cinematic soundGood quality productConnects to the internet through your wi-fi for continuous and uninterrupted musicDual acoustic ports have been precisely tuned to enhance performanceAll new sonos sub hear and feel the difference with sub the wireless subwoofer for deep bassOverviewExperience every rumble, roar and beat you've been missing with clean, pulse-pounding bass. Sub takes over the lowest frequencies so paired speakers are free to focus on mid-range and high frequencies for a richer, more powerful sound experience all around. Made to be seen and heard, Sub features a sculptural shape and high-gloss finish. Stand it upright or lay it on its side. Quickly add Sub to your system over WiFi with a little help from the Sonos app. Feel bass like never before when you include a pair of Subs in your home cinema setup. Build the perfect sound system over time when you mix and match Sonos speakers. SpecificationsProduct Weight 16 KGColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box 1 Subwoofer, ManualProduct Length 158 mmProduct Height 402 mmProduct Width/Depth 389 mmFeatures Compact Size, Smart, WirelessModel Number SUBG3AU1BLKModel Name SUBG3AU1BLK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1845b1e8-1927-4615-b3c1-d4f6fd90b180</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1fc3805e-4b36-4703-ab63-bab99d4ef669/web/1_1732186317914.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0072405160764</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3777332212</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 512GB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/942cfea7-2742-494f-8139-7367047fb100</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/79b4198a-a19a-442c-8ab4-f9ba9fcb277d/web/1_1732188422336.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037773322121</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2195946458</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Blue Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Blue TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6T3AH/A,MU7A3AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bebf8af8-05d4-40bc-b3fd-fbab202e34bf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/07e0d9a4-c06b-4405-8abe-88242bb10a14/web/1_1732030573269.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021959464583</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4464305466</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Sub (Gen 3) -The Wireless Subwoofer for Deep Bass SUBG3AU1WHT White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact design for easy carryingIntegrated with special drivers that eliminate vibration and rattle to enable you to hear pure bassMade with high-quality material for long-term useSpecificationsColour Name WhiteProduct Length 158 mmProduct Height 402 mmProduct Width/Depth 389 mmModel Number SUBG3AU1WHTModel Name SONOS SUBWOOFER SUBG3AU1WHT WHITE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/736a6541-4306-4eba-b470-759a521dfb20</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eab65a0a-4649-4b9c-a0c8-6b5a85604735/web/1_1732186119760.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044643054662</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5038358902</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max Physical Dual Sim 256GB Natural Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ecaa325e-9a15-4bf3-8c36-101a8fe7db1d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3db8e918-8209-4df9-a22c-390a421483b4/web/1_1732107467457.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050383589029</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9014045703</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Navy 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome NavyOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356EZKPMEAModel Name SM-A356EZKPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/19d2ea1e-7d32-4282-84df-f968e8b6feac</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a119b10c-2f8d-41c9-836f-a0c498205738/web/1_1732110363850.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>825 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090140457031</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8698832858</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max Physical Dual Sim 256GB Black Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/aea491ae-506b-4e5a-8ae8-0ed889bdbc60</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b5251fce-400d-498e-8b75-22376e0ad318/web/1_1732107568796.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5100 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086988328589</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6540130583</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Lemon 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome LemonOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356EZYPMEAModel Name SM-A356EZYPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/54b222a9-d7db-40df-8921-1c55f209af9b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8cea7e80-8a73-48f6-8340-2808ee69aadc/web/1_1732110501693.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>825 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065401305833</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1027539531</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Yellow 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name YellowOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZYIMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c0fb4b54-08bd-4b1a-b7df-457d1eb21716</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/39f49568-c58e-4928-bf52-ca436d18ce07/web/1_1732107339336.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>615 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010275395312</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
