<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>7964863046</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Watch 5 Active Midnight Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience a vibrant 2. 0″ LCD display, ensuring crystal-clear visibility in any lighting conditions. Enjoy the convenience of Bluetooth calling, allowing seamless communication directly from your wrist. SpecificationsMaterial TPUColour Name Midnight BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 11. 4 mmFeatures Heart Rate Monitor, Sleep Monitor, SpO2 MonitorModel Number BHR8784GLModel Name Redmi Watch 5 Active</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/97bc30af-21a4-42e8-b3d8-10181f4f2086</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6ccaff1e-1823-4be0-9787-a4248a3570b3/web/1_1728980182587.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>157 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079648630467</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4054143241</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 4 Wathet Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>ANC noise cancellation, 3 microphones, ip54 protectionDust and water resistance ip54Up to 6 hours with headphones and an additional 30 hours with a charging boxSpecificationsColour Name BlueConnection Type True WirelessWhat's In The Box Truewireless HeadphonesAudio Headphone Type In-EarEarplug Type EarbudsModel Number 38562Model Name 38562Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/07324ed0-7fa2-4a96-bb29-16de7fea405a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0eb96fda-a516-42e1-9577-89f6771caf52/web/1_1728984627704.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>62 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040541432410</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6034937960</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Watch 4 | 1.97″ AMOLED Display | Supports Bluetooth Calling | Aluminum Alloy Frame | Up To 20 Days Battery Life Obsidian Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Ultra large 1. 97″ AMOLED display, LTPS 5Hz / 60Hz refresh rateExquisite aluminum alloy frameUp to 20 days long battery lifeSupports Bluetooth CallingSupports 5-system GNSSAdvance health and workout trackingOverviewRedmi Watch 4 adopts a sturdy and reliable aluminum alloy frame* for the first time for a more elevated design feel. Make a fashion statement with two available color options. The exquisite stainless-steel rotating crown adds high-end finesse to even the smallest details and its gentle spin gives a more comfortable experience. SpecificationsMaterial Aluminium AlloyColour Name Obsidian BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 97 inModel Number BHR7854GL | M2315W1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c14cae2a-13c2-49a6-b9a8-8e5d28b37965</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e6a0657e-79fe-4a58-b44a-0fc0ad4fabde/web/1_1728968038146.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>257.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060349379601</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7991476909</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Android TV Stick with Built in Chromecast – Full HD 1080p (MDZ-24) Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Bluetooth remote with Google Assistant allows you to use voice-activated commands to access any feature from the comfort of your couchSmart Cast with built-in Google Chromecast allows you to effortlessly cast content from your smartphone or laptop directly to your TVFeatures 4K HDR technology with high-speed 4K processing to deliver vibrant colours and detailed contrast levels in every sceneDolby DTS HD technology works seamlessly to deliver a surround sound audio experienceFeatures 8GB of internal memory to store your favourite applicationsOverviewAbout The Brand:Xiaomi was founded in 2010 in Beijing by now multi-billionaire Lei Jun when he was 40 years old, along with six senior associates. Lei had founded Kingsoft as well as Joyo. com, which he sold to Amazon for $75 million in 2004. In August 2011, Xiaomi released its first smartphone and, by 2014, it had the largest market share of smartphones sold in China. Initially the company only sold its products online; however, it later opened brick and mortar stores. By 2015, it was developing a wide range of consumer electronics. In 2020, the company sold 146. 3 million smartphones and its MIUI operating system has over 500 million monthly active users. In the second quarter of 2021, Xiaomi surpassed Apple Inc. to become the second-largest seller of smartphones worldwide, with a 17% market share, according to Canalys. [8] It also is a major manufacturer of appliances including televisions, flashlights, unmanned aerial vehicles, and air purifiers using its Internet of Things and Xiaomi Smart Home product ecosystems. Xiaomi keeps its prices close to its manufacturing costs and bill of materials costs by keeping most of its products in the market for 18 months, longer than most smartphone companies, The company also uses inventory optimization and flash sales to keep its inventory low. SpecificationsInternal Memory 8 GBProduct Weight 28. 5 gColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box 1xTV Stick, 1xRemoteProduct Length 30 mmProduct Height 92. 4 mmProduct Width/Depth 15 mmFeatures Business, Ergonomic, Personal, Cordless, Indicator LightsModel Number MDZ-24-AB / MDZ-24-AAModel Name Mi TV StickItem Quantity 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/23d65098-bc40-4b8d-aa52-05e8142eb6ba</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/323c7ea1-c2db-4ba9-a7dc-75b56b8981d1/web/1_1728967833471.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>128.45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079914769099</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6123794165</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI Band 9 Smart Watch, Ultra-Thin Design And Comfortable Wearing, Scientific Sleep Analysis, Durable Battery Life, IOS And Android Starry Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Ultra design: 1. 47 Inch amoled screen, 8. 99mm thin, 14g weightScientific sleep tracking: Upgraded sleep efficiency analysis, and sleep basic physiological analysisFast charging, durable battery life: 45 minutes to fully charge, 5 minutes fast charge can be used for 2 days. Maximum 2-week battery life, 9 days of normal useCustomized workout types: Huawei band 9 offers a multitude of workouts that you can customize as requiredCompatible with android and iOSOverviewHUAWEI Band 9 is a brand new, high-end sports band which has a full-sized color touchscreen, side button control, and is water resistant to 50 meters. This smart wearable product integrates a wide range of features, including workout detection, smart heart rate monitoring, workout assistant, multiple workout modes, sleep monitoring, message notifications, automatic SpO2 measurement, and music playback control. SpecificationsMaterial FluoroelastomerBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 14 gColour Name Starry BlackBand Material FluoroelastomerDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDFace/Dial Shape RectangularBand Size Medium/LargeProduct Length 43 mmProduct Height 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 25 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 47 inModel Number KIM-B19Model Name Huawei Band 9</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c6a3e3fe-87a8-44ac-8f09-14c57ee84f67</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6d45c92e-097c-4cf0-8dee-06f13c576e74/web/1_1728969103383.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>195 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061237941658</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2672956534</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Outdoor Camera CW300 EU | 2.5K Ultra-Xlear Picture Quality 4MP | IP66 Water And Dust Resistant | AI Human Tracking | Two-Way Intercom | White</g:title>
      <g:description>2. 5K ultra-clear picture quality, smart security in any weather 4MPSmart full-color night visionBidirectional gimbal movementIP66 water and dust resistantAI Human TrackingAudible and visual alarmTwo-way IntercomWired + Wi-Fi dual networkMJA1 security chipOverviewUltra-clear picture quality Amazing details even zoomed in The 4MP camera with the f/1. 6 large aperture lens presents 2. 5K ultra-clear picture quality, offering a clearer and finer image when you zoom in for more details. Four full-color night vision LEDs Achieve clear visibility at night The camera comes with a white light that automatically lights up at night when it recognizes a human figure, providing a colored image in dark surroundings. Horizontal and vertical gimbals Greater viewing angle for more peace of mind The dual-motor pan-tilt zoom design allows users to rotate the lens in all directions via their smartphone, allowing for a larger viewing angle as well as more flexible and reassuring protection. Professional IP66 water and dust resistant design No fear of adverse weather conditions The IP66 water and dust resistance rating enables stable performance in adverse weather conditions. Human detection supported Automatic notification when someone approaches The camera uses a next-generation local AI human-detection algorithm to detect humans more accurately and faster, no cloud needed. When a person is detected, the camera automatically records alert videos and sends notifications to your smartphone. Track a human body as it moves The camera intelligently tracks human movement. When someone is detected and locked on to, it automatically tracks and records videos of the person as they move and sends notifications to your smartphone. Audible and visual alarm for active defense With alarm notifications sent to your smartphone When the camera detects someone in the monitoring area, it will automatically trigger an audible alarm with high-frequency flashing lights to drive away potential intruders. It will also simultaneously send an alarm message to Mi Home/Xiaomi Home app. Two-way voice calling Handle noisy outdoor environments with ease The camera comes with a built-in high-sensitivity microphone and high-quality high-power speaker, boosted with an AI noise cancellation algorithm. The long pickup range ensures loud and clear sound even under complex outdoor conditions. Voice Control Voice control works with Amazon Alexa or Google Assistant Wired + Wi-Fi dual network Say goodbye to lag 2. 4GHz Wi-Fi network supported. The camera also comes with a built-in Ethernet port so you can choose your preferred connection method. The connection is more stable, reducing connection disruptions and providing a smooth user experience. Hardware-level protection Your privacy is safe Each built-in MJA1 security chip is provided with a unique key and credential to effectively protect the data communication and privacy of users with financial-grade security measuresSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 4 MPModel Number CW300 | BHR8097EU | BHR8095GBModel Name Xiaomi Outdoor Camera CW300</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a6f25607-896b-4b1d-8e87-0c14f12ab761</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3ba3d2cd-58b1-44ec-b589-c09e7a544674/web/1_1728977002065.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>194.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026729565347</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4182886109</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI WATCH FIT 2 Active Edition Smartwatch With 1.74"FullView Display Durable Battery Life Automatic SpO2 Monitoring Midnight Black</g:title>
      <g:description>The ambient light display allows automatic adjustment of brightness on the watch suited to your environmentTrack all stages of sleep every night and keep a tab on your sleep health with the sleep monitoring feature on the watchSports friendly it is splash and sweat resistance makes it the perfect fitness companion to haveKeep a track of your well being and health right from your wrist with noise health suite featuring a variety of health featuresMonitor your heart rate and blood oxygen levels on the go with the heart rate and spo2 monitor and it also comes with guided breathing to help you relax and embrace mindfulnessOverviewA smartwatch is a wearable computer in the form of a watch; modern smartwatches provide a local touchscreen interface for daily use, while an associated smartphone app provides for management and telemetry (such as long-term biomonitoring). While early models could perform basic tasks, such as calculations, digital time telling, translations, and game-playing, smartwatches released since 2015 or later have more general functionality closer to smartphones, including mobile apps, a mobile operating system and wifi/bluetooth connectivity. Some smartwatches function as portable media players, with fm radio and playback of digital audio and video files via a bluetooth headset. Some models, called watch phones (or vice versa), have mobile cellular functionality like making calls. while internal hardware varies, most have an electronic visual display, either backlit lcd or oled. some use transflective or electronic paper, to consume less power. They are generally powered by a rechargeable lithium-ion battery. Peripheral devices may include digital cameras, thermometers, accelerometers, pedometers, heart rate monitors, altimeters, barometers, compasses, gps receivers, tiny speakers, and microsd cards, which are recognized as storage devices by many other kinds of computers. software may include digital maps, schedulers and personal organizers, calculators, and various kinds of watch faces. The watch may communicate with external devices such as sensors, wireless headsets, or a heads-up display. Like other computers, a smartwatch may collect information from internal or external sensors and it may control, or retrieve data from, other instruments or computers. It may support wireless technologies such as bluetooth, wi-fi, and gps. For many purposes, a "watch computer" serves as a front end for a remote system such as a smartphone, communicating with the smartphone using various wireless technologies. Smartwatches are advancing, especially their design, battery capacity, and health-related applications. health-related applications include applications measuring heart rate, spo2, workout, etc. SpecificationsCharging Type Lightning to USBMaterial FluoroelastomerBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 30 gColour Name Midnight BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box Watch x 1 Charging Cradle (including the charging cable) x 1 Quick Start Guide &amp;amp; Safety Information &amp;amp; Warranty Card x 1Band Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Dial Material MetalTrending Huawei Watch FitProduct Length 46 mmProduct Height 10. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 33. 5 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 74 inFeatures Indicator Lights, Rechargeable, Pocket Size, Water Resistant, Sweat ResistantModel Number YDA-B09SModel Name Watch Fit 2 Active EditionItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0f71ab3b-2d63-4ed7-bf95-9babd4fd0de3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8ed110b6-4f51-435a-b1ba-031d16e29c4f/web/1_1728977992040.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>380 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041828861091</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3158316893</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Band 8 Graphite Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Display - 1. 62 Inch amoled, 490x192 pix, 326 ppi, 60 Hz200+ Custom watch facesHeart rate and sleep monitoring150+ Workout modesUp to 16 days battery lifeBluetooth 5. 1 BLE connectivityOverviewXiaomi Smart Band 8 has been upgraded with Easy-detachable Straps that not only allow you to easily switch between different strap designs and materials, but also allows you to remove the strap entirely. The elegant body features a stylish metallic finish, now available in two new midframe colours: Champagne Gold and Graphite Black. A higher refresh rate delivers a super smooth experience, with eye-catching operation and swipe motions. Stepless automatic brightness adjustment with precise adaptation to the ambient brightness. Whenever you raise your wrist, the brightness will adjust to the perfect level that is also gentle on your eyes. SpecificationsColour Name Graphite BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Model Number BHR7165GL/CI51439Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/822ff3a8-8970-4c74-bb6b-7ee151306b75</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7aaa032b-db94-4648-a966-81d2e4bbe4e4/web/1_1728977656811.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>98.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031583168931</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6527054097</g:id>
      <g:title>realme Buds T100 True Wireless Earbuds With AI Noise Cancelling Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>True wireless bluetooth headset. Call noise reductionLong battery life 28h. Support flash chargeLow latencyOverviewModel：Realme Buds T100. Wireless connection：Bluetooth 5. 3. Battery life：Headphone + charging compartment: 28h music playback. Function：AAC, SBC. Charging port：Type-C. Water resistant： IPX5 (earbuds only). Dynamic driver size：10mmSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 400 mAhProduct Weight 35 gColour Name BlueConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life Less than 8 hrsWhat's In The Box Realme Techlife Buds T100 *1, User Guide *1, Silicone Eartips *6Audio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WiredEarplug Type EarbudsProduct Length 6. 1 mmProduct Height 4. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 2. 8 mmFeatures Bluetooth, Water Resistant, Active Noise CancellationModel Number RMA2109Model Name BUDS T100</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/860792ef-701a-4dfa-8565-5d2be8a47f55</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/adbdd82a-879b-4bfe-9575-1f1c2322731d/web/1_1728978510758.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>79 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065270540977</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5495744839</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi TV A Pro 32 Inch HD Smart LED Google TV With 360° Bluetooth Remote Control Chromecast Built-In L32M8-A2ME Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Premium metallic frame with bezel-less design32" HD smart LED TV, Google TVGoogle Assistant built-in, Smart home control hub, Chromecast built-in, Supports MiracastNetflix, Prime Video and Youtube pre-installed. Thousands of apps available in Google PlaySpeaker (Sound Output) 2 × 10W, Supports Dolby Audio™, DTS-X and DTS® Virtual: X SoundOverviewThe ultra-narrow bezel design provides a high screen-to-body ratio far beyond that of standard TVs. From the instant you turn on the TV, high-resolution images in stunning colors blanket the screen for an immersive experience. Featuring an exquisite metallic frame with a unibody design, Xiaomi A Pro Series makes a real statement in any home. The 2 × 10W high-power stereo speakers fill the room with rich high and bass tones and provide an immersive sound experience. Google TV™ brings together movies, shows, and more from across your apps and subscriptions and organizes them just for you. Discover new things to watch with recommendations based on what you watch and what interests you, from across your subscriptions and content available to you. Your TV is more helpful than ever. Ask Google to find movies, stream apps, play music, and control the TV - all with your voice. Even get answers, control smart home devices, and more. Just say "Ok Google" or press the Google Assistant button on the remote to get started. Easily control your smart TV with the 360° Bluetooth remote control. The Chromecast built-in™* and Miracast allow you to continue watching what's on your smart mobile devices on a bigger screen, elevating your visual experience. The powerful quad-core A55 CPU combined with 1. 5GB RAM + 8GB ROM* offers smoother operation and more space for your favourite apps. Designed with a 2. 4GHz/5GHz Wi-Fi solution, various commonly used ports and Bluetooth 5. 0 to easily connect to different devices and adapt to more audio and video entertainment scenarios,SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 1080pInternal Memory 8 GBProduct Weight 3. 9 KGScreen Size 32 inRefresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System Google TVWhat's In The Box 60° bluetooth remote control × 1 Screws bag × 1 Stand × 2 Power cable × 1 User manual × 1 Warranty card × 1Number of Cores Quad CoreViewing Distance 1. 7 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 715. 7 mmProduct Height 423. 7 mmProduct Width/Depth 82. 5 mmFeatures Smart TV, Wi-Fi, AndroidModel Number L32M8-A2MEModel Name Xiaomi TV A Pro 32"Number of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5552be6b-a493-4da4-b01f-6a40a84cc289</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d0d4f0e7-8f12-450d-ae3d-0af318f931a0/web/1_1728972797686.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>485 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054957448392</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5562757902</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi 50W 20000 mAh Power Bank Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Shield devices from short-circuit, over heatingSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number PB2050SZMModel Name PB2050SZMItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7aecf6cf-013d-47b5-b7f4-b3a4d8ba99c0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/90cb6e81-7b04-46a9-9ce2-20d2acd66495/web/1_1728974869947.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>104.25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055627579026</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8106163527</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI AX3 AX3000 (WS7100) Dual Band Wi-Fi Router, Dual-core Wi-Fi 6 Plus Revolution, Wi-Fi Speed up to 3000 Mbps, Supports Access Point Mode, Parental Control, Guest Wi-Fi white</g:title>
      <g:description>Offers ample space to store all your essentialsMade of durable quality materialIt is accented with gold-tone detailingSpecificationsColour Name whiteWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Dual BandWireless Standard AXMax Data Transfer Rate 2. 4 GbpsModel Number 53038507Model Name 53038507</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/255331be-6a84-4410-8cdd-2545095195fb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0325b22f-056c-4874-ab70-1466e21529ca/web/1_1728981903246.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>184 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081061635271</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1711520481</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Watch 5 Active Matte Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience a vibrant 2. 0″ LCD display, ensuring crystal-clear visibility in any lighting conditions. Enjoy the convenience of Bluetooth calling, allowing seamless communication directly from your wrist. SpecificationsMaterial TPUColour Name Matte SilverBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 11. 4 mmFeatures Heart Rate Monitor, Sleep Monitor, SpO2 MonitorModel Number BHR8790GLModel Name Redmi Watch 5 Active</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f0fa32ab-e0e7-45b2-a2ae-775e0eca5038</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/33ea5328-9a37-4801-8522-cdf6d3192468/web/1_1728987993997.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>157 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017115204810</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3576745942</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Smart Band 8 Chinese Version Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBattery: 190mAh Battery capacity, up to 16 days charging time approximately 1 hoursWater resistance: 5Atm has a water resistance of up to 50mActivity tracking: Calculate steps, distance, calories burned, female health monitor, blood oxygenHealth monitoring: 24-Hour heart rate monitoringSensor: Six axis accelerometer, six axis gyroscopeSpecificationsColour Name BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Model Number Smart Band 8Model Name Smart Band 8Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b13b93c-3170-4d33-8b95-efe6de97580c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/50855e83-d0c2-4c51-9096-49d8beba31f2/web/1_1728982506441.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>109 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035767459426</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4770272181</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W Portable Speaker Red</g:title>
      <g:description>Enjoy dynamic and powerful sound with transparent and balanced audio, thanks to its large mesh area design. Rich Bass: Dual large-size passive woofer radiators and exclusive woofer boost mode deliver fuller and richer bass for energetic sounds. Expertly tuned with dynamic equilibrium, smart volume balancing, and dynamic woofer extension for superior audio. Up to 12 hours of uninterrupted playback on a full charge, with Type-C 15W fast charging support for extended enjoyment. Sleek and Portable Design: Curved lightweight body design makes it easy to hold and carry, perfect for music enjoyment anywhere. Dust and Water Resistance: IP67-rated protection ensures reliable performance outdoors in any weather condition. Bluetooth 5. 4: Faster and more stable connection for lossless audio quality. TWS Stereo Combo: Connect two identical speakers for superior immersive sound experiences in smart stereo mode. Hands-Free Calling: Answer calls with a single tap for clear and crisp hands-free conversations while multitasking. OverviewXiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W Portable SpeakerSpecificationsProduct Weight 730 gColour Name RedConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life 6 HoursProduct Length 9. 2 cmProduct Height 18 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 1 cmModel Number 30W SpeakerModel Name 30W Speaker</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/397554c0-6821-49bd-a687-b24a69c8cbee</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/88831320-b08d-429f-a440-0d335efb1435/web/1_1728990718686.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>169 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047702721819</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7055705837</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 4 Active White</g:title>
      <g:description>12mm dynamic driver - Experience powerful bass: The 12mm dynamic driver is even larger than before. With expert tuning by the Xiaomi Acoustic Lab, it delivers enhanced bass and heightened acoustics, providing a pleasing listening experience for users worldwide. Noise cancellation for calls - Outstanding performance in noisy environments: Each earbud comes equipped with a high-sensitivity microphone that leverages to mitigate ambient background noise interruptions, ensuring optimal clarity of speech for effective communication even in noisy environments. 28-hour ultra-long battery life - Let good music keep you company longer: The earbuds’ battery life lasts up to 5 hours on a single charge and up to 28 hours* with the portable charging case, so you can enjoy great music day and night. Bluetooth 5. 3 - Fully upgraded: The earbuds are now equipped with the latest Bluetooth 5. 3 technology, which allows for reduced power consumption, greater signal stability, and stronger resistance to interference. Even when surrounded by multiple devices, it still provides reliable transmission without any interference. Low-latency mode - Smooth gaming experience: With Bluetooth 5. 3, you can easily initiate low-latency mode for an immersive gaming experience with exceptional precision. Ensuring you don't miss any crucial moments in the game and enabling you to efficiently control it with accuracy. Touch control - Control from anywhere: The touch control operations* allow you to smoothly and easily switch between different modes using light touches. ENC: Enjoy crystal-clear conversations even in noisy environments, as the powerful mic captures your voice with remarkable clarity while Environmental Noise Cancellation (ENC) actively reduces background noise for an uninterrupted and immersive calling experience. Stay connected and communicate effortlessly with our premium audio solution. IPX4: Designed to withstand the elements, our Redmi Buds 4 Active are built with an IPX4 rating, providing reliable protection against water splashes and sweat. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteDepartment UnisexConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type In-EarFeatures BluetoothModel Number BHR8000GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/389359b0-5615-4adf-9a8d-7a96a706ca10</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/28f0d6c7-4ca8-43d5-bc94-45c53df1e6ff/web/1_1728983605524.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>60.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070557058373</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4568194774</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Camera C300 New Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Zoom in on objects and capture clearer details and colors with 2304*1296 resolutionF1. 4 Large Aperture and 6P LensInvisible 940nm infrared LEDs offer you enhanced night vision without making any interruptionCombined with the application of AI with deep learning technology, the optimized algorithm effectively filters invalid alarms and makes the alarm more accurateThe dual motor head enables the camera to rotate and capture a full 360° horizontal view and 108° vertical viewSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDDisplay Resolution 2304x1440Colour Name WhiteVideo Recording Resolution Type 2KCamera Resolution 3 MPModel Number XMC01Model Name XMC01</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f3367f2a-0633-49a0-bdf7-b9ae1862c71c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6ff4a424-723e-471c-8a08-41c7f7608194/web/1_1728983771549.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>118 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045681947749</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1390434695</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mesh System AC1200 (2-pack) | 2.4GHz and 5GHz dual-band 1200Mbps |Covers up to 2,800 ft² /260 m² White</g:title>
      <g:description>Prearranged kit pairing2. 4Ghz and 5GHz dual band supportCovers up to 2,800 ft² /260 m²Full Gigabit Ethernet portSleek and minimalistic designEffortless self-networkingOverviewAntenna: Internal Antennas Network Port: 2 x 10/100/1000Mbps WAN/LAN auto-sensing port Indicator: 1 Mesh/Reset Button: 1 Power Port: 1 Protocol Standards: IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab Bands: 2. 4GHz, 5GHz 2. 4GHz Wi-Fi: 300Mbps (802. 11ac) 5GHz Wi-Fi: 867Mbps (802. 11ac) Operating System: MiWi-Fi ROM Wi-Fi Encryption: WPA-PSK/WPA2-PSK/WPA3-SAE encryption Management Applications: Supports Web, Mi Home/Xiaomi Home App (Android, iOS) Operating Temperature: 0-40℃ Storage Temperature: -40-70℃ Operating Humidity: 10%-90%RH (non-condensing) Storage Humidity: 5%-90%RH (non-condensing) Product Dimensions: 8. 9 x 8. 9 x 15. 4cm (per unit)SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 9 KGColour Name WhiteSet Includes 2x mesh system, 1x power adapter, 1x network cable, 1x user manual, 1x warranty cardWireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard ACProduct Length 25. 8 cmProduct Height 9. 4 cmProduct Width/Depth 15. 9 cmFeatures App Enabled, Wireless AC, Wireless NModel Number DVB4451GL | RD13Model Name Xiaomi Mesh System AC1200 (2-pack)Wireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/973cd5dc-c2fa-44b5-bc0d-2ddc4172d39c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f6973cae-eaca-425f-8cea-83d821504221/web/1_1728987553742.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013904346952</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4030539762</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 13C Dual SIM Glacier White 6GB RAM 128GB 4G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Powerful mediatek helio G85Smooth 6. 74 inch 90Hz display50MP AI triple cameraSupport 18W fast chargingSpecificationsSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 74 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Glacier WhiteCondition NewModel Number 2311DRN14I | 23106RN0DAModel Name Redmi 13C</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/250066e1-98d9-473f-bc73-e724db42fcfd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/56ff5b0a-420c-46a1-b260-6a4f48df5aa0/web/1_1728985025040.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Realme</g:brand>
      <g:price>356 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040305397627</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7142843417</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6R3AH/A,MU793AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/42f4a9b4-b30a-4d59-9970-f11ced2a9f73</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3309548c-e013-4e01-9dee-71771b93fff2/web/1_1728973212111.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071428434173</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5626509255</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI Watch Fit 3 Smartwatch, 1.82 Inch Amoled Display, Comfortable And Stylish Design, Scientific Workout Coach, Upgraded Health Management, Compatible With iOS And Android Black</g:title>
      <g:description>1. 82-Inch ultra-large amoled bezel-less screen, comfortable and stylish on the wristScientific workout coach: Quick-workout animations, help you warm up and stretch before and after your workoutHealth management: Huawei watch fit 3 uses huawei trusleep™ technology to accurately detect whether you are in a deep sleep, and subsequently provide you with sleep quality assessments and suggestions for improving the quality of your sleepSmart life: Bluetooth call, independent music playback, multi-task management and calendar appCompatible with iOS and androidOverviewHUAWEI WATCH Fit 3 is a premium smart watch with 5 ATM water resistance, a color touchscreen, rotating crown, and side button controls. The watch comes with a wide range of fitness, health, making it suitable for daily wearing and high-level fitness. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 26 gColour Name BlackBand Material FluoroelastomerDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDWhat's In The Box Watch, Charging Pad, Quick Start Guide, Safety Information, And Warranty CardFace/Dial Shape SquareBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Huawei Watch FitProduct Length 43. 2 mmProduct Height 9. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 36. 3 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 82 inModel Number Solo-B09S, SLO-B09Model Name Huawei Watch Fit 3, SLO-B09</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6384f712-14cc-4e9b-9486-a75f0a9968dd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cba13ccb-8c45-49c5-bf11-add3498fac56/web/1_1728967203281.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056265092557</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7467998458</g:id>
      <g:title>Huayu Universal Remote Control for All LCD/LED or Plasma TV, Infrared</g:title>
      <g:description>Model Number: RM-1130Brand: HuayuColor: BlackCompatible with: TVs</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8c44c7ce-784d-432a-bf30-065088a94d0a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7ded2d56-120a-47c4-b92d-af4558934b92/web/1_1728971826484.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>34.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074679984589</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4838409516</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 86-Inch Ultra-HD 4K Smart Android TV 11 With 120Hz Refresh Rate | 178 Degrees Angle | 3D Sount Effects Dolby Atmos Supports Google Voice Assistant, Chromecast Built-In | Xiaomi TV Max 86" Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>Xiaomi TV Max 86" features ultra-large 86" and full-screen display, ultra-high screen-to-body ratio, wide viewing area and 4K ultra HD resolution, bringing you a cinematic experience at home120Hz ultra-high refresh rate coupled with 4K 120Hz MEMC (Motion Estimation and Motion Compensation) technology enables millisecond-level frame interpolation, delivering stutter-free images of high-speed scenesThe Full-Array Local dimming backlighting system has multiple zones, which allows the large display to have better control over light and shade, rendering images with more layersOverviewUltra-large 86" display. Xiaomi TV Max 86" features ultra-large 86" and full-screen display, ultra-high screen-to-body ratio, wide viewing area and 4K ultra HD resolution, bringing you a cinematic experience at home. Dual 120Hz For a refreshing viewing experience. 120Hz ultra-high refresh rate coupled with 4K 120Hz MEMC (Motion Estimation and Motion Compensation) technology enables millisecond-level frame interpolation, delivering stutter-free images of high-speed scenes. Your viewing experience is greatly improved whether you watch a sporting event, an action film or play a competitive video game. Full-Array Local dimming Stunning contrast. The Full-Array Local dimming backlighting system has multiple zones, which allows the large display to have better control over light and shade, rendering images with more layers. 1. 07 billion colors* DCI-P3 restores the true colour of films. Adopting the cinema-level DCI-P3 wide color gamut, Xiaomi TV Max 86" can rendering accurate colors just as the film director intended. With 1. 07 billion color depth, the image looks smoother than ever between color transitions. HDMI 2. 1 Smooth video gaming experience. With the new HDMI 2. 1 port, you can connect your TV to the game consoles for a 4K 120Hz ultra-high quality transmission of images. Featured by low latency and high-speed response, the TV brings additional fun to the family. Dolby Vision HDR transforms your TV experience with an ultra vivid picture that brings entertainment to life, and with Dolby Vision IQ, it leverages the full intelligence of your TV to deliver a perfect picture in your room at every moment. Speaker system with 4 drivers. Superior audio experience. The speaker system with 4 drivers and air-duct bass boost design make sounds played out from the TV richer and more powerful, providing more immersive audio experience. The Dolby Atmos and DTS:X technology not only reflects the details of sound, but also produces three-dimensional sound with an overhead dimension, creating more immersive and richer sound effects for you. The TV has a powerful quad-core A73 CPU and 3GB RAM + 32GB ROM, which can process multiple tasks simultaneously and high-frame-rate images with ease. Wi-Fi 6 For next generation network connections. The TV is among the first to support the next-generation Wi-Fi 6, or IEEE P 802. 11ax protocol. With the higher network bandwidth, the TV can significantly increase the transmission efficiency and network environment*Feel free to pick your favourites from more than 400,000 films and TV shows* or download from over 7,000 apps and games available in the Google play* store. The TV can also play online videos from multiple streaming media platforms such as Netflix, Prime Video, and YouTube. You can use Google Voice Assistant to control your lifestyle. Search for movies, ask specific questions, check the weather, all in control with your words within a up to a three-meter range. 360° Bluetooth remote control. Control the TV more freely. It also has a one-button access to Netflix and Prime video, so that your favorite contents are just one click away. SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 4KRAM Size 32 GBInternal Memory 3 GBProduct Weight 43. 6 KGScreen Size 86 inRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name GreyDisplay Type LEDProduct Height 128 cmProduct Width/Depth 22 cmModel Number Xiaomi TV Max 86"Model Name Xiaomi TV Max 86"</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b7f3cb86-37d5-49c1-81bc-d399519b8ff7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b79d9857-ab8e-4445-97f6-996a074dbc84/web/1_1728975128505.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>4190 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048384095168</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5891076341</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI Band 9 Smart Watch, Ultra-Thin Design And Comfortable Wearing, Scientific Sleep Analysis, Durable Battery Life, IOS And Android Charm Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>Ultra design: 1. 47 Inch amoled screen, 8. 99mm thin, 14g weightScientific sleep tracking: Upgraded sleep efficiency analysis, and sleep basic physiological analysisFast charging, durable battery life: 45 minutes to fully charge, 5 minutes fast charge can be used for 2 days. Maximum 2-week battery life, 9 days of normal useCustomized workout types: Huawei band 9 offers a multitude of workouts that you can customize as requiredCompatible with android and iOSOverviewHUAWEI Band 9 is a brand new, high-end sports band which has a full-sized color touchscreen, side button control, and is water resistant to 50 meters. This smart wearable product integrates a wide range of features, including workout detection, smart heart rate monitoring, workout assistant, multiple workout modes, sleep monitoring, message notifications, automatic SpO2 measurement, and music playback control. SpecificationsMaterial FluoroelastomerBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 14 gColour Name Charm PinkBand Material FluoroelastomerDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDFace/Dial Shape RectangularBand Size Medium/LargeProduct Length 43 mmProduct Height 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 25 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 47 inModel Number KIM-B19Model Name Huawei Band 9, KIM-B19</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c286a888-6587-496a-a6e7-1c7638087717</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/74b43be9-11a6-4e95-a672-bccf6d289eb4/web/1_1728970769165.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>193 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058910763416</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4058752790</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Camera C400 4MP 360° Rotation AI Human Detection 2.4GHz/5GHz Wi-Fi Support Compatible With Alexa Google Home</g:title>
      <g:description>Ultra-clear video in 2. 5K with 4MP camera:Updated to a 4MP camera with a resolution of 2560x1440With the large aperture and the 6P lens, the images delivered are more vivid:Combined with the 6P lens, the camera effectively reduces light refraction. Night vision with no visible red glow for clearer and safer monitoring:Sleep undisrupted with no visible red glow at night and no visual pollution. Smart IoT connectivity and interaction with other smart devices. Works with Google Home and AlexaHuman voices heard through large-diameter speakers with separate sound cavity are so real as if they are speaking to you in personOverviewThe dual-motor pan-tilt zoom design enables the lens to rotate up, down, left and right. When checking your smartphone outside your home, you can have a panoramic view of what happens at your home, giving you a complete sense of security. Real-time two-way voice calling with smart noise reduction enabled for clear conversations. AI-driven human detection and tracking; Smart IoT connectivity and interaction with other smart devices. Works with Google Home and Alexa. Fully encrypted to protect your privacy; Support for 2. 4GHz / 5GHz Wi-Fi; The H. 265 encoding technology allows you to save storage space and enable smoother data transmission. The high-quality, large diameter design of speakers enhances the stereo sound quality of speakers, while amplifying and restoring the true nature of sounds. When making two-way voice calls with your baby, you feel as if your baby is next to you. The product supports two-way real-time voice calling* and can pick up audio within a distance of up to 5 metres* for smoother call conversations; smart noise reduction is enabled for the microphone for clearer conversations. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 4 MPModel Number MJSXJ11CMModel Name MJSXJ11CM</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a07cc141-5b3b-4b9a-8c8a-060b707f9867</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7dec2802-6801-42fc-bd9e-46c9a3218988/web/1_1728969652494.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>146 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040587527903</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5793207441</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 5G CPE Pro Router Qualcomm 5G Chip,Fast Wi-Fi 6 AX5400,OFDMA,Mesh Networking,NFC,Game Acceleration,Heat Dissipation,Gigabit Ethernet Ports-CB0401 Global Version White</g:title>
      <g:description>Qualcomm 5G chip:Ignite your online adventures with the Qualcomm CPU, designed to support SA/NSA dual-mode networking and a wide range of global 5G frequency bands. Backwards compatible with 4G LTE and equipped with 3GPP R16 supportFaster internet, More fun:Experience a new era of web browsing, streaming, and gaming. The Xiaomi 5G CPE Pro boasts download speeds of up to a staggering 3. 4Gbps, ensuring you’re always ahead of the digital curveFast wifi 6 – 5400 class experience:With dual-band speeds reaching up to an astonishing 5378mbps, downloading large games and 4K films becomes a breeze. Gamers will relish in a smoother, more immersive experienceExtensive connectivity, Anywhere:The Xiaomi 5G CPE Pro transforms 4G/5G signals into robust Wi-Fi, enabling high-speed Internet connectivity anywhere there’s cellular coverageSmooth multi-device experience:With OFDMA + MU-MIMO technology, up to 16 devices can seamlessly share the connection with minimal latency, making it ideal for multiplayer gaming and group video chatsHigh 160MHz bandwidth:The innovative 160MHz bandwidth ensures a congestion-free “online motorway,” delivering faster downloads, smoother streaming, and a richer online experienceConvenience of NFC:Connect effortlessly with NFC technology. No more fussing with complicated passwords – simply tap to connect your Android-powered devicesEnhanced security with WPA3:Your network’s security is our priority. Benefit from next-gen encryption standards for peace of mind and a more secure home network. IPv6 for greater efficiency:Enjoy enhanced address space, forwarding efficiency, and security with IPv6 compatibilitySpecificationsColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard 5GModel Number CBO401Wireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac/ax，IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ab1e72c8-49af-48ea-a678-0fa5fb849595</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/96f3b5d1-e13d-428a-a4ad-caf6d669369b/web/1_1728971993410.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>819 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057932074418</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6110100240</g:id>
      <g:title>e World Single Monitor Arm Desk Mount | Gas Spring Monitor Arm | Full Motion Articulating Height Adjustable | Fits 21 22 23 24 27 30 32 Inch VESA Compatible Computer Screen | Clamp and Grommet Base.</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemUNIVERSAL SINGLE MONITOR ARM MOUNT - Fits all brands of 19 20 21 24 27 29 30 32 inch computer screens, with a maximum support weight of 20 pounds each, using the 75x75mm or 100x100mm VESA square bolt hole pattern found on the back of the monitors. Comes with interchangeable C-clamp or grommet base mount for use on desktops up to 3. 3 inches thick. FEATURES - Gas spring monitor arm is heavy duty, counterbalanced and makes for effortless adjustments and comes with integrated, hide-away cable management. Aircraft grade aluminum alloy construction will stand the test of time. FULLY ADJUSTABLE - Single arm monitor mount can tilt, swivel, raise and/lower (see 6th image down for details). Screen can be rotated a full 360 degrees for portrait or landscape orientation. EASY INSTALLATION: Monitor arm desk mount quickly mounts to desks and comes with all mounting hardware, tools, and instructions necessary for assembly. Quick-release detachable VESA plate mounts to back of monitor first, then slides onto arm in seconds!SATISFACTION GUARANTEED – We believe in the quality of our single arm monitor mount and satisfaction of our customers is our top priority. If you are not happy with our mount for any reason, Please feel free to contact us to get a FULL REFUND. Mounting type Tabletop MountMovement type Swivel, Tilt, ArticulatingBrand e world unbox happinessMaterial AluminumMaximum Compatible Size 32 Inches</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7e02ddb6-25d6-41c9-96d4-28efb14f87b8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/125c4b61-1550-4a1f-95b6-2c7331073087/web/1_1728975036838.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>73.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061101002409</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5706588906</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 67W Charging Combo Type-A UK White</g:title>
      <g:description>Including a charging cableUSB-A to type-COutput: 5V⎓3A / 5-20V⎓6. 2-3. 25A 67W maxInput: 100–240V~, 50/60Hz, 1. 7ASpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number BHR6036GB / MDY-12-EGModel Name 40036Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d9712aa8-796c-418c-bd1c-73c840c1c222</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/429318a4-85fc-4361-be6c-848d797907e3/web/1_1728978138832.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057065889064</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3981957202</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI B320-323 - 4G Router, WiFi 4, Unlocked Supports All SIM Cards & Networks, White</g:title>
      <g:description>HUAWEI 4G CPE 5s keeps the signal rapid, raring, and ready to go, whether it's your apartment, office, shop—or somewhere else!Plug-and-play Wi-Fi has never been so easy! Just insert a nano-SIM card and power on the device, to get connected without the hassle of broadband or network cables!Whether you're conferencing, streaming, downloading, or simply surfing the web, this mobile router makes everything seamless. HUAWEI 4G CPE 5s is powered by High Power User Equipment (HPUE). This ensures that the signal remains robust even in rural, mountainous, and industrial areas, and underground parking garages. HUAWEI 4G CPE 5s connects with up to 32 devices at the same time,4 so that everyone can watch, listen, game, and browse to their heart's contentSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFi 4Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard 4GModel Number B320-323Model Name B320-323Wireless Standard Value 300</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6ceb9c8c-4d4e-4b5b-83d3-d61e375529aa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/231892b4-f1a7-4b5c-91d6-f042d7d9606a/web/1_1728975294482.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>228 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039819572026</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6092204178</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 5 | Bluetooth Wireless Earbuds With Active Noise Cancellation | Bluetooth 5.3 | Up To 40 Hour Battery | Multi-Functional Touch Control Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Redmi Buds 5 has a noise reduction depth of 46dB, which is 11dB higher than Redmi Buds 4. And the noise reduction effect has been improved to 3. 5 times. Up to 99. 5% reduction in background noiseSupport broadband noise reduction at 2000Hz, covering more low-frequency scenes in daily lifeSupports three gear noise reduction and transparency mode adjustment, allowing for comfortable gear selection in different environmentsSupporting call anti wind noise function, Redmi adopts Xiaomi's self-developed AI anti wind noise algorithm for the first time, which can withstand wind speeds up to 6m/sIndependent rear chamber structure design, four sound effects settingsSingle 10 hours battery life for full day useEquipped with a charging box, the 40 hours battery life for one week useEquipped with super-fast charging, charging for 5 minutes and listening to music for 2 hoursSupport for Google Fast pair, dual device connectivitySpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type On-EarModel Number M2316E1 | BHR7627GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6dff200c-c2d3-4656-9bba-365fd5d991f2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e677bed0-78ce-4bdf-a8a7-9eee32bed5cd/web/1_1728976723769.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>121.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060922041789</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7845447029</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Camera C301 | 3MP with 2K Image Quality | MJA1 Security Chip | Voice Control | 8GB to 256GB microSD Supported | Cloud Storage</g:title>
      <g:description>2K image quality, more reliable home protectionPhysical lens shielding protecting privacy at the sourceMJA1 security chip, finance-grade data protectionFully encrypted data transmission, AES-128 encryption for cloud data, and customisable sleep time. With 3MP and a resolution of 2304×1296, the camera displays 2K imagesLarge aperture and 4P lens delivering more vivid images360° Horizontal view 107° Vertical viewReal-time two-way voice callsLarge-diameter speaker for clear remote callsFull colour night vision for longer colour image timeEnhanced infrared night vision for clear images on dark nightsHuman detection and active alertOverviewPhysical lens shielding, protecting privacy at the source The camera lens can be hidden upwards into the body for physical shielding, ensuring security and peace of mind MJA1 security chip, finance-grade data protection Each chip has a unique key and credential, effectively ensuring data communication and storage security, and providing reassuring finance-grade protection. Fully encrypted to protect your privacy Fully encrypted data transmission, AES-128 encryption for cloud data, and customisable sleep time. 3MP ultra-clear visual experience With 3MP and a resolution of 2304x1296, the camera displays 2K images, providing more subtle details and more realistic visuals. Large aperture and 4P lens, delivering more vivid images Featuring a large aperture and 4P lens, the camera effectively reduces light refraction, delivering clear and crisp image quality that provides a transparent and lifelike viewing experience. Dual gimbals for flexible rotation, worry-free large viewing angle The dual-axis pan-tilt-zoom motor enables you to control the camera’s lens with your smartphone, allowing it to rotate in any direction—up, down, left, or right—for a wider viewing angle and a more secure viewing experience. Real-time two-way voice calls, remote communication with family Real-time two-way voice calls and a 5-meter sound pickup range allow you to chat with family anytime, anywhere. Large-diameter speaker for clear remote calls Using an embedded large-diameter speaker with a separate sound cavity and a microphone featuring intelligent noise cancellation, the camera provides a loud and clear voice during your remote calls with your family. Full colour night vision for longer colour image time With the assistance of the built-in high-sensitivity image sensor, the camera can better adapt to low-light environments and retain colour images for a long period of time. Enhanced infrared night vision for clear images on dark nights The camera has six built-in infrared illuminators and can capture clear images even on dark nights without producing red light or disturbing your family's sleep. Human detection and active alert The camera supports local AI-based human detection to detect humans more accurately and quickly without on-cloud processing. When someone is detected, the camera automatically sends an alert to your smartphone Easy to view Slide through the timeline to easily find and view videos. Voice control Work with Alexa or Google Assistant Support for flat and inverted mounting, suitable for multiple scenarios Thoughtful design for a seamless user experience Two storage options, choose as you like H. 265 encoding technology Save storage space and bandwidth with smooth video playbackSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 3 MPModel Number BHR8683GL | MBC23 | C301Model Name Xiaomi Smart Camera C301Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/82a15966-6170-4e8d-b7fd-a86ba2016b3f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/731a8ca9-2b17-4263-9d1e-adfd712f4934/web/1_1728977221706.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>116 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078454470298</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3213767052</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Band 8 Pro, High-Resolution Large 1.74" AMOLED Display Black</g:title>
      <g:description>1. 74”AMOLED screen,60Hz high refresh rate,336PPICorning GG3 cover glass, more solid compare to 7proSupport ambient light sensor that allow the display brightness to automatically adjust for your eyes4-channel monitoring channel(Increase heart rate accuracy by 10% and blood oxygen accuracy by 5%)All-day SpO2 level tracking, continuous sleep monitoring, 24-hours heart rate monitoring, and sleep breathing monitoring150+ workout modes to record your heart rate and burned calories. 10 on-wrist running courses, could vibrate and light the screen to remind you to meet your heart rate and pace goals. 3D warm up and Relaxation Private Education CoursesBuilt-in GNSS Support independent GNSS, supporting 5-star positioning system: Beidou, GPS, GLONASS, Galileo, qzss. Up to 14-day battery lifeSupport 14 days daily use and 6 days AOD use. 5ATM water resistanceSupports 50 meter deep waterproofingOverviewXiaomi Smart Band 8 Pro Black, 1. 74”AMOLED screen,60Hz high refresh rate,150+ workout modes to record your heart rate and burned calories, Updated ID apperance, metallic frame that coated with NCVM, Support 14 days daily use and 6 days AOD use, Supports 50 meter deep waterproofingSpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 74 inModel Number BHR8017GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/da0f5470-489c-4335-a16d-3154549f7cef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/380f2159-d5c6-484b-8398-dca506a24346/web/1_1728976862928.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>198 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032137670528</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5865481604</g:id>
      <g:title>EleTab Dual Monitor Mount Stand - Height Adjustable Monitor Arm Stand Fully Articulating Counterbalance Gas Spring Desk Mount for Two 17 to 32 inch Screens</g:title>
      <g:description>Mounting type Wall Mount, Tabletop MountMovement type ArticulatingBrand EleTabMaterial Alloy SteelMaximum Compatible Size 32 InchesAbout this itemmanufacturer: OtherItem Trademark: OTHERItem Category: Flat Screen Display Mount</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/329278f8-69f0-4fb1-aad6-8cbe99f40445</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7a5ce811-a7f8-4bd7-9730-aeaa69c38e7f/web/1_1728975484930.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058654816041</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4099671921</g:id>
      <g:title>Nothing Ear Stick White</g:title>
      <g:description>Nothing Ear (stick) - Wireless Half In-Ear Earbuds, Bass Lock Technology, Bluetooth 5. 2, Waterproof, White. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 36 mAhProduct Weight 54. 6 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessAverage Battery Life Less than 8 hrsUsage Type Business (Call/work)What's In The Box 1. TWS set (a pair of earbuds and 1 charging case. ) 2. Type-C to Type-C cable 3. User guide 4. Safety and Warranty informationAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WiredEarplug Type EarbudsProduct Length 88 mmProduct Height 30 mmFeatures Bluetooth, Volume Control, Water ResistantModel Number B157Model Name B157Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cb800111-130a-4f8f-a4d9-d49abfa8d3c9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e1a7429b-fff4-4dc6-be64-329c85be7da1/web/1_1728980659743.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>219 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040996719210</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8339167146</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi AX3200 High-Speed Performance Wi-Fi 6 802.11ax Wireless Frequency Dual-band Wi-Fi Offers Both 2.4GHz and 5GHz Swift Wireless Speed Up to 2976Mbps Reliable Connection For Up to 254 Devices Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Fast 3202Mbps Wi-Fi 6*ultra-fast wireless experienceMesh networking support. Seamless, whole-home Wi-Fi 6 coverageOFDMA Multi-device transmission with less congestionSupports 4x4 MU-MIMO multiple antennas on the router to serve multiple devicesSpecificationsColour Name BlackWireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard 5GModel Number AX3200/DVB4314GLModel Name AX3200/DVB4314GLWireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac/ax，IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4b852d51-9f15-4dc7-8165-3462870330fd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/afbb60ae-a413-48c2-8726-2f91c334161e/web/1_1728980796631.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>192.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083391671462</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3102664731</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 33W Charging Combo Type A White</g:title>
      <g:description>Smart device identification. AC 100-240V wide range voltageAutomatic power adjustmentEnhanced safetySpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number 40038Model Name 40038Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ddaf1aed-e94d-4372-ae61-4812d047f7a8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6d34e657-da2c-4e67-ad0f-78157ec9b57a/web/1_1728982257875.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>48 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031026647313</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9077667739</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mini LED Gaming Monitor G Pro 27i | E-sports flagship | 180Hz high refresh rate | HDR1000 Bright picture | FreeSync Graphics | 1ms Fast response | 1152-zone Mini LED | RGB ambient light Multicolor</g:title>
      <g:description>HDR1000 Clear and bright picture180Hz high refresh rate Silky smooth gaming experienceFreeSync For tear-free graphics1ms Fast response1152-zone Mini LED Outstanding picture qualityQuantum dots and a wide colour gamut 99% DCI-P3RGB ambient light E-sports appearanceComfortable low blue light TÜV Low Blue Light CertificationOverviewOutstanding picture quality-Premium Mini LED for a brilliant superior display 1152-zone Mini LED with 4608 beads. Every detail, meticulously displayed The full-array Mini LED backlight technology with 1152 zones and 4608 beads provides precise control over the image display and delivers exquisite detail and captivating light and shadow effects. SpecificationsProduct Weight 6. 8 KGScreen Size 27 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Screen Features High Refresh RateRefresh Rates 180HzMonitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name MulticolorDisplay Type IPSConnection Type DisplayPortSet Includes Display x1 Base x1 Power adaptor x1 User manual x1 Colour accuracy report x1 Base mount x1 DP cable x1What's In The Box Display x1 Base x1 Power adaptor x1 User manual x1 Colour accuracy report x1 Base mount x1 DP cable x1Adaptive Sync Technology NoneProduct Length 613. 35 mmProduct Height 526. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 169. 45 mmWattage 65 WFeatures Adjustable Tilt Function, Backlit, Gaming, High Refresh Rate Display, VESA CompatibleModel Number P27QBA-RGPGLModel Name Xiaomi Mini LED Gaming Monitor G Pro 27iNumber of HDMI Ports 2Number of Display Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f56ec052-6d7f-4f99-97c6-a58de312c198</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/af3e91ec-94b4-4cd4-9498-7f4f7dbfbb99/web/1_1728980009669.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1249 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090776677391</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7915790509</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Band 8 Active | 1.47" LCD Display | Slim 9.99mm Ultra-Slim Body | 5ATM Water Resistant | up to 14 Days Battery Life | 100+ watch faces | 50+ Workout Mode Full Scale Fitness Tracking Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Vibrant 1. 47" TFT display: 1. 47”big screen, easier to view information. Appropriate UI/UX design, display more and detailed information on every pageLight 9. 99mm ultra-slim bodyFull-scale fitness tracking: All-day heart rate monitoring. Advanced sleep tracking. All-day SpO2 monitoringColorful straps and watch faces: 3 colorful TPU straps to choose your style. 100+ watch faces and could customize your own photo to show on bandWater resistant up to 50m: 5ATM water proof level that can be used during swimmingUltra long battery life: Up to 14-days battery life for normal daily use50+ Workout modes, including 10 professional workout modes, suitable for sports beginnersOverviewThe skin-friendly TPU material is soft, smooth and more waterproof, enabling you to exercise freely. A full spectrum of color combinations allows you to show your unique personality. The brand-new interface and more than 100 watch faces to choose from allow you to match faces and straps according to your personal preferences and style. SpecificationsColour Name BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Model Number M2302B1, BHR7422GLModel Name Smart Band 8 Active Black, M2302B1, BHR7422GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4e1e61c1-ec52-4694-b24e-12761159b49f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a92136d0-2bbd-4c15-895c-069f217068f7/web/1_1728980530444.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>74 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079157905094</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8420142081</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Outdoor Speaker 30W IP67 Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>POWERFaUL SPEAKER: With a power output of 30W, this Xiaomi Sound Outdoor speaker delivers high-quality sound and impressive volumeHEAVY DUTY DESIGN: Built for outdoor use, features a water and dust resistant housing, ideal for camping, pools, or outdoor parties. Long battery life: Enjoy up to 12 hours of continuous playback on a single charge thanks to its 2600mAh battery. Wireless connectivity: Bluetooth 5. 4 compatible0 for stable connection and hassle-free audio streaming from your device. OverviewThe Xiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W is a powerful portable speaker designed to bring sound to your outdoor adventures. With 30W output power and sturdy construction, this Bluetooth speaker will let you enjoy your favorite music with high-quality sound anywhere. Its long battery life gives you up to 12 hours of continuous playback, while its IP67 rating makes it water and dust resistant, ideal for camping, going to the beach, or just relaxing in the backyard. In addition, its compact and lightweight design makes it easy to carry. With a Bluetooth range of up to 25 meters, you can control your music wirelessly from your smart device. The Xiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W is the perfect companion for your outdoor adventures, offering you powerful and long-lasting sound in a portable, rugged package. SpecificationsColour Name BlueConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life 6 HoursProduct Length 9. 2 cmProduct Height 18 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 1 cmModel Number 30W SpeakerModel Name 30W Speaker</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/57839f2e-2c9c-442b-905f-2882a5218ef2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/79951187-6417-405c-bae4-a1e74f8bcb4f/web/1_1728981747586.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>153 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084201420812</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5222962572</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi True Wireless Redmi Buds 3 With Charging Case White</g:title>
      <g:description>The dual high-sensitivity microphones built into the Redmi Buds 3, coupled with mic with Qualcomm cVc echo canceling and noise suppression technology, dynamically reduce ambient noise and effectively minimize echoesDelivers crystal clear voice quality no matter where you are. And with a 95ms ultra-low latency function to ensure sound and picture synchronization when playing gamesThe Pop-up function just needs to simply open the charging case and tap the phone screen when the pop-up window appears, connecting and paring so easyThe battery levels of the earbuds and the charging case can be seen at a glanceRedmi buds 3 equips Qualcomm QCC3040 chip and Bluetooth 5. 2 technology delivers faster sound transmission, more stable, low power consumptionEquipped with a 12 mm dynamic driver deliver rich 3D surround stereo bass tones, clear high tones, and consistently superior sound qualitythe built-in light sensor will pause the music when one earphone is removed, and then put it on, the music will be resumed automaticallyOverviewThe dual high-sensitivity microphones built into the redmi buds 3, coupled with mic with qualcomm cvc echo canceling and noise suppression technology, dynamically reduce ambient noise and effectively minimize echoes. Delivers crystal clear voice quality no matter where you are. And with a 95ms ultra-low latency function to ensure sound and picture synchronization when playing games. 【Miui pop-up window function brings easy and quickly paring】: the pop-up function just needs to simply open the charging case and tap the phone screen when the pop-up window appears, connecting and paring so easy. And the battery levels of the earbuds and the charging case can be seen at a glance. Note please: only support xiaomi smartphones(mi 11 lite 5g, mi 10 lite 5g, mi 10t, redmi note 10 5g, redmi note 10 pro, etc. ), And the miui version should be upgraded to the latest stable version. 【In-ear detection &amp;amp; bluetooth 5. 2 &amp;amp; Stereo sound】: redmi buds 3 equips qualcomm qcc3040 chip and bluetooth 5. 2 Technology delivers faster sound transmission, more stable, low power consumption. Equipped with a 12 mm dynamic driver deliver rich 3d surround stereo bass tones, clear high tones, and consistently superior sound quality. And the built-in light sensor will pause the music when one earphone is removed, and then put it on, the music will be resumed automatically. 【Type-c interface fast charging &amp;amp; extra long battery life】: equipped type-c interface and 10-minute fast charge can enjoy up to 1. 5 Hours playback. Though small and lightweight, the redmi buds 3 offers both power and comfort. Enjoy up to 5 hours of battery life on a single charge, or up to 20 hours' use when paired with the charging case. 【Ultra-light &amp;amp; ip54 dust water resistant】: weighing only 4. 5G(0. 158Oz) each, the small exquisite fuselage which closely fit the contours of your ear canal, it's not easy to lose or fall out when you wear them moving or running. Redmi buds 3 true wireless earbuds have been expertly designed to meet ip54* dust and water resistance standards(level 5 dustproof and level 4 water-resistant), making the earbuds safe from spills and sweat. SpecificationsBattery Size 310 mAhProduct Weight 27. 7 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box Headphone AccessoriesAudio Headphone Type In-EarProduct Length 5. 9 inProduct Height 1. 02 inProduct Width/Depth 2. 95 inModel Number M2104E1/BHR5174GLModel Name Redmi buds 3Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d4efb325-3854-4214-a213-9f2906883386</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ead89703-adf6-49ab-94ad-b54ddd98231d/web/1_1728988836936.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>43.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052229625724</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3872166543</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Outdoor Camera CW400 | 2.5K Ultra-Clear Picture Quality | IP66 Water Resistance | 360° Horizontal View And 160° Vertical View | AI Human Detection | Dual-Antenna Network</g:title>
      <g:description>4MP with large aperture ultra-clear 2. 5K picture qualityFour-light, smart full-colour night vision truly clear images, even in the dark nightProfessional design with IP66 water resistance ready for tough-weather conditionsHorizontal and vertical dual gimbals more flexible and reliableHigh-gain dual-antenna design enhanced, clearer wi-fi signalTwo-way voice calling to make conversation easier Smart noise cancellation for any outdoor environmentAI human detection to effectively filter out false alarms warning you only when a person is detectedAudible and visual warning, active defense instant alarms sent to your smartphoneTime-lapse photography record your wonderful memoriesMJA1 security chip maximum privacy and safetyLocal and cloud dual storage double protection of critical informationSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 4 MPModel Number BHR7625HK | MJSXJ04HL | CW400</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/58320d4a-78bb-401c-94d4-28336c295dc7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fda00e7f-c019-400b-8e1f-1b6467b9662d/web/1_1728987252391.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>248.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038721665437</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8700273421</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Outdoor Camera Bw500 | 2.5K Full-Colour Night Vision | Ip67 Dust And Water Resistance | 8Gb Built-In Storage | Encrypted Data Transmission | White</g:title>
      <g:description>2. 5K clear and smooth imaging A leap in picture quality that is truly outstandingf/1. 6 large aperture Superior imaging with more light transmission36° wide field of view Enhanced wide-angle coverage minimises blind spots10m full-colour night vision Security around the clockBlack and white night visionFull-colour night visionSuper large battery capacity for 180 days of worry-free recordingThe 10,000mAh* high-capacity battery ensures long-lasting power for up to six monthsLow-power consumption system design Energy-efficient on-demand power distribution5W solar panels Keep recording even during power outages that can buy separatelyProfessional IP67* dust and water resistance rating Protection against wind and rain1. 2T computing chip Efficient detection for intelligent protectionOverviewAI-powered for efficient protection and security. Boasts 6 fantastic features and is powerful and durable. 6-month durable battery ensures worry-free usage. Feel more assured about your movement. 2. 5K full-colour night vision. Enhanced security with clear nighttime imaging. 1. 2T powerful computing power. Fast and accurate detection. Professional IP67 dust and water resistance rating. Stay protected in tough weathers. Encrypted data transmission Protect your data privacy. 8GB built-in storage. Keep data secureSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 2. 5 pxModel Number MJSXJ06BY | BW500Model Name Xiaomi Outdoor Camera BW500</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f19ac8aa-644c-4fd6-bd03-5f39fca2bf8e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f375fca1-cfe9-4ae3-865d-9b72f0e07fa4/web/6_1728987819507.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>344 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087002734218</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7796655169</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Speaker With Built-in Google Home White</g:title>
      <g:description>A kind of sound effect mode of human hearing sense debuggingWirelessly stream high-quality sound from your smartphone or tabletOffers crystal clear phone call experience with its built-in noise-cancelling speakerphoneSpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box 1 x Xiaomi Mi Smart Speaker Google Assistant, 1 x Charging Cable, 1 x User ManualModel Number L09GModel Name Mi Smart Speaker</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/be620d78-6a8a-4e60-87e0-127b60c01184</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3a2102a5-ed87-4e2f-9473-069979eab70c/web/1_1728988433221.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>144 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077966551693</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8317137488</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 10W Wireless Power Bank Black</g:title>
      <g:description>10w wireless charging10000mah capacityDual usb a output portsUsb c input portLed indicator lightsCompatible with qi enabled devicesMulti layer safety protectionSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number BHR5460GL/WPB15PDZMModel Name BHR5460GL/WPB15PDZMItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/28c9f4a9-d0de-4c4f-98e0-6f0d66df3170</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2d2839ad-a700-4e77-96b7-0497f1ba0968/web/1_1728988625561.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>83.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083171374880</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9805084044</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Smart Plug Wi-Fi White</g:title>
      <g:description>Control and automate your electrical devices anywhere with your fingertips with the connected WiFi socket. Plug works with any box without the need for a hub or paid subscription serviceVoice control of your devices connected to the outlet via Google AssistantSpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name WhiteConnection Type WifiModel Number GMR4015GLModel Name Smart PlugItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/82f824a9-2dd5-4245-a53a-e56bf528a31e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dee18bd7-2d69-49e6-8f06-cdd4c6e4d06b/web/1_1728989345065.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>79 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098050840448</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9455261474</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Power Bank 3 Ultra Compact 10000 mAh Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Our world is getting faster and faster. That's why we have the best Power Banks, such as the new Xiaomi Power Bank 3. Designed to allow you to charge everything, it allows you to charge up to 3 devices at the same time as it has one USB-A port and two high-quality USB-C ports. You can charge all kinds of devices in the easiest way thanks to its maximum power of 22. 5W. It also has the latest fast-charging technology, which will keep your devices charged in the best way. This is a high-powered model which only takes 3. 5 hours to fully charge a device if we use a USB port, charging two devices simultaneously in 6 hours. The most interesting powerbank by Xiaomi. Take this easy-to carry model eveywhere. This new PowerBank is very thin, so you can carry it with you without any problem. As for its design, it includes four LEDs located under a button that indicates power parameters and the current maximum capacity, you can check at all times the amount of energy we have in our portable battery. These will light up intermittently to indicate the percentage that is left. It is made of aluminium alloy and is highly resistant to sudden changes in temperature, short circuits, hardware overheating and other problems you may have when using it. The most spectacular model you will find. Battery type: lithium polymer battery Capacity: 10000mAh 3. 7V (37Wh) Nominal Capacity: 5500mAh 5. 1V / 2. 6A Maximum output power: 22. 5W Operating temperature: 0 ° C ~ 40 ° C Input port: Micro-USB, USB-C Output port: 2 x USB-A 1 x USB-C 1 x Micro USB Input: 5. 0V 2. 0A / 5. 0V 2. 4A Output: USB-A port: 5V 2. 4A / 9. 0V 2A / 12. 0V 1. 5A MAX USB-C port: 5V 3A (22. 5W MAX) Charging time: Approximately 3. 5 hours (9V / 2A or 12V / 1. 5A adapter, standard cable) Approximately 6 hours (5V / 2A adapter, standard cable) Quick charge: 3. 0 + PD Dimensions: 90 x 63. 9 x 24. 4 mm Weight: 200 grOverview1 x USB-A, 1 x USB-C - Power Protection - Status Button - LED indicator - Black Colour - Lightweight &amp;amp; Portable Design - Simultaneous Charging of 3 Devices - Fast ChargeSpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WiredModel Number BHR4412GLModel Name Power BankItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4f1f3fa9-5a55-43d8-be9b-d7dd3fb4c767</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c5b1a0b0-f0e4-41a1-a05c-acd07827312a/web/1_1728989121124.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>72.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094552614747</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6100369810</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi AX3000 Mesh System NE (2- Pack) WiFi 6 White</g:title>
      <g:description>Mesh Seamless Roaming : Xiaomi Mesh technology enables your smartphone to seamlessly and automatically switch to higher-speed Wi-Fi nodes. Whether you are moving from room to room or from upstairs to downstairs. NFC Quick Connection : Simply touch the NFC area of your phone to the top of the router to quickly connect to wi-fi without manually entering the password. Extensive Multiple Connection : Supporting simultaneous connections for up to 256 devices. Whether streaming, gaming, or working, it delivers a robust network experience. Easy To Use : The two router are pre-paired at the factory. Choose any one of the routers to complete the network configuration, the other one will automatically establish a mesh network with it upon power- on. You can use the MI Home/Xiaomi App. Package Content : Router x 2, Power Adaptor, Network Cable, User Manual. OverviewIt works with routers that support Xiaomi Mesh for networking, to achieve seamless network coverage for larger households so you can connect anywhere. SpecificationsProduct Weight 460 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableSet Includes Package Content : Router x 2, Power Adaptor, Network Cable, User Manual. What's In The Box Router x 2, Power Adaptor, Network Cable, User Manual. Wireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard AXProduct Length 8. 9 cmProduct Height 21. 4 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 9 cmModel Number RD28Model Name AX3000 NEItem Quantity 1Wireless Standard Value AX3000</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/329fe799-8d89-45fe-a563-67b5bb7538e5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/303106f1-9c65-4dda-b2f9-6c723e867db2/web/1_1728989507232.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>334 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061003698106</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2860721239</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 50W Wireless Charging Stand Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Efficient and safe. Optimal viewing angle. Quiet heat dissipationCharging on the go, 100% charge in 42 minutes. Compatible with the Qi wireless charging standardOptimal tilt angle. Built-in silent cooling fan perfect for desks or bedsides minimal noise12 layers of smart protection secure layered protectionSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number 40460Model Name 40460Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/355752ba-67a1-4dbe-aaf1-b6095689b27c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/60f3a633-edf9-47f0-9aef-a1872f14f7b7/web/1_1728990590943.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>169 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028607212398</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8169947615</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 13C Dual Sim Clover Green 6Gb Ram 128Gb 4G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Smooth 6. 74" 90Hz display50MP AI triple cameraMassive 5000mAh (typ) battery, Up to 23 hours of video streamingSupports 18W fast charging* 5 mins for 5 hours music playbackPowerful octa-core processor Up to 1tb expandable storageDurable quality you can trust, 500,000 times power button tests, 300 times Roller test, 20,000 times Headphone jack test, 20,000 times charging port testCorning® Gorilla® glass screen reliable protectionRedmi 13C's display helps reduce visual fatigue with both TÜV low blue light certification and TÜV flicker-free certificationRedmi 13C delivers smooth and stable performance thanks to the reliable MediaTek Helio G85, an octa-core processor that balances power and efficiencyOcta-core processor, Up to 2. 0GHz cpu speed, 290070 Antutu V10 benchmarkUp to 16gb with 8gb extended ramUp to 1tb expandable storageSpecificationsSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 74 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Clover GreenOperating System AndroidOperating System Number 13Processor Number G85Network Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTekNumber of Cores Octa CoreCondition NewModel Number 2311DRN14I | 23106RN0DAModel Name Redmi 13C Dual SIM Clover Green 6GB RAM 128GB 4G</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eb4c969e-3a7e-4d5b-9ce8-c584cdee8f32</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/87017a7a-07ce-49a8-bf94-b65729d4b366/web/1_1728989875578.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>348 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081699476154</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8454175550</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor X9b Dual SIM 5G Sunrise Orange 12GB RAM 256GB - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 1. 5K Retinal Resolution / SGS 5-star Whole-device Drop Resistance Certification / 5-fold Eye Protection[12GB RAM + 25G GB Memory] Enjoy great performance &amp;amp; plenty of room for photos, movies, songs, and apps—and 20GB Super large memory(RAM Turbo)108MP Lossless Capture Camera, 108MP main Camera/ Motion Capture/ 3X lossless Zoom[Superfast 5G performance] Unleash entertainment at 5G speed with the Qualcom Snapdragon, a powerful octa-core processor with frequencies up to 2. 1GHz. [Massive battery and speedy charging] Work and play nonstop with a long-lasting 5800mAh battery, then recharge quickly. OverviewA luxury look and Xtra power, Honor X9b 5G is designed to stand out with HONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 360° Anti-Drop Protection, 6. 78" Amoled+ 120Hz display. Capture incredibly clear photos and smoother videos with a 108MP+5MP+2MP camera system featuring motion capture &amp;amp; 3X lossless zoom. Honor X9b 5G is a device you will fall in love with at first touchSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5800 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 185 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 78 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Sunrise OrangeDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13Processor Number Qualcomm snapdragon SM6450Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 163. 6 mmProduct Height 75. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Accelerometer, Proximity SensorsModel Number ALI-NX1Model Name X9bPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c322f388-4e8e-4f74-a299-ff9b687cde03</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1f736094-534d-4139-83c1-3caf895a9d5a/web/1_1728994367807.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>925 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084541755506</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8900677693</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + ESIM Pink 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 1TB Storage, Pink, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 MAhInternal Memory 1 TBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 InSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber Of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BLIHMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/396f2c52-777b-4113-b386-b5582f08eb8b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b2380624-6bee-423b-9bd9-20ac0f0e7dd1/web/1_1728995244081.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089006776935</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8103281797</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWL3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7b49d733-eeaa-4fc1-871a-76c94e3f99df</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/efebdb91-cef3-461e-afe8-c17c995bd2f5/web/1_1728995947656.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081032817972</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6232216591</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - White Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN13</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c48988f9-ee29-4127-ac1f-dbd8e650ff7f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ee31558d-9809-4d98-8e32-0d02f263ba94/web/1_1728996462810.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062322165911</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
