<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>8156198574</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Samsung galaxy z flip6, AI phone, 12GB ram, 256GB storage, silver shadow, android smartphone, 50MP camera, flexcam, long battery lifeGalaxy ai: Your self-expression tool, galaxy z flip6, is compact and eye-catching, with galaxy AI and a pro-level 50mp cameraDesign: Most compact. Big impact. Galaxy z flip6's new floating design is modern, slim and sleek50mp camera: The upgraded 50MP wide rear camera processes your pics through the provisual engine to capture stunning scenes and richer portraitsFlexcam: The flexcam uses auto zoom to zoom in or out on subjects, and provides a preview on the flexwindow for a hands-free selfie experienceSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 4 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Flip 6Model Name Flip 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0e0087b4-9a94-4fb8-b1c6-e33210fc6c7f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f7c0e1ad-9ff5-4cf8-b552-4df937d52cd3/web/1_1729497110602.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081561985746</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1404908799</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24+ Single+eSIM Onyx Black 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Easy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24+ feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24+A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Onyx BlackDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24+Model Name Galaxy S24+Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ae3bc83f-7181-45b5-8ea6-704f4a2fff81</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8e801376-d974-4929-b1cb-1cf9bf15961d/web/1_1729497503586.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2580 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014049087991</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8687843954</g:id>
      <g:title>Microsoft Surface Pro Edition Copilot+ PC 13 Inch OLED Display, Snapdragon X Elite Processor/16GB RAM/1TB SSD/Qualcomm Adreno GPU/Windows 11 Home English Dune</g:title>
      <g:description>Engineered For Maximum Performance: Breeze through demanding multi-tasking and elevate your productivity, creativity, and entertainment experience! Microsoft Surface Pro (11th Edition) features the game-changing Snapdragon X Elite, one of the smartest and most efficient processors for Windows in its class. It also boasts 16GB LPDDR5X RAM with 3. 4 GHz max multithread frequency, offering supercharged performance, seamless responsiveness, stunning graphics, and low power consumption. AI Powerhouse: Unleash your full potential with the Snapdragon X Elite, featuring a Qualcomm AI Engine with an integrated Hexagon NPU to boost your creativity, elevate your video calls, fortify your security, and streamline your productivity. With blazing-fast speeds, Snapdragon X Elite can run generative AI LLM models over 13B parameters on-device. Plus, it supports Windows Studio Effects and various AI-accelerated applications to unlock endless possibilities. Smart &amp;amp; User-Friendly: Take advantage of next-level intelligence and convenience. Connect, stream, download, and sync efficiently with lightning-fast Wi-Fi 71 and HBS Multi-Link support. You can also enjoy smooth transitions between devices with Snapdragon Seamless, bask in incredible audio with the Snapdragon Sound™ Technology Suite, and get robust security with Qualcomm Secure Processing Unit – all designed to transform your user experience. Innovative Flexibility: Engineered to revolutionise your workflow, the Surface Pro perfectly merges the power of a laptop and the versatility of a tablet, all in one unit. Transform your device according to your needs, thanks to its iconic 165-degree fluid kickstand design and seamless compatibility with the Surface Pro Flex Keyboard (sold separately)2. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 3. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 2880x1920Colour Name DuneKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type PixelSenseDisplay Resolution Type QHDConnection Type HDMIAverage Battery Life 14 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version Windows 11 HomeOperating System WindowsUsage Type BusinessModel Series Microsoft Surface ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 12-CoreRAM Type DDR5External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number ZIB-00046Model Name Surface Pro 11 Copilot+ PCHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot YesNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version Qualcomm Snapdragon X Elite</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f151c41b-8c18-477e-8d4e-d07b8d1be632</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/563c1d42-ddf1-4678-9ac9-1f0694f263a4/web/3_1729501125611.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Microsoft</g:brand>
      <g:price>9500 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086878439548</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8487892399</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Single+eSIM Titanium Gray 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The legacy of Galaxy Note is alive and well. Write, tap, and navigate with the precision your fingers wish they had on the new, flat displayCapture stunning details with the most megapixels on a smartphone and AI processing. The enhanced ProVisual Engine recognises objects - improving colour tone, reducing noise, and bringing out detailWith 1. 6x larger pixels and a wider Tele OIS, photos and videos are brighter and more stable, making even distant subjects clearly stunning from sunup to sundown and everything in betweenSpace Zoom puts you in the middle of the action, even at night. With 1. 6x larger pixels and a wider Tele OIS, photos and videos are brighter and more stable — making even distant subjects clearly stunningWith massive capacity and greater energy efficiency, ultra's battery gives you extra life when it matters most you know, like the epic boss battle you've been gearing up forOverviewBehold the Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra smartphone, an exceptional amalgamation of incredible technology and superior sophistication. Whether you're typing up a storm or jotting something down, Note Assist makes a long story shortSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 8 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 3168x1440Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Titanium GrayDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature QuadFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24 UltraModel Name Galaxy S24 UltraPrimary Camera (MP) 200+50+12+10 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a992cd03-177b-4b0e-8d64-bf68505f8c72</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/70b68fec-3b80-4c99-aff6-c0d8a0cc0529/web/2_1729497300808.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3190 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084878923999</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1355585101</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 Dual SIM Yellow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Samsung galaxy z flip6, AI phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB storage, blue, android smartphone, 50MP camera, flexcam, long battery lifeGalaxy AI: Your self-expression tool, galaxy z flip6, is compact and eye-catching, with galaxy al and a pro-level 50MP cameraDesign: Most compact. Big impact. Galaxy z flip6's new floating design is modern, slim and sleek50MP camera: The upgraded 50mp wide rear camera processes your pics through the provisual engine to capture stunning scenes and richer portraitsFlexcam: The flexcam uses auto zoom to zoom in or out on subjects, and provides a preview on the flexwindow for a hands-free selfie experienceSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 4 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name YellowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Flip 6Model Name Flip 6</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f6466f80-6ac5-4f57-a292-8aeaf2dbd40d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4fa15de0-44b8-4dc1-bcc0-8281af9539a0/web/1_1729496979765.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2875 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013555851010</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3630013046</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Cobalt Violet, 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Easy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Cobalt VioletDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0dd0bf54-1ff0-496b-b733-6840cb78abf8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d2e5704a-4523-43c9-8df7-af5ade540424/web/1_1729507067529.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2449 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036300130468</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8446331314</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4614630f-05c6-4e3d-8468-aacc8fc0234f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e594dc37-82d4-4269-82d4-ccc4143df4e9/web/1_1729506279326.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4990 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084463313143</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7852521522</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 256GB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4dc8231d-886a-4068-945c-8de65077df12</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b8d5ba9c-893a-4700-85bb-752481220c86/web/1_1729486055657.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4553.05 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078525215223</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7504709502</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Air 2024 (6th Generation) M2 11-Inch 256GB Blue Wi-Fi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M2, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad AiriPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Air packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Air and an expansive 13″ iPad Air that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 7606 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type WifiDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad AirModel Name iPad AirPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/572ea4b4-1851-4b14-8551-7924a746aedc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cb2c5fb5-52ab-4296-894f-08ea4fe753d1/web/1_1729488074395.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2770 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075047095029</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5671451267</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 ( 5th Generation) M4 11-Inch, 256GB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1e43b8e8-4136-41ef-a833-c04b4fdf99ad</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fdec8558-8b58-4005-a827-f15eaf46d40c/web/2_1729489882839.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4590 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056714512674</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5751906574</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS + Cellular 42mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Ink Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Ink Sport LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWX83QA/AModel Name MWX83QA/A, MWX83ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/39175072-5409-4576-aef3-b561232f80d6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/19fb9365-8d6d-4af3-bf97-a5d150cfda36/web/1_1729490243522.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1995 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057519065747</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9666174008</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS + Cellular 40mm Midnight Aluminium Case With Midnight Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Midnight Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number MRG73QA/A , MRGA3QA/A, MRG73ZP/AModel Name MRG73QA/A , MRGA3QA/A, MRG73ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fe879728-f4b2-4346-bb8c-847a6b181091</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/91753235-5d94-4dd2-9a49-b15703857f44/web/1_1729488750220.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>888 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096661740089</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7047855222</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Gen) 10.9 inch Blue 64GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Blue 64GB 5GModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fa82f525-5fb1-4600-b6c9-10617cfc8b2c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f11987eb-9c86-4203-97aa-95248172b8e8/web/1_1729489573536.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1848.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070478552226</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3461599639</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Era 300 UK E30G1UK1BLKR2/E30G1AU1BLKR2 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>With next-level audio that hits from every direction, era 300 doesn’t just surround you, it puts you inside your musicConnect to all your content and devices using wifi, bluetooth, and 3. 5 mm line inImmerse yourself in an unrivaled dolby atmos experience when you pair two with arc or beam gen 2OverviewFeel sound all around. Spatial audio like only Sonos can do spatial audio. Introducing Era 300. SpecificationsProduct Weight 4. 47 KGColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Power CableProduct Length 169 mmProduct Height 189 mmProduct Width/Depth 260 mmFeatures Wireless, Bluetooth, Compact Size, Ethernet (LAN), SmartModel Number E30G1UK1BLKR2/E30G1AU1BLKR2Model Name Sonos Era 300 UK (Black)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/697dfc43-df0e-4e53-9468-8c3f2d3c569a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/13f54a9c-81b2-412a-9274-95ba8e1160b6/web/1_1729489356803.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1890 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034615996397</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8315285575</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Sub (Gen 3) -The Wireless Subwoofer for Deep Bass SUBG3AU1WHT White</g:title>
      <g:description>Compact design for easy carryingIntegrated with special drivers that eliminate vibration and rattle to enable you to hear pure bassMade with high-quality material for long-term useSpecificationsColour Name WhiteProduct Length 158 mmProduct Height 402 mmProduct Width/Depth 389 mmModel Number SUBG3AU1WHTModel Name SONOS SUBWOOFER SUBG3AU1WHT WHITE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/164817b8-942c-45b0-b595-60b292446974</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/78fd0deb-507f-4789-b156-b58f0a6189c7/web/1_1729490810312.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3590 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083152855759</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1867907068</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Gen) 10.9 inch Blue 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Blue 256GB 5GModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9c72f909-cadd-4bd2-9a27-93b4527d11fd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/954afd25-ab24-4353-8403-4e4e75c40210/web/1_1729491323425.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2590 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018679070682</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3612839025</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS + Cellular 46mm Silver Aluminium Case With Denim Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Denim Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 46 mmModel Number MWY03QA/A, MWY13QA/A, MWY13ZP/AModel Name MWY03QA/A, MWY13QA/A, MWY03ZP/A, MWY13ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ba5dbe80-938e-4b11-9ced-530d4025de75</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/67792c4b-ac4a-43f4-94b4-82bf7d8174b2/web/1_1729494335631.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036128390259</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6802055147</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Lilac Purple</g:title>
      <g:description>Compact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Lilac PurpleProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ed8bb25f-3a92-49a9-a01a-993f9d388d42</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/333f726f-fbd0-4c28-93e7-5aa578e44899/web/1_1729493104672.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>285 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068020551476</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6346754328</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS + Cellular 42mm Silver Aluminium Case With Denim Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Denim Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWX33QA/A, MWX43QA/AModel Name MWX33QA/A, MWX43QA/A, MWX33ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a3fd21da-4469-40af-adab-f2bb800b6628</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/184a382b-7d88-473f-be73-2ef3668d654c/web/1_1729494496168.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1949 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063467543282</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8939996505</g:id>
      <g:title>Sonos Move - Portable Speaker Black</g:title>
      <g:description>The durable, battery-powered smart speaker for outdoor and indoor listening. Get brilliant sound anywhere with the weatherproof and drop-resistant Move. Control with your voice, the Sonos app, and Apple AirPlay 2 at home, and stream via Bluetooth when WiFi isn't available. Finely tuned to your surroundingsEnjoy surprisingly rich bass, a wide soundstage, and automatic Trueplay tuning, which continually adapts the sound for where you are and what you’re listening to. Voice ControlThe Google Assistant and Amazon Alexa are built right in so on WiFi you can play music, check news, set alarms, get your questions answered, and more, completely hands free. WiFi and BluetoothStream over WiFi and connect Move to the rest of your Sonos system at home. Switch to Bluetooth when you're offline. Weather-resistantWith an IP56 rating, Move stands up to humidity, rain, snow, dust, salt spray, UV rays, and extreme heat and cold. Simple rechargingGet up to 11 hours of battery life. Set the speaker on the included indoor charging base for quick power whilst you listen, and get power wherever you need it with an additional charging base. Introducing Sonos RadioEnjoy thousands of stations, including live radio and exclusive programming, on your system through the Sonos app. SpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number MOVE1UK1BLKModel Name MOVE1UK1BLK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c63c8ee-b23c-43a6-a218-476aba3023a0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5db2b07d-a857-4627-8747-ab3bff8b0c1d/web/1_1729495406389.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089399965053</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3908152987</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24+ Single+eSIM Cobalt Violet, 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Easy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24+ feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24+A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Cobalt VioletDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24+Model Name Galaxy S24+Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6f199f63-fff3-4c74-8c1c-86a8a0869f27</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/13f293ea-dbd4-421b-be92-c077232f68f8/web/1_1729496808128.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2690 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039081529872</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
