<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>7760354322</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple HomePod Smart Speaker Space Gray</g:title>
      <g:description>Use HomePod to send messages using just your voice. And when you receive a text, Siri can read it to youHomePod is a hub for controlling your smart home accessories - from a single light bulb to the whole house - with just your voiceApple Music unlocks virtually every song you can imagine. Siri helps you find exactly what you want to hear, and what you want to hear next - including new music across a huge range of genres and moodsPlace HomePod anywhere in the room. It automatically analyzes the acoustics, adjusts the sound based on the speaker’s location, and separates the music into direct and ambient soundMulti-room speaker support with AirPlay 2, Six-microphone array for far-field Siri, Internal bass-EQ Microphone, High-excursion woofer with custom amplifier, Stereo pair capable, Array of seven horn-loaded tweeters, each with its own custom amplifierOverviewAudio Technology -- High-excursion woofer with custom amplifier, Array of seven horn-loaded tweeters, each with its own custom amplifier, Six-microphone array for far-field Siri, Internal low-frequency calibration microphone for automatic bass correction, , Direct and ambient audio beamforming, Transparent studio-level dynamic processing. Audio Sources -- Apple Music, iTunes Music Purchases, iCloud Music Library with an Apple Music or iTunes Match subscription, Beats 1 Live Radio, Apple Podcasts, AirPlay other content to HomePod from iPhone, iPad, iPod touch, Apple TV, and Mac. Audio Formats -- HE-AAC (V1), AAC (16 to 320 Kbps), protected AAC (from iTunes Store), MP3 (16 to 320 Kbps), MP3 VBR, Apple Lossless, AIFF, WAV, and FLAC. Touch Surface -- Tap or hold + or – for volume up/down, Touch and hold for Siri, Tap to play/pause music or Siri, Double-tap to skip, Triple-tap to skip back . System Requirements -- iPhone 5s or later, iPad Pro, iPad (5th generation), iPad Air or later, iPad mini 2 or later, or iPod touch (6th generation) running iOS 11. 2. 5 or later; 802. 11 Wi-Fi Internet access; Apple Music subscription for full music functionalityThe all-around sound of home. HomePod is a breakthrough speaker that adapts to its location and delivers high-fidelity audio wherever it’s playing. Together with Apple Music and Siri, it creates an entirely new way for you to discover and interact with music at home. And it can help you and your whole family with everyday tasks — and control your smart home — all with just your voice. Major sound, minor scale. This purposefully designed speaker creates rich, nuanced sound that defies its size. HomePod combines custom Apple-engineered audio technology and advanced software to deliver precision sound that fills the room. And at less than 18 centimetres tall, HomePod fits anywhere in your home. Deep bass with range you can feel. The Apple-designed high-excursion woofer is positioned at the top of the speaker facing upwards, creating a wide range of deep bass that surpasses any traditional speaker. A six-microphone array, along with an internal bass-EQ microphone, analyses and compensates for the effect of the room on the bass response, providing rich, consistent sound. And a powerful motor drives the diaphragm a remarkable 20 millimetres, so the bass shines through even when the volume is low. Far and away an incredible listener. Designed to be seen and heard. HomePod is wrapped in a seamless mesh fabric designed for aesthetics and acoustic performance. Available in white and space grey, it’s gorgeous from every angle — yet virtually transparent to the sound waves passing through it. SpecificationsProduct Weight 2. 5 KGColour Name Space GrayConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessProduct Height 172 mmProduct Width/Depth 142 mmModel Number MQHW2Model Name MQHW2Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/93617235-e868-49d6-a2fb-e8e2ff16fca4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6c950cc7-679a-461d-bf85-0453fb6003e7/web/1_1732884338825.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1317.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077603543227</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2647589753</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 256GB, WiFi - Blue - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YESFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - BlueModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - BluePrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c9742a2a-569d-49cc-b6c2-bbe2bacbbadd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76086366-8746-43af-97e7-2b5cd5b6ee33/web/1_1732885158881.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2228.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026475897532</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9449237303</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Air 2024 (6th Generation) M2 13-Inch 128GB Starlight 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M2, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad AiriPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Air packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Air and an expansive 13″ iPad Air that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name StarlightCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad AirModel Name iPad AirPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/88f68651-86e4-4411-b6b5-bdbf74b8e582</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f2c220db-4aac-456d-a073-4e90789bebf7/web/1_1732885047695.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094492373032</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9330108136</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MX2Y3ZS/A Liquid XDR Retina 16-Inch Display, M4 Pro Chip 14-Core /48GB RAM/512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>16-core Neural Engine16-inch Liquid Retina XDR display²Three Thunderbolt 5 ports, HDMI port, SDXC card slot, headphone jack, MagSafe 3 portMagic Keyboard with Touch IDForce Touch trackpad 140W USB-C Power Adapter Apple IntelligenceSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 48 GBInternal Memory 512 GBScreen Size 16. 2 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS SequoiaOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedProcessor Version M4 Pro Chip 14-Core CPU 20-Core GPUFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number MX2Y3ZS/AModel Name MacBook ProHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version M4 Pro Chip 14-Core CPU 20-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/20c21190-c86e-4f54-b8bb-7c87e1d8297d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5a612176-3e7f-419e-809c-d754e6325fa6/web/1_1732884921656.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>12399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093301081366</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7470103857</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MX303 Liquid XDR Retina 16-Inch Display, M4 Max Chip 14-Core /36GB RAM/1TB</g:title>
      <g:description>16-core Neural Engine16-inch Liquid Retina XDR display²Three Thunderbolt 5 ports, HDMI port, SDXC card slot, headphone jack, MagSafe 3 portMagic Keyboard with Touch IDForce Touch trackpad 140W USB-C Power Adapter Apple IntelligenceSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 36 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 16. 2 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type 4. 5KAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS SequoiaOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number MX303ZS/A MX303X/AModel Name MacBook ProHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 4SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version M4 Max Chip 14-Core CPU 32-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a74ee537-6030-405b-b7d4-ac90b68f814a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f96e0d2e-9a55-4821-89e5-051cdb0e5532/web/1_1732884144202.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>16090 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074701038570</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8403949058</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 FE Silver 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The vibrant screen lets details shine, and the cinematic experience is enhanced with the incredible sound by AKGYou can multi-task with ease and launch up to three apps all at once. And with over 1TB of storage when you use a microSD card, your important files can stay at handYou're watching videos, giving you plenty of time for a streaming marathonSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 12. 4 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band LTECamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless BluetoothModel Number SM-X516BZSAMEAModel Name Tab S9 FEPrimary Camera (MP) 8 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d2834109-551a-4025-ace7-7c6659b218fb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/91591ed2-2c0a-411d-b182-7fe007ab0a82/web/1_1732884770841.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1682 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084039490582</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3283036749</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Natural Titanium Case With Natural</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple new LaunchSpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Natural Titanium Milanese Loop - MConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size Small/MediumSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MX5R3QA/AModel Name RZ410633739C</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ea0cf6f0-4717-46ca-bc01-e267369534a8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/59bb1e78-dced-4221-81ae-ecb69802c15a/web/1_1733286778410.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3694 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032830367497</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1881430035</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS + Cellular 42mm Rose Gold Aluminium Case With Plum Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Plum Sport LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 42 mmModel Number MWXC3QA/AModel Name MWXC3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/74c35501-4e29-47fa-a02e-72182abc839b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d1bd76bc-d483-469a-9ae7-7d796166b6b0/web/1_1733288396146.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2095.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018814300353</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7733663334</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS 45mm Starlight Aluminium Case With Starlight Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app. ECG app. High and low heart rate notifications. Irregular rhythm notification. Emergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimatesBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Starlight Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 45 mmModel Number MR983QA/A , MR983ZP/A, MR9P3LL/A, MR963LL/A, MR983LL/AModel Name MR983QA/A, MR983LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/517e7ed4-5e5e-4e95-b149-6004d960f71d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5e7031cb-85b2-4d89-9725-09ca1d6e3e94/web/1_1733288821549.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1570.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077336633349</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6578367326</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MNWC3 16-Inch  Apple M2 Pro Chip With 12-Core CPU/16GB RAM/512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>Go all day thanks to the power-efficient design of the M2 Pro or M2 Max chip. And MacBook Pro delivers exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. Take on demanding projects with the M2 Pro or M2 Max chip. M2 Pro has up to 12 CPU cores, up to 19 GPU cores and up to 32GB unified memory. M2 Max has 12 CPU cores, up to 38 GPU cores and up to 96GB unified memory. All your pro apps run lightning-fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Xcode, Affinity Designer, Microsoft 365, and many of your favourite iPhone and iPad apps. The 14. 2-inch Liquid Retina XDR display features Extreme Dynamic Range, over 1,000 nits of brightness for stunning HDR content and pro reference modes for doing your best work on the go. Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 1 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 16 inDisplay Resolution 1366x768Screen Features TouchscreenColour Name SilverDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 12-CoreRAM Type DDR5External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 MBFeatures Built In Speaker, SD Card SlotModel Number MNWC3Model Name New MacBook Pro 16 M2HDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 3SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version Apple M2 Pro Chip With 12-Core CPU And 19-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2f8cf3a2-aae6-4953-9ef8-649da3131b9f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cc9858bb-4210-4435-b01e-16f85b248bdd/web/1_1732884594684.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>8299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065783673261</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4130348263</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Thunderbolt 4 (USB‑C) Pro Cable (1 m) Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Featuring a black braided design that coils without tangling, this 1-meter cable supports Thunderbolt 3, Thunderbolt 4, and USB 4 data transfer up to 40Gb/s, USB 3 data transfer up to 10Gb/s, DisplayPort video output (HBR3), and charging up to 100W. Use this cable to connect a Mac with Thunderbolt 3 or 4 (USB-C) ports to Thunderbolt (USB-C) and USB displays and devices such as Studio Display, Pro Display XDR, docks, and hard drives. You can also use this cable to connect iPhone 15 Pro to Mac. SpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number MU883ZE/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/67da823d-fcfd-4d2b-bbab-82d5d0b12c08</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/29ea1d7e-bfbf-43c8-86b3-6230bb19f111/web/1_1733290061517.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>228 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041303482636</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9647997560</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Magnetic Fast Charger To USB-C Cable White</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple Watch Magnetic Fast Charger to USB-C CableOverviewWe wanted to make charging your Apple Watch utterly effortless. Fast charge your Apple Watch Series 8 and Apple Watch Ultra. ¹ Simply hold the connector near the back of the watch, where magnets cause it to snap into place automatically. It’s a completely sealed system free of exposed contacts. And it’s very forgiving, requiring no precise alignment. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number MT0H3ZE/AModel Name NAItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/489ac5c0-24f4-4040-a910-1a07be8b20cb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/de2446e6-b756-4ff3-9afc-e875ee2409b6/web/1_1733289813309.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>139 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096479975604</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7516835307</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Thunderbolt 2 Adapter White</g:title>
      <g:description>Adapter lets you connect Thunderbolt and Thunderbolt 2 devices such as external hard drivesUsing this adapter with an Apple Thunderbolt Display requires a power source, because the display does not provide power through the adapterOverviewIn addition, it can be used to connect Thunderbolt-enabled displays — such as the Apple Thunderbolt Display and LG Thunderbolt 2 displays — to any of the Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) ports on your MacBook Pro. However, using this adapter with an Apple Thunderbolt Display requires a power source, because the display does not provide power through the adapter. SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 06 KGColour Name WhiteConnection Type WiredModel Number MMEL2/MMEL2AM/AModel Name Thunderbolt 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7b15cf6a-b175-45a1-82a2-8df56a17dccd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bd6f40b8-4c0b-4937-83fb-da73fb2834f1/web/1_1733289633769.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>165 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075168353077</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9521687606</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS + Cellular 41mm Smartwatch With Silver Aluminum Case With Sport Band M/L</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple Watch Series 9 [GPS+Cellular 41mm] Smartwatch with Silver Stainless steel Case with Storm Blue Sport Band M/L. Fitness Tracker,Blood Oxygen &amp;amp; ECG Apps,Always-On Retina Display,Water ResistantSpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelColour Name Storm BlueBand Size Medium/LargeTrending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 10. 7 mmModel Number MRJ33QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d8101f69-3765-4262-9bbb-4e7f548685cf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/80f57e48-ddaa-4c81-ae02-fddeedfe5983/web/1_1733289269234.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1451 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095216876068</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2923614521</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple EarPods In-Ear Earphones White</g:title>
      <g:description>EarPods are the next thing in rich sound and great comfort. Secure and comfortable. Maximum control. Superior audio. For use at home or on the goSpecificationsColour Name WhiteDepartment Adult UnisexConnection Type WiredAudio Jack 3. 5 mmModel Number MWTY3ZEA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/befd3270-5a98-4850-843b-02a9c766af74</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/642362d1-634c-41ce-abf3-02917589daf3/web/1_1733289440834.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>84 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029236145217</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6689142773</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2024) GPS 44mm Starlight Aluminium Case With Lake Green Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay connected on the go, go, goGet a closer look at your shut‑eyeTrack your heart health without missing a beatCarbon neutral - A big step towards a smaller footprintWater resistance - Swim-suitableOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Lake Green Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number MXEW3QA/AModel Name MXEW3QA/A, MXEW3LL/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b93c16e1-2bf8-4440-88da-1127974443ed</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f8d02b3a-eea4-4e7a-b5e3-2a3a7ca223bf/web/1_1733287680790.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>938.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066891427739</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6511190120</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Thunderbolt 4 (USB‑C) Pro Cable (1 m) Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Featuring a black braided design that coils without tangling, this 1-meter cable supports Thunderbolt 3, Thunderbolt 4, and USB 4 data transfer up to 40Gb/s, USB 3 data transfer up to 10Gb/s, DisplayPort video output (HBR3), and charging up to 100W. Use this cable to connect a Mac with Thunderbolt 3 or 4 (USB-C) ports to Thunderbolt (USB-C) and USB displays and devices such as Studio Display, Pro Display XDR, docks, and hard drives. You can also use this cable to connect iPhone 15 Pro to Mac. SpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number MU883ZE/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6c62ad70-fcd8-4e08-b2ec-6918ba26dbb6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7e603b14-c4ae-4408-94b8-dc6e0c63ea6f/web/1_1733289053868.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>228 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065111901202</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4127445491</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple USB-C To Headphone Jack Adapter White</g:title>
      <g:description>High bandwidth provides perfect performance of sounds in various range of tonesprovides high resolution and stable soundsHigh grade electronic components used in the manufacturing to assure extended working lifeUSB-C to 3. 5 mm Headphone Jack AdapterConnect devices that use a standard 3. 5 mm audio plug like headphones or speakers to your USB-C devices. Works with all devices that have a USB-C connector and support iOS 10 or later. OverviewThis USB 2. 0 cable connects your iPhone, iPad or iPod with Lightning connector to your computer’s USB port for syncing and charging. Or you can connect to the Apple USB Power Adapter for convenient charging from a wall outlet. The USB-C to USB Adapter lets you connect iOS devices and many of your standard USB accessories to a USB-C– or Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C)–enabled Mac. Plug the USB-C end of the adapter into a USB-C or Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) port on your Mac, and then connect your flash drive, camera or other standard USB device. You can also connect a Lightning to USB cable to sync and charge your iPhone, iPad or iPod. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteBrand Compatibility AppleWhat's In The Box AdaptersModel Number MU7E2ZM/A, MW2Q3ZE/AModel Name A2155</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/612de6e4-ba79-4856-9a2f-2a433fe2c6b0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/814d101b-0ea1-494a-903c-f7e594290486/web/1_1733290507995.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>46 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041274454915</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2531983931</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Apple Thunderbolt 4 Pro Cable (1.8m) Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Transfer data at up to 40Gb/sUSB 3. 1 Gen 2 data transfer at up to 10Gb/sDisplayPort video output (HBR3)Connect to Thunderbolt 3, Thunderbolt 4, or USB-C- and USB-enabled devices and displaysUp to 100 watts of power deliverySpecificationsColour Name BlackWattage 4 WModel Number MN713ZM/AModel Name MN713ZM/AItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a75a3ae8-6c7d-46e8-abba-b4de2ce792fe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1c073242-3ab3-4ed4-a55d-5fd4b2b09795/web/1_1733290694430.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>461 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025319839318</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7578811349</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Lightning To Usb Camera Adapter White</g:title>
      <g:description>Enables fast charging of supported devices and seamless data transfersSturdy cable construction prolongs service lifeSmall size makes it easy to carry aroundOffers ultra-powerful features to charge securely at high speedSpecificationsColour Name WhiteBrand Compatibility AppleModel Number MD821AM-AModel Name Charger-3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7cade6a7-407d-4c80-a334-8a2cacae96a0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1e6d185c-057d-4019-972d-d965983cc661/web/1_1733290913824.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>124 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075788113495</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1969268914</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Thunderbolt 3 (USB‑C) Cable (0.8 m) White</g:title>
      <g:description>This 0. 8-meter cable supports Thunderbolt 3 data transfer up to 40 Gbps, USB 3. 1 Gen 2 data transfer up to 10 Gbps, DisplayPort video output (HBR3), and charging up to 100W. Use this cable to connect a Mac with Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) / USB 4 ports to Thunderbolt 3 devices such as docks, hard drives, and displays. You can daisy-chain up to six Thunderbolt 3 devices. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number MQ4H2Model Name MQ4H2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/818210ce-778a-4921-9733-b84730846644</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/63ae7f1b-ff54-4f19-8367-e8b34d1369f4/web/1_1733291324565.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>174 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019692689141</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7958268671</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Lightning to SD Card Camera Reader White</g:title>
      <g:description>Lightning to SD card camera reader, easy to download photos and videos from your digital camera to your iPad or iPhoneMade with high quality material ensure durabilityDesigned to protect devices against short circuitsEnsures high-speed data transmissionLight weight and portable size easy to carry anywhereOverviewApple inc. Is an american multinational technology company headquartered in cupertino, california, that designs, develops, and sells consumer electronics, computer software, and online services. It is considered one of the big five companies in the U. S. Information technology industry, along with amazon, google, microsoft, and facebook. Its hardware products include the iPhone smartphones, the iPad tablets computer, the Mac personal computer, the iPod portable media player, the Apple watch smartwatch, the Apple tv digital media player, the AirPods wireless earbuds, the AirPods max headphones, and the HomePod smart speaker line. Apple's software includes ios, ipados, macos, watchos, and tvos operating systems, the itunes media player, the safari web browser, the shazam music identifier, and the ilife and iwork creativity and productivity suites, as well as professional applications like final cut pro x, logic pro, and xcode. Its online services include the itunes store, the ios app store, Mac app store, Apple arcade, Apple music, Apple tv+, Apple fitness+, imessage, and icloud. Other services include apple store, genius bar, applecare, Apple pay, Apple cash, and Apple card. SpecificationsCharging Type Lightning PortProduct Weight 36 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type WiredFeatures Personal, Business, Ergonomic, Travel, Pocket SizeModel Number MJYT2ZM/AItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d4a3f0c1-8586-4e02-abab-5e87e130d48c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/26350425-2246-4604-9bce-d898367d4dd6/web/1_1733291462386.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>119 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079582686711</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8620695913</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple USB-C to Lightning Adapter White</g:title>
      <g:description>The USB-C to Lightning Adapter lets you connect your Lightning accessories to a USB-C-enabled iPhone or iPad to conveniently provide three key functions — charging, data and audio — with a single adapter. This adapter has a braided cable for added durability. Plug the USB-C end of the adapter into the USB-C connector on your iPhone or iPad, then connect your Lightning accessorySpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number MUQX3ZE/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6da91a39-4798-452c-83d3-cb880d3ec6ee</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/10134003-461c-4251-8043-3267d455c33a/web/1_1733292054224.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>124 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086206959137</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6637329006</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Thunderbolt Cable White</g:title>
      <g:description>You may now use this Thunderbolt Cable from Apple to connect Thunderbolt enabled devices to the Thunderbolt or Thunderbolt 2 ports on your MAC. It’s 2 meters long and comes in white colour. Interface - USBSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 12 KGColour Name WhiteConnection Type WiredCable Length Under 2 FeetProduct Length 6. 5 inProduct Height 3. 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 10. 7 cmFeatures Mechanical, ErgonomicModel Number MD861</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/66bc5e4a-d954-40df-acb6-0faca055fd7d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a352e31e-f9d9-4862-8ab8-0fff7d7b94f7/web/1_1733292153337.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>179 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066373290066</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6294829428</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Lightning to 3.5 mm Headphone Jack Adapter White</g:title>
      <g:description>Lets you connect devices that use a 3. 5 mm audio plug to your Lightning devicesLightning to 3. 5 mm Headphone Jack AdapterWorks with all devices that have a Lightning connector and support iOS 10 or later, including iPod touch, iPad, and iPhoneSleek design makes it easy to carrySurge protection, short circuit protection and advanced safety features keeps your devices safeHook up your classic wired headphones to the latest devices using this Lightning to 3. 5mm conversion cable from Apple. The standard 3. 5mm line-in makes set-up easy too – plug your headphones in then connect any iPhone, iPad or iPod with a lightning port and you’re good to goOverviewApple Inc. designs, manufactures and markets smartphones, personal computers, tablets, wearables and accessories, and sells a variety of related services. The Company's products include iPhone, Mac, iPad, and Wearables, Home and Accessories. SpecificationsCharging Type 3. 5 MM Female to MaleProduct Weight 27 gColour Name WhiteBrand Compatibility AppleWhat's In The Box 1 x AdaptersProduct Length 4 cmProduct Height 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 1 cmFeatures Personal, Travel, Pocket SizeModel Number MMX62 / MMX62ZE/A/MMX62ZM/AModel Name A1749Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/43ec96b7-56da-4afb-a854-88ba5356fca8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/260f1a22-1986-4009-a1d7-f74b8a79ce18/web/1_1733291614838.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>38 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062948294286</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3517443094</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple USB-C Charge Cable (2 m) white</g:title>
      <g:description>This 2-meter charge cable — with USB-C connectors on both ends — is ideal for charging, syncing, and transferring data between USB-C devices. Pair the USB-C Charge Cable with a compatible USB-C power adapter to conveniently charge your devices from a wall outlet and take advantage of fast-charging capabilities. USB-C Power Adapters sold separately. Apple recommends the following pairings: 12-inch MacBook with USB-C port with the 30W USB-C Power Adapter 13-inch MacBook Air with Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) ports with the 30W USB-C Power Adapter 13-inch MacBook Pro with Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) ports with the 61W USB-C Power Adapter 15-inch MacBook Pro with Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) ports with the 87W USB-C Power Adapter 16-inch MacBook Pro with Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) ports with the 96W USB-C Power Adapter 11-inch iPad Pro (1st and 2nd generation), 12. 9-inch iPad Pro (3rd, 4th, and 5th generations), iPad Air (4th generation), and iPad mini (6th generation) with the 20W USB-C Power AdapterSpecificationsColour Name whiteModel Number MLL82Model Name MLL82</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d5ed829a-57b2-4690-82bb-777ea7036545</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f2ee7626-888c-48a4-be8b-5e9afed10636/web/1_1733291931754.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>84 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035174430940</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9320478059</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple USB-C to Magsafe 3 Cable (2 m) White</g:title>
      <g:description>This 2-meter charge cable features a magnetic MagSafe 3 connector that helps guide the plug to the power port of your MacBook ProPair it with a compatible USB-C power adapter to conveniently charge your MacBook Pro from a wall outlet and take advantage of fast-charging capabilitiesThe magnetic connection is strong enough to resist most unintended disconnects, but if someone trips on the cableSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number MLYV3ZE/AModel Name MLYV3ZE/AItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a833f804-c696-4966-8c98-f71f209db6ac</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0634f565-f06e-4392-be93-56cbada00f44/web/1_1733291738890.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093204780595</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8065312255</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Cable White</g:title>
      <g:description>Makes charging your Apple Watch utterly effortless. Combines MagSafe technology with inductive charging. Completely sealed system free of exposed contacts. Very forgiving, requiring no precise alignment. Completely sealed system free of exposed contactsIt’s a completely sealed system free of exposed contacts. And it’s very forgiving, requiring no precise alignment. Fast charging is only compatible with Apple Watch Series 7. Other models will have regular charge times. OverviewWe wanted to make charging your Apple Watch utterly effortless. So we arrived at a solution that combines our MagSafe technology with inductive charging. It’s a completely sealed system free of exposed contacts. And it’s very forgiving, requiring no precise alignment. You simply hold the connector near the back of the watch, where magnets cause it to snap into place automatically. It’s a completely sealed system free of exposed contacts. And it’s very forgiving, requiring no precise alignment. Fast charging is only compatible with Apple Watch Series 7. Other models will have regular charge times. SpecificationsCharging Type Multi-purpose ChargersColour Name WhiteProduct Length 1 mModel Number MX2E2Model Name MX2E2Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d505ec0f-1d7e-4134-b710-321f46772065</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/638134e1-e550-46b3-a3ef-e8c39c31c131/web/1_1733292291411.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>128 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080653122557</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4815255143</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 15 Pro 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number iPhone 15 ProModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ce5e649a-bbc8-4392-8400-4060e008d071</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/717bbf44-9dd0-4157-9d89-f838ddc27ee8/web/1_1733293346840.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048152551438</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2482443369</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWR3AE/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/517cc0f9-2ba1-418d-8ae3-c81b4a71a11f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/60ac54d0-5f1a-4621-a670-4b8e4c7f5b8e/web/1_1733293837667.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>7149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024824433691</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3726759573</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 256GB, WiFi - Starlight With Facetime</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name StarlightCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - StarlightModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - StarlightPrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4c5d12f5-302e-4005-abfe-c08680f52aec</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ce7ef094-3b7d-4cce-bb5b-27ed74265515/web/1_1733294788288.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2219 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037267595734</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5876637336</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 256GB, WiFi - Blue With Facetime</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YESFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - BlueModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - BluePrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/26472db7-c7dd-485e-a4d0-8b191c489e40</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e53e1ffa-3511-4217-ac78-d542f7cc1dbd/web/1_1733294566065.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2267.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058766373364</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2528880949</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 512GB, WiFi, Silver With Standard Glass</g:title>
      <g:description>The all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number MVX53AB/AModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/05a5569a-5fbf-4109-9494-d65b41438094</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dc4663ea-f6ed-4a7b-bc4e-f015f80a4f08/web/1_1733294204946.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025288809497</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7238065237</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 512GB, WiFi, Silver With Standard Glass</g:title>
      <g:description>The all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0e18a63e-57af-447d-8a82-6c22ae25ca5e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4aff66d9-1970-4d23-b105-f5d0c2ea2c82/web/1_1733292947381.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5514 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0072380652377</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8715936333</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Black Titanium Case</g:title>
      <g:description>Life is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Titanium Milanese Loop - SConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size SmallSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MX4W3QA/AModel Name MX4W3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/edb72263-636a-49d7-95e1-b548290ebd2f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/763a689e-d917-41ec-8b93-a3b132dd77de/web/1_1733294953555.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>3799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087159363330</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6651799109</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple USB-C To USB Adapter White</g:title>
      <g:description>Profoundly articulated to serve a dual functionStreamlined to exude lossless audio with exemplified chargingProficiently circuited to ensure efficient and stable transmissionAugmented tension points prohibit splitting of connectorsRenders voltage protection against incorporated overload to ensure the safety of your devicesThe adapter supports up to 3 Amps of power output for powering and fast charging of USB Type-C enabled devicesOverviewConnect standard USB Type-A enabled devices and peripherals (flash drives, keyboards, mice) to USB Type-C enabled devices with the USB Type-C to USB 3. 1 Gen 1 Female Adapter. Available in black or white, the high-quality adapter ensures easy connections and reliable performance. The USB Type-A to USB Type-C adapter makes it possible to easily charge USB Type-C enabled devices. The cable is ideal for connecting new Type-C enabled devices with legacy cables and peripherals using a Type-A connector such as flash drive, keyboard, or mouse. The adapter supports up to 3 Amps of power output for powering and fast charging of USB Type-C enabled devices. The cable’s USB Type-C connector offers a user-friendly reversible design that makes it possible to easily connect the cable to a device. No more wondering which way faces up when plugging it in. Type-C connector is half the width and one-third the height of a standard USB-A connector and only slightly larger than Lightning or Micro-A USB connectors. SpecificationsProduct Weight 18 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type WiredWhat's In The Box USB-C To USB AdapterCable Length Under 2 FeetProduct Length 7 cmProduct Height 1 cmProduct Width/Depth 1 cmWattage 10 WFeatures Personal, Business, Ergonomic, Pocket Size, TravelModel Number MJ1M2Model Name MJ1M2Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ae541ca6-4d45-4cd2-9959-ae98c9b91d45</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a6ae28d5-8f5e-42b5-a47c-ed49922010aa/web/1_1733287067716.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>72 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066517991095</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
