<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>8691628114</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 GPS + Cellular, 49mm Titanium Case With Blue Ocean Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCarbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhonePrecision dual‑frequency GPS, Cellular connectivity, Family Setup, Pair multiple watches with one iPhoneEmergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash Detection SirenUp to 36 hours. Up to 72 hours in Low Power Mode. Fast chargingBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewApple’s brightest Always-On Retina display is easy to see, even in harsh sunlight. More room for adding complications to customize your watch face and enough space to view six metrics at once. Made for recreational water sports, scuba, and free diving for descents to 40 meters. The Depth app shows the time, current depth, water temperature, duration under water, and maximum depth you’ve reached. The Oceanic+ app puts a dive computer on your wrist. Ocean Band is light and flexible, with a titanium buckle and adjustable loop for a secure fit even during high-speed water sports. The Compass app delivers helpful views and details like elevation, incline, longitude, and latitude. See the last place where you had cellular reception. Mark your location with Compass Waypoints. Backtrack uses GPS to map where you’ve been so you can retrace your steps. Alpine Loop is an extremely rugged and secure band to meet the needs of all outdoor adventurers. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Blue Ocean BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MREG3AE/A, MRF73ZA/A , MREG32P/A, MREG3ZP/A, MREG3LL/A, MREG3LW/AModel Name MREG3AE/A, MREG3VC/A, MREG3NF/A, MREG3B/A, MREG3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3beb29ca-fad7-442a-943a-0594bae8ffc7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/23aba3ec-ba28-4ac9-88f1-c0a8d2db1c1b/web/1_1725005613553.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2523 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086916281146</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5709933511</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 Dual SIM Blue 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung galaxy z flip6, AI phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB storage, blue, android smartphone, 50MP camera, flexcam, long battery lifeGalaxy AI: Your self-expression tool, galaxy z flip6, is compact and eye-catching, with galaxy al and a pro-level 50MP cameraDesign: Most compact. Big impact. Galaxy z flip6's new floating design is modern, slim and sleek50MP camera: The upgraded 50mp wide rear camera processes your pics through the provisual engine to capture stunning scenes and richer portraitsFlexcam: The flexcam uses auto zoom to zoom in or out on subjects, and provides a preview on the flexwindow for a hands-free selfie experienceSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 4 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name BlueDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Flip 6Model Name Flip 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d3b51adc-dd67-42e3-8f9c-fc00a0a4fa82</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ae6d0e59-d2b8-45de-81af-ea62cf655f70/web/1_1725006379150.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2391 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057099335117</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9447209897</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24+ Single+eSIM Cobalt Violet, 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEasy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24+ feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24+A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Cobalt VioletDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24+Model Name Galaxy S24+Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4f308c5e-9603-4432-bd58-718131b6465d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/95dc9e2b-ab2b-4ce5-93e0-2df5e3db6f4f/web/1_1725017658754.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2685 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094472098979</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9045621116</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Blossom Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Blossom PinkProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c67e5b02-c8e6-4ffc-8857-2aab970f7a0b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/71d0ad15-48da-4317-8a7e-039be5045308/web/1_1725018493519.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>312 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090456211167</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3293569749</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Clay White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. The instax mini 12 instant camera is the updated version that comes in 5 amazing pastel shades with great auto exposure and selfie mode with simple operations. Get your instant memories and selfies and brighten up your world with a handy version of the mini-series Featuring programmed electronic shutter speed, flash brightness, and automatic adjustments to ambient light, the FUJIFILM Instax Mini 12 Instant Camera ensures bright and well-exposed photos effortlessly. Thus, you can say goodbye to underexposed or overexposed shots, as it optimises settings based on the surrounding light conditions, allowing you to capture stunning images wherever and whenever inspiration strikes. Boasting a built-in selfie mirror, this instant camera takes your selfie game to the next level. Plus, with automatic flash adjustment, you'll always get well-lit selfies without any hassle. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Clay WhiteProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/73d15ad3-a5d4-4529-9932-531ed8cb3be3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5226dd4f-3b31-4aa1-89e4-66fd62286b51/web/1_1725017905818.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>282 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032935697499</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2311496167</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MR7K3 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU: 14.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 8GB Unified Memory, 1TB SSD Storage And Works with iPhone/iPad English Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 1 TBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3Usage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MR7K3ZS/A / MR7K3LL/A/MR7K3HN/A MR7K3X/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b43538e-1e82-44b8-9b97-b926f7038454</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/022b83c0-3a7c-4c4e-ba0b-ca02358ec11f/web/1_1725021397235.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5899 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023114961678</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1428192669</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5 Single Sim + eSim Icy Blue 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung Pay may not workOverviewSamsung pay and Samsung Care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMColour Name BlueDisplay Type Foldable Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number SM8550-AC Snapdragon 8 Gen 2Fast Charging YesProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Z Fold 5Model Name Z Fold 5Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0af15e11-2c4d-4598-a4e4-226817627ea1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/981f5cae-fc71-48b2-830f-00a36c07c2cc/web/1_1725009943660.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3479 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014281926690</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2843632944</g:id>
      <g:title> I PHONE 14 PRO COVER</g:title>
      <g:description>Crystal clear acrylic phone case. Compatible with Iphone 14 Pro. Scratch resistantSpecificationsMaterial AcrylicProduct Weight 2 gColour Name BLUE/PURPLEWhat's In The Box COVERPhone Case Material PVCModel Compatibility iPhone 14 ProType of Case Back CoverProduct Length 5 cmProduct Height 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 2 cmModel Number NAModel Name ISELLItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b370548-97ef-496d-9c36-b2d534948bb9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7cdaca42-080e-4243-948e-24737b5c1658/web/1_1727411846549.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028436329441</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2276786413</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Navy 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome NavyOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356EZKPMEAModel Name SM-A356EZKPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3136c375-4cb3-4445-90ed-a10f6923ea87</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aaee1c95-fe0a-4c1e-aca9-1df2e1d99690/web/1_1727414295965.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>805 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022767864138</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6526765557</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Blue Black 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Blue BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZKDMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/1D6NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/592136ef-d382-482f-a551-efff72e99511</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/abfe370b-fea4-416e-96bf-ad064997aeee/web/1_1727415037528.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>625 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065267655578</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5012558264</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Lilac 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome LilacOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356ELVPMEAModel Name SM-A356ELVPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/82208da8-cca6-45eb-b5d2-dbc01ab8e7f4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/49d2f014-2613-4110-9fbd-f9246d8c8110/web/1_1727415455732.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>805 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050125582646</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9371907102</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Light Blue 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A25 5G's 6. 5-inch, super amoled display details up to 1,000 nits brightness while enhanced with vision booster for clear outdoor visibilityDesign: Clean camera layout, sleek profile, unique patterns and haze finish. Available in blue black, blue and yellowCamera: Equipped with a 50mp main camera, the device is ready to capture high-resolution images assisted with OIS. Captures crisp selfies with an enhanced 13mp front cameraBattery: A 5,000mah battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256ELBDMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/1D6NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e374c337-8ad3-4576-bfa3-3573ae20b18d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/452acf0a-13cc-4af4-9e5a-b262a0223076/web/1_1727415245191.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>625 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093719071027</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6908109943</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Blue BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZKHMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2723d877-1dac-4d1c-a8da-b81f96b40dc9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/796e7d65-c13b-47a5-8d7c-62e16da72fb2/web/1_1727416690053.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>713 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069081099433</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3534268759</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro Dual SIM Forest Green 8GB RAM 256GB - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS120Hz FHD+ amoled displayImmersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels67W turbo charging with 5000mAh typ batteryMediaTek helio G99-ultraOverviewUltra-clear 200MP camera with OIS |120Hz FHD+AMOLED display | Immersive viewing with ultra-thin bezels | 67W turbo charging with 5000mAh (typ) batterySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 187 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 67 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Forest GreenDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version Android 13Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number 7th_generation_intel_kaby_lake_7y30_processor 4nmFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile Phone/ Adapter/ USB Type-C Cable/ SIM Eject Tool/ Protective Case/ Quick Start Guide/ Warranty Card/ Safety informationNetwork Frequency Band LTENumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleCondition NewProduct Length 161. 1 mmProduct Height 74. 95 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 256 GBSensor Proximity Sensors, ambient_light_sensor, AccelerometerModel Number 23117RA68GModel Name Redmi Note 13 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 200MP+8MP+2MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3fe76258-4531-40d0-af10-425893e3addf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/33b0b5b5-8c37-4b3c-a693-45d8b5b50b60/web/1_1727416970617.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>710 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035342687596</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2292482472</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab A9 Plus Dark Blue/Navy 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylish with a touch of cool, the galaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ features a sleek design and a smooth metal body. Enjoy samsung’s signature tablet design in graphite, silver and navy with each hue highlighting effortless charmGalaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ come with up to 8GB of RAM memory, ensuring less lag while you multi-task. Plus, the built-in 128GB storage saves all your hi-res videos, photos and files. You can expand the storage with a microSD card — up to 1TBConquer multiple tasks at once. With galaxy tab A9+, you can sketch out architectural plans and choose captivating visuals and video chat — up to three apps all on one screen without ever closing a windowTake a deep dive into a rich soundscape with speakers that provide an enveloping audio experience. Whether you're enjoying a movie or music, galaxy tab A9+ lets you fully engage in 3D sound with stunning clarity and depthKeep your information safe and sound. Store important data in the secure folder and monitor the overall security status of your device on the privacy dashboard. Make the most of your samsung galaxy experience, worry-free of security issuesSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name Dark Blue/NavyCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTECamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless WirelessModel Number SM-X216BDBEMEAModel Name Tab A9 Plus</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/20a37858-afa5-4b3f-8a45-bd49f723743f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76450799-836e-41f8-b75c-b5ae496f3e10/web/1_1727413968977.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022924824722</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8749643574</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 6 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVHMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/da5d55ba-4a3d-4142-a1a7-93579746c19c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/192056ff-571f-4002-bc3f-08cecffd95ce/web/1_1727415631676.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>453.60 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087496435745</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2008445987</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Light Blue 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FLBGMEAModel Name Galaxy A15Primary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2ee5ee27-10c4-476b-8904-0f2033946ce3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7b2caae4-c750-49b0-9d0f-316782c70d2a/web/1_1727415864517.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>520 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020084459877</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6993184143</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Light Green 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 4 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Light GreenOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FLGDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ae49d8ab-c31c-4372-8566-d93f239281e6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/00e91874-98bb-40f0-82c3-8af8124711ca/web/1_1727420167338.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>280 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069931841434</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7065484203</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Ice Blue 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome Ice BlueOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356ELBPMEAModel Name SM-A356ELBPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8dfa1556-74ea-492a-b64c-3d47fbf14b95</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/26d27e95-2d2f-4fed-9cc9-dd49f679cc4d/web/1_1727420676468.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>810 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070654842035</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5077103008</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor X9b Dual SIM 5G Sunrise Orange 12GB RAM 256GB - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 1. 5K Retinal Resolution / SGS 5-star Whole-device Drop Resistance Certification / 5-fold Eye Protection[12GB RAM + 25G GB Memory] Enjoy great performance &amp;amp; plenty of room for photos, movies, songs, and apps—and 20GB Super large memory(RAM Turbo)108MP Lossless Capture Camera, 108MP main Camera/ Motion Capture/ 3X lossless Zoom[Superfast 5G performance] Unleash entertainment at 5G speed with the Qualcom Snapdragon, a powerful octa-core processor with frequencies up to 2. 1GHz. [Massive battery and speedy charging] Work and play nonstop with a long-lasting 5800mAh battery, then recharge quickly. OverviewA luxury look and Xtra power, Honor X9b 5G is designed to stand out with HONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 360° Anti-Drop Protection, 6. 78" Amoled+ 120Hz display. Capture incredibly clear photos and smoother videos with a 108MP+5MP+2MP camera system featuring motion capture &amp;amp; 3X lossless zoom. Honor X9b 5G is a device you will fall in love with at first touchSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5800 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 185 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 78 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Sunrise OrangeDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13Processor Number Qualcomm snapdragon SM6450Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 163. 6 mmProduct Height 75. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Accelerometer, Proximity SensorsModel Number ALI-NX1Model Name X9bPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1d414497-2937-42f9-ae76-520c1f38066f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fc181b5a-fafb-49f1-86db-aa3946483255/web/1_1727420860669.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>925 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050771030089</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9193742585</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab A9 Plus Silver 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylish with a touch of cool, the galaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ features a sleek design and a smooth metal body. Enjoy samsung’s signature tablet design in graphite, silver and navy with each hue highlighting effortless charmGalaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ come with up to 8GB of RAM memory, ensuring less lag while you multi-task. Plus, the built-in 128GB storage saves all your hi-res videos, photos and files. You can expand the storage with a microSD card — up to 1TBConquer multiple tasks at once. With galaxy tab A9+, you can sketch out architectural plans and choose captivating visuals and video chat — up to three apps all on one screen without ever closing a windowTake a deep dive into a rich soundscape with speakers that provide an enveloping audio experience. Whether you're enjoying a movie or music, galaxy tab A9+ lets you fully engage in 3D sound with stunning clarity and depthKeep your information safe and sound. Store important data in the secure folder and monitor the overall security status of your device on the privacy dashboard. Make the most of your samsung galaxy experience, worry-free of security issuesSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTECamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless WirelessModel Number SM-X216BModel Name Tab A9 Plus</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2035feea-8531-40b0-a543-c4be925cd952</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f0f000d8-9b2e-4d17-b103-f6307aed7a9c/web/1_1727421191077.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>734 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091937425851</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2597776176</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Blue/Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A15Primary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e0199873-60f0-4efb-a06f-8004589f01f5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b371e715-2a57-48f3-8ece-f92ccdf4085b/web/1_1727413698081.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>525 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025977761761</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3764554769</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea CM822 8-Inch Smart Kids Tablet Single SIM 6GB RAM 256GB 5G Purple</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThis 8"Inch WVGA Capacitive IPS touch screen LCD of CM822 android tab provides consistent and accurate colors from all viewing angles. Support 5. 0MP back camera and 2. 0MP front camera to take pictures or make video calls with powerful. Quad core processor provides an overall lag-free performanceOverviewThe C idea CM822 is a budget friendly tablet that will fit nicely in anyone's arms. It features a 8" WVGA IPS LCD screen. It has a TF card slot which allows you to expand the memory with up to an additional 64GB. The C idea CM822 features with a 2MP front camera and 5MP rear camera (Kids Version). SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPRAM Size 6 GBInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 319 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 8 inDisplay Resolution 800x1280Primary Camera Resolution 5 MPColour Name PurpleCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Micro SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System Version Android 12Operating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 2 - 4. 9 MPVoice Calling Capability YesWhat's In The Box Android Tablet*1, UK Charger*1, Type-C cable*1, Screen Protector *1,Book Cover*1,OTG*1, Kids Watch*1,Touch Pen*1, TWS Bluetooth Headset*1,Colour Marker*6,Random Cartoon stickers*1,Sand painting*1,Key Ring*1,Finger Buckle*1 User Manual*1Network Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSNumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDBattery Type Lithium PolymerFinish PlasticProduct Length 206. 2 mmProduct Height 9. 2 mmProduct Width/Depth 129 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM822Model Name Kids TabletPrimary Camera (MP) 5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fdddb172-eab3-4f96-97d6-89331d35ca38</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d8f07cfc-7982-4e39-95b7-6aa84804c982/web/1_1727432681010.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>179 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037645547690</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2954902590</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 200 LITE Cyan Lake Dual SIM 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights108MP rear camera, portrait in the spotlightHonor 200 lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your handExtra-large AMOLED view, boundless with brightness and clarityOverviewThe Portrait Master 108MP &amp;amp; 50MP Glorious Portrait Risk-free Dimming AMOLED Display Lightweight Drop-resistant Design 108MP Rear Camera, Portrait in the Spotlight 50MP Light-sensitive Selfie, Fantastic group photo Ultra-slim in Shape, Crafted in Style Drop-Proof, Trust Enhanced Risk-Free Dimming Eye-Care Display 256GB Ultra-large Storage Dynamic in Design, Elegant in Heart HONOR 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, Exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your hand. 6. 78mm Thickness 166g Weight Selfie Light 50MP Front Camera 108MP Main Camera f/1. 75 aperture Marco Camera f/2. 4 aperture Wide &amp;amp; Depth Camera f/2. 2 aperture AI Wide-angle Selfie 78° FOV mode works while taking selfies, and switches to 90° FOV mode whlie taking groupfies. Multi-focal Portrait, the Art of Boken The Rear camera features three focal choices, each showing a side of your unique charm. 108MP image,Uncompromising Clarity The 108MP HD Rear camera can capture the excitement of your life clearly and vividly. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4500 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Colour Name Cyan LakeDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number 6080Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek DimensityNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number LL-NX1 , LLY - NX1Model Name HONOR 200 LITEPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f2e6e659-ea71-4dc1-a84b-78075a916cc7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c1248c94-d457-4b8d-945e-2dd6476b4ca9/web/1_1727433300965.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>810 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029549025909</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1516219219</g:id>
      <g:title>C idea 5G Android Tablet CM813 Pro 8 Inch Zoom Supported Smart Tab with Quad Core CPU Bluetooth Wifi Silicon Protective Case cover (Grey)</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights• C idea 8" inch tablet is thin and light, making it portable for anywhere use. This WVGA IPS screen makes your images more crisp and delicate. It enables you to view pictures and videos with the high definition visual enjoyment. • The CM513 Pro Pro smart tab has a powerful Quad Core CPU can run many applications faster and smoother. • With 5MP back camera and 2MP front camera, you can get high quality pictures anytime and anywhere. OverviewC idea 8" Android Smart Tablet CM813 Pro is your gateway to the internet. It offers a High Quality IPS Touch Screen that is easy to navigate. The Quad Core Processor enables you to open apps and programs on the go. The 2. 0 MP Front and 5. 0 MP Back camera capture every precious moment. The 6GB RAM and 256GB ROM store all your important documents and photos. The TF Card upto 64GB is expandable. The 5G LTE, WIFI, Bluetooth enables seamless connectivity. The ZOOM Supported Camera captures the smallest of details with perfect clarity. ●Item : 8" Smart Tablet PC ●Brand: C idea ●Model : CM813 Pro Specification: •Network : 5G LTE/Wifi •Display : 8" inch WVGA Capacitive IPS Touch Screen(600*1024) •Operating System : Android •CPU: MTK •Chipset : Quad Core •Flash+Ram : 256GB+6GB •Expandable Memory : Up to 64GB •Support Zoom : Yes •Camera : Front - 2MP Back - 5MP •Flash Light: Yes •Wi-Fi Support : Yes •Bluetooth Connect : Yes •Face Recognition : Yes •Power Input : 5V/2A •Dimension : 10. 8mm Slim BodySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPRAM Size 6 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8 inDisplay Resolution 1024x600Primary Camera Resolution 5 MPColour Name GreyCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type Nano SIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System AndroidNetwork Type 5GSecondary Camera 2 - 4. 9 MPModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTENumber of Cores Quad CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraFlash LEDBattery Type Lithium PolymerProduct Length 12. 6 cmProduct Height 1. 08 cmProduct Width/Depth 21. 1 cmMaximum Expandable Memory 64 GBModel Number CM813 ProModel Name C idea CM Series</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/345ff037-106f-4220-94ce-07d143606fe6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f43794c0-90f6-4dc7-aaa8-439f986322f6/web/1_1727434561011.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>175 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015162192197</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3175099523</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Buds 3 Pro Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDual AMP ~ Crystal Sound ~ The Blade LightsAI Technology Support ~ Pinch Control &amp;amp; Swip360 Audio Recording ~ Super Clear CallAmbient Sound - 3 Mic VPUDynamic Noise adjustmentOverviewSamsung Galaxy Buds 3 ProSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 53 mAhProduct Weight 46. 5 gColour Name SilverDepartment Adult UnisexConnection Type True WirelessAverage Battery Life Less than 8 hrsUsage Type Sports &amp;amp; FitnessWhat's In The Box Buds &amp;amp; Charger caseAudio Jack Type-CAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WiredEarplug Type EarbudsProduct Length 24. 4 mmProduct Height 48. 7 mmFeatures Bluetooth, Water Resistant, Voice Assistant, Active Noise Cancellation, Volume ControlModel Number SM-R630NZAAMEA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/88a28a12-706a-4dd3-9603-248be710b9f9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/600f6632-e310-431d-a0db-203d48d3ac4d/web/1_1727435664273.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>834 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031750995230</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1063753565</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZKHMEA/SM-A057FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f821160d-f87b-4329-9162-e8b35df9bba7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b2d2e770-b95f-4975-aed5-7b8498c42a7d/web/1_1727436142321.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>440 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010637535653</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5724965302</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Pro MRW23 Laptop M3 Pro chip with 12‑core CPU, 18‑core GPU: 16.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 36GB Unified Memory, 512GB SSD Storage English Space Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 36 GBInternal Memory 512 GBScreen Size 16 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3 ProUsage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRW23ZS/A/ MRW23X/A/ MRW23LL/A/MRW23HN/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Pro chip with 12‑core CPU, 18‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3d9eaa92-6626-47d5-8c26-59d6fceeed63</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/715dfebb-84b3-4e82-97f9-44e803f3720a/web/1_1725011316567.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>9399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057249653023</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3324183036</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5 Single Sim + eSim Cream 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung Pay may not workOverviewSamsung pay and samsung care+ may not work in this regionSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMPrimary Camera Resolution 50 MPColour Name CreamDisplay Type Foldable Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13. 0Processor Number SM8550-AC Snapdragon 8 Gen 2Fast Charging YesProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDBattery Type Lithium PolymerModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Z Fold 5Model Name Z Fold 5Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/75fcb6b7-c3cf-4e17-a951-b9ac01d37a01</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/59e3bcf8-8f66-4aaf-b89a-0928b76e47bd/web/1_1725018733109.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>3646 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033241830365</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5778822495</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXD33 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU Processor/16GB RAM/512GB SSD/Intel UHD Graphics English Starlight</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name StarlightLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Graphics Processor Series Intel UHDDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3Usage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXD33LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/11b2a137-1e9f-4d10-a1e9-5d07c145de18</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e4026745-35c2-431b-b954-0bf326e4c27c/web/1_1725020847241.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057788224951</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8550428817</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MRW13 Laptop M3 Pro Chip With 12‑Core CPU, 18‑Core GPU: 16.2-Inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 18GB Unified Memory, 512GB SSD Storage And Works With IPhone/IPad English Space Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Go all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 18 GBInternal Memory 512 GBScreen Size 16 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3 ProUsage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRW13ZS/A / MRW13LL/A/MRW13HN/A / MRW13X/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Pro chip with 12‑core CPU, 18‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/169e3dc4-b5ca-4a88-8612-a2e5160e3b6d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/27637bbd-f87a-4fde-94c0-7b5c417c85cd/web/1_1725624300647.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>7999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085504288178</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3496794751</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 Dual SIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSamsung galaxy z flip6, AI phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB storage, blue, android smartphone, 50MP camera, flexcam, long battery lifeGalaxy AI: Your self-expression tool, galaxy z flip6, is compact and eye-catching, with galaxy al and a pro-level 50MP cameraDesign: Most compact. Big impact. Galaxy z flip6's new floating design is modern, slim and sleek50MP camera: The upgraded 50mp wide rear camera processes your pics through the provisual engine to capture stunning scenes and richer portraitsFlexcam: The flexcam uses auto zoom to zoom in or out on subjects, and provides a preview on the flexwindow for a hands-free selfie experienceSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 4 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Flip 6Model Name Flip 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f843e729-6b29-4d05-984e-6c3c9a54e6b9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ca1b3383-a47b-459d-972c-acb05a3319b3/web/1_1725003485424.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034967947511</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3977136000</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MRW33 Laptop M3 Max chip with 14‑core CPU, 30‑core GPU: 16.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 36GB Unified Memory, 1TB SSD Storage And Works with iPhone/iPad English Space Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 36 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 16 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3 MaxUsage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRW33ZS/A / MRW33X/A / MRW33LL/A/MRW33HN/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Max chip with 14‑core CPU, 30‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c205a91d-99da-4c9a-bfa2-cee4db75d557</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/db399ebd-3e72-40f4-a0ae-7f83c944a12b/web/1_1725008401266.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>11099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039771360006</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1259057405</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Onyx Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEasy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Onyx BlackDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/daacc1f8-285d-4a0c-b4d8-3917de53baf9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a9629ff3-7071-47dd-8d40-21b7b0307873/web/1_1725007367542.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2431 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012590574052</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3592640481</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 512GB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast, and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/df6a1384-a129-4e5d-8de1-a3e5c78f311f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/37e60e22-28fe-40e8-a6e6-7471aaa2a4cc/web/1_1725006073108.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035926404816</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4351787550</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM 20-Sheet Instax Film Photo Paper</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSpecially designed and labeled cartridge facilitates easy loadingHelps you to create vivid colour photographs with natural skin tonesThe compact size enables you to place it in your walletinstax mini film offers stunning-quality instant pictures that fit in a purse, wallet or mini photo frame. Professional quality instant film technology ensures accurate colour and sharpness with every frame, not to mention a unique and highly attractive way to capture and share your memories. OverviewThis 54X86mm film is designed for Fujifilm Instax Mini 7s/8/25/90/9. With white photo edge for DIY information. Good partner for your unforgettable journey. 20 sheets photo paper designed for Fujifilm Instax Mini 7s/8/25/90/9. High-speed ISO 800, with excellent grain, create photos of vibrant color and natural skin tones. The cartridge is specially designed and labeled for easy loading. 54X86mm credit card size, can be placed in your wallet or purse, easy to carry. 46X62mm image size, with white paper edge for you to DIY photo information. Usage:1. To install the film correctly, please match the yellow mark on film with that on camera film slot. 2. Please don't press the black surface of film or the sunken part of package. 3. After the photo slide out, you can shake it, place it into pocket or just wait until image emerges. 4. Do not open the rear camera cover until you get all the photo paper filmed. Film Type: Color, Instant Film Roll: Yes, Film Format: 45 mmSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box Instax MiniProduct Length 62 mmProduct Width/Depth 46 mmModel Number GE34Model Name GE34Item Quantity 20</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/309e9ece-1f2e-487a-b20a-3ae5f6aaeae3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e5b886c2-aa0c-4676-89bd-800726c226bb/web/1_1725006786089.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>69 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043517875501</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6269097569</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 1TB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 16 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 1024 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d16eb641-28a6-43a2-becb-3706608e24a5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ec441a06-4e88-4c3f-ae80-97750a08450b/web/1_1725010565129.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>6289 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062690975693</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9298658014</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRYV3 15-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU Processor/8GB RAM/512GB SSD/Intel UHD Graphics English Midnight</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 15 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name MidnightLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Graphics Processor Series Intel UHDDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3Usage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRYV3AB/A / MRYV3X/A / MRYV3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/41d741c0-da19-464f-95b3-18fd5864ec0e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b42d3170-f4ae-4a09-b791-f6d2c85e38e0/web/1_1725007829979.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4819 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092986580140</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7466880638</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Pastel Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Pastel BlueProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2082b651-a7fb-48bb-8476-82b424e2410e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ed0825d3-8d18-4634-b3fb-49ba2a8e20fc/web/1_1725005343052.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>284 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074668806380</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4226547886</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Cobalt Violet, 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEasy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Cobalt VioletDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/687ee513-29f0-4f48-8c9e-849a84357664</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b962810b-5199-4464-8ab5-67b5b9390fd1/web/1_1725020251049.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2494 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042265478866</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3762893102</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Mint Green</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Mint GreenProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/391b4925-bf2c-43eb-9602-4a60c9a57d05</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c0262e23-21ea-4c0c-b839-cd2068f01cd3/web/1_1725021098491.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>307 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037628931027</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9766036010</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MTL83 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU: 14.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 8GB Unified Memory, 1TB SSD Storage And Works with iPhone/iPad English Space Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 1 TBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3Usage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MTL83LL/A / MTL83X/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/42f1fe70-ae76-404c-a5ae-a09c2276bd30</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/10f3f2e3-850a-403f-8d7e-b19f59c8eec6/web/1_1725019989230.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097660360100</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5790338071</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MRW13 Laptop M3 Pro chip with 12‑core CPU, 18‑core GPU: 16.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 18GB Unified Memory, 512GB SSD Storage And Works with iPhone/iPad English Space Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGo all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 7 GHzRAM Size 18 GBInternal Memory 512 GBScreen Size 16 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space BlackLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSProcessor Type Apple M3 ProUsage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4Processor Brand AppleExternal Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MRW13ZS/A / MRW13LL/A/MRW13HN/A / MRW13X/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 Pro chip with 12‑core CPU, 18‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c2b59927-5e97-4e4a-8c43-1a4444c54344</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aedd5393-31ae-4148-bb9e-05c267a43dff/web/1_1725019218846.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>7999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057903380715</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3552773047</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 512GB, 5G, Space Black With Standard Glass - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast, and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space BlackCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5b127a0e-cc57-485d-9b38-6cd89aba9861</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/51550ae2-46b3-476e-8f52-abcae271739b/web/2_1725882815952.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035527730475</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2020091802</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 Dual SIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Samsung galaxy z flip6, AI phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB storage, blue, android smartphone, 50MP camera, flexcam, long battery lifeGalaxy AI: Your self-expression tool, galaxy z flip6, is compact and eye-catching, with galaxy al and a pro-level 50MP cameraDesign: Most compact. Big impact. Galaxy z flip6's new floating design is modern, slim and sleek50MP camera: The upgraded 50mp wide rear camera processes your pics through the provisual engine to capture stunning scenes and richer portraitsFlexcam: The flexcam uses auto zoom to zoom in or out on subjects, and provides a preview on the flexwindow for a hands-free selfie experienceSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 4 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Flip 6Model Name Flip 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3b2c1e58-f290-43a2-8392-9addf6fa0b80</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/571800d2-9280-42e6-a61a-5afd0cbeb433/web/1_1725882471128.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020200918028</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7379715380</g:id>
      <g:title>Dji Mini 3 With Remote Control</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMini size powerful imagingStunning footage al all hoursAmazing results effortlesslyGo far with 10km transmission51 Min extended flight timeOverviewFilm in 4K HDR Video for crystal clear aerial shots. With Dual Native ISO Fusion, Mini 3 enables the capture of details in highlights and shadows, both day and night. With True Vertical Shooting, you can easily capture tall landmarks like skyscrapers and waterfalls. And after capturing, it's in the perfect orientation to post to Instagram or TikTok. Its flight time can be extended up to 51 minutes with the Intelligent Flight Battery Plus (sold separately), but the aircraft will weigh more than 249 g. Fly More combo offers up to 114 minutes of total flight time. Wind Resistant and 3-Axis Gimbal for Stable - With its Level 5 wind resistant and 3-axis mechanical gimbal, Mini 3 can capture consistently smooth 4K imagery. rushless motors enhance power and allow takeoff at altitudes up to 4,000 meters. Up to 10 km (32,800 feet) [5] of HD video transmission and has excellent anti-interference capabilities, giving you the ability to freely explore vast landscapes and see clearer. SpecificationsColour Name GreyModel Number DJI-MVM300-SC / MT3PDModel Name DJI-MVM300-SC</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1f52255c-7435-42c4-8699-3d29a583c22d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/367f4920-9e03-4df7-87c5-9e9b4a712404/web/1_1725007082282.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>DJI</g:brand>
      <g:price>1629 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073797153808</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5811700566</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 Dual SIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Samsung galaxy z flip6, AI phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB storage, blue, android smartphone, 50MP camera, flexcam, long battery lifeGalaxy AI: Your self-expression tool, galaxy z flip6, is compact and eye-catching, with galaxy al and a pro-level 50MP cameraDesign: Most compact. Big impact. Galaxy z flip6's new floating design is modern, slim and sleek50MP camera: The upgraded 50mp wide rear camera processes your pics through the provisual engine to capture stunning scenes and richer portraitsFlexcam: The flexcam uses auto zoom to zoom in or out on subjects, and provides a preview on the flexwindow for a hands-free selfie experienceSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 10 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 4 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Flip 6Model Name Flip 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a3638170-d734-43c5-b663-7ef0d34909fe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/75691e34-5bc3-46c7-90d4-c65f33b415d4/web/1_1725623503879.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058117005661</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6134380236</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Clay White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. The instax mini 12 instant camera is the updated version that comes in 5 amazing pastel shades with great auto exposure and selfie mode with simple operations. Get your instant memories and selfies and brighten up your world with a handy version of the mini-series Featuring programmed electronic shutter speed, flash brightness, and automatic adjustments to ambient light, the FUJIFILM Instax Mini 12 Instant Camera ensures bright and well-exposed photos effortlessly. Thus, you can say goodbye to underexposed or overexposed shots, as it optimises settings based on the surrounding light conditions, allowing you to capture stunning images wherever and whenever inspiration strikes. Boasting a built-in selfie mirror, this instant camera takes your selfie game to the next level. Plus, with automatic flash adjustment, you'll always get well-lit selfies without any hassle. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 gColour Name Clay WhiteProduct Length 10. 41 cmProduct Height 12. 19 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 cmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/47fa664f-a6c2-49ea-922f-4cdde0257b17</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/122fdd48-e864-41cd-9922-d98be60166fb/web/1_1725623831600.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>282 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061343802362</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9515226554</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Black Titanium</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN03</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0fe538c7-8e4f-433d-9b9a-79de873ad8d1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d1ccde67-0bd7-4520-8680-4e4bf8f8ed8b/web/1_1727437402933.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095152265544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9403015132</g:id>
      <g:title>IPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWJ3AE/A , MYWJ3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8d209fd4-5d9b-49cb-817c-b97db4225e79</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/53a60e40-186b-4429-8f6b-c5360273c536/web/1_1727437818532.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6080 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094030151320</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4941237537</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Natural Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN33</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/06e4f25d-9234-461d-a304-5ccda427545e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/300a4a82-f1c4-481e-a4bc-ccdf10a6bd14/web/1_1727438201419.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049412375375</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8566146886</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - USA Version (e-SIM only)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion USA VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/514b96d5-6f69-453f-a13e-5ddb1cb1e5a2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bc31305b-fb44-4325-a1f5-8b45edbc2017/web/1_1727438745748.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5449 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085661468864</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8763422739</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - USA Version (e-SIM only)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion USA VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5fc73093-7a82-4f31-8afc-ffb661793f77</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8553918a-af25-4b65-9204-add8a9dd62fe/web/1_1727438422772.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087634227393</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9507216441</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 ProModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f4b9a95f-ed0f-48df-a6f0-60d6c694c331</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7c5adc6b-2f38-4d4a-b563-4c6cdf7879b8/web/1_1727439367323.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4958 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095072164415</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9569866447</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - USA Version (e-SIM only)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion USA VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b12b230a-1991-40d6-bf25-b822cb3326ad</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9ae878a1-54aa-4e8e-95c3-5a87ea84067d/web/1_1727439122292.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6330 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095698664474</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1492705667</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/aafd30c4-2016-4da9-aa10-31ce6694df69</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/21d68aee-d5cd-490e-8794-bd98235d56e6/web/1_1727440610947.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014927056675</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7895407481</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your home screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your lock screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the action buttonIn the redesigned photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like people and petsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b3107d76-4bcf-44e4-8db1-72bb5a3d9a61</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8e1cbb12-3555-4d2e-9bc1-fce67c84968a/web/1_1727439658874.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5823.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078954074811</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8098958299</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/da4ad74b-1c7c-4d63-9eaa-19d0c3f30784</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/01a9416a-9f7a-48ec-87c3-78a821056857/web/1_1727440420270.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080989582995</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9810767408</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/af7074dc-eaa4-4cd3-9793-a5b32fb3126e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aae5939e-73e7-4a59-a62c-76f98f4b5769/web/1_1727440889602.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5717.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098107674088</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5514596541</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/49e9b1f1-35a4-43a9-a5d6-1d9b2bcedaa9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d322019c-a2a2-4322-a9f3-223498a7bbbb/web/1_1727440214001.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6825 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055145965417</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8199649081</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN23AE/A , MYN23AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b3e6549a-836f-4401-95d5-b4d5e6cd9c88</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/00be7786-e3e4-4fc2-acea-d6eb37c2d98b/web/1_1727439938427.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5185 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081996490815</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3811682261</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - USA Version (e-SIM only)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion USA VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e6e13045-31a3-4d1b-986e-8c3dec43e8b2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fafd1896-0db3-4a37-8406-5f5ee92aec09/web/1_1727440284466.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6349 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038116822612</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7545112454</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7d0f3626-e449-473c-b231-fa5b46f7ca95</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0b7bf3bb-904d-420a-9b45-aab7925b44ba/web/1_1727437069747.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075451124544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6005105475</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - White Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN13</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9909af24-3993-47ac-918c-3eb0c462c625</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/407fd4db-0fa1-44ec-83e6-4ac7467da4c3/web/1_1727436658892.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060051054759</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2999901464</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9b2c11ff-2aaf-4221-bb5b-5d295f5a8d74</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f56bfc62-b8c7-438d-ad37-3aff05519b29/web/1_1727439982953.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>7745 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029999014645</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1348518604</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/69da9ac5-acdb-47c3-bc5a-4e4fc8905449</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a373eec9-6c7a-4a80-8a3d-774096d392a6/web/2_1727442153685.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013485186046</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8316519366</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Single+eSIM Marble Grey 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEasy to grip. Satisfying to hold. With their unified design and satin finish, Galaxy S24 feels as smooth as it looksThey're the upgrades you've waited for. More screen. More battery. More processing power. There's so much more to love about Galaxy S24A true pixel powerhouse that will not disappoint ever. Snap high-res pics for that will no doubt withstand the test of time for years to comeSearch like never before with circle to search. Simply trace an object to get Google Search results. It's a new visual way to find what you're looking forGet quick language translation on your next phone call. That's right, AI helps you communicate outside your own language while you talk on the phone. And get this, it even works on messagingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMProcessor Speed 3. 39 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 2 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Primary Camera Resolution 50 MPRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Marble GreyDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type Quad HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CBattery Type Lithium IonNetwork Type 5GCondition NewSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number Galaxy S24Model Name Galaxy S24Primary Camera (MP) 50+10+12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d582722c-d136-40ea-8b93-39f75b22aea1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b944a274-42c4-434c-a7d2-706ad53eb332/web/1_1725018195854.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>2421 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083165193664</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
