<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>8743882030</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Condenser Microphone With Accessories Set BM-800 Black/Gold</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStandard pick-up minimizes background noise and isolates the main sound sourceAdopt demanding complete electronic circuit control, capture rich, full-bodied soundShock mount effectively reduces trill caused by vibrationSpecificationsProduct Weight 1. 4 KGColour Name Black/GoldProduct Length 42 cmProduct Height 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 24 cmModel Number BM-800Model Name BM-800</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/54bc9b9f-d64f-4f9f-af8a-0b3a23bc0f09</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/66f96e0c-72f9-4d01-a53b-27c227ff13ad/web/1_1724840291522.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>109 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087438820301</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5413280220</g:id>
      <g:title>Beauenty Professional Condenser Audio Streaming Kit Black/Gold</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights3. 5mm aux jack condenser microphone mic works with laptops and computersAdjustable shock mount allows for a customized fitIdeal for radio broadcasting, voice-over sound and audio recordingLarge condenser microphone element for warm, rich recordings. The cardioid pick-up pattern minimizes background noise and isolates the main sound source. . Smooth, extended frequency response is excellent for singing, speech and instrumentsOverload-protection switch (-10dB) minimizes distortion from loud sound sources. . Bass-reduction switch reduces room noise. The professional condenser microphone internally adopts precise full electronic circuit control and has fine features of cardioid-directional pick-up, high-sensitivity output, low noise, wide dynamic range, etc. It is widely used in specialized occasions such as in the recording studio, the broadcast radio, the stage performance, the late-stage production of movie and television plays and the household computer recording. OverviewLarge condenser microphone element for warm, rich recordings. The cardioid pick-up pattern minimizes background noise and isolates the main sound source. . Smooth, extended frequency response is excellent for singing, speech, and instruments. Overload-protection switch (-10dB) minimizes distortion from loud sound sources. Bass-reduction switch reduces room noise. The professional condenser microphone internally adopts precise full electronic circuit control and has fine features of cardioid-directional pick-up, high-sensitivity output, low noise, wide dynamic range, etc. . It is widely used in specialized occasions such as in the recording studio, the broadcast radio, the stage performance, the late-stage production of movie and television plays, and the household computer recording. SpecificationsProduct Weight 1. 55 KGColour Name Black/GoldConnection Type WiredBrand Compatibility GeneralMobileWhat's In The Box 1xMicrophone, 1xStand, 1xCable, 1xMount, 1xNet and 1xMicrophone CoverProduct Length 44 cmProduct Height 9 cmProduct Width/Depth 26 cmFeatures Business, Ergonomic, PersonalModel Number BM700Model Name BM700Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/31070192-053f-40ce-8785-fc1f845b4c62</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5a3f8cbc-d438-4908-90b1-252d299324e0/web/1_1724907428506.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054132802209</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3837449267</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic V380 Mini Home Monitoring Security Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe premium quality material offers superior performanceWell-defined circuit ensures efficient functioningEffectively replaces your damaged part, ensuring the device is back to it's prime conditionSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDProduct Weight 340 gColour Name WhiteVideo Recording Resolution Type HDSensor Type CMOSNight Vision Lens YesProduct Length 8. 7 cmProduct Height 11. 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 7 cmFeatures Wi-Fi enabled, Removable Memory Card, HD Movie ModeModel Number V380</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8a808cb7-02d8-4b54-9cb6-1083a20cb789</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5e779e85-4f3c-4cae-a3ae-e69deff36ce3/web/1_1724906278768.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>98.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038374492671</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8656917509</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - White Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN13</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/12acb73c-34dd-4c8d-9967-5b77c9d45e5e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6c470b43-5d5c-4b71-9b1c-236cad525013/web/1_1727938486785.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086569175090</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3151615033</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Black Titanium</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN03</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ddb44718-900f-44ce-b301-d50c892195fd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4e29de11-e3e6-496d-a09b-9db0b25e6842/web/1_1727938930471.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031516150330</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4052562752</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Natural Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN33</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8f9da021-9d43-41c7-b0ee-d25d5eb5a197</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b309c40e-9233-40b9-98da-a7e911662114/web/1_1727939415091.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040525627528</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1247632236</g:id>
      <g:title>SUP Retro Portable Mini Handheld Gaming Consoles</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsApplicable to tv system, so that you can easily enjoy vivid and exciting games on a big screen. With extra controler (included) 2player can play together. High definition display, precise images transmission without delaying. Rechargeable lithium battery, support up to 3-4 hours of continuous game play. Good gift for your children, friends, both boys and girls will like it. Dual language(English, Arabic),Compact size and lightweight, convenient for carrying. OverviewSup Game Box Retro Classic Game Two-Player Machine with Remote Handheld Game Player Console Built-in 400 classic games Can be played on TV Rechargeable Lithium-ion battery and USB cable 6 hours of continuous game play after full charge Small size and light weight, suitable for traveling Perfect gift for children, retro game lovers, collectors Classic 8 bit games player. High quality video game portable console. With free built-in 400 classic games. Can connect to the TV, Support AV output. Language: English 7. 600mah rechargeable Li-ion battery supply. Digital gaming system, the handheld game console is very slim, portable and stylish. ]A digital multi-platform device that can be played on a TV. High-definition pictures of the game, no Caton. Arcade retro games, football, sports, puzzles, arcade, shooting, action, racing, fighting games, adventures, etcSpecificationsProduct Weight 200 gColour Name RedConnection Type WiredWhat's In The Box 1 x Retro game console FC, 1 x Handle,1 x User manual, 1 x AV cable, 1 xUSB cable, 1x 600MA lithium ion battery. Type of Console Software Game Boy Advance ClassicProduct Length 16 cmProduct Height 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 11 cmModel Number Retro Game ConsoleModel Name Retro Game Console</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b22cd3a3-994c-4159-9674-f274ea6b3e57</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8d3530f1-54f8-4410-9d2d-a2d618a66ebe/web/1_1724846382932.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012476322364</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4720286699</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Wi-Fi Wireless 720P/0.9MP HD IP Security Surveillance Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>Motion detection works perfectly with app message alarm (no photo)Make sure you are always the first when things happenNo ethernet cable is required during the entire network connection processSpecificationsProduct Weight 302 gColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 0. 92 MPModel Number 440835</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/557351c6-4668-4dbf-84ba-140f39b2a856</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fb3c40ef-4dee-4fcb-96b2-1ad2b60bcaf7/web/1_1724838323467.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>93.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047202866997</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8082892613</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic 12X50 Telescopio Bak4 Prism Night Vision Dual Green Film Monocular Zoom Telescope For Phone Hunting Professional Hiking Eyepiece</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsModel Number BAK4</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c7eed9c2-7bb6-4c32-aa69-7ee00082b841</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0044c176-6f71-48bf-91d8-880e508b9cf2/web/1_1724834862017.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080828926133</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
