<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9454733758</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee LED Strip Light S</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmart App and Voice ControlSegmented Color ControlEnhanced Music ModeUltra Bright BeadsFor The DIY Fans30m Of Effortless Remote ControlMatter CompatibleAdaptable For Major Festivities And MoreSpecificationsColour Name RGBType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number 6974316999218Model Name H612ABD1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/72bcbbfa-5c3d-4af1-a93b-7dd8774d3476</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d64b68ca-e238-422b-9d17-4e33eb059ad1/web/1_1731748463608.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>189 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094547337583</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5797738680</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless Controller For PlayStation 5 - Cosmic Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSturdy construction ensures longevity and durabilityMoulded from high-grade material to avoid chipping even through prolonged usageExudes an exquisite craftsmanship that manifests an accentuating showIt is one of the largest music companies (largest music publisher &amp;amp; second largest record label) and the third largest film studioHear higher-fidelity1 sound effects through the built-in Speaker in supported gamesIt operates as one of the world's largest manufacturers of consumer and professional electronic productsOverviewSony Group Corporation is a Japanese multinational conglomerate corporation headquartered in Kōnan, Minato, Tokyo. As a major technology company, it operates as one of the world's largest manufacturers of consumer and professional electronic products, the largest video game console company and the largest video game publisher. Through Sony Entertainment Inc, it is one of the largest music companies (largest music publisher &amp;amp; second largest record label) and the third largest film studio, making it one of the most comprehensive media companies, being the largest Japanese media conglomerate by size overtaking the privately held, family-owned Yomiuri Shimbun Holdings, the largest Japanese media conglomerate by revenue. Sony, with its 55 percent market share in the image sensor market, is the largest manufacturer of image sensors, the second largest camera manufacturer, and is among the semiconductor sales leaders. It is the world's largest player in the premium TV market for a television of at least 55 inches (140 centimeters) with a price higher than $2,500 as well as second largest TV brand by market share and, as of 2020, the third largest television manufacturer in the world by annual sales figures. The company's slogan is Be Moved. Their former slogans were The One and Only (1979–1982), It's a Sony (1982–2005), like. no. other (2005–2009) and make. believe (2009–2013). Sony has a weak tie to the Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group (SMFG) corporate group, the successor to the Mitsui keiretsu. Sony is listed on the Tokyo Stock Exchange (in which it is a constituent of the Nikkei 225 and TOPIX Core30 indexes) with an additional listing in the form of American depositary receipts listed in the New York Stock Exchange (traded since 1970, making it the oldest Japanese company to be listed in an American exchange), and was ranked 122nd on the 2020 Fortune Global 500 list. SpecificationsProduct Weight 500 gVersion KSA VersionColour Name Cosmic RedConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box 1 Wireless Controller, Instruction ManualType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Product Length 6. 9 cmProduct Height 18. 9 cmProduct Width/Depth 18. 8 cmFeatures With Microphone, Voice AssistantModel Number CFI-ZCT1W/CFI-ZCT1J 07/CFI-ZCT1J 02/CFI-ZCT1G 02Model Name CFI-ZCT1W</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a7bddc9e-954b-4b4c-96e2-6fe6e78fdd61</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fd8c9c6d-0012-44f8-bd40-4b203b401cd6/web/1_1731763839871.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>238 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057977386804</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7850136349</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit Pop 3s Ultra-large 1.96" HD AMOLED Display,Fashionable Curved & Metallic Design With Bluetooth Phone Calls Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSensor :- Accelerometer sensor, Heart Rate sensor and 3-axis motion sensorNotification :- Calendar Reminder, Call Notification ,Sedentary reminders,Smartphone Apps Notifications etcWatch Functions :- Bluetooth Phone Call;Weather;Multiple Sports Modes;Sleep Monitor;Heart Rate Monitor; Mobile Phone Music Control; Mobile Phone Camera Control; Find My PhoneOverviewPop 3s Ultra-large 1. 96" (4. 9 Cm) HD AMOLED Display,Fashionable Curved &amp;amp; Metallic Design with bluetooth phone calls. Music Control, Camera Control, Find Phone, Breath Training, 12/24-hour, Stopwatch, Clock, Weather Forecast, Date Display, Dial, Cloud Multi-Dial, Custom Dial, OTA Upgrade, Multi-Language UI Interface, Multi-Language, Data Storage, All-Day Data, Call Notification, Message Reminder, Alarm Reminder, Step Goal Completion Reminder, Binding Confirmation Reminder, Low Battery Reminder, Brightness Adjustment, Vibration Adjustment, Wear Monitoring, Lift Wrist to Wake Screen, Power Saving Mode, Smart DND, Quick Settings, Female Cycle, Voice Assistant, Blood-oxygen Saturation Measurement,Monitoring of Heart Rate, Sleep and Sports DataSpecificationsMaterial SiliconeColour Name SilverWhat's In The Box Smartwatch, Magnetic Charger, User ManualBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 96 inModel Number A2318Model Name A2318</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/aa6af3fa-5cc5-4a2c-b234-02b2fc9365a1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a8cae01a-17cd-4016-a3a5-3dfc2e22b43e/web/4_1731747170321.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>167 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078501363498</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4597277120</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Clip 4 Portable Bluetooth Speaker Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsJBL Pro Sound delivers surprisingly rich audio and punchy bass from Clip 4's compact size. JBL Clip 4's ultra-portable design goes great with the latest styles, and its colorful fabrics and expressive details make it look as great as it sounds. With a redesigned carabiner that's integrated into the speaker itself for extra protection, take your JBL Clip 4 anywhere and everywhere. Just clip on on a belt, strap, or buckle and go explore the worldWirelessly stream music from your phone, tablet or any Bluetooth enabled deviceTo the pool, to the park JBL Clip 4 is IP67 waterproof and dustproof so you can bring your speaker anywhere. Overview• Cool, portable, and waterproof. • The vibrant fresh looking JBL Clip 4 delivers surprisingly rich JBL Original Pro Sound in a compact package. • The unique oval shape fits easy in your hand. • Fully wrapped in colorful fabrics with expressive details inspired by current street fashion, it’s easy to match your style. • The fully integrated carabiner hooks instantly to bags, belts, or buckles, to bring your favorite tunes anywhere. • Waterproof, dustproof, and up to 10 hours of playtime, it’s rugged enough to tag along wherever you explore. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box JBL Clip 4 Portable Bluetooth Speaker (Black) USB Type-C Cable Limited 1-Year WarrantyModel Number JBLCLIP4BLKModel Name JBLCLIP4BLK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ffff5534-0343-4a46-9225-8e39643ef7b0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5eda44ee-6789-4024-8c17-181c60a5e89a/web/1_1731748483601.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>178 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045972771206</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1819065576</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic TRIX SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins for PS5 Console</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalised Style: TRIX SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates offer a sleek, customised look for your PS5 console. Protective Design: These shell panels shield your console from dust, scratches, and other potential damage. Easy Installation: Simply remove the original faceplate and replace it with the TRIX SLIM Disc Edition cover. Precise Fit: Designed specifically for the PS5 console, ensuring a seamless and secure fit. Durable Construction: Crafted from high-quality materials for long-lasting performanceOverviewElevate your PlayStation 5 gaming experience with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. These sleek, protective shell panels offer a stylish and customisable look for your PS5 console. Crafted with precision, these face plates provide a secure, dust-proof, and scratch-resistant barrier, ensuring your console remains pristine. With an easy installation process, you can effortlessly swap out the original panels and transform the appearance of your PS5. Embrace personalisation and protect your gaming investment with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. SpecificationsColour Name BlackType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number TRZ-SLIM DISC F/P BLACKModel Name TRZ-SLIM DISC F/P BLACK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bef4c6c1-9f6e-48b2-8780-5c6140519559</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cdf761f7-8a1b-4424-9619-31cd45ba1632/web/1_1731749785537.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>179 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018190655764</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7050305465</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic TRIX SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins for PS5 Console</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalised Style: TRIX SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates offer a sleek, customised look for your PS5 console. Protective Design: These shell panels shield your console from dust, scratches, and other potential damage. Easy Installation: Simply remove the original faceplate and replace it with the TRIX SLIM Disc Edition cover. Precise Fit: Designed specifically for the PS5 console, ensuring a seamless and secure fitDurable Construction: Crafted from high-quality materials for long-lasting performanceOverviewElevate your PlayStation 5 gaming experience with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. These sleek, protective shell panels offer a stylish and customisable look for your PS5 console. Crafted with precision, these face plates provide a secure, dust-proof, and scratch-resistant barrier, ensuring your console remains pristine. With an easy installation process, you can effortlessly swap out the original panels and transform the appearance of your PS5. Embrace personalisation and protect your gaming investment with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. SpecificationsColour Name RedType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number TRZ-SLIM DISC F/P REDModel Name TRZ-SLIM DISC F/P RED</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/97da6df8-ab1e-4e90-af0e-385b4a3d660d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/07a44975-59b5-4554-b931-3e78226cea7b/web/1_1731749182576.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>179 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070503054657</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2417363619</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Wave 200TWS True Wireless In-Ear Headphones Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights20 hours of combined playback with 5 hours in the earbuds and 15 hours in the caseFeel the sound with the deep bass powered by the 8mm drivers and add fun to your routineNow you can take calls or listen to music with either bud (or both), with dual connect technology, choose which one to use and leave the other one in the case to save battery lifeOverviewJBL DEEP BASS SOUND: Feel the sound with the Deep Bass powered by the 8mm Dynamic drivers and add fun to your routine. UPTO 20 HOURS OF PLAYTIME: With 5 hours in the earbuds and 15 hours in the case, the JBL Wave 200TWS don’t drop until you do. QUICK CHARGE: Running Low on Charge, worry not. A quick 15min of charge provides you with playtime upto an Hour. DUAL CONNECT TECHNOLOGY: With the Dual Connect Technology on the Wave 200 TWS, take calls or listen to music with either bud (or both). Choose which one to use and leave the other one in the case to save battery life. TOUCH CONTROLS FOR CALLS AND VOICE ASSISTANT: Just a touch of the earbud is what you need to control calls, sound or your mobile device’s voice assistant and stay in touch with your world. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box Headphone and ChargerAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number JBLW200TWSBLKINModel Name W200TWSBLK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e6a63160-d502-4ff0-a5b9-54b40c407dc9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1e864156-fb25-4fc1-a129-7bc87d899f6a/web/1_1731749903943.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>179 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024173636194</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9615002510</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Wind 3 FM Bluetooth Handlebar Speaker, Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDock/Handlebar Mount: Allow for effortless docking/undocking into included mounting bracket, specifically designed for bicycle &amp;amp; motorcycle handlebars. Two different EQ modes: ‘Sport’ mode for outdoors; ‘Bass’ for indoors. Multiple Playback Sources: Bluetooth, FM Radio, TF/ Micro SD, AUX in. Allow you choose freely for your favorite listening source. LED Display: Easy-to-read, make your riding and outing more convenient and safer. IP67 waterproof and dustproof: Give you the privilege to take your speaker anywhere. Hands-free Phone Call: Hands-free calling on the go with built-in microphone. up to 5 hours (dependent on volume level and audio content)OverviewJBL Wind 3 is Portable Bluetooth Speaker for Cycles, including two family members: WIND3 and WIND3 Slim version. Both are Bluetooth-enabled speakers, while WIND3 support more playback possibilities such as FM Radio, AUX in, and TF/microSD Media playback. You can choose whatever you like to suit your needs. Clipped onto your backpack shoulder strap, looped on a lanyard/tether, or even docked onto your bicycle handlebars, JBL Wind 3 delivers sound anywhere you go. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life 10 HoursModel Number Jbl Wind 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ca44a864-30cb-4c94-9be3-86e48e3d8015</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76b8671a-f6e7-4153-b612-4a054495c9e0/web/1_1731750112950.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>182 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096150025109</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2055456633</g:id>
      <g:title>Portable Audio Replacement Parts & Tools</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCrystal clear sound quality and user-friendly interfaceSturdy, portable and stylish designOffers stunning audio output by recording crisp highs and subtle lowsBuilt-in, direct USB connection for quick file transfer to your PCJust plug the directly into a free USB port for instant connection, no USB cable is requiredSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 2 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 14. 7 cmProduct Height 16. 3 cmProduct Width/Depth 4. 8 cmModel Number ICD-PX370</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/81b17e23-46e8-47fa-9699-18898e3ed67a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d04587f9-94b2-46e5-b6fc-ea3cf39d1c2c/web/1_1731757430848.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>215 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020554566333</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1973686087</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee LED Strip Light S, RGBICW Technology, 64+ Scene Modes, Smart App Control, Transparent Protective Epoxy Coating, IP67 Rated Protection, 10m Length | H612CBD1</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmart App and Voice ControlSegmented Color ControlEnhanced Music ModeUltra Bright BeadsFor The DIY Fans30m Of Effortless Remote ControlMatter CompatibleAdaptable For Major Festivities And MoreSpecificationsColour Name RGBType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number 6974316999225Model Name H612CBD1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e911753d-c47a-46a2-8d34-9d2842579017</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d5d59c17-dda8-494f-88de-4dcb61bc95fb/web/1_1731758610377.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>219 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019736860871</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7329708793</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless Controller For PlayStation 5 - White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDiscover a deeper, highly immersive gaming experience with the innovative new PS5 controller, featuring haptic feedback and dynamic trigger effectsThe DualSense wireless controller also includes a built-in microphone and create button, all integrated into an iconic, comfortable designFeel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motors. In your hands, these dynamic vibrations can simulate the feeling of everything from environments to the recoil of different weaponsExperience varying levels of force and tension as you interact with your in-game gear and environments. From pulling back an increasingly tight bowstring to hitting the brakes on a speeding car, feel physically connected to your on-screen actions. Batteries ‏ : ‎ 1 Lithium ion batteries required. Product Dimensions ‏ : ‎ 8. 5 x 4 x 19 cm; 500 GramsSwitch Voice Capture on and off Using the Dedicated Mute ButtonOverviewHeighten Your SensesThe DualSense wireless controller for PS5 offers immersive haptic feedback, dynamic adaptive triggers and a built-in microphone, all integrated into an iconic design. Bring gaming worlds to lifeHaptic feedbackFeel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motors. In your hands, these dynamic vibrations can simulate the feeling of everything from environments to the recoil of different weapons. Adaptive triggersExperience varying levels of force and tension as you interact with your in-game gear and environments. From pulling back an increasingly tight bowstring to hitting the brakes on a speeding car, feel physically connected to your on-screen actions. Find your voice, share your passionBuilt-in microphone and headset jack Chat with friends online using the built-in microphone — or by connecting a headset to the 3. 5-mm jack. Easily switch off voice capture at a moment's notice with the dedicated mute button. Create buttonCapture and broadcast your most epic gaming moments with the create button. Building on the success of the pioneering SHARE button, "create" offers players more ways to produce gaming content and broadcast their adventures live to the world. A gaming icon in your hands Take control with an evolved, two-tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with enhanced sticks and a reimagined light bar. SpecificationsProduct Weight 500 gVersion KSA VersionColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box 1 ControllerType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Product Length 6. 9 cmProduct Height 18. 9 cmProduct Width/Depth 18. 8 cmFeatures With Microphone, Voice AssistantModel Number CFI-ZCT1J/CFI-ZCT1W/CFI-ZCT1G/CFI-ZCT1NA/CFI-ZCP1Model Name DualSense</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8c06a67d-e957-4246-926e-5f5cb2fefe20</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/523938c6-956c-4e01-b400-05529f5ba6a1/web/1_1731763985308.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>238 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073297087931</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2518926919</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 DualSense Wireless Controller - Sterling Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to life - Feel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motors. In your hands, these dynamic vibrations can simulate the feeling of everything from environments to the recoil of different weaponsFind your voice, share your passion - Chat online through the built-in microphone. Connect a headset directly via the 3. 5mm jack. Record and broadcast your epic gaming moments with the create buttonA gaming icon in your hands - Take control with an evolved, two-tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with enhanced sticks and a reimagined light bar. The DualSense wireless controller retains many DUALSHOCK 4 features, returning for a new generation of playBluetooth pairing - The controller pairs directly with your compatible iPad, iPhone, Mac or Apple TV5 via Bluetooth, bringing signature PlayStation comfort and next-gen precision to your gaming experience. You can even enjoy the controllers touch pad, motion sensor and experience its adaptive trigger effects in compatible games. Multi-device connectivity - Connect using a USB Type-C cable or Bluetooth technology and easily play on more devices including Windows PC and Mac computersSpecificationsColour Name Sterling SilverConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFI-ZCT1J 08Model Name RZ896495001C</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c28d445d-33f8-4dc3-8335-a315d8a09d91</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0c1568b1-1b2e-47f5-8e44-4a74c7d7cb95/web/1_1731773988530.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>259 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025189269192</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6970039760</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless PS5 Controller- Pink (Official Version)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDiscover an even more intense and engaging gaming experience1 that brings the action in your hands to lifeThe dualsense wireless controller provides immersive haptic feedback, dynamic adaptive triggersTake control with an advanced two tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with improved sticksOverviewPS5 DualSense Wireless Cont 03X NOVA PINKSpecificationsVersion UAE VersionColour Name PinkConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFIZCT1WNOVAPINKModel Name CFIZCT1WNOVAPINK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c0c3befc-8472-4724-afe8-3150c846fdd4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bfb0243b-d640-4572-85d7-35ac16fa8ba5/web/1_1731775348391.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>274 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069700397605</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5912384380</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless Controller For PlayStation 5 - Starlight Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to lifeFind your voice, share your passionA gaming icon in your handsSoft-touch finish for a premium feelOverviewIlluminate your PS5 gaming space with the DualSense Starlight Blue Wireless Controller. Part of an expanded line-up of galaxy-themed accessories, this vibrant blue design is inspired by the radiating glow of stars that light up the cosmos. Discover a deeper, highly immersive gaming experience that brings the action to life in the palms of your hands. The DualSense Wireless Controller offers immersive haptic feedback, dynamic adaptive triggers and a built-in microphone, all integrated into an iconic comfortable design. (Available when feature is supported by game. Compared to DUALSHOCK 4 Wireless Controller. Internet and account for PlayStation Network required. )SpecificationsProduct Weight 430. 91 gVersion KSA VersionColour Name Starlight BlueConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box ControllerType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Product Length 9 cmProduct Height 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 3 cmModel Number CFI-ZCT1J 05/CFI-ZCT1G 05/CFI-ZCT1WModel Name CFI-ZCT1 BLUE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/54d1bd77-81e0-4960-b012-a04ea8e403bd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f69663a7-6292-4248-a502-05c50c8da8e3/web/1_1731763634460.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>237.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059123843803</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7450455316</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless PS5 Controller Midnight Black (Official Version)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDiscover an even more intense and engaging gaming experience1 that brings the action in your hands to lifeThe dualsense wireless controller provides immersive haptic feedback, dynamic adaptive triggersTake control with an advanced two tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with improved sticksOverviewPS5 DualSense Wireless Cont 01X BLACKSpecificationsVersion UAE VersionColour Name Midnight BlackConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFIZCT1WMIDNIGHTBLACKModel Name CFIZCT1WMIDNIGHTBLACK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/035356df-71d6-494e-99a1-18e9eedf1cde</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/88740fab-f061-49b9-8410-41a492c1a6d8/web/1_1731763733793.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>237.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074504553164</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6015984475</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee Phantasy Outdoor LED RGBIC Strip Lights 10m with WiFi</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsWater-Resistant Design64 Scene ModesEasy InstallationMusic Mode + DIY Mode30m Remote Control Range and Smart App ControlOverviewThe new addition to the strip light family will not disappoint when it comes to transforming your indoor/outdoor look. With a water-resistant coating, you've ensured a safe and colorful lighting experience. SpecificationsColour Name MulticolourConnection Type WiredModel Number 6974316993575Model Name 67053</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c786e471-9c72-466a-8818-c6ea84fd8e3f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f25b9ca3-266c-448f-bfee-285d4d7bc1f4/web/1_1731774447359.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>268 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060159844757</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1442520330</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit GTR Mini Smartwatch Midnight Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMaximize Your Style - Super Slim &amp;amp; Light Design, Stainless Middle FrameThe Finer Side of Fitness - 120+ Sports Modes &amp;amp; Smart Recognition 5 ATM Water-resistanceHealth-centered Zepp OS 2. 0 - Power-efficient Operating System Rich Ecosystem with Games &amp;amp; 3rd Party Apps24/7 Health Management - 24H Heart Rate, SpO2 &amp;amp; Stress Monitoring Track Sleep Quality &amp;amp; Daytime NapsWeightless Power - Up to 14 Days' Battery LifeSpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelColour Name Midnight BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 28 inModel Number GTR-MINI-Midnight BlackModel Name GTR-MINI-Midnight Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8c2c0ad8-5938-4cd0-b338-716e784efc37</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/de70c623-5044-49c6-b042-87cd1c142497/web/1_1731823094659.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>308 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014425203304</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9103956493</g:id>
      <g:title>HYPERX Cloud II Wired Over-Ear Gaming Headphones For PS4, PS5, XOne, XSeries, Nintendo Switch And PC</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe HyperX Cloud II Gaming Headset is ideal for high intensity gaming. Its frequency range of 15 to 25,000Hz makes it perfect for in game chat and team communication. The accessory’s USB Audio Sound Card helps the headset generate virtual 7. 1 surround sound, making it perfect for gaming tournaments where nothing but the best is required. The HyperX Cloud II Gaming Headset’s memory foam ear pads ensure the audio that is generated is heard clearly, even in environments with a lot of background noise. The pads sit comfortably on your ears, enabling you to don the headset for hours on end at a time. Lets you game comfortably and get the best audio experience on PC, Mac and consolesInterchangeable ear cups for varying sound profiles and different texture optionsEasily toggle Surround Sound 7. 1 on and off with a touch of a button. Includes independent audio and microphone volume controls for added convenience. The Internal sound card DSP amplifies audio and voice for optimal HiFi gaming experienceHyperX Cloud II is HiFi capable with 53mm drivers and delivers superior audio performance in gaming or professional audio environments. Its crystal-clear low, mid and high tones plus enhanced bass-reproduction create an immersive gaming experienceTeamSpeak certifies the voice quality to be clear and crisp with excellent sound quality. No audible echoes, background noises or voice distortions were detected in tests. Other compatible chat clients include Skype, Mumble and VentriloHyperX Cloud II comes with 100% memory foam ear pads and interchangeable ear cups for varying sound profiles and different texture options. Generate a virtual surround sound experience to create distance and depth that enhances any gaming, movie or music experience. It’s plug and play, which means no drivers are neededOverviewThe HyperX Cloud was built to be an ultra-comfortable gaming headset with amazing sound. We put a lot of thought into the details of our HyperX signature memory foam, the premium leatherette, clamping force, and weight distribution to create a headset that’s comfortable through long gaming sessions. It’s no wonder that it’s become the preferred gaming headset for millions of gamers. Whether you want to focus on the competition or relax with some of your favorite games, there’s a Cloud that’s perfect for you. SpecificationsProduct Weight 275 gColour Name Black/RedConnection Type WiredWhat's In The Box 1 X Microphone &amp;amp; HeadsetsType of Console Software PC GamesProduct Length 17 cmProduct Height 12 cmProduct Width/Depth 7 cmFeatures With Microphone, Noise CancellingModel Number 4P5M0AAModel Name KHX-HSCP-RD</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/89a3798c-49fc-41f9-835a-a59120c55cc6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c1b92092-e851-4ab6-97a9-708d2b783868/web/1_1731824580564.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>325 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091039564939</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9847722264</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony Dualshock Wireless Controller For PlayStation 4</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGet the edge with a much tighter sense of control over in-game actionsBring your games to life and hear every detail with sound effects coming directly from your DUALSHOCK 4 wireless controllerSee even more of your games with the integrated light bar that glows with various colours depending on in-game actionListen to your games in private and hear every boom, bang and blast with an integrated 3. 5mm audio jack for your headphonesCharge the controller's internal battery from your PS4 USB port, giving you hassle-free charging as you play1 lithium ion batteries requiredOverviewAt Sony, our mission is to be a company that inspires and fulfills your curiosity. Using our unlimited passion for technology, content and services to deliver groundbreaking new excitement and entertainment, as only Sony can. No other consumer electronics company today is as steeped in history and innovation as Sony. Sony’s humble beginning started in Japan in 1946 from the sheer determination and hard work of two bright and enterprising young men. Both Masaru Ibuka and Akio Morita joined hands in making their dream of a successful global company a reality, the only purpose is to fill the world with emotion, creativity and technology. The Sony Group recognises that its businesses have direct and indirect impact on the communities in which we operate. Find out how Sony is contributing towards being a positive global citizen. Corporate Social Responsibility is an integral part of Sony"s corporate philosophy. Careers at Sony Discover the diverse and interesting career opportunities available at Sony that offer you professional growth and success. Sony manufactures and distributes electronics products and provides related solutions. The Company produces televisions, cameras, mobiles, audio and video products. game equipment, and more. Sony Group also engages in game production, movie production, music production, and other business Moreover, the company also makes and distributes motion pictures, television productions and media networks under its Pictures branding. Its motion pictures include production, acquisition and distribution of live-action and animated motion pictures and direct-to-video content. The company also deals in music recording, publishing and distribution. the company also provides financial services, including life insurance for individuals and non-life insurance for business. The company is a known name also in digital and physical supply chain solutions to business customers in the entertainment, education, and information industries. SpecificationsProduct Weight 400 gColour Name Jet BlackConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box 1 ControllerType of Console Software PlayStation 4 (PS4)Product Length 20 cmProduct Height 7. 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 17. 7 cmModel Number CUH-ZCT2/E/CUH-ZCT2JModel Name DualShock 4</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/97f8c0b1-de6e-4104-927a-8298895f2a3b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/02007090-785d-4169-8fde-dbe2df655060/web/1_1731763136230.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>229 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098477222643</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4941261604</g:id>
      <g:title>Nintendo Switch Joy-Con (Pastel Purple / Pastel Green)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsJoy Cons Controller for SwitchStable Connection &amp;amp; Support WirelessDouble Vibration &amp;amp; Wake-up FunctionComfortable to Hold &amp;amp; Long Playing TimeSpecificationsColour Name Purple/GreenType of Console Software Nintendo SwitchModel Number HAC-A-JAWAF-MSEModel Name HAC-A-JAWAF-MSE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/406d3dc6-724b-4243-9be5-1be273c82a38</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/49327663-fe4f-4260-9f3e-e122faf528bc/web/1_1731764318924.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>240 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049412616041</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3469767330</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless Controller for PlayStation 5 - Purple</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to lifeFind your voice, share your passionA gaming icon in your handsBring fantastic motion control to supported games with the built-in accelerometer and gyroscope. You can easily Charge and play, now with USB Type-C Connectivity. Sony DualSense Wireless Controller for PlayStation 5 also has an Integrated speaker by which we can Select games that take on an extra dimension with higher-quality sound effects bursting from the controllerFor having an advanced gaming experience, the new Sony DualSense Wireless Controller for PlayStation 5 is a fantastic option, feels physically responsive, and gives feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motors. In your hands, these dynamic vibrations can simulate the feeling of everything from environments to the recoil of different weaponsOverviewFor having an advanced gaming experience, the new Sony DualSense Wireless Controller for PlayStation 5 is a fantastic option, feels physically responsive, and gives feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motors. In your hands, these dynamic vibrations can simulate the feeling of everything from environments to the recoil of different weapons. Experience varying levels of force and tension as you interact with your in-game gear and environments. From pulling back an increasingly tight bowstring to hitting the brakes on a speeding car, the special feature in Sony DualSense Wireless Controller for PlayStation 5 is it feel physically connected to your on-screen actions. And we can also Chat with friends online using the built-in microphone. Easily switch voice capture on and off at a moment’s notice with the dedicated mute but Capture and broadcast your most epic gaming moments with the create button. Bring fantastic motion control to supported games with the built-in accelerometer and gyroscope. You can easily Charge and play, now with USB Type-C Connectivity. Sony DualSense Wireless Controller for PlayStation 5 also has an Integrated speaker by which we can Select games that take on an extra dimension with higher-quality sound effects bursting from the controller. SpecificationsProduct Weight 435. 4 gVersion KSA VersionColour Name Galactic PurpleConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box ControllerType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Product Length 22. 86 cmProduct Height 20. 32 cmProduct Width/Depth 7. 62 cmModel Number CFI-ZCT1 PURPLE/CFI-ZCT1W/CFI-ZCT1J 04/CFI-ZCTI1GModel Name CFI-ZCT1 PURPLE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8392ef2e-b1ea-423a-b88b-310a6c21318f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b5f94158-3996-4a68-90e9-bfb3dbe6807a/web/1_1731764706665.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>243 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034697673308</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8590063159</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee RGBIC LED Strip Lights With Protective Coating</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmart Voice ControlRGBIC EffectsSmart App ControlExpansive Music Sync Mode64+ Preset Scene ModesOverviewAdd extra brightness to any room in your home. These LED strip lights use Wi-Fi and Bluetooth to easily control the colors and effects to personalize your lighting. SpecificationsColour Name MulticolorWhat's In The Box Gaming LED LightsType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number 6974316991007Model Name 57776</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/594f5d91-b64b-4fe0-84d6-4fa7e44ce04c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7ccaae2b-5343-4c3e-9650-11f8cd7ba2a1/web/1_1731765188236.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>248 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085900631592</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9929200224</g:id>
      <g:title>Nintendo Joy-Con Controller For Nintendo Switch</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsOne controller or two, vertical or sideways, attached to the console or separateJoy‑Con controllers give you total gameplay flexibilityPass a single Joy‑Con to a friend for instant two-player funHD Rumble puts you in the game with physical feedback, while the IR Motion Camera opens up new experiences like Nintendo LaboEach Joy-Con has a full set of buttons and can act as a standalone controller, and each includes an accelerometer and gyro-sensor, making independent left and right motion control possibleSpecificationsColour Name GreyConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software Nintendo SwitchModel Number [HAC-A-JAAAA-USZ]Model Name Joycon</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3dfe8a42-1372-4904-b7ad-89f4ed5b5c27</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d0ac0055-26c1-4ebd-a329-085577652e3c/web/1_1731767340744.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099292002243</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7636871172</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic TRIX SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins for PS5 Console, Faceplate Protective</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylish Design: These slim disc edition face plates offer a sleek and modern look to complement your PS5 consoleProtective Shell: Constructed from durable materials, these covers shield your console from dust, scratches, and other damage. Easy Installation: Simply snap the face plates onto your PS5 for a quick and secure fit. Customisable: With multiple colour options available, you can personalise the appearance of your console. Precise Fit: Designed specifically for the PS5, these face plates ensure a snug and seamless fitOverviewElevate your PlayStation 5 gaming experience with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. These meticulously crafted faceplate covers offer superior protection for your PS5 console, shielding it from dust, scratches, and everyday wear and tear. Designed with precision and attention to detail, these sleek skins seamlessly replace your original faceplates, enhancing the overall aesthetic of your gaming setup. Effortlessly install these protective shells and enjoy a refreshed look while safeguarding your cherished console. With their slim profile and precise fit, these faceplates ensure a snug and secure attachment, maintaining the console's streamlined appearance. Embrace a new level of personalisation and defence for your PS5 with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. SpecificationsType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number TRZ-COD F/PModel Name TRZ-COD F/P</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f8f85928-2770-419a-810d-194874ebdba4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6f056d0f-7061-44ec-a392-c1f80bc43c94/web/3_1731766941311.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0076368711728</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1738396617</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic TRIX SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins for PS5 Console, Faceplate Protective</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStylish Design: These slim disc edition face plates offer a sleek and modern look to complement your PS5 console. Protective Shell: Constructed from durable materials, these covers shield your console from dust, scratches, and other damageEasy Installation: Simply snap the face plates onto your PS5 for a quick and secure fit. Customisable: With multiple colour options available, you can personalise the appearance of your consolePrecise Fit: Designed specifically for the PS5, these face plates ensure a snug and seamless fitOverviewElevate your PlayStation 5 gaming experience with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. These meticulously crafted faceplate covers offer superior protection for your PS5 console, shielding it from dust, scratches, and everyday wear and tear. Designed with precision and attention to detail, these sleek skins seamlessly replace your original faceplates, enhancing the overall aesthetic of your gaming setup. Effortlessly install these protective shells and enjoy a refreshed look while safeguarding your cherished console. With their slim profile and precise fit, these faceplates ensure a snug and secure attachment, maintaining the console's streamlined appearance. Embrace a new level of personalisation and defence for your PS5 with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. SpecificationsType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number TRZ-God War F/PModel Name TRZ-God War F/P</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0507ca8d-0a3a-48f5-8ac3-6bd3a5448124</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2074db63-4ee8-45dc-b5f4-5a5a7b1e2d98/web/1_1731766357137.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017383966175</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6431505649</g:id>
      <g:title>Panasonic KX-TG6712UE1 Cordles Phone, Black</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsModel Number KX-TG6712Item Quantity 5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9efe9f65-82a6-4c97-b7ee-f72f30d6ffe5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f86db5f6-d45d-4ca5-a91b-598eff7f07c2/web/1_1731772294300.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>249 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064315056497</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6093348372</g:id>
      <g:title>PXN V3II Racing Game Steering Wheel With Brake Pedal</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe rounded steer ensures a superior and firm grip to minimize hand strainIncludes a foldable game pedal with spring and brake control for added convenienceBuilt-in dual vibration motors offer real life gaming experienceIntelligent cruise function releases your feet to enjoy the driving gamesSpecificationsProduct Weight 3. 6 KGColour Name BlackProduct Length 36 cmProduct Height 28 cmProduct Width/Depth 33 cmModel Number PXN-V3PROModel Name V3II</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/75614a77-cdbf-4881-871e-109647be6e13</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f8d8ddde-6dcd-401c-9f00-fb2860ab7861/web/1_1731774907020.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>269 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060933483721</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4465434056</g:id>
      <g:title>HYPERX Cloud II Gaming Headset For PC And PS4 And Xbox One, Nintendo Switch, Wired</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUSB audio sound card with 7. 1 virtual surround sound53mm drivers neodymium magnetsNoise cancelling microphone via inline sound cardEcho Cancelling via Inline Sound Card. Ambient noise attenuation:approx. 20 dBaSpecificationsColour Name RedConnection Type WiredType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number 4P5M0AAModel Name Cloud2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/581b7c18-d4bb-4397-9e41-7828d29b8b42</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/697259ea-2a3c-4315-adb7-1452e507ea1b/web/1_1731774271773.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>265 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044654340563</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4145198677</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 DualSense Wireless Controller (Official Version) - Volcanic Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to life - Feel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motorsFind your voice, share your passion - Chat online through the built-in microphone. Connect a headset directly via the 3. 5mm jack. Record and broadcast your epic gaming moments with the create buttonA gaming icon in your hands - Take control with an evolved, two-tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with enhanced sticks and a reimagined light barThe DualSense wireless controller retains many DUALSHOCK 4 features, returning for a new generation of playBluetooth pairing - The controller pairs directly with your compatible iPad, iPhone, Mac or Apple TV5 via Bluetooth, bringing signature PlayStation comfort and next-gen precision to your gaming experienceSpecificationsVersion KSA VersionColour Name Volcanic RedConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number CFIZCT1W07XVOLCANICRED/CFI-ZCT1J 07Model Name CFIZCT1W07XVOLCANICRED</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c6c58361-a6b4-45bd-ae8f-d31d17451eea</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/261ec687-2772-491b-92c0-5ed5ac319647/web/1_1731774814715.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>269 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041451986772</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1000187671</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless Controller for PlayStation 5 Cosmic Red (Official Version)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDiscover an even more intense and engaging gaming experience1 that brings the action in your hands to lifeThe dualsense wireless controller provides immersive haptic feedback, dynamic adaptive triggersTake control with an advanced two tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with improved sticksOverviewPS5 DualSense Wireless Cont 02X REDSpecificationsVersion UAE VersionColour Name Cosmic RedConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFIZCT1WCOSMICREDModel Name CFIZCT1WCOSMICRED</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/364bde9a-5c97-439e-85ba-d00d545ceeab</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f6d2be5c-4b38-4fe0-b541-3fb599188636/web/1_1731773694184.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>259 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010001876719</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9587261053</g:id>
      <g:title>Nintendo Splatoon 2 Pro Controller</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPro Controller is larger than the Switch's included Joy-Con controllers, even when they're placed in their Grip accessoryController also has a more traditional layout, most notably with its full d-pad, which is important for games that require digital precisionIncludes motion controls, HD rumble, built-in NFC for amiibo functionality, and moreFight faster and smarter with new and returning techniques, like the perfect shield and directional air dodgeThis controller allows you to play comfortably for longer periods of time when the console is in tv mode or tabletop modeOverviewCharging Lifespan - 40 HoursSpecificationsProduct Weight 189 gColour Name Black/Pink/GreenConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box USB-C To USB-A Cable, ControllerType of Console Software Nintendo SwitchProduct Length 1. 39 cmProduct Height 13. 58 cmProduct Width/Depth 16. 98 cmModel Number 45496590642Model Name Splatoon 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1e37b1a4-bf64-4eef-9243-29f829ad9261</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ba6ef577-4e41-4650-a617-ac5dc6302a72/web/1_1731773848508.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>259 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095872610532</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9353647860</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 DualSense Wireless Controller - Cobalt Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to life - Feel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motorsFind your voice, share your passion - Chat online through the built-in microphone. Connect a headset directly via the 3. 5mm jack. Record and broadcast your epic gaming moments with the create buttonA gaming icon in your hands - Take control with an evolved, two-tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with enhanced sticks and a reimagined light barThe DualSense wireless controller retains many DUALSHOCK 4 features, returning for a new generation of playBluetooth pairing - The controller pairs directly with your compatible iPad, iPhone, Mac or Apple TV5 via Bluetooth, bringing signature PlayStation comfort and next-gen precision to your gaming experienceSpecificationsVersion UAE VersionColour Name Cobalt BlueConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFI-ZCT1J 09Model Name CFI-ZCT1J 09</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4d5f0adb-d6c8-4d5e-bb1f-1be45547dbb1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/44769283-65b9-47d7-86a0-1f890e4f4407/web/1_1731773452366.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>259 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093536478603</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8462190055</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 DualSense Wireless Controller - Volcanic Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to life - Feel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motorsFind your voice, share your passion - Chat online through the built-in microphone. Connect a headset directly via the 3. 5mm jack. Record and broadcast your epic gaming moments with the create buttonA gaming icon in your hands - Take control with an evolved, two-tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with enhanced sticks and a reimagined light barThe DualSense wireless controller retains many DUALSHOCK 4 features, returning for a new generation of playBluetooth pairing - The controller pairs directly with your compatible iPad, iPhone, Mac or Apple TV5 via Bluetooth, bringing signature PlayStation comfort and next-gen precision to your gaming experienceSpecificationsVersion UAE VersionColour Name Volcanic RedConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFI-ZCT1J 07 , CFI-ZCT1WModel Name CFI-ZCT1J 07</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f7699586-b35a-49a8-821b-ded9c6805096</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f249b195-8893-452d-849f-45d3753c4a4d/web/1_1731773771947.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>259 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084621900550</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3074005161</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 DualSense Wireless Controller Official Version - Cobalt Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to life - Feel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motorsFind your voice, share your passion - Chat online through the built-in microphone. Connect a headset directly via the 3. 5mm jack. Record and broadcast your epic gaming moments with the create buttonA gaming icon in your hands - Take control with an evolved, two-tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with enhanced sticks and a reimagined light barThe DualSense wireless controller retains many DUALSHOCK 4 features, returning for a new generation of playBluetooth pairing - The controller pairs directly with your compatible iPad, iPhone, Mac or Apple TV5 via Bluetooth, bringing signature PlayStation comfort and next-gen precision to your gaming experienceSpecificationsVersion KSA VersionColour Name Cobalt BlueConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number CFIZCT1W09XCOBALTBLUE , CFI-ZCT1WModel Name CFIZCT1W09XCOBALTBLUE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/59d37a24-e4bf-4ee3-b65b-338b3487d181</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d7d380bc-6b2b-42aa-8875-264508dcaafe/web/1_1731774171694.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>265 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030740051611</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5469293266</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless Controller for PlayStation 5 (Official Version) - White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to life - Feel your in-game actions and Environment simulated through haptic feedback. Experience varying force and tension at your fingertips with adaptive triggers. Chat online through the built-in microphone, connect a headset directly via the 3. 5mm jack, Switch voice capture on &amp;amp; off using the dedicated mute button, record &amp;amp; broadcast your epic gaming momentsEnjoy a comfortable, evolved design with an iconic layout and enhanced sticks, intuitively interact with select games using the integrated motion sensor; Hear higher-fidelity1 sound effects through the built-in Speaker in supported gamesTake control with an advanced two tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with improved sticksElevate PC gaming with advanced features like haptic feedback and adaptive triggers in a range of blockbuster PC titles; Stream games from your PS5 or PS4 console to your PC and other devices via the PS Remote Play App** and play with the DualSense controllerOverviewPS5 DualSense Wireless ControllerSpecificationsVersion UAE VersionColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFIZCT1WModel Name CFIZCT1W</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b6ec7a1a-38e9-45e1-b7f9-4f8324e8a04a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/483e584b-a667-4cb2-ae33-f1155f684baa/web/1_1731775136326.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>269 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054692932668</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3355077340</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless PS5 Controller - Purple (Official Version)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDiscover an even more intense and engaging gaming experience1 that brings the action in your hands to lifeThe dualsense wireless controller provides immersive haptic feedback, dynamic adaptive triggersTake control with an advanced two tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with improved sticksOverviewPS5 DualSense Wireless Cont 04X PURPLESpecificationsVersion UAE VersionColour Name PurpleConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFIZCT1WPURPLE/CFI-ZCT1WModel Name CFIZCT1WPURPLE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c4d100b-9a6e-40a5-ad9d-1a905c411486</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/55c06142-c5eb-494b-89fd-f2014e717821/web/1_1731822179298.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>285 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033550773407</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5674553060</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless PS5 Controller- StarLight Blue (Official Version)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDiscover an even more intense and engaging gaming experience1 that brings the action in your hands to lifeThe dualsense wireless controller provides immersive haptic feedback, dynamic adaptive triggersTake control with an advanced two tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with improved sticksOverviewPS5 DualSense Wireless Cont 05X ICE BLUESpecificationsVersion UAE VersionColour Name Starlight BlueConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFIZCT1WBLUEModel Name CFIZCT1WBLUE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d927efe4-bf2e-48af-8fd9-e9c4eea6d159</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dd031939-a0ef-414d-8473-29d33d2d3497/web/1_1731775048454.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>269 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056745530609</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6164196732</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit GTR Mini Smartwatch Misty Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMaximize Your Style - Super Slim &amp;amp; Light Design, Stainless Middle FrameThe Finer Side of Fitness - 120+ Sports Modes &amp;amp; Smart Recognition 5 ATM Water-resistanceHealth-centered Zepp OS 2. 0 - Power-efficient Operating System Rich Ecosystem with Games &amp;amp; 3rd Party Apps24/7 Health Management - 24H Heart Rate, SpO2 &amp;amp; Stress Monitoring Track Sleep Quality &amp;amp; Daytime NapsWeightless Power - Up to 14 Days' Battery LifeSpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelColour Name Misty PinkBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 28 inModel Number GTR-MINI-Misty PinkModel Name GTR-MINI-Misty Pink</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8665f3a6-994e-4fe1-b933-5c0de5a2fd8c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c27ead04-e05e-489b-bd82-889a7e5b16e3/web/1_1731823532518.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>311 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061641967329</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4172001334</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee Neon LED Strip Light</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUse the Govee Home App to access a selection of lighting effects that best suits your personal aesthetic. Your light will glow in a variety of neon-like colors to add a soft and pleasant ambiance to any part of your space. Pair your light with Alexa and Google Assistant to access the Smart Voice Control feature. Get hands-free access to various features on the Govee Home App such as Music Mode, where your light will sync to your favorite audio. Customize your lighting your way using our innovative RGBIC technology. The integrated IC chip allows for multiple color options on a single light. Your colors, effects, and more can be adjusted using the Govee Home App. OverviewColor: RGBIC Control Method: Voice Control, APP Control, Control Box Length: 3m Water Resistant: Yes Voltage: 24VSpecificationsColour Name MulticolorWhat's In The Box Gaming LED LightsType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number 6974316991434Model Name 54884</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/536cf431-20ff-4bd2-a278-c8b1ed9f24bd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c800a88a-3439-4eb1-b6c2-aab4e9df474d/web/1_1731775499246.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>275 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041720013345</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7683487081</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee Envisual TV Backlight 3S (55~65 inch) (Netfilx)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFish-Eye Coreection correcting Edge distotion for more accurate color matchingView Bigger Dive DeeperWorks With AlexaWorks With Google homeOverviewGovee Envisual TV Backlight 3S (55~65 inch) (Netfilx)SpecificationsColour Name MulticolourConnection Type WiredModel Number 6974316999850Model Name 71313</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7eb84383-1429-44f3-b4d4-1941d01799b6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9b2560d2-fa91-4877-b837-3467bc3f1167/web/1_1731823433763.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>310 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0076834870812</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6673761189</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony Sony INZONE H3 Wired Gaming Headset, Over ear Headphones with 360 Spatial Sound</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSpatial Sound for Precise Detection of enemy’s location and distance to win in FPS/TPS gamesWith newly developed virtualiser, the audio signals that normally output in 2ch (stereo) will be reproduced in 7. 1ch sound that precisely capture the sounds from enemies’ footsteps and attacks360 Spatial Sound Personalizer optimize the sound field for individual hearing characteristics by using personal HRTF data estimated from ear imagesComfort-oriented headband design for long gameplay with wide head cushion, highly smooth comfortable nylon earpad &amp;amp; low side pressureClear voice chat with high-quality boom microphone with Flexible flip-up design &amp;amp; mute functionOverviewSony INZONE H3 Gaming Headset with Boom Microphone for PC/PS5SpecificationsColour Name White- H3Connection Type WirelessModel Number MDRG300/WModel Name MDRG300/W</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d7e3e3a7-3a8a-495c-9da6-4cfe9c6dc266</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fdd75c87-a2db-44f2-8bbc-3ace9baf0dba/web/1_1731824367623.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>409 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066737611896</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4455869441</g:id>
      <g:title>beats Studio Buds True Wireless Noise Cancelling Earphones Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsActive Noise CancellingMore Music Less NoiseUp to 8 hours of listening timeSpecificationsColour Name RedConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneModel Number MJ503AE/A / MJ503CH/AModel Name MJ503AE/A / MJ503CH/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/58da95dc-25bd-4a65-bf69-38dc78da7514</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d5f175e9-dee7-41ec-a001-d000d6156a34/web/1_1731854521926.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>429 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044558694410</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2544642317</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee RGBIC String Indoor Downlights 5m</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMultiple Modes: Use one-touch switching to find the most suitable lighting mode for your RGBIC string downlights, including scene modes, music modes, DIY modes, and more! The string lights is also cuttable for more possibilities!Party On with Music Mode: Transform the way your string wall lights shine with our energetic music modes. Expand your lighting game during parties, weddings, or any special occasion while your lights dance with your hottest tunes. Get Inspired with DIY Mode: Have complete creative control of your RGBIC downlights with our exciting DIY mode. Using Govee Home App, you can choose from millions of color options, adjust the brightness, etc. for fully customizable lighting!Easy Installation: These smart downlights are adaptable to most curvatures and corners for flexible installation options. Wherever you decide to place them, they will stay in place as long as you need them. Note: Unplug the lights before cutting. OverviewRGBIC Lighting Effects: Explore a vibrant rainbow of colors with 16 million color options and a lighting effect depth of up to 100 cm. Use your smart string lights to adorn your space with endless combinations you can easily customize. SpecificationsColour Name MulticolourConnection Type WiredModel Number 6974316997801Model Name 68570</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/41e6e139-ca3b-4128-bf89-f0e9fd74c614</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/48f4f26e-6a08-4656-bd97-486114f5948b/web/1_1731824893195.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>325 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025446423176</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5066214383</g:id>
      <g:title>Microsoft Xbox Elite Wireless Controller Series 2 For Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDesigned to meet the core needs of today’s competitive gamers, including just the components you need to unleash your best gameEnhance your aiming with new adjustable-tension thumbsticks, fire even faster with shorter hair trigger locks, and stay on target with a wrap-around rubberized gripEnjoy limitless customization with exclusive button mapping options in the Xbox Accessories appStay in the game with up to 40 hours of rechargeable battery life and refined components that are built to lastUse Xbox Wireless, Bluetooth, or the included USB-C cable to play across your Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One, Windows PC, and mobileOverviewPlay like a pro with the world's best performing controller. The Xbox Elite Series 2 Wireless Controller in White gives you more than 30 ways to play like a pro thanks to the new adjustable tension sticks, new interchangeable components (sold separately), and rechargeable battery offering up to 40 hours of battery life and endless customization via the Xbox Accessories app. Compatible with all your devices: Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One X, Xbox One S, Xbox One, Windows 10|11 PC, Android and iOS. ​SpecificationsColour Name Core WhiteConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software Xbox Series XModel Number 4IK-00002/4IK-00003 / 1797Model Name Xbox Elite</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d36cce68-0331-48fe-8357-85752466c9d5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1f802f31-44a6-414f-a3b2-83ca0f0a9557/web/1_1731825716625.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>415 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050662143836</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8695722657</g:id>
      <g:title>beats Studio Buds True Wireless Noise Cancelling Earphones White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsActive Noise CancellingMore Music Less NoiseUp to 8 hours of listening timeSpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneModel Number MJ4Y3AE/AModel Name FL6GKPKW0RP3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4f830345-586c-42b7-adae-912a0b8a0bbd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/82006176-efdd-4f11-a503-e53665c10309/web/1_1731827763051.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>419 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086957226571</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8747683733</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit GTR Mini Smartwatch Ocean Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMaximize Your Style - Super Slim &amp;amp; Light Design, Stainless Middle FrameThe Finer Side of Fitness - 120+ Sports Modes &amp;amp; Smart Recognition 5 ATM Water-resistanceHealth-centered Zepp OS 2. 0 - Power-efficient Operating System Rich Ecosystem with Games &amp;amp; 3rd Party Apps24/7 Health Management - 24H Heart Rate, SpO2 &amp;amp; Stress Monitoring Track Sleep Quality &amp;amp; Daytime NapsWeightless Power - Up to 14 Days' Battery LifeSpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelColour Name Ocean BlueBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 28 inModel Number GTR-MINI-Ocean BlueModel Name GTR-MINI-Ocean Blue</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/296de583-f163-414d-b589-c0a614eba37e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/477bf077-c55d-4f83-b786-8c7c9837b9a0/web/1_1731827337314.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>339 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087476837330</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2047313335</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Tune 235NC True Wireless Noise Cancelling IN-EAR Earbuds Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmartly designed 6. 0mm drivers enhanced by the stick form factor deliver JBL's Pure Bass Sound so you'll feel every pulsing beat. Hear more of what you want, less of what you don't. Active Noise Cancelling technology with 2 microphones lets you minimize audio distractions. As part of our noise cancelling technology, with Ambient Aware you can tune into your surroundings at any time so that you feel safer when you're out in the world, while TalkThru lets you stop for a quick chat without having to remove your headphones. Enjoy hassle-free, hands-free calls in stereo. The Tune 235NC TWS are equipped with 4 microphones, so you'll always be heard with perfect clarity. Never hesitate to take or make a call again. OverviewTackle your day one song at a time with the JBL Tune 235NC TWS. True wireless earbuds give you 40 hours of exceptional JBL Pure Bass Sound, while the ergonomic and water-resistant design gives you all-day comfort in any weather. Connect calls simply and seamlessly with 4 mics that cancel out ambient noises offering perfect calls anywhere. And with Active Noise Cancelling and Smart Ambient technology, you choose whether you want to tune out the world or engage with your surroundings. The light stick-closed design ensures comfort all-day long. Add to that, the JBL Headphones App lets you personalize your entire listening experience. Stay connected to your world, your way. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessAudio Jack Type-CAudio Headphone Type In-EarFeatures Bluetooth, Earhook, Active Noise CancellationModel Number JBL235NCTWSBLKModel Name JBL TUNE 235NCItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4529cd1b-941f-4e73-9415-bcab8d71b37d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fcff50c9-dce5-4749-a119-db5afbc925fa/web/1_1731825852875.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>339 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020473133357</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3705159002</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic TRIX SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins for PS5 Console</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalised Style: TRIX SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates offer a sleek, customised look for your PS5 consoleProtective Design: These shell panels shield your console from dust, scratches, and other potential damage. Easy Installation: Simply remove the original faceplate and replace it with the TRIX SLIM Disc Edition cover. Precise Fit: Designed specifically for the PS5 console, ensuring a seamless and secure fit. Durable Construction: Crafted from high-quality materials for long-lasting performance. OverviewElevate your PlayStation 5 gaming experience with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. These sleek, protective shell panels offer a stylish and customisable look for your PS5 console. Crafted with precision, these face plates provide a secure, dust-proof, and scratch-resistant barrier, ensuring your console remains pristine. With an easy installation process, you can effortlessly swap out the original panels and transform the appearance of your PS5. Embrace personalisation and protect your gaming investment with the TRIX: SLIM Disc Edition Face Plates Cover Skins. SpecificationsColour Name PurpleType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number TRZ-SLIM DISC F/P PurpleModel Name TRZ-SLIM DISC F/P Purple</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/707afd4a-7bdc-4385-b336-a26b0ff6eebe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4d850af6-6b0f-43a5-a50e-fcbf6260685a/web/1_1731749622497.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>179 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037051590020</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1616268636</g:id>
      <g:title>PXN Game Steering Wheel For PlayStation/Xbox/Switch/PC With H-Patten Shifter and 3 Pedal -wired</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMORE RACING GAMES : PXN-V9 game steering wheel can provide PC platform with European truck simulation, truck life, Maxthon China, Shenli Corsa and other games; Xbox can be adapted to Horizon 4, Dust 2. 0, Forza Motorsport series ,Racing Project 2 and other games; PS platform includes Need for Speed 20, F1 2019, Super Touring Car, Driving Club, etc. ; Switch includes Asphalt, Sonic Racing, Mario Kart and other games. HIGH-QUALITY STRUCTURE : The PS4 racing wheels is made of non-slip ABS matte non-slip material, with real dual vibration motors, with 7 powerful suction cups and C-shaped fixing frame, which can maintain a more comfortable and long-lasting gaming experience. For better It is convenient for players to use PXN V9 racing wheels. We have prepared the "V9 Tool" APP. Players can search for "V9 Tool" in the Apple App Store to download and install. HIGH-END RACING SIMULATOR : PC racing wheel provides 270/900° rotation switching function, toggle the button under the steering wheel to switch. The handbrake shift lever of the PS4 game steering wheel is designed for professional racing games, 6-in-one manual gearshift lever allows players to experience the sense of presence brought by manual braking and shifting, and supports forward and R reverse gears; handbrake and high-low performance modes adopt button design to reduce false contacts. PC DUAL ANALOG STEERING WHEEL : PC dual-mode driver, used to play computer racing, freely switch between the two modes, with a three-in-one linear pedal (clutch, brake and accelerator), adjust the strength of the pedal Realize the control of the throttle and brake,support automatic endurance,throttle lock value; steering wheel can be rotated 270/900°, rubber texture coated wheel handle, equipped with sports car-style paddles,manual gear shifting,imitating the ergonomic design of racing wheels. OverviewPLAY MULTI-PLATFORM GAMES : PC game racing wheels steering wheel with USB connection port, compatible with Xbox One / Xbox Series X&amp;amp;S/PC / PS3/ PS4 / P5 Nintendo Switch platform, and compatible with Windows 7/8/10 operating system(Please download the application:PXN Play or V9 Tool to test the function and mapping buttons)SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WiredWhat's In The Box Gaming Steering Wheel For PS5, PS4, PS3, Xbox, Switch, PCType of Console Software PS4/PS5Model Number PXN V9Model Name Gaming Steering Wheel For PS5, PS4, PS3, Xbox, Switch, PC</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/63cad496-5879-4b79-ba66-810f44a5b1da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/416deaa1-148e-4d2b-b2e1-eecc9fba7b39/web/1_1731855204656.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>439 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016162686365</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3480527872</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee Govee Envisual TV Backlight (55~65 inch)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUpgraded Fish-eye Correction Camera Technology: Corrects fisheye distortion lenses, which expands the effective color-matching range for more accurate edges. Upgraded Govee Envisual Technology: The upgraded Govee TV backlight with a fisheye lens correction camera has more accurate color capturing. 4 Colors in 1 with RGBIC+W: These TV lights add an extra warm white chip to enhance movies and gaming. Full Compatibility for Any TV Content: The TV Backlight 3 Lite instantly captures the color of any TV screen without compatibility issues. Smart Activation: Manage your TV LED strip lights with Govee Home App or voice commands via Alexa and Google Assistant. SpecificationsColour Name MulticolourType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number 6974316997597Model Name 68850</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9e1e1785-0f30-479b-9a25-97c6f17d01f1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/11a8791d-2d2d-4e4a-afbb-a5c4db3d90f5/web/1_1731854140209.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>429 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034805278722</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6682448609</g:id>
      <g:title>beats Studio Buds True Wireless Noise Cancelling Earphones Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsActive Noise CancellingMore Music Less NoiseUp to 8 hours of listening timeSpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneModel Number MJ4X3AE/A / MJ4X3CH/AModel Name PL6FXFNU0RP2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1307bbc7-2f91-46c6-b7a5-9b1c3743cfb3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/90e987ea-b84c-46a5-b20b-bf29661f4738/web/1_1731855434515.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>439 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066824486093</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8381011558</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless Controller For PlayStation 5 - Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBring gaming worlds to lifeFind your voice, share your passionA gaming icon in your handsFeel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motors. In your hands, these dynamic vibrations can simulate the feeling of everything from environments to the recoil of different weaponsExperience varying levels of force and tension as you interact with your in-game gear and environments. From pulling back an increasingly tight bowstring to hitting the brakes on a speeding car, feel physically connected to your on-screen actionsChat with friends online*** using the built-in microphone or by connecting a headset to the 3. 5mm jack. Easily switch voice capture on and off at a moment’s notice with the dedicated mute button. ***Internet and account for PlayStation Network requiredOverviewWhether you enjoy playing solo or multiplayer games online, the Sony PS5 DualSense Wireless Controller can offer responsive gaming controls. Its dual actuators offer physically responsive feedback to your gaming motions. In addition, these dynamic vibrations can mimic a range of sensations, such as the feel of several environments and the recoil of a plethora of weapons. Moreover, with this Controller's adaptive triggers, your on-screen actions can have a realistic effect, whether you're releasing a severely constricted bowstring or slamming on the brakes of a fast-moving car. Feel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motors. In your hands, these dynamic vibrations can simulate the feeling of everything from environments to the recoil of different weapons. Experience varying levels of force and tension as you interact with your in-game gear and environments. From pulling back an increasingly tight bowstring to hitting the brakes on a speeding car, feel physically connected to your on-screen actions. SpecificationsProduct Weight 430. 91 gVersion KSA VersionColour Name Nova PinkConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box ControllerType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Product Length 7. 62 cmProduct Height 20. 32 cmProduct Width/Depth 17. 78 cmModel Number CFI-ZCT1 PINK/CFI-ZCT1W/CFI-ZCT1J 03Model Name CFI-ZCT1 PINK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f4754f1c-251f-44a8-9230-bdae6a1917db</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/420db4ff-9a3e-4412-8895-93f829354c81/web/1_1731763531121.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>235 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083810115584</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8490983896</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DualSense Wireless PS5 Controller - Grey Camouflage</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFeel your in-game actions and environment simulated through haptic feedback Experience varying force and tension at your fingertips with adaptive triggersChat online through the built-in microphone Connect a headset directly via the 3. 5mm jack Switch voice capture on and off using the dedicated mute button Record and broadcast your epic gaming moments with the create buttonEnjoy a comfortable, evolved design with an iconic layout and enhanced sticks Charge and play with a built-in battery and USB Type-CIntuitively interact with select games using the integrated motion sensor Hear higher-fidelity* sound effects through the built-in speaker in supported gamesExperience varying levels of force and tension as you interact with your in-game gear and environments From pulling back an increasingly tight bowstring to hitting the brakes on a speeding car, feel physically connected to your on-screen actionscOverviewDiscover a deeper, highly immersive gaming experience with the innovative new PS5 controller, featuring haptic feedback and dynamic trigger effects. The DualSense wireless controller also includes a built-in microphone and create button, all integrated into an iconic, comfortable design. SpecificationsVersion KSA VersionColour Name Grey CamouflageConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFI-ZCT1J 06/CFI-ZCT1W/CFI-ZCT1G 06Model Name B0BHT4N8MF</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eb4dc006-a60d-4664-8093-dd27e2ad3ebf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/849f317d-e5db-4e03-886c-1d15e27b8799/web/1_1731763378266.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>235 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084909838964</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6540090122</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony Digital Voice Recorder With MP3 Recording And Playback ICD-PX240 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRecord MP3 audio and play it back through a 300mW speakerLong battery life enables up to 32hrs recording (MP3 8kbps)4GB of memory lets you store up to 1043hrsOrganize, protect, and delete files and foldersOverviewAbout the Company Sony is a Japanese multinational conglomerate corporation headquartered in Kōnan, Minato, Tokyo. In 2018, Sony was ranked 97th in the Fortune Global 500 list. Its diversified business includes consumer and professional electronics, gaming, entertainment and financial services. The company owns the largest music entertainment business in the world, the largest video game Console business and one of the largest video game publishing businesses. Also, it is one of the leading manufacturers of electronic products for the consumer and professional markets, and a leading player in the film and television entertainment industry. It works to inspire and fulfill your curiosity. Using its unlimited passion for technology, content and services. It is dedicated to deliver groundbreaking new excitement and entertainment as it has been doing till date. SpecificationsProduct Weight 72 gColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box 1xRecorder,Quick Start GuideProduct Length 21. 3 inProduct Height 115. 2 inProduct Width/Depth 38. 5 inFeatures Compact Size, Receiver, Smart, WirelessModel Number ICD-PX240Model Name ICD-PX240</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3af8c0f8-ad72-4fcb-8804-d7c238f39ebe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7dbc19d6-ee54-4f52-86cf-07e1669fbd8f/web/1_1731750667897.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>183 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065400901227</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2964143571</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit GTR 2 Smartwatch Lightning Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe ambient light display allows automatic adjustment of brightness on the watch suited to your environmentTrack all stages of sleep every night and keep a tab on your sleep health with the sleep monitoring feature on the watchSports Friendly It is Splash and sweat resistance makes it the perfect fitness companion to haveKeep a track of your well being and health right from your wrist with Noise Health Suite featuring a variety of health featuresWhen the pressures of daily life start to pile up, or you want the comfort of having planned ahead, the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro smart fitness watch is there for you. OverviewYou can set the watch to monitor stress levels all day, get alerts for abnormally high stress levels, perform a manual stress level test on-demand and open the watch's breathing exercise if high stress detected. Whether you’re an athlete, a professional, or someone who just wants to get more active in daily life, heart health is important. The Amazfit GTR 3 Pro smart watch can monitor your heart rate all day – even while swimming. With alerts for abnormally high or low heart rates, as well as tracking heart rate zones so you can optimize your workouts, the watch is a comprehensive and easy-to-use health partner for everyone. Stressful work days or inconsistent sleep schedules can lead to poor sleep quality. With the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro fitness watch, you can check your sleep data quickly, easily, and directly on the watch screen - so there's no need to go searching through your phone when you first wake up. You can set the watch to monitor stress levels all day, get alerts for abnormally high stress levels, perform a manual stress level test on-demand and open the watch's breathing exercise if high stress detected. Match your mood, an outfit or the occasion with a wide selection of more than 150 stylish watch faces, all of which have a matching always-on display. Want a more high-tech feel? Step into the future and choose from 15 animated watch faces. Prioritize preferred features with 23 editable modular dials - or even upload your own photo as the background image for true personalization. When you’re out for a walk, working out, or seeing friends, you can leave your phone in your pocket. Through Bluetooth connection to your phone, the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro smart watch can receive phone calls. Easily set an alarm, ask questions, get a translation and more with Alexa, which is built into the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro smart watch. If you’re out and don’t have internet access, the smart watch also has an offline voice assistant for you to perform operations like engaging a sports mode or opening a health metric feature via voice command. Special Features: Sleep Monitor, Multisport Tracker, Activity Tracker, Notifications, Heart Rate Monitor, Device Interface - Primary: Touchscreen. SpecificationsMaterial SiliconeBattery Size None NoneColour Name Lightning GreyWhat's In The Box Amazfit GTR 2 Smartwatch, Manual, Charging BaseBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Dial Material AluminiumSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 39 inModel Number 44027234353404Model Name GTR2 Lightning Grey</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5ad50557-0b39-4995-945c-8c18fc5846b1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7f58ec23-2754-4a9e-bbaa-df7889f88fe0/web/1_1731928317692.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>358 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029641435712</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8405715078</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony Pulse 3D Wireless Headset For PS5 And PS4</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe PULSE 3D wireless headset features a refined design with dual noise-cancelling microphones, and built-in rechargeable battery, plus an array of easy-access controlsHow games were made to sound, fine-tuned for 3D audio on PS5 consoles, enjoy comfortable gaming with refined earpads and headband strapDesigned for gamers, chat with your friends through the hidden noise-cancelling microphones, quickly adjust audio and chat settings with easy-access controlsEnjoy up to 12 hours of wireless play with the built-in rechargeable battery, easily connect to your PS5 or PS4 console using the wireless adaptorOverviewInject a stylish urban aesthetic into your PS5 gaming with this Grey Camouflage headset – fine-tuned to deliver the 3D Audio made possible by the PlayStation 5 console. SpecificationsVersion International VersionColour Name Grey CamouflageConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box Microphone &amp;amp; HeadsetsType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFI-ZWH1E06 / CFI-ZWH1J06</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7e9d3a63-9b6f-4f21-9850-052481065c85</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/73dae43d-f1ab-4888-b863-c1be3647b7af/web/1_1731926284761.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>345 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084057150789</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5211559916</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony 2.1 Channel Home Theatre Satellite Speakers SAD20 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsLatest Bluetooth technology to maximize device compatibility and pairing speedHigh-capacity battery provides long hours of playtimeClean bass sound you can easily pick up and put in your bagJust one cable required to connect and is easy to control by user friendly Remote controllerYou can connect it with mobile, TV or your PC and bring great sound to all your entertainmentOverviewFront Speaker Driver Size- 80 mm, Speaker Type- 2. 1 Channel, Centre Speaker Impedance- 4 ohms, Frequency Response- 40Hz-150HzSpecificationsProduct Weight 5 KGColour Name BlackWattage 60 WModel Number SAD20Model Name Sony</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ea23066f-0ca0-4a67-8b42-4192dc2faaf8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6817c68e-43fa-4558-aeb8-62a8c5b206f6/web/1_1731931764090.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>389 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052115599160</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9786087892</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit Active Smart Watch</g:title>
      <g:description>Amazfit Active Smart Watch With Ai Fitness Exercise Coach, Gps, Bluetooth Calling, Music, 14 Day Battery, 1. 75 Inch Amoled Display, Alexa Built-In, Fitness Watch For Android And iPhone Petal PinkHighlightsSuper-light and stylish design: The amazfit active smartwatch is like finery with a mind of a super-computer. Feel confident and ready for action, anytime and anywhereUltra-long 14-day battery life: Life doesn't pause, and neither should you. Stay charged through meetings, moments, and milesAI-powered training guidance by zepp coach: Sometimes, the hardest part of leading an active life is just finding the time. Zepp coach harnesses the power of AI to generate workout plans that are tailored to you5 Satellite positioning systems and route navigation: The amazfit active smart watch will track every turn you take through the city streets and every trail you explore through the great outdoorsBluetooth phone calls and music playback: Via bluetooth connection to your phone, the smart watch can answer incoming calls or dial outgoing calls, control your phone's camera and music, and moreSpecificationsMaterial SiliconeColour Name Petal PinkWhat's In The Box Smartwatch Including Standard Strap, Magnetic Charging Cable, Instruction ManualBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 75 inModel Number ctive PinkModel Name Active Pink</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/26811e07-ef0d-48dd-94d7-7c24ba1e79ce</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c8c1c5fd-10de-442c-84d9-46670bcbd49e/web/4_1731928546938.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>364 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097860878924</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6524473510</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit Active Smart Watch With Ai Fitness Exercise Coach</g:title>
      <g:description>Amazfit Active Smart Watch With Ai Fitness Exercise Coach, Gps, Bluetooth Calling, Music, 14 Day Battery, 1. 75 Inch Amoled Display, Alexa Built-In, Fitness Watch For Android And iPhone Lavender PurpleHighlightsSuper-light and stylish design: The amazfit active smartwatch is like finery with a mind of a super-computer. Feel confident and ready for action, anytime and anywhereUltra-long 14-day battery life: Life doesn't pause, and neither should you. Stay charged through meetings, moments, and milesAI-powered training guidance by zepp coach: Sometimes, the hardest part of leading an active life is just finding the time. Zepp coach harnesses the power of AI to generate workout plans that are tailored to you5 Satellite positioning systems and route navigation: The amazfit active smart watch will track every turn you take through the city streets and every trail you explore through the great outdoorsBluetooth phone calls and music playback: Via bluetooth connection to your phone, the smart watch can answer incoming calls or dial outgoing calls, control your phone's camera and music, and moreSpecificationsMaterial LeatherColour Name Lavender PurpleWhat's In The Box Smartwatch Including Standard Strap, Magnetic Charging Cable, Instruction ManualBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 75 inModel Number Active LavenderModel Name Active Lavender</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6c63d34b-997b-4c0d-8e5f-7ddd6888fe11</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c3277afd-df97-44e3-8c1a-7aed5d4f8266/web/1_1731929249509.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>374 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065244735101</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2927563071</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony INZONE H3 Wired Gaming Headset</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSpatial Sound for Precise Detection of enemy’s location and distance to win in FPS/TPS gamesWith newly developed virtualiser, the audio signals that normally output in 2ch (stereo) will be reproduced in 7. 1ch sound that precisely capture the sounds from enemies’ footsteps and attacks360 Spatial Sound Personalizer optimize the sound field for individual hearing characteristics by using personal HRTF data estimated from ear imagesComfort-oriented headband design for long gameplay with wide head cushion, highly smooth comfortable nylon earpad &amp;amp; low side pressureClear voice chat with high-quality boom microphone with Flexible flip-up design &amp;amp; mute functionOverviewSony INZONE H3 Gaming Headset with Boom Microphone for PC/PS5SpecificationsColour Name White- H3Connection Type WirelessModel Number MDRG300/WModel Name MDRG300/W</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5dd2143d-f271-43e7-87a4-40d55e340cf8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a61a02d1-83f8-4117-9103-0be6222e399d/web/1_1731932268802.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>409 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029275630712</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2425975154</g:id>
      <g:title>dji OSMO Mobile SE Intelligent Gimbal</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPortable, Foldable, and Magnetically Quick - Take this compact gimbal on all your adventures. Snap-in and out with ease with the magnetic clamp to capture the second you want to shootUpgraded Active Track 5. 0 - Track your subject at further distances, and keep your subject in frame even if they are on the move. Keep tracking their profile as they run to shoot a goal or spin around in a dance recitalEffortless Editing - Whether it's shot-by-shot assistance with DJI Mimo's ShotGuides or the mulude of templates to choose from in LightCut, go beyond just cutting down clips and get edits that inspireSmooth Footage - Elevate your shots with 3-axis stabilization. With a next-gen control algorithm, Osmo Mobile SE compensates in real-time for buttery smooth footageLandscape and Portrait - From theater-worthy dramatic shots to light and casual social media content, switch effortlessly between horizontal and vertical shooting. . New Status Panel - Quickly and conveniently check the battery level, system indicator status, and gimbal mode. Switch button Follow, Tilt Lock, FPV, and Spin Shot mode to get dynamic shotsPost sale Warranty Support provided directly by DJI UAE Support centerOverviewUnfold, snap-in, and start rolling. Osmo Mobile SE's lightweight foldable body and magnetic quick-release design make it easy to carry and capture at a moment's notice. With the newly added status panel, you can switch gimbal modes with the push of a button. An array of intelligent features helps to dynamically shoot and highlight moments, adding a creative flair to anything you want to capture. Whether it's a game-winning touchdown or baby's first steps, you're ready. Just clamp in your smartphone, snap it onto the gimbal, and start shooting. The gimbal and magnetic phone clamp can be separated, which allows you to snap your smartphone in or out to call and share the exciting news. SpecificationsColour Name GreyCamera Resolution 2 MPModel Number DJI-ZM500SE/OK2OOModel Name DJI-ZM500SE/OK2OO</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c5c64ccf-bec4-41da-980f-5cadd3d8baff</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bbdc2d12-b1cb-49a9-a818-8012624278d6/web/1_1731931591999.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>DJI</g:brand>
      <g:price>388 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024259751544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7072262795</g:id>
      <g:title>Godox X3 TTL Wireless Flash touchscreen Trigger for Nikon</g:title>
      <g:description>Godox X3 TTL Wireless Flash touchscreen Trigger for Nikon</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/970dd218-a3c4-4f26-9a3c-45c30b7dfc91</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7bb5125b-0878-4592-aa96-474e7a6026aa/web/1_1731931612389.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070722627953</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6600894183</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit Active Edge Smart Watch With Stylish Rugged Sport And Fitness Design</g:title>
      <g:description>Amazfit Active Edge Smart Watch With Stylish Rugged Sport And Fitness Design, GPS, AI Health Coach For Gym, Outdoor, Workouts And Exercise, 16 Days Battery, 10 Atm Water Resistant Lava BlackHighlightsTraining templates: Customize your workout routine by creating training templates in the zepp app, and sync them to the watchInterval training: Streamline your training by creating interval training plans directly on the watch itselfConnect to workout devices : Connect the watch to a heart rate belt or cycling power meter, thanks to the immense bluetooth connectivity of the zepp OS 2. 0Better than any gym buddy, the amazfit active edge comes with an intelligent strength training mode that canPortrait watch faces : Upload your own images; the watch will alternate them with every glanceSpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Lava BlackConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 32 inModel Number Active Edge Lava BlackModel Name Active Edge Lava Black</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f2f78e58-da56-42cf-992c-230020df7e29</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0a6efd80-dc4d-45e6-9b79-fb8f0d4569f4/web/1_1731931024857.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>382 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066008941837</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8250868200</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Flip 5 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsJBL Flip 5 Portable Wireless Bluetooth SpeakerBring the party anywhere, Don’t sweat the small stuff like charging your battery. Flip 5 gives you more than 12 hours of, playtimePremium sound qualitySpecificationsProduct Weight 540 gColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box 1 x Bluetooth SpeakerProduct Length 7. 1 inProduct Height 2. 7 inProduct Width/Depth 2. 9 inModel Number JBLFLIP5BLACKModel Name jbl Portable Bluetooth</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c25e6781-9e60-47ef-b823-8dc23d59d542</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7c779450-ce0a-4526-b3be-54a30179825b/web/1_1731931707052.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082508682001</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7427980934</g:id>
      <g:title>Microsoft Xbox Elite Wireless Controller Series 2</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDesigned to meet the core needs of today’s competitive gamers, including just the components you need to unleash your best gameEnhance your aiming with new adjustable-tension thumbsticks, fire even faster with shorter hair trigger locks, and stay on target with a wrap-around rubberized gripEnjoy limitless customization with exclusive button mapping options in the Xbox Accessories appStay in the game with up to 40 hours of rechargeable battery life and refined components that are built to lastUse Xbox Wireless, Bluetooth, or the included USB-C cable to play across your Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One, Windows PC, and mobileOverviewPlay like a pro with the world's best performing controller. The Xbox Elite Series 2 Wireless Controller in White gives you more than 30 ways to play like a pro thanks to the new adjustable tension sticks, new interchangeable components (sold separately), and rechargeable battery offering up to 40 hours of battery life and endless customization via the Xbox Accessories app. Compatible with all your devices: Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One X, Xbox One S, Xbox One, Windows 10|11 PC, Android and iOS. ​SpecificationsColour Name Core WhiteConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software Xbox Series XModel Number 4IK-00002/4IK-00003 / 1797Model Name Xbox Elite</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5c1fb1bf-9ef6-496c-a7e1-99016a391f68</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/30ab975e-d107-4563-aef2-359a9f2b4a79/web/1_1731932608227.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>415 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074279809343</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8688265509</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit Active Edge Smart Watch With Stylish Rugged Sport And Fitness Design</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsTraining templates: Customize your workout routine by creating training templates in the zepp app, and sync them to the watchInterval training: Streamline your training by creating interval training plans directly on the watch itselfConnect to workout devices : Connect the watch to a heart rate belt or cycling power meter, thanks to the immense bluetooth connectivity of the zepp OS 2. 0. Better than any gym buddy, the amazfit active edge comes with an intelligent strength training mode that canPortrait watch faces : Upload your own images; the watch will alternate them with every glanceSpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Mint GreenConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 32 inModel Number Active Edge Mint GreenModel Name Active Edge Mint Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f7bd0788-1c89-463b-90b0-41efbea4401d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/babdf694-5400-49b2-baef-6e166099d874/web/1_1731932515140.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>415 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086882655095</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4182373340</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL Waterproof True Wireless In-Ear Sport Headphones Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights30 Hours of Playback (6 hours in buds/24 hours in case). Powerhook Design for Ergonomic Fit and easy control. IPX7 Sweatproof and Waterproof. OverviewA serious workout deserves serious gear. JBL Endurance Peak II true wireless headphones deliver JBL Pure Bass sound to fuel your workout, while providing comfort and connectivity to keep you going strong. Get next-level motivation with 30 hours of combined battery life, starting from the moment you wear them, thanks to the Powerhook. Intuitive touch controls allow you to take hands-free calls and access your voice assistant, while dual connect ensures you’ll always be in control as the earbuds work independently. Their ergonomic fit and sweatproof/waterproof design let you exercise longer and harder, wherever your workout takes you. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothUsage Type Sports &amp;amp; FitnessAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number JBLENDURPEAKIIBLKModel Name JBLENDURPEAKIIBLK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/17f0af24-9ea7-4c31-8f16-618836176358</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a8cea431-377d-4e65-87b3-347e17bb9496/web/1_1731932550597.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>398 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041823733409</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2541381118</g:id>
      <g:title>beats Studio Buds True Wireless Noise Cancelling Earphones White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsActive Noise CancellingMore Music Less NoiseUp to 8 hours of listening timeSpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneModel Number MJ4Y3AE/AModel Name FL6GKPKW0RP3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/73d813f7-3a22-4a77-a86d-86aabd93110b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/618b3090-c7b4-4cd6-a243-1aecdfa9f84f/web/1_1731932666688.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>419 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025413811180</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2730652666</g:id>
      <g:title>Govee Envisual TV Backlight (55~65 inch)</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUpgraded Fish-eye Correction Camera Technology: Corrects fisheye distortion lenses, which expands the effective color-matching range for more accurate edges. Upgraded Govee Envisual Technology: The upgraded Govee TV backlight with a fisheye lens correction camera has more accurate color capturing. 4 Colors in 1 with RGBIC+W: These TV lights add an extra warm white chip to enhance movies and gaming. Full Compatibility for Any TV Content: The TV Backlight 3 Lite instantly captures the color of any TV screen without compatibility issues. Smart Activation: Manage your TV LED strip lights with Govee Home App or voice commands via Alexa and Google Assistant. SpecificationsColour Name MulticolourType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number 6974316997597Model Name 68850</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/127f6e22-fae8-47a2-940b-93938bb7d769</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9d26b569-b92f-464c-a608-c4def20c5195/web/1_1731932987517.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>429 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027306526669</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8101297940</g:id>
      <g:title>beats Studio Buds True Wireless Noise Cancelling Earphones Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsActive Noise CancellingMore Music Less NoiseUp to 8 hours of listening timeSpecificationsColour Name RedConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneModel Number MJ503AE/A / MJ503CH/AModel Name MJ503AE/A / MJ503CH/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/68850cec-c946-4309-82f2-04378b3aae4a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/db9067d5-f0bb-4250-bba4-38e4acbccefe/web/1_1731932801018.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>429 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081012979409</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7000764618</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PS5 DualSense Wireless Controller - Astro Bot Limited Edition</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe controller’s design features Astro’s signature blue accents on the handles and buttons, carved-in, sci-fi lines as well as the trademark playful pair of eyes on the touch pad. Feel physically responsive feedback to your in-game actions with dual actuators which replace traditional rumble motors. In your hands, these dynamic vibrations can simulate the feeling of everything from environments to the recoil of different weapons. Experience varying levels of force and tension as you interact with your in-game gear and environments. From pulling back an increasingly tight bowstring to hitting the brakes on a speeding car, feel physically connected to your on-screen actions. Chat with friends online using the built-in microphone –or by connecting a headset to the 3. 5mm jack. Easily switch voice capture on and off at a moment’s notice with the dedicated mute button. Take control with an evolved, two-tone design that combines an iconic, intuitive layout with enhanced sticks and a reimagined light bar. Charge and play, now via USB Type-C. OverviewDiscover a deeper, highly immersive gaming experience that brings the action to life in the palms of your hands. The DualSense™ wireless controller offers immersive haptic feedback, dynamic adaptive triggers and a built-in microphone, all integrated into an iconic comfortable design. SpecificationsColour Name White/BlueConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFIZCT1WZ3XASTROBOTModel Name CFIZCT1WZ3XASTROBOT</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ec98bbbe-5e33-446a-994a-226eae60a7bc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5216a97d-ac23-4817-b71f-69f5d16183cc/web/1_1731933489827.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>447 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070007646181</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7736799698</g:id>
      <g:title>PXN Game Steering Wheel For PlayStation/Xbox/Switch/PC With H-Patten Shifter and 3 Pedal -wired</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMORE RACING GAMES : PXN-V9 game steering wheel can provide PC platform with European truck simulation, truck life, Maxthon China, Shenli Corsa and other games; Xbox can be adapted to Horizon 4, Dust 2. 0, Forza Motorsport series ,Racing Project 2 and other games; PS platform includes Need for Speed 20, F1 2019, Super Touring Car, Driving Club, etc. ; Switch includes Asphalt, Sonic Racing, Mario Kart and other games. HIGH-QUALITY STRUCTURE : The PS4 racing wheels is made of non-slip ABS matte non-slip material, with real dual vibration motors, with 7 powerful suction cups and C-shaped fixing frame, which can maintain a more comfortable and long-lasting gaming experience. For better It is convenient for players to use PXN V9 racing wheels. We have prepared the "V9 Tool" APP. Players can search for "V9 Tool" in the Apple App Store to download and install. HIGH-END RACING SIMULATOR : PC racing wheel provides 270/900° rotation switching function, toggle the button under the steering wheel to switch. The handbrake shift lever of the PS4 game steering wheel is designed for professional racing games, 6-in-one manual gearshift lever allows players to experience the sense of presence brought by manual braking and shifting, and supports forward and R reverse gears; handbrake and high-low performance modes adopt button design to reduce false contacts. PC DUAL ANALOG STEERING WHEEL : PC dual-mode driver, used to play computer racing, freely switch between the two modes, with a three-in-one linear pedal (clutch, brake and accelerator), adjust the strength of the pedal Realize the control of the throttle and brake,support automatic endurance,throttle lock value; steering wheel can be rotated 270/900°, rubber texture coated wheel handle, equipped with sports car-style paddles,manual gear shifting,imitating the ergonomic design of racing wheels. OverviewPLAY MULTI-PLATFORM GAMES : PC game racing wheels steering wheel with USB connection port, compatible with Xbox One / Xbox Series X&amp;amp;S/PC / PS3/ PS4 / P5 Nintendo Switch platform, and compatible with Windows 7/8/10 operating system(Please download the application:PXN Play or V9 Tool to test the function and mapping buttons)SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WiredWhat's In The Box Gaming Steering Wheel For PS5, PS4, PS3, Xbox, Switch, PCType of Console Software PS4/PS5Model Number PXN V9Model Name Gaming Steering Wheel For PS5, PS4, PS3, Xbox, Switch, PC</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0296f2c5-7831-4b2e-8540-4c1ee7a53180</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/89898fb3-f8de-4953-b28b-0a4f674c0f8c/web/1_1731933174097.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>439 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077367996987</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2457383976</g:id>
      <g:title>PXN V9 Racing Wheel Steering Wheel Driving Wheel 270°/ 900°</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe game steering wheel can be used for PC, Xbox one, PS4, PS3, Xbox series s/x, Nintendo Switch; when connecting to PC, it can be connected directly with a USB data cable. Special attention (but when connecting PS4 and Xbox, you need to use the original handle to connect the racing steering wheel)One-click switch button, 270° and 900°, (900° is suitable for playing truck games, such as European truck simulation, American truck simulation) (270° is suitable for playing racing games, such as Need for Speed, Forza speed horizon)The V9 racing steering wheel has pressure-sensitive pedals to simulate a real racing car. Dual-Motor feedback driving force racing wheel to provide realistic gaming experience, Intelligent auto-adjust vibration levels according to different driving scene. 11inch/28cm in diameter, with an ergonomic designOverviewPXN V9 PC Steering Wheel V9 270/900°PS4 Steering Wheel Dual-Motor Feedback Driving with Pedals and Shifter game racing wheel for PS4, Xbox One, Xbox Series X/S. PS3, N-Switch, PC 1. 【Multi-platform compatibility】: PXN-V9 wired USB connection port PC game racing steering wheel, compatible xbox one/Xbox Series X/S, PS4, PS4 SLIM, PS4 Pro, PS3, N-SWITCH, and compatible with PC . windows 7 / 8/10 operating system(Please download the application:【PXN Play or V9 Tool】 to test the function and mapping buttons) ,The gear lever is only available in truck mode. (Not for Apple Desktop/Laptop/XBOX ONE PS5 XBOX 360) 2. 【PS4/XBOX connection method 】1. you need to use PS4/Xbox the original gamepad to guide,2. Before booting, make sure that the host and the original handle are off,3. Use the micro USB cable with data transmission function to connect the steering wheel and the original handle,4. Connect the steering wheel to the host. After the original handle is connected to the steering wheel, turn on the host. 5. After booting, press the HMOE button on the steering wheel. Can be manipulated to guide success. 3. 【Software Application】. In order to better experience the fun of the game, the player can easily use the PXN V9 racing steering wheel. Special Design Applications: We support the steering wheel angle, sensitivity, vibration intensity adjustment, buttons function test, and game button preset scenes. We have prepared a "V9 Assistant" app. Players can search for "V9 Assistant" in the Apple App Store and installed. 4. 【Ergonomic Design】: PXN-V9 game drive wheel built-in dual motor, through different degrees of vibration, simulates real driving scene, with real dual vibrating motor (weak feedback) . pxn-v9 racing wheel by non-slip ABS matte non-slip material made, with 7 powerful suction cups and C-shaped fixtures, can maintain more comfortable, longer use time is not fatigued, lasting gaming experience 5. 【High-end Racing Simulator】: PXN V9 racing steering wheel provides a rotation angle switch: The dial switch can switch from 270 degrees to 900 degrees steering. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessType of Console Software PC GamesModel Number V9Model Name Gaming Racing Steering Wheel</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1537904e-1992-431a-9c9e-61e9551b7e69</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9a2cfac9-1c6a-4ebf-acc5-2beff280d0be/web/1_1731933406714.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>439 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024573839768</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9412005721</g:id>
      <g:title>beats Studio Buds True Wireless Noise Cancelling Earphones Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsActive Noise CancellingMore Music Less NoiseUp to 8 hours of listening timeSpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneModel Number MJ4X3AE/A / MJ4X3CH/AModel Name PL6FXFNU0RP2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b879f5d5-32ff-4bf9-a8f5-e4f11422486f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/930b66a7-caf6-4a43-a93a-b70a214f9463/web/1_1731933247481.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>439 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094120057211</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3780787784</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony DVD Home Theater System DAV-TZ140 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights5. 1ch surround sound for a cinematic experienceMicro-satellite speakers and a subwoofer let you hear the full rangePlay movies, music and photos from a USBSupport for Dolby digital and Dolby prologicPlay cds as well as dvdsSpecificationsColour Name BlackProduct Length 42. 93 cmProduct Height 55. 9 cmProduct Width/Depth 22. 35 cmWattage 300 WModel Number DAV-TZ140</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/99fd2ffb-80ee-48cb-ba84-5a865fe93ac7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6c5021be-8330-4c5b-9585-10a4a39627a4/web/1_1731933965088.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>449 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037807877849</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4911889052</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit GTR 3 Pro Ultra HD AMOLED Display Smartwatch Leather Brown</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsWith the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro you can test your heart rate, blood-oxygen saturation, stress level and breathing rate in a single tap of the watch, for a result in as little as 45 seconds4. Recognizing the importance of the role blood-oxygen saturation5 (SpO2) levels play in human health, the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro's advanced biosensor is able to automatically monitor your SpO2 level 24 hours a day, thanks to the new Zepp algorithm. With unprecedented visual clarity that reaches 331 ppi, the large 1. 45-inch screen of the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro shows you exactly what you want, when you want it, and is visible even under bright sunlight. It can help you understand how well your body is absorbing oxygen, and the amount of oxygen delivered to your bodyThe remarkable sensor and app in Apple Watch Series 6 allow you to take on-demand readings of your blood oxygen as well as background readings, day and nightThe band's stunning AMOLED Display seems to float on air, sitting atop a highly-breathable strap, which wraps around the wrist with easeTurn a treasured picture into a memorable watch face, via the Health App, to keep a beloved pet, cherished memory, or iconic image, in your sights and close on handThe battery is more than equipped to handle business trips and vacations, running for up to two weeks in typical usage scenarios, and up to 10 days in heavy usage scenariosThe TruSport fitness system tracks high-level metrics like running ability index, VO2Max, recovery time, and training effect, with data-driven tips and engaging TriRing check-in tasks6, to get you raring to goThe most essential phone features, like incoming calls and messages, weather forecasts, and music controlsOverviewThe best smart devices integrate easily into your lifestyle and make everyday activities more convenient. The Amazfit GTR 3 Pro is a reliable, versatile and advanced lifestyle partner that is there for you whether you’re going to work, the gym or out with friends. The Amazfit GTR 3 Pro brings a smooth and simple user-experience. Quickly access the data you need and conveniently transition from one feature to another, with a smartwatch that does the basics better than ever. The Amazfit GTR 3 Pro can intelligently recognize10 your motions and begin recording related sports data, as soon as you begin any of these eight sports: Outdoor Running, Treadmill, Walking, Indoor Walking, Outdoor Cycling, Pool Swimming11, Rowing Machine, and Elliptical. The watch is equipped with a new self-developed motion algorithm, which assesses specialized data such as maximum oxygen uptake (VO2 Max), full recovery time, training load and training effect. Stay informed of performance aspects that can affect recovery, progress and exercise capacity, and track your performance data more professionally. Whether you’re a team player or prefer the focus of working out by yourself, the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro is the ultimate easy-to-use sports smartwatch. With over 150 built-in sports modes* to suit your choice of activity, the watch can track metrics like heart rate, calories burned, and more. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CMaterial LeatherBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 250 gColour Name BrownConnection Type GPSWhat's In The Box watch, charger, manualDial Material PlasticTrending Amazfit Gtr 3 ProProduct Length 9. 5 cmProduct Height 5. 4 cmProduct Width/Depth 10. 01 cmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 45 inFeatures Multi-Touch, Mechanical, Pocket Size, Programmable, Water ResistantModel Number A2040Model Name GTR 3 proItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3e315b96-fbbb-4162-bd44-657185e255a9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b82468c9-4b56-4e1a-8d5a-b31b04f98e45/web/1_1731934379623.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>464 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049118890523</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6454521211</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit GTR 3 Pro Ultra HD AMOLED Display Smartwatch Infinite Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsWith the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro you can test your heart rate, blood-oxygen saturation, stress level and breathing rate in a single tap of the watch, for a result in as little as 45 seconds4. Recognizing the importance of the role blood-oxygen saturation5 (SpO2) levels play in human health, the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro's advanced biosensor is able to automatically monitor your SpO2 level 24 hours a day, thanks to the new Zepp algorithm. With unprecedented visual clarity that reaches 331 ppi, the large 1. 45-inch screen of the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro shows you exactly what you want, when you want it, and is visible even under bright sunlight. The ultra HD AMOLED display boasts a 70. 6% screen-to-body ratio, which is among the highest for round smartwatches that are currently available. Keep a track of your well being and health right from your wrist with noise health suite featuring a variety of health featuresOverviewThe best smart devices integrate easily into your lifestyle and make everyday activities more convenient. The Amazfit GTR 3 Pro is a reliable, versatile and advanced lifestyle partner that is there for you whether you’re going to work, the gym or out with friends. The Amazfit GTR 3 Pro brings a smooth and simple user-experience. Quickly access the data you need and conveniently transition from one feature to another, with a smartwatch that does the basics better than ever. The Amazfit GTR 3 Pro can intelligently recognize10 your motions and begin recording related sports data, as soon as you begin any of these eight sports: Outdoor Running, Treadmill, Walking, Indoor Walking, Outdoor Cycling, Pool Swimming11, Rowing Machine, and Elliptical. The watch is equipped with a new self-developed motion algorithm, which assesses specialized data such as maximum oxygen uptake (VO2 Max), full recovery time, training load and training effect. Stay informed of performance aspects that can affect recovery, progress and exercise capacity, and track your performance data more professionally. Whether you’re a team player or prefer the focus of working out by yourself, the Amazfit GTR 3 Pro is the ultimate easy-to-use sports smartwatch. With over 150 built-in sports modes* to suit your choice of activity, the watch can track metrics like heart rate, calories burned, and more. SpecificationsCharging Type Lightning to USBMaterial RubberBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 57 gColour Name Infinite BlackConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularWhat's In The Box watch, charger, manualBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Dial Material PolycarbonateTrending Amazfit Gtr 3 ProProduct Length 46 mmProduct Height 11 mmProduct Width/Depth 46 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 45 inFeatures Indicator Lights, Rechargeable, Pocket Size, Water Resistant, Sweat ResistantModel Number GTR3 proModel Name GTR 3 proItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dae310b0-f441-4637-8856-cd0e3ca4fc6b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/94b6e0e4-9bde-4648-a9b5-80875954070d/web/1_1731934571958.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>468 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064545212113</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6998935516</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Desert Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWN3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/01b2f647-cf48-4cdd-9c7e-31524ffa59bc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/145ea608-9ed6-468e-8384-ff787adebc9a/web/1_1731646568572.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069989355167</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8388100611</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Natural Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWP3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d9890db4-7057-4ab3-a49c-254872d804e7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0e39bc53-87dd-48cd-ac4b-e713fbf50673/web/1_1731646335281.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5650 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083881006118</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4235957878</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWL3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d330faac-1893-410b-8078-def8ae8d30eb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/36747cb5-7fa4-42a5-88bd-fa9c88889fb0/web/1_1731646157818.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042359578786</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
