<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>4430974799</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple AirPods Max Bluetooth Over-Ear Active Noise Cancellation Headphones Green</g:title>
      <g:description>Designed for an exceptional fit knit mesh canopy and acoustically engineered memory foam ear cushionsHigh fidelity audio the custom built driver produces a wide frequency range that uncovers the rich details of every soundNoise control active noise cancellation for immersive sound transparency mode to hear the world around youActive noise cancellation blocks outside noise so you can immerse yourself in music﻿ transparency mode for hearing and interacting with the world around you﻿Spatial audio with dynamic head tracking provides theater like sound that surrounds you﻿ computational audio combines custom acoustic design with the Apple h1 chip and software for breakthrough listening experiencesDesigned with a knit mesh canopy and memory foam ear cushions for an exceptional fit﻿ magical experience with effortless setup on head detection and seamless switching between devices﻿Easily share audio between two sets of AirPods on your iPhone iPad iPod touch or Apple tv﻿ 20 hours of listening movie watching or talk time with active noise cancellation and spatial audio enabledOverviewUse Apple AirPods Max Over-Ear wireless headphone with mic which comes with Apple-designed dynamic driver. It comes with optical sensor (each ear cup), position sensor (each ear cup), case-detect sensor (each ear cup), accelerometer (each ear cup), gyroscope (left ear cup). It is equipped with Apple h1 headphone chip (each ear cup). From cushion to canopy, this headphone is designed for an uncompromising fit that creates the optimal acoustic seal for many different head shapes — fully immersing you in every sound. The canopy spanning the headband is made from a breathable knit mesh, distributing weight to reduce on-head pressure. The stainless steel frame wrapped with a soft-to-the-touch material for a remarkable combination of strength, flexibility and comfort. Telescoping arms smoothly extend and stay where you set them, for a consistent fit and seal. when you get Apple AirPods max over-ear wireless headphone with mic online, you also get awesome headphone along with its features. It comes with active noise cancellation. It comes with transparency mode. It comes with adaptive eq. It provides with a battery life of up to 20 hours. Storage in the smart case preserves battery charge in ultra-low-power state. It is equipped with bluetooth 5. 0 connectivity support. It offers with a perfect balance of exhilarating high-fidelity audio and the effortless magic of AirPods. The beautifully anodised aluminium cups feature a revolutionary mechanism that allows each cup to rotate independently and balance pressure. The digital crown lets you precisely control volume, skip between tracks, answer phone calls and activate siri. Spatial audio with dynamic head tracking gives you a theatre like experience for movies and shows, with sound that surrounds you. A quick 5-minute charge delivers 1. 5 hours of listeningSpecificationsCharging Type Lightning to USBBattery Size 664 mAhProduct Weight 384 gColour Name GreenConnection Type WirelessAverage Battery Life 16hrs - 24hrsUsage Type Sports &amp;amp; FitnessWhat's In The Box Wireless headphones, manualAudio Headphone Type Over-EarCharging Case Type WiredProduct Length 18. 71 cmProduct Height 16. 86 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 4 cmFeatures Bluetooth, Volume Control, Active Noise Cancellation, Foldable, Voice AssistantModel Number MGYN3, MGYN3AM/AModel Name MGYN3Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/24c1d28d-805d-4e5c-9ca9-e44721648d48</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/48486bdb-46bf-48d4-9e60-9e7f7b4f93e5/web/1_1732690192022.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1671 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044309747990</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8558670568</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS 44mm Midnight Aluminium Case With Midnight Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Midnight Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number MREA3QA/A, MREA3QH/A, MREA3LL/A, MREA3ZP/AModel Name MREA3QA/A, MREA3QH/A, MREA3LL/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1f15ca63-fe00-4ff9-8369-1fbb6a9f884d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e4b1912e-6577-4e5e-a4b9-dc8627252821/web/1_1732689977256.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>948.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085586705686</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6679934214</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Watch FE 40mm International Version Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Body Composition, Advanced running analysis, Personalized Heart Rate Zone, Health monitoring: Heart Package (HR Alert, IHRN &amp;amp; ECG), Sleep ApneaCamera remote view, Quick camera access, Find my phone, All-in-one digital wallet, parental control, family setupOverviewSamsung Galaxy Watch FESpecificationsMaterial AluminumBattery Size None NoneColour Name BlackBand Material SiliconeDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSWhat's In The Box StrapFace/Dial Shape RoundBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number SM-R861NZKAMEA-InternationalModel Name WatchFE 40mm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8abbcfa1-960c-4f69-af63-5933842c1dfe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f05fb125-9885-4564-830b-90dc1b48d64c/web/1_1732689870166.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>396 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066799342141</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5951517285</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max Physical Dual Sim 1TB Desert Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2a9b8a14-2dd3-4c29-99bb-18b54f1355e3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/10e98449-b9fb-483b-9e90-39616cf442fc/web/1_1732698617609.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>7291.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059515172856</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6326736554</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max Physical Dual Sim 512GB Natural Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/90f5f71b-7a76-4b6c-989a-96c8cf6c56a6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/32a7a668-07da-4b3c-b055-4e4abf849c25/web/1_1732697852185.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6050 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063267365541</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5124401291</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/68702ebf-8b19-4f62-b713-95aa7c58bb3f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cf3590f9-efe3-4685-90fb-0fbbcc7107b4/web/1_1732698380820.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>7699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051244012915</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4607031247</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 256GB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYN13AE/A , MYN13AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/891fb6d8-2397-4b1a-ad71-576650b60efc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ed0df6df-67a6-4a61-9a56-546a2793cb57/web/1_1732699438854.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4811 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0046070312476</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4679244775</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Watch 6 Classic 47 Mm Cellular Smartwatch Graphite/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing BP &amp;amp; ECG on Galaxy Watch : Keep a track of your well-being by monitoring and tracking your blood pressure &amp;amp; ECG easily and more conveniently, right on your wrist. Introducing Contactless Secure Payments : make payments from your wrist with a simple Tap &amp;amp; Pay feature enabled by Samsung WalletFreedom with LTE : Stay connected with your world even when you leave your phone behind. Enjoy seamless access to calls, messages, music streaming &amp;amp; much more on the go. OverviewAdvanced Sleep Coaching: Know your sleep with our new and improved sleep tracking technology. Plan your bedtime, detect snoring, understand and track your sleep on your wrist. Personalized HR: Create your own customized HR zones with just 10min of outdoor running. Maximize the output of your workouts with Zone alerts (Warm-up, Fat burn, Cardio etc. )SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CMaterial CombinationProduct Weight 59 gColour Name Graphite/BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Product Length 46. 5 mmProduct Height 10. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 46. 5 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 47 mmModel Number SM-R965FZKAXSGModel Name Watch6 Classic 47 MM, SM-R965FZKAEUAItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8920ba9b-aa44-4e82-b7d8-e21c3282c047</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6a1bc67d-3274-433f-9f56-7caac017c557/web/1_1732699073423.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>865 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0046792447753</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6023500371</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Watch 6 Classic 43 Mm GPS Smartwatch Graphite/Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing BP &amp;amp; ECG on Galaxy Watch : Keep a track of your well-being by monitoring and tracking your blood pressure &amp;amp; ECG easily and more conveniently, right on your wrist. Introducing Contactless Secure Payments : make payments from your wrist with a simple Tap &amp;amp; Pay feature enabled by Samsung WalletFreedom with LTE : Stay connected with your world even when you leave your phone behind. Enjoy seamless access to calls, messages, music streaming &amp;amp; much more on the go. OverviewAdvanced Sleep Coaching: Know your sleep with our new and improved sleep tracking technology. Plan your bedtime, detect snoring, understand and track your sleep on your wrist. Personalized HR: Create your own customized HR zones with just 10min of outdoor running. Maximize the output of your workouts with Zone alerts (Warm-up, Fat burn, Cardio etc. )SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CMaterial CombinationProduct Weight 52 gColour Name Graphite/BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Product Length 42. 5 mmProduct Height 10. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 42. 5 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 43 mmModel Number SM-R950NZKAMEAModel Name Watch6 Classic 43 Mm, SM-R950, SM-R950NZKAEUA, SM-R950NZKALTAItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f47f0a3b-a3d5-45c1-876d-754a8dc8288d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fcbf2381-3385-4f69-a546-75370afc727c/web/1_1732698086907.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>659 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060235003719</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5642590168</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Physical Dual Sim 256GB Natural Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 ProModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e1df510a-0347-4314-9f00-419e991b42ed</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/26cb4645-b45c-4363-9082-cf866ecc52fb/web/1_1732696912085.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056425901682</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1657616736</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MRXW3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU/8GB RAM/512GB</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name MidnightKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MRXW3JA/A MRXW3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a4a68b7e-04c3-469e-8373-ea9753deb297</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6b3a85bc-3320-46e9-9377-f15ded743143/web/1_1732697712558.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4391 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016576167368</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2974678097</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Smart Tag 2 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>REDESIGNED TO DO MORE: The redesigned Galaxy SmartTag2 is made so you can keep calm and keep track*; Its design makes it easy for you to tag and carry your belongingsEASY TO USE: It's IP67-rated water- and dust-resistant, activates your compatible IoT devices and stays powered for up to 500 days or even up to 40% more on Non-Power Saving ModeRELAX, YOU'VE GOT IT TAGGED: Simply register a new Galaxy SmartTag2 and get started right away with SmartThings Find; With its intuitive tracking experience, you now have a way to keep track of things you love right in the palm of your handSEARCH NEAR WHEN IT'S NOT FAR: Lose something Switch on Search Nearby and get guided instructions to your item's location via Compass View; If you still don't see it, just ring your Galaxy SmartTag2 to have it send out an audible signalSpecificationsMaterial PlasticColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothCountry of Origin South KoreaModel Number EI-T5600BBEGWWModel Name EI-T5600BBEGWWItem Quantity 1. 0Model Compatibility Samsung</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/70352399-76a9-44b0-89f2-6015895f184c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7e9a2b25-1035-4159-bf93-77e9c06a16c0/web/1_1732696270692.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>67 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029746780977</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6573863138</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Homepod 2nd Generation Smart Speaker - MQJ83 White</g:title>
      <g:description>4-inch high-excursion woofer Array of five horn-loaded tweeters, each tweeter with its own neodymium magnet Internal low-frequency calibration microphone for automatic bass correction Advanced computational audio with system sensing for real-time tunTap Play/Pause Double-tap Skip Triple-tap Skip back Touch and hold Siri Tap or hold + or – Volume up/downSound Recognition7 Temperature and humidity8 AccelerometerSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number MQJ83Model Name MQJ83</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eded7474-3e4b-40fc-9bdb-c34aed1a4fcf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7aa5b991-bc95-4290-ab6e-0c51b56db29d/web/1_1732689723257.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1291 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065738631384</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1924934899</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS + Cellular 40mm Midnight Aluminium Case With Midnight Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Midnight Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number MRG73QA/A , MRGA3QA/A, MRG73ZP/AModel Name MRG73QA/A , MRGA3QA/A, MRG73ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/67c72293-bb87-495d-89ef-37e12e78c5d6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9596891f-a4b4-4ddf-bb9d-5f03e1c6d35b/web/1_1732688949435.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>994.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019249348996</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5715644298</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Pink - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name PinkCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Pink 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c366ea0-2da5-4974-b50c-001720a00a73</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/757a7b6b-571a-41de-96bf-b313f1b2135b/web/1_1732688826347.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1289 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057156442987</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7930080092</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Smart Tag 2 White</g:title>
      <g:description>REDESIGNED TO DO MORE: The redesigned Galaxy SmartTag2 is made so you can keep calm and keep track*; Its design makes it easy for you to tag and carry your belongingsEASY TO USE: It's IP67-rated water- and dust-resistant, activates your compatible IoT devices and stays powered for up to 500 days or even up to 40% more on Non-Power Saving ModeRELAX, YOU'VE GOT IT TAGGED: Simply register a new Galaxy SmartTag2 and get started right away with SmartThings Find; With its intuitive tracking experience, you now have a way to keep track of things you love right in the palm of your handSEARCH NEAR WHEN IT'S NOT FAR: Lose something Switch on Search Nearby and get guided instructions to your item's location via Compass View; If you still don't see it, just ring your Galaxy SmartTag2 to have it send out an audible signalSpecificationsMaterial PlasticColour Name WhiteConnection Type BluetoothCountry of Origin South KoreaModel Number EI-T5600BWEGWWModel Name EI-T5600BWEGWWItem Quantity 1. 0Model Compatibility Samsung</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6e06d7a2-b111-41de-89b5-8e82631e32f6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2bc7a016-5944-443d-b5b7-68aaf32d4f49/web/1_1732687603814.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>67 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079300800924</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8125956417</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MR7J3 Laptop, 14.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display,8GB, 512GB SSD </g:title>
      <g:description>Go all day thanks to the power-efficient design of Apple silicon. The MacBook Pro laptop delivers the same exceptional performance whether it’s running on battery or plugged in. All your pro apps run lightning fast including Adobe Creative Cloud, Apple Xcode, Microsoft 365, SideFX Houdini, MathWorks MATLAB, Medivis SurgicalAR, and many of your favorite iPhone and iPad apps. ADVANCED CAMERA AND AUDIO — Look sharp and sound great with a 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a studio-quality three-mic array, and a six-speaker sound system with Spatial Audio. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MR7J3ZS/A / MR7J3X/A / MR7J3LL/A/MR7J3HN/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3152bb31-719f-4446-8082-e97d8e29fd41</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e76f5e61-9ae6-4282-be54-89177dba673d/web/1_1732686244209.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4481 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081259564178</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3833745295</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Airpods Max ( USB-C) Purple</g:title>
      <g:description>Active Noise Cancellation, with Adaptive Audio and Transparency modePersonalised Spatial Audio with dynamic head trackingLoud Sound ReductionVoice Isolation, Hey Siri and Siri InteractionsDust, sweat and water resistant AirPods and Charging CaseOverviewThe ultimate over‑ear personal listening experience — now in fresh new colours. AirPods Max deliver stunningly detailed, high‑fidelity audio. Personalised Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking for sound that surrounds you. Footnote ⁴ Pro‑level Active Noise Cancellation to remove unwanted sound. Footnote ³ Transparency mode to comfortably hear the world around you. Up to 20 hours of battery life on a single charge. Footnote ¹³ Effortless setup and on‑head detection for a magical listening experience. Now with USB‑C for easy charging. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CProduct Weight 386. 2 gColour Name PurpleDepartment Adult UnisexConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box AirPods Max (USB‑C), Smart Case, USB-C Charge Cable, DocumentationAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type On-EarCharging Case Type WiredProduct Length 168. 6 mmProduct Height 187. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 83. 4 mmModel Number MWW83ZEA/MWW83ZE/AModel Name MWW83ZE/AItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/52079f9a-7276-4ddf-844e-805acf902f63</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/982fa0bd-03f6-4cd2-9fe3-f09d1b535982/web/1_1732699302516.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2029 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038337452957</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3577339280</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 256GB WiFi Silver - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Silver 256GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3df1e8d1-4a15-48e0-bcf2-50e6495b3f55</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/da5e3ab7-a491-480a-9448-8497874f884d/web/1_1732700683296.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1899 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035773392809</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1285698420</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS 40mm Silver Aluminium Case With Storm Blue Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Storm Blue Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number MRE13QA/A , MRE23QA/A, MRE23QH/A, MRE13SE/A, MRE23LL/A, MRE13LL/AModel Name MRE13QA/A , MRE23QA/A, MRE13LL/A, MRE23LL/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/85fcff92-f53c-4c2f-9c7f-7e8d8ca4da93</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6307b4da-15fd-4b4c-a584-caf8b04ed000/web/1_1732699762078.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>798.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012856984205</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7209663942</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 1TB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 199 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 ProModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a23fcf43-bb24-4a26-bd43-0fc6571fcc77</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c3759537-94e2-4dd8-8282-baed8c4a17af/web/1_1732700374128.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0072096639426</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6842810074</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Natural Titanium Case With Blue Trail Loop - M/L</g:title>
      <g:description>Featuring a stunning, new black titanium case, Apple Watch Ultra 2 is the ultimate sports and adventure watch. It has all the connectivity, health and safety features for the every day. And it takes training further with the most accurate GPS in a sports watchUltra 2 is built for extremes. Now available in black titanium, the 49 mm case is designed for the toughest environments, and it’s certified to EN13319, the internationally recognised standard for diving accessoriesAction on the spot. The customisable Action button gives you precise control over starting a workout, marking a segment or moving on to the next intervalA battery made for the long run. Wherever you find yourself, the last thing you want to worry about is your battery. Ultra 2 is engineered to perform at peak conditions longer, so you can perform at yoursApple Watch Ultra 2 is the perfect partner whether you’re riding indoors, road cycling, mountain biking or commuting. From Bluetooth-enabled accessories to metrics to seeing them easily while you’re riding, you’re always ready to rollOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Blue Trail Loop - M/LConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size Medium/LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MX4L3QA/AModel Name MX4L3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4c5ec9a0-aab3-4fbf-85a4-f0f7d4be4882</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d8cc898b-0a75-485a-9200-eea902e1adc9/web/1_1732700819139.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2936.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068428100740</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7836311493</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Pro - 2024 (7th Generation) M4 13-Inch, 256GB, 5G,  International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M4, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad ProiPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Pro packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Pro and an expansive 13″ iPad Pro that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type Wifi+CellularDisplay Type OLEDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number M4Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless 5GBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad ProModel Name iPad ProPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2d456d3e-04bd-4f2c-aaed-a93894c57470</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8bd2ec4b-4d11-4aa1-b3d1-6242826fd76f/web/1_1732700243158.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078363114931</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1219380216</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWP3AE/A , MYWP3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/37c75369-8c94-4439-8ab6-9ec3af8a9534</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0473e1a1-38bf-4bde-b1d8-c83e5d075e0f/web/1_1732702582003.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5650 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012193802163</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2646760753</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro 128GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYMX3AE/A , MYMX3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f42c93cb-4804-43c5-9b06-7665492e8cd6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/06245b59-2489-4dfd-8d4d-7cb89dce3831/web/1_1732703079558.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4250 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026467607538</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2509971501</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2024) GPS 40mm Midnight Aluminium Case With Ink Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay connected on the go, go, goGet a closer look at your shut‑eyeTrack your heart health without missing a beatCarbon neutral - A big step towards a smaller footprintWater resistance - Swim-suitableOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Ink Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number MXEA3QA/AModel Name MXEA3QA/A, MXEA3ZP/A, MXEA3LL/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1258e1a1-312a-468f-9ba2-bdec41997bd3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a89afdd8-45ae-48ce-a778-388d88c5374e/web/1_1732701737186.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>760 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025099715017</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7303004803</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Plus 128GB Teal 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 16 is called the ""iPhone 16 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A18 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4006 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1290x2796Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name TealDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 160. 9 mmProduct Height 77. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 8 mmModel Number iPhone 16 PlusModel Name iPhone 16 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8d937f2a-d38d-48e4-b5cc-4f38b9514af1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d80cf14f-4265-4669-a777-cd799a6a5ebd/web/1_1732702887486.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073030048038</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9584169803</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS 40mm Midnight Aluminium Case With Midnight Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Midnight Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number MRE03QA/A, MRE03LL/A, MRE03QH/AModel Name MRE03QA/A, MRE03ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bca174a9-cf54-4393-8ca9-2300ff3eb913</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9f75337b-6543-49ce-b9b5-4fa2515cf0fe/web/1_1732705110853.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>798.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095841698035</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6255093068</g:id>
      <g:title>iPhone 16 Plus 256GB Teal 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 16 is called the ""iPhone 16 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A18 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4006 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1290x2796Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name TealDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MXVL3AE/A , MXVL3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7594e528-7376-437a-b7db-8352f4a080fe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7f3e10f8-6051-4af1-9fe5-ee9762280e9c/web/1_1732701837178.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3899 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062550930688</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6211048198</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Air 2024 (6th Generation) M2 13-Inch 128GB Starlight Wi-Fi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M2, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad AiriPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Air packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Air and an expansive 13″ iPad Air that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 8000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name StarlightCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type WifiDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 11 inches &amp;amp; aboveSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad AirModel Name iPad AirPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c426af8f-4171-4ee2-abb4-adeeb1c981e4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/06d65ea2-bc60-44dc-8ddd-ce132bf959f9/web/1_1732702150692.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>3098.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062110481988</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3915714309</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 256GB Black 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A15 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3561 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1179x2556Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MYDW3AE/A , MYDW3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16Primary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3f4f62ca-fd85-476d-93ef-280efaa255da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3363e86d-c7db-4752-96ad-f49ff3d54400/web/1_1732705798998.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039157143094</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3264216858</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 256GB, WiFi- International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space GreyCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability yesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - Space GreyModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 256 - Space GreyPrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/84555142-2246-4459-a548-ef9db92a1515</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cee3e93e-6e5e-4425-be13-bc8ab344d757/web/1_1732704731591.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2208.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032642168589</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4455451258</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Homepod 2nd Generation Smart Speaker MQJ73 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>4-inch high-excursion woofer Array of five horn-loaded tweeters, each tweeter with its own neodymium magnet Internal low-frequency calibration microphone for automatic bass correction Advanced computational audio with system sensing for real-time tunTap Play/Pause Double-tap Skip Triple-tap Skip back Touch and hold Siri Tap or hold + or – Volume up/downSound Recognition7 Temperature and humidity8 AccelerometerSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number MQJ73Model Name MQJ73</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b5e39d59-5322-4e15-896f-6181dc338962</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1667ec61-e02b-4cb8-be4a-a4a185597c23/web/1_1732705988653.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1277.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044554512589</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8213506157</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS 44mm Silver Aluminium Case With Storm Blue Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Storm Blue Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number MREE3LL/A, MREC3QA/A, MREC3LL/AModel Name MREE3ZP/A, MREE3LL/A, MREC3LL/A, MREC3QA/A, MREE3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/341777c3-752d-4fef-8c71-967661778b31</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ca657824-d9b4-4c7b-b980-538384b7f024/web/1_1732706082688.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>939.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082135061576</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2866423916</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 128GB Ultramarine 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSuper Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A15 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3561 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1179x2556Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name UltramarineDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MYDU3AE/A , MYDU3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16Primary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b4f8e7e-99be-444d-ad47-31a8aa9ea7ac</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/80eca94a-b1c8-4874-b0b2-ac2f111db4ba/web/1_1732710052081.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3344 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028664239161</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8993721709</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Physical Dual Sim 256GB White Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3577 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 3 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 71. 5 mmProduct Height 149. 6 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 ProModel Name iPhone 16 ProPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f9d3affa-7952-4337-9df7-58c822effbc5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eff8188e-2574-4f41-9eb5-4b46f0157d0a/web/1_1732711580525.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089937217095</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8989048588</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS 44mm Silver Aluminium Case With Winter Blue Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Winter Blue Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number MREF3QA/A, MREF3LL/A, MREF3QH/AModel Name MREF3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a5c8ff52-7353-4403-9928-8e3690f60ed4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cc15963e-12ff-4f48-a623-3a32fd7a4e55/web/1_1732711470168.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>938.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089890485883</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5846519056</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Watch 6 Classic 43 Mm GPS Smartwatch Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing BP &amp;amp; ECG on Galaxy Watch : Keep a track of your well-being by monitoring and tracking your blood pressure &amp;amp; ECG easily and more conveniently, right on your wrist. Introducing Contactless Secure Payments : make payments from your wrist with a simple Tap &amp;amp; Pay feature enabled by Samsung WalletFreedom with LTE : Stay connected with your world even when you leave your phone behind. Enjoy seamless access to calls, messages, music streaming &amp;amp; much more on the go. OverviewSamsung Galaxy Watch6 Classic 43 mm Smartwatch, SilverSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CMaterial CombinationProduct Weight 52 gColour Name SilverDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Product Length 42. 5 mmProduct Height 10. 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 42. 5 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 43 mmModel Number SM-R950NZSAMEAModel Name Watch6 Classic 43 Mm, SM-R950NZSAEUE, SM-R950NZSAEUA, SM-R950NZSALTA / SM-R950NZSATGYItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2d57865a-1e17-42b8-9e2b-d769ed4bdc2e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/79896308-4dca-4f5a-81c0-5f78099a22f7/web/1_1732711370656.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>659 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058465190569</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9576153695</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS + Cellular 41mm Midnight Aluminium Case With Midnight Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneEmergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash DetectionTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimatesUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewThe Workout app gives you a range of ways to train plus advanced metrics for more insights about your workout performance. An aluminium Apple Watch Series 9 paired with the latest Sport Loop is carbon neutral. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Get approximate distance and directions to your iPhone with Precision Finding on supported iPhone models. Apple Watch Series 9 requires iPhone Xs or later with iOS 17 or later. With watch straps in a range of styles, materials and colours, as well as stylish and functional watch faces with complications tailored to your interests, you can change your watch to fit your mood or the moment. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Midnight Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 41 mmModel Number MRHR3QA/A , MRHT3QA/A , MRJH3ZA/A , MRJJ3ZA/AModel Name MRHR3QA/A , MRHT3QA/A, MRHR3ZP/A, MRHR3J/A, MRHT3LL/A, MRHR3LL/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b6fc76ed-a4a6-4aba-a870-beffde1254ab</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/47154bf9-598a-4216-826a-219c8e4a557e/web/1_1732711263787.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1291 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095761536950</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6203888784</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Plus 256GB Black 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 16 is called the ""iPhone 16 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A18 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4006 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1290x2796Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MXVG3AE/A , MXVG3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/67059726-0945-43bb-a4f1-3559f3f61453</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9114d1b4-897b-4888-9b5e-37dd80655a72/web/1_1732711060754.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3899 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062038887848</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8163251857</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Gen) 10.9 inch Blue 256GB WiFi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Expandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number MPQ93ZP/A , MPQ93LL/AModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/106a9fc8-b2f5-442c-883b-6e97a37afcda</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0a13afe3-ff42-48c4-bcba-89b8efc52373/web/1_1732710644694.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1875 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081632518576</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9350608652</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Air 2024 (6th Generation) M2 11-Inch 256GB Space Grey Wi-Fi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>The new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M2, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad AiriPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Air packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Air and an expansive 13″ iPad Air that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 7606 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name Space greyCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type eSIMConnection Type WifiDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone flashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof and Dust ProofModel Number iPad AirModel Name iPad AirPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1ce4beba-4595-4a19-9811-b303dfa11ad6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e7913e20-b48e-4dae-bd21-7e68cc68ccf1/web/1_1732710941600.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>2591 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093506086524</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7366150050</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 9 GPS + Cellular 45mm Silver Stainless Steel Case With Storm Blue Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app. ECG app. High and low heart rate notifications. Irregular rhythm notification. Emergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash DetectionUp to 18 hours, Up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode, Fast chargingTemperature sensing, Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimatesSpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelColour Name Storm Blue Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 45 mmModel Number MRMN3QA/A , MRMP3QA/AModel Name MRMN3QA/A , MRMP3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8851d66b-1518-4cf8-b2ac-4b742c8f13f8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cdb07b2e-6184-4949-ae11-466eb700d272/web/1_1732710739913.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1709 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073661500509</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6347425240</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Tab A9 Graphite 4GB RAM 64GB Wifi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylish with a touch of cool, the galaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ features a sleek design and a smooth metal body. Enjoy samsung’s signature tablet design in graphite, silver and navy with each hue highlighting effortless charmGalaxy tab A9 and tab A9+ come with up to 8GB of RAM memory, ensuring less lag while you multi-task. Plus, the built-in 128GB storage saves all your hi-res videos, photos and files. You can expand the storage with a microSD card — up to 1TBConquer multiple tasks at once. With galaxy tab A9+, you can sketch out architectural plans and choose captivating visuals and video chat — up to three apps all on one screen without ever closing a windowTake a deep dive into a rich soundscape with speakers that provide an enveloping audio experience. Whether you're enjoying a movie or music, galaxy tab A9+ lets you fully engage in 3D sound with stunning clarity and depthKeep your information safe and sound. Store important data in the secure folder and monitor the overall security status of your device on the privacy dashboard. Make the most of your samsung galaxy experience, worry-free of security issuesSpecificationsRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 7 inPrimary Camera Resolution 8 MPColour Name GraphiteCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System AndroidTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesModel Year 2023Voice Calling Capability NoNetwork Frequency Band WiFiCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraWireless WirelessModel Number SM-X110NZAAMEA / SM-X110/ SM-X115Model Name Tab A9</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/97495670-5922-4981-b12b-695d09d473ad</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d53a6520-3151-4925-92be-7814846550c9/web/1_1732709753366.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063474252405</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3256348457</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 GPS + Cellular, 49mm Titanium Case With Large (Band fits 165–210mm wrists.) </g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, S9 SiP, Double tap gesture, Precision Finding for iPhoneBlood Oxygen app. ECG app. High and low heart rate notifications. Irregular rhythm notification. Emergency SOS International emergency calling Fall Detection and Crash Detection SirenUp to 36 hours. Up to 72 hours in Low Power Mode. Fast chargingPrecision dual‑frequency GPS, Cellular connectivity, Family Setup, Pair multiple watches with one iPhoneBlood Oxygen - No Longer Available. OverviewApple’s brightest Always-On Retina display is easy to see, even in harsh sunlight. More room for adding complications to customize your watch face and enough space to view six metrics at once. Made for recreational water sports, scuba, and free diving for descents to 40 meters. The Depth app shows the time, current depth, water temperature, duration under water, and maximum depth you’ve reached. The Oceanic+ app puts a dive computer on your wrist. Ocean Band is light and flexible, with a titanium buckle and adjustable loop for a secure fit even during high-speed water sports. The Compass app delivers helpful views and details like elevation, incline, longitude, and latitude. See the last place where you had cellular reception. Mark your location with Compass Waypoints. Backtrack uses GPS to map where you’ve been so you can retrace your steps. Alpine Loop is an extremely rugged and secure band to meet the needs of all outdoor adventurers. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Blue Alpine LoopConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size Medium/LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MREQ3LL/A, MREQ3ZP/A,MREQ3LW/A, MREQ3B/A, / MREQ3AE/AModel Name MREQ3LL/A, MREQ3ZP/A,MREQ3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8fc5091d-e9c4-45bf-9cc6-905b71893587</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e65b8540-e0fb-42d7-bc0e-3c53e3eacf58/web/1_1732709851369.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2902.15 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032563484577</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5163106691</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS 44mm Starlight Aluminium Case With Starlight Sport Loop</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Starlight Sport LoopConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number MRE63QA/A, MRE63LL/A, MRE63QH/AModel Name MRE63QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1171c7f1-d275-449c-ba77-f92355ef2323</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5c196b6a-4fcc-4f96-8c6e-e8f84a5f1ccb/web/1_1732709442182.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>843.15 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051631066910</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5783107152</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy-A16 Dual SIM Blue Black 4GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>90 Hz refresh rate 6. 50-inch touchscreen display offering a resolution of 1080x2340 pixels (FHD+)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Colour Name Blue BlackDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTENumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Accelerometer, gyroscopeModel Number SM-A166EZKDMEAModel Name Galaxy-A16 5GPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/20044f66-c00f-4dd2-b2c7-18ee9a963432</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c3116d8e-661b-464a-acb8-68e8840347b5/web/1_1732710455921.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>596.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057831071525</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4662720977</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max Physical Dual Sim 256GB White Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0c8192e2-e287-4268-934b-c0c95f49bbd9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f144dd3e-2dfc-4f18-87e2-ac0c462495f8/web/1_1732625120141.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0046627209778</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1768546920</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2021 (6th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 64GB, WiFi, Purple  - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>All-screen design with a stunning 21. 08-centimetre (8. 3-inch) Liquid Retina display with wide colour, True Tone and 500 nits of brightnessTouch ID integrated into the top button for fast, easy and secure authenticationEnjoy incredible performance and all-day battery life with the A15 Bionic chipUse the 12MP Ultra Wide front camera with Centre Stage for more natural video callsWi-Fi 6. Experience high internet speeds with the fastest Wi-Fi availableAnd with up to 80 percent faster graphics ipad mini lets you immerse yourself in whatever you do use realistic brushes to create a watercolour experience unreal ar and play graphics intensive gamesIpad mini has all day battery life so it’s always ready for any task or project keep working creating and playing without missing a beatOverviewThe iPad is a brand of iOS and iPadOS-based tablet computers that are developed by Apple Inc. The iPad was conceived before the related iPhone but the iPhone was developed and released first. Speculation about the development, operating system, and release of the original iPad began in 2002 prior to its introduction on January 20, 2010. The iPad range consists of the original iPad lineup and the flagship products iPad Mini, iPad Air, and iPad Pro. The iPhone's iOS operating system (OS) was initially used for the iPad but in September 2019, its OS was switched to a fork of iOS called iPadOS that has better support for the device's hardware and its user interface is customized for the tablets' larger screens. The iPad's App Store is subject to application and content approval. Many older devices are susceptible to jailbreaking, which circumvents these restrictions. The original iPad was well-received for its software and was recognized as one of the most-influential inventions of 2010. As of the third quarter of 2021, iPad had a market share of 34. 6%; beside personal use, the iPad is used in the business, education, healthcare, and technology sectors. There are two variants of iPad; one has only Wi-Fi and one has support for cellular networks. Accessories include the Apple Pencil, Smart Case, Smart Keyboard, Smart Keyboard Folio, Magic Keyboard, and several adapters. The sixth generation of iPad Mini was announced and released on September 24, 2021. It uses an Apple A15 Bionic chip, with a 40% faster 6-core CPU and 80% faster 5-core GPU. Its 16-core Neural Engine and AI accelerators within the CPU delivers a 2x boost of AI performance. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPProcessor Speed 2. 93 GHzRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5124 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBProduct Weight 293 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name PurpleCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System Version iOS 15Operating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2021Voice Calling Capability noOperating System Number 15Processor Number A15 BionicFast Charging NoWhat's In The Box Tablet, manualNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 4K video recording at 30 fpsAudio Jack No Audio JackBattery Type Lithium IonWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantFinish AluminumProduct Length 134. 8 mmProduct Height 195. 4 mmProduct Width/Depth 6. 3 mmSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, BarometerModel Number Apple iPad Mini 6th GenModel Name iPad Mini 2021 (6th Generation)Pixels Per Inch 327Primary Camera (MP) 12 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d13c9581-4fd8-4409-8262-80932f03ac7f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ee439f6b-e811-4a05-bebd-5e2419a22383/web/1_1732625425121.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1591 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017685469206</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7108506476</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Watch 6 40 Mm GPS Smartwatch Graphite</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing BP &amp;amp; ECG on Galaxy Watch : Keep a track of your well-being by monitoring and tracking your blood pressure &amp;amp; ECG easily and more conveniently, right on your wrist. Introducing Contactless Secure Payments : make payments from your wrist with a simple Tap &amp;amp; Pay feature enabled by Samsung WalletPremium Watch : Designed with finest materials - Sapphire Crystal Glass &amp;amp; Armor Aluminum Dial. IP68 / 5ATM Water &amp;amp; Dust ResistanceOverviewAdvanced Sleep Coaching: Know your sleep with our new and improved sleep tracking technology. Plan your bedtime, detect snoring, understand and track your sleep on your wrist. Personalized HR: Create your own customized HR zones with just 10min of outdoor running. Maximize the output of your workouts with Zone alerts (Warm-up, Fat burn, Cardio etc. )SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CMaterial CombinationProduct Weight 28. 7 gColour Name GraphiteDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Product Length 40. 4 mmProduct Height 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 38. 8 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number SM-R930NZKAMEAModel Name Watch6 40 Mm, SM-R930NZKAEUA, SM-R930NZKDWEUItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4cb455c9-157b-42f0-85f3-c46dbbc4d15f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7837e920-03d0-41d0-b7c9-62dad8c28d10/web/1_1732681649004.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>497 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071085064768</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1442741736</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2023) GPS + Cellular 44mm Midnight Aluminium Case With Midnight Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Carbon neutral combinations available, Retina display Up to 1000 nits, S8 SiPHigh and low heart rate notifications, Irregular rhythm notificationEmergency SOS, International emergency calling, Fall Detection and Crash DetectionAvailable cellular connectivity, Family Setup pair multiple watches with one iPhoneOverviewAll the essentials to help you monitor your fitness, keep connected, track your health and stay safe. Now up to 20% faster, with features like Crash Detection and enhanced workout metrics, it’s a better value than ever. It works seamlessly with your Apple devices and services. Unlock your Mac automatically. Find your devices with a tap. Apple Watch requires an iPhone 8 or later with the latest iOS version. Water resistant to 50 metres. Three finishes. And a redesigned, colour-matched back case made with a new production process that reduces its carbon emissions by over 80%. SpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Midnight Sport BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 44 mmModel Number MRH53QA/A , MRH83QA/A, MRH73LL/AModel Name MRH53QA/A , MRH83QA/A, MRH83ZP/A, MRH53ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2ad44dd9-d094-4f2b-afa3-c6ab94fc7eca</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0949c109-766c-4dbc-9bba-ee78dce20554/web/1_1732682012096.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1093.45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014427417365</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8953634018</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 15 Pro 128GB White Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 1” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for a 3x optical zoom and 15x digital zoom. Up to 23 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MTU83AH/A,MTUW3AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e448a1c6-b674-41ec-9b03-3bb281b322c5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c94c250b-0d41-4429-9b6d-e233b9f7c4e9/web/1_1732682294161.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4171 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089536340187</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2972836907</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 128GB, WiFi - Blue  - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 128 - BlueModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 128 - BluePrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e7491dd8-7c8b-4a13-bd6f-bdcd1d51bd13</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f652266c-27c6-4725-bfb6-0efc13fad5bd/web/1_1732682723915.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029728369077</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6978193351</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Plus 128GB Black 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 16 is called the ""iPhone 16 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A18 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4006 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1290x2796Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 160. 9 mmProduct Height 77. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 8 mmModel Number iPhone 16 PlusModel Name iPhone 16 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f7aeebd8-67aa-4586-83d9-96429106e730</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1ff3779e-f745-4d06-9569-37e0f36e40e3/web/1_1732684015606.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069781933518</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9468059466</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Silver - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name SilverCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number MPQ03AB/A, MPQ03ZP/AModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4b2680c6-a19c-45b2-88aa-4e547851fe01</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2dfb3a04-3bf8-4513-9315-0609d129043b/web/1_1732684449374.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1329 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094680594669</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8173396167</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Homepod Mini White</g:title>
      <g:description>Compatible With : Ios, The Homepod Mini Hides Siri , Apple 'S Digital Assistant . Get Weather Updates, Connect With Other Apple Devices, Set Reminders, And Make Your Shopping ListIn Addition, As A Member Of A Smart Home , Siri Automates Processes And Handles Devices, As Long As You Ask It, With Homepod Mini , You Can Control Compatible Apple Homekit Devices In Your Home And Automate Their OperationAfter You Add Devices Through The Home App , Your Voice Is Enough For Them To Work. Just Ask Siri To Turn On The Lights Or Heat The Room And She Will Take ActionA HomePod mini in each room can play music independently or all play the same song for multi-room audioWhen in the same room, they can be combined for stereo sound and one detects the location of the other, to automatically adjust the balance between themThe HomePod mini will work effortlessly with other Apple devices such as your MacBook and iPhone. Heading out, You can continue listening to your podcast via your iPhone. All you have to do is bring your phone close to the HomePod mini to continue listening. Oh, and you can even perform various chores at home with the help of Siri. Easily communicate with your family members using your voice. You can use the Intercom feature if you have multiple HomePods in your house the HomePod mini will keep your personal information safe so it is an assistant who you can trust and make a part of your daily routineWrapped in a perfectly seamless mesh fabric, the HomePod mini is an attractive addition to your home. Oh, and its backlit touch surface on the top will ensure a quick and easy control. If you have multiple HomePod mini speakers in the house, you can even have a connected sound system for your homeOverviewAs An Apple Digital Assistant , Siri Has The Ability To Recognize The Voice Of Up To 6 Different People At Home And Create 6 Different Profiles Where They Will Be Tailored To The Needs And Desires Of Each Person. So Siri Learns And Makes Better Suggestions For You, Built To Deliver Sound From Anywhere, The Homepod Mini Adjusts Its Performance Based On Its Location In The Room. Inside A Small Speaker (Less Than 8. 3 Cm High) Fit Four Microphones With Noise-Canceling Technology And With The Help Of The Apple S5 Processor Which Optimizes The Movements Of The Redesigned Driver To Direct The Sound Evenly In The Area With Rich Bass . Plus, music and calls continue easily on the HomePod mini, simply by bringing your iPhone or iPad close to it and the sound is transferred to the speaker, With more than one HomePod mini in the house, you can easily communicate with the rest of your family using Intercom (intercom). Ask Siri to send your voice message to all the other HomePod mini in the house or to a specific room and get the answer. At the same time, Intercom works with other Apple devices from where it allows you to communicate with the house remotely, It is designed to keep your personal information secure. You can talk freely as the HomePod mini turns on with its switch or just by listening to the phrase "Hey, Siri". Finally, although the HomePod mini communicates with the iPhone to read your messages and notes, none of this information is sent to Apple. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box Portable Bluetooth SpeakersProduct Height 9. 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 4 cmModel Number MY5H2LL/A, MY5H2ZP/AModel Name HomePod miniItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7bcdf451-a48b-4375-8831-3e37134c8a3b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e87f7a18-0812-4e2d-b7d7-0412bb9448f5/web/1_1732684563340.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>387.85 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081733961677</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2005836822</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Blue - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Expandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number MPQ13AB/AModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)Primary Camera (MP) 12MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fb07b282-f0fa-474c-9ccd-a82d743733b9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/936e361a-178b-4ace-b1cd-8b836e29b7c1/web/1_1732683034456.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1295 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020058368228</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1731557504</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 256GB WiFi Blue - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Supports stylus pen (1st gen)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number MPQ93AB/AModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b0c671c6-7bcf-4a60-8670-81c8b615783b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/164d06e7-6a4e-4036-8f9a-35c5f0104e47/web/1_1732684727852.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1911 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017315575048</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5240533649</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max 512GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number MYWL3AE/A , MYWL3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3def0a70-004b-4b87-a3fa-6acdf2d10dc0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/80ec04df-42aa-4911-bcae-330328ac0be6/web/1_1732685346474.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5931 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052405336499</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5732712923</g:id>
      <g:title>APPLE iPhone 16 Pro Max Physical Dual Sim 512GB Black Titanium 5G Without FaceTime</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion Physical Dual SIM VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/da7cd57c-10de-40c5-9ecc-344dddbaa145</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/848d8f40-95c0-486f-ab86-5104194c0903/web/1_1732685625433.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6291.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057327129235</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9794297213</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Mini 2024 (7th Generation) 8.3-Inch, 128GB, WiFi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>iPadOS comes with powerful features and built-in apps designed to take advantage of the unique capabilities of iPad. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5078 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 8. 3 inDisplay Resolution 1440x2560Primary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name StarlightCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System iOSNetwork Type 5GTablet Screen Size 8. 1 - 9 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability YesFast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSGlass Technology Gorilla GlassCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDWireless BluetoothBattery Type Lithium PolymerSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Scanner, gyroscopeModel Number IPad mini 7th Gen 128 - StarlightModel Name IPad mini 7th Gen 128 - StarlightPrimary Camera (MP) 12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/18967e41-02d1-417c-8964-7fb695ee8eeb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/979de7ce-f481-427d-9f39-6cd7b10d69e3/web/1_1732683741258.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1751 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097942972137</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2652362525</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 128GB Black 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A15 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3561 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1179x2556Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MYDQ3AE/A , MYDQ3AH/AModel Name iPhone 16Primary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b71b21f2-addf-43f1-aeac-8199c22a9413</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7268cd18-5984-4d90-9942-b64f9901aaec/web/1_1732686341600.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3584 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026523625254</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4380643986</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Plus 256GB White 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 16 is called the ""iPhone 16 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A18 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4006 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1290x2796Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name WhiteDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 160. 9 mmProduct Height 77. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 8 mmModel Number iPhone 16 PlusModel Name iPhone 16 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e983ba1a-143c-487b-b349-541bab97c4d6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bf53f3e1-0e4d-4c0f-9000-a8693299736c/web/1_1732686703114.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4021 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043806439865</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7424839014</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Plus 256GB Teal 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Super Retina XDR displayAluminum with color-infused glass back Action buttonA18 chip with 5-core GPUAdvanced dual-camera system 48MP Fusion | 12MP Ultra Wide Super-high-resolution photos (24MP and 48MP) Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control Macro photography Spatial photos and videos Latest-generation Photographic StylesCamera Control Easier way to capture Faster access to photo and video toolsOverviewThe iPhone 16 models come in 6. 1 and 6. 7-inch sizes. The new 6. 7-inch iPhone 16 is called the ""iPhone 16 Plus"". Apple's iPhone 16 models features flat edges, an aerospace-grade aluminum enclosure, and a glass back that enables wireless charging Apple is using the same A18 chip that was in the iPhone 13 Pro models for the iPhone 16 models, but there is an updated internal design that allows for better thermal performance. The A18 chip offers a Hexa-core CPU, a 5-core GPU, and 16-core Neural Engine. The iPhone 16 models include a dual-core accelerometer that can measure up to 256Gs, and the accelerometer and a high dynamic range gyroscope power a Crash Detection feature that can contact emergency services if you're in a serious accident and can't reach your iPhone. Apple also uses other sensors to power this feature, so the barometer detects changes in cabin pressure, the GPS watches for speed changes, and the microphone can listen for car crash noises. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4006 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMDisplay Resolution 1290x2796Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name TealDisplay Type Retina DisplayOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile + Charging CableProcessor Name AppleNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash Dual Tone flashAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Water ResistantModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 160. 9 mmProduct Height 77. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 8 mmModel Number iPhone 16 PlusModel Name iPhone 16 PlusPrimary Camera (MP) 48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/165f9fa9-19df-4fc6-8d51-d60d117a945a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cac6dc80-e2e2-441d-af7b-f6fb16742a9b/web/1_1732688348209.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4099 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074248390148</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4092689436</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple AirPods Max Bluetooth Over-Ear Active Noise Cancellation Headphones Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>Designed for an exceptional fit knit mesh canopy and acoustically engineered memory foam ear cushionsHigh fidelity audio the custom built driver produces a wide frequency range that uncovers the rich details of every soundNoise control active noise cancellation for immersive sound transparency mode to hear the world around youActive noise cancellation blocks outside noise so you can immerse yourself in music﻿ transparency mode for hearing and interacting with the world around you﻿Spatial audio with dynamic head tracking provides theater like sound that surrounds you﻿ computational audio combines custom acoustic design with the Apple h1 chip and software for breakthrough listening experiencesOverviewUse Apple AirPods Max Over-Ear wireless headphone with mic which comes with Apple-designed dynamic driver. It comes with optical sensor (each ear cup), position sensor (each ear cup), case-detect sensor (each ear cup), accelerometer (each ear cup), gyroscope (left ear cup). It is equipped with Apple h1 headphone chip (each ear cup). From cushion to canopy, this headphone is designed for an uncompromising fit that creates the optimal acoustic seal for many different head shapes — fully immersing you in every sound. The canopy spanning the headband is made from a breathable knit mesh, distributing weight to reduce on-head pressure. The stainless steel frame wrapped with a soft-to-the-touch material for a remarkable combination of strength, flexibility and comfort. Telescoping arms smoothly extend and stay where you set them, for a consistent fit and seal. when you get Apple AirPods max over-ear wireless headphone with mic online, you also get awesome headphone along with its features. It comes with active noise cancellation. It comes with transparency mode. It comes with adaptive eq. It provides with a battery life of up to 20 hours. Storage in the smart case preserves battery charge in ultra-low-power state. It is equipped with bluetooth 5. 0 connectivity support. It offers with a perfect balance of exhilarating high-fidelity audio and the effortless magic of AirPods. The beautifully anodised aluminium cups feature a revolutionary mechanism that allows each cup to rotate independently and balance pressure. The digital crown lets you precisely control volume, skip between tracks, answer phone calls and activate siri. Spatial audio with dynamic head tracking gives you a theatre like experience for movies and shows, with sound that surrounds you. A quick 5-minute charge delivers 1. 5 hours of listeningSpecificationsCharging Type Lightning to USBBattery Size 664 mAhProduct Weight 384 gColour Name PinkConnection Type BluetoothAverage Battery Life 16hrs - 24hrsWhat's In The Box Wireless headphones, manualAudio Headphone Type Over-EarCharging Case Type WiredProduct Length 18. 71 cmProduct Height 16. 86 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 4 cmFeatures Bluetooth, Volume Control, Active Noise Cancellation, Foldable, Voice AssistantModel Number MGYM3, MGYM3RU/AModel Name MGYM3Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/79ff6a69-4107-4681-8e29-9a04d8b88d8e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c1963667-c8fc-4ed2-b64b-9f3fd5886c86/web/1_1732688590109.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1629 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040926894369</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5784573094</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch SE (2024) GPS 40mm Silver Aluminium Case With Denim Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Apple New launch productSpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Denim Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 40 mmModel Number MXEC3QA/A, MXED3QA/A, MXEC3LL/A, MXED3LL/A, MXED3LL/AModel Name MXEC3QA/A, MXED3QA/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/48b6ccf5-8c0c-4793-8810-440686d23f00</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3e4c77a4-396a-4e38-81d4-9c49cf5e07fd/web/1_1732689301320.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>790.45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057845730944</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
