<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>7050133447</g:id>
      <g:title>cmf by NOTHING Watch Pro Smartwatch With Bluetooth Calling, AMOLED Display, IP68 Water Resistant Dark Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>Get reminder to drink water at set time intervalsGet reminder to stand and stretch after sitting for a certain period of timeGuidance to inhale and exhale to relax and relieve stressTrack and record sleep time and wake-uptime; monitor sleep stages awake, light sleep, deep sleep, REM and durationsTrack and record the daily average,maximum, and minimumstresslevels, and the ratio of relaxed, normal, medium, and high stresslevelsOverviewFrom running to high-intensity interval training, covering most of the daily sports. Track exercise duration (hours, minutes, seconds), calories, real-time heart rate, pace,steps, distance and more. Stay motivated by setting your exercise goals and achieve it. Resistant to water splash and sweatSpecificationsMaterial MetalBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 31. 1 gColour Name Dark GreyDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDConnection Type GPSFace/Dial Shape SquareBand Size LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 10 mmModel Number D395Model Name D395</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3d9e89d8-3da2-4b55-86a8-177ca3b8673c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c1cfac07-4260-4062-8daf-e899e35f5d1d/web/1_1727350981023.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>201 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070501334478</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7745440190</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple 2023 Newest MacBook Pro MTL73 Laptop M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU: 14.2-inch Liquid Retina XDR Display, 8GB Unified Memory, 512GB SSD Storage And Works with iPhone/iPad(International version) English Space Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>The Apple MacBook Pro is a high-performance laptop designed for professionals and power users. With its sleek and durable aluminum build, it exudes elegance and durability. The MacBook Pro boasts a stunning Retina display with vibrant colors and sharp details, making it ideal for creative work and multimedia consumption. Powered by Apple's powerful M-series chips, the MacBook Pro delivers exceptional performance for demanding tasks, from video editing and photo manipulation to software development. The efficient architecture of these chips ensures long battery life, allowing you to work or play for extended periods without needing to recharge. The MacBook Pro is equipped with a comfortable keyboard and spacious trackpad for precise navigation. It also features a wide range of ports, including Thunderbolt 4 for fast data transfer and connection to external displays. With its combination of power, portability, and premium features, the MacBook Pro is a top choice for those seeking a high-performance laptop. SpecificationsProcessor Speed 4. 4 GHzRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 14 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishDisplay Type Liquid Retina XDRAverage Battery Life Above 20 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type Multimedia &amp;amp; DesigningModel Series Apple MacBook ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneModel Number MTL73LL/A / MTL73ZS/A/MTL73X/A / MTL73ZP/A/MTL73HN/A MTL73B/AModel Name Macbook ProHDMI Output yesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot yesNumber of HDMI Ports 1. 0Processor Version M3 chip with 8‑core CPU, 10‑core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/18b292a8-250c-4378-9aa0-e78de4275fdd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8e4b681f-f089-4b58-8f9f-7fd8ae2a93e8/web/1_1727351830539.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077454401905</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3407355921</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple MacBook Air MLXY3 13-Inch Display : Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU, 256GB/ English Keyboard(International version) Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>13. 6-inch Liquid Retina display with True ToneCome through loud and clear on calls wherever you are, thanks to the three-mic array with advanced beamforming algorithms to capture clean audioImmerse yourself in movies and music with improved stereo separation and vocal clarity from two tweeters and two ultra-thin woofers. Spatial Audio with support for Dolby Atmos places sound all around youComfortable and quiet, Magic Keyboard now has a full-height function key row for quick access to favourite controls and shortcuts. Touch ID makes it easy to unlock your Mac and enter passwords all at the touch of a fingerThe quick-release MagSafe power connector easily attaches and detaches with magnets, preventing any unintended flightsSpecificationsRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13. 6 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name SilverLaptop Type NotebookDisplay Type Retina DisplayDisplay Resolution Type Full HDAverage Battery Life 16 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version OS XOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 0 GBModel Number MLXY3/MLXY3B/A/MLXY3LL/A / MLXY3X/A / MLXY3HN/AModel Name MacBook Air 13 M2HDMI Output noNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot noProcessor Version Apple M2 chip with 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b60d38cf-6608-44e5-aadb-32367f437757</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/77e4cf6b-a5db-4a18-9fd9-f40bab7ce8c9/web/1_1727354476204.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>4269 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034073559219</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9187790574</g:id>
      <g:title>iPhone 15 Pro 128GB Black Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 1” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for a 3x optical zoom and 15x digital zoom. Up to 23 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Black TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MTU73AH/A,MTUV3AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c77e534b-920c-41f5-bd41-a358c8411e91</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/29bb9219-8f3d-43ff-988e-eadf046a0210/web/1_1727352747364.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3729 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091877905741</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4006726207</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple New 2024 MacBook Air MXCR3 13-inch Display, Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU Processor/16GB RAM/512GB SSD/Intel UHD Graphics(International version) English Space Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>1080p FaceTime HD cameraTwo Thunderbolt / USB 4 portsSupport for up to two external displays (with laptop lid closed)Magic Keyboard with Touch ID35W Dual USB-C Port Compact Power AdapterSpecificationsProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 1920x1080Colour Name Space GreyLaptop Type NotebookKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version ‎Intel UHD 630Display Type Liquid Retina XDRDisplay Resolution Type Full HDStorage Type SSDOperating System Version macOS MontereyOperating System macOSUsage Type PersonalModel Series Apple MacBook AirProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 16-CoreRAM Type DDR4External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory 2 GBModel Number MXCR3JA/A, MXCR3LL/AModel Name MacBook AirHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2. 0SD Card Slot YesProcessor Version Apple M3 Chip 8-Core CPU 10-Core GPU</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3984fd70-a1e6-4a67-8b57-b7986cfcb54a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2894e56e-a4ae-47aa-972b-a85d59eb4423/web/1_1727353661839.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>5399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040067262072</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4941237537</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Natural Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN33</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/06e4f25d-9234-461d-a304-5ccda427545e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/300a4a82-f1c4-481e-a4bc-ccdf10a6bd14/web/1_1727438201419.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049412375375</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9810767408</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/af7074dc-eaa4-4cd3-9793-a5b32fb3126e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aae5939e-73e7-4a59-a62c-76f98f4b5769/web/1_1727440889602.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098107674088</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2843632944</g:id>
      <g:title> I PHONE 14 PRO COVER</g:title>
      <g:description>Crystal clear acrylic phone case. Compatible with Iphone 14 Pro. Scratch resistantSpecificationsMaterial AcrylicProduct Weight 2 gColour Name BLUE/PURPLEWhat's In The Box COVERPhone Case Material PVCModel Compatibility iPhone 14 ProType of Case Back CoverProduct Length 5 cmProduct Height 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 2 cmModel Number NAModel Name ISELLItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0b370548-97ef-496d-9c36-b2d534948bb9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7cdaca42-080e-4243-948e-24737b5c1658/web/1_1727411846549.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028436329441</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6259340550</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad 2022 (10th Generation) 10.9-inch 64GB WiFi Blue - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylus support (1st gen only)SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 4 GBInternal Memory 64 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 10. 9 inPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count No SIM CardSIM Type No SIM CardConnection Type WifiOperating System iOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveModel Year 2022Voice Calling Capability NoOperating System Number iPadOS 16Processor Number A14Network Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Hexa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleBattery Type Lithium IonModel Number iPad (2022) Blue 64GB WiFiModel Name iPad 2022 (10th Generation)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3282a349-5589-47bb-9614-c50a96b4b7e1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2b4dec55-e288-4d94-858d-8a828ea25fb4/web/1_1727352380306.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price>1435 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062593405501</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4087536078</g:id>
      <g:title>Original JBL GO3 wireless Bluetooth Speaker Subwoofer Outdoor Speaker Waterproof Bass Sound Mini Speaker multiple colour</g:title>
      <g:description>JBL Introducing the JBL GO 3 Bluetooth Speaker: portable, ultra-compact, with bold style and JBL Sound Pro. It combines with your style and accompanies you on the go Stream your music from your phone or tablet and enjoy up to 5 hours of music in a single charge with this Bluetooth speaker: wireless and hassle-free At the beach, pool, or even in the rain, the party never stops: the GO 3 features an IP67 certified waterproof and dustproof design Express your style: The GO 3 impresses with its modern design and expressive details. It is also available in a wide variety of colours inspired by the most current fashion Box contents: 1 x JBL GO 3 portable Bluetooth speaker, dimensions: 87. 5 x 75 x 41. 3 mm, 1 x quick start guide, 1 x safety plug, 1 x USB type C cable, blue/pinkSpecificationsColour Name BLUEProduct Length 8 cmProduct Height 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 3 cm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/806fb278-1cfe-42bd-9206-d4d4408e5bef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ce9e11ea-26e1-47be-bfe6-ec91563b7a2f/web/1_1727354705535.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>189 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040875360786</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9515226554</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Black Titanium</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN03</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0fe538c7-8e4f-433d-9b9a-79de873ad8d1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d1ccde67-0bd7-4520-8680-4e4bf8f8ed8b/web/1_1727437402933.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095152265544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7545112454</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7d0f3626-e449-473c-b231-fa5b46f7ca95</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0b7bf3bb-904d-420a-9b45-aab7925b44ba/web/1_1727437069747.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075451124544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6005105475</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - White Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN13</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9909af24-3993-47ac-918c-3eb0c462c625</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/407fd4db-0fa1-44ec-83e6-4ac7467da4c3/web/1_1727436658892.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060051054759</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1348518604</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/69da9ac5-acdb-47c3-bc5a-4e4fc8905449</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a373eec9-6c7a-4a80-8a3d-774096d392a6/web/2_1727442153685.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013485186046</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7513954994</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 7-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in Black, Silver and Light Green, Galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the Galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front Camera, the 2MP Depth Camera and the 50MP Wide-angle CameraEquipped with a powerful octa-core, 4/6GB of memory and 64/128GB internal storage, Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handThe 5,000mAh (typical)** battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of Super Fast Charging, Galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVDMEAModel Name SM-A057FLVDMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/05d34c81-1185-456e-a8f5-390e597cb446</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5b4617ed-92c6-4628-96a4-5acbe1bb7204/web/1_1727673153057.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>375.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075139549942</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6219561389</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 4 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZKGMEA / SM-A057FZKDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e16dbfa4-5f6a-417a-9539-87f3cb65db69</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2f200f95-df7c-4a1f-bb71-2274937251eb/web/1_1727674159558.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>354.25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0062195613892</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9267782077</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor 200 LITE Starry Blue Dual SIM 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights108MP rear camera, portrait in the spotlightHonor 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your handExtra-large AMOLED view, boundless with brightness and clarityOverviewThe Portrait Master 108MP &amp;amp; 50MP Glorious Portrait Risk-free Dimming AMOLED Display Lightweight Drop-resistant Design 108MP Rear Camera, Portrait in the Spotlight 50MP Light-sensitive Selfie, Fantastic group photo Ultra-slim in Shape, Crafted in Style Drop-Proof, Trust Enhanced Risk-Free Dimming Eye-Care Display 256GB Ultra-large Storage Dynamic in Design, Elegant in Heart HONOR 200 Lite leads the ultra-slim fashion among bar phones, Exquisitely crafted and lightweight in your hand. 6. 78mm Thickness 166g Weight Selfie Light 50MP Front Camera 108MP Main Camera f/1. 75 aperture Marco Camera f/2. 4 aperture Wide &amp;amp; Depth Camera f/2. 2 aperture AI Wide-angle Selfie 78° FOV mode works while taking selfies, and switches to 90° FOV mode whlie taking groupfies. Multi-focal Portrait, the Art of Boken The Rear camera features three focal choices, each showing a side of your unique charm. 108MP image,Uncompromising Clarity The 108MP HD Rear camera can capture the excitement of your life clearly and vividly. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 4 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4500 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Colour Name Starry BlueDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number 6080Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek DimensityNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDNetwork Type 5GCondition NewModel Number LLY-NX1Model Name HONOR 200 LITEPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/115e0f75-a62c-419d-8309-0fa07f12e26a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/004f7bb5-0ed5-404a-970a-c3fbbd2fa576/web/1_1727673590390.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>810 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092677820777</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5483353974</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi A3 Dual SIM Midnight Black 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRefined and Stylish DesignSmooth 6. 71'' 90Hz Dot Drop displayMassive 5000mAh (typ) battery, and provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W chargingSecure fingerprint and AI face unlockSupports up to 1TB expandable storageOverviewThe ultra-thin design, paired with the clean flat frame, appears exquisite and stylish. Hold the phone with one hand to embrace trends and lightness. Provide a USB Type-C port supporting 10W charging*. 5000mAh ultra-large battery, reducing battery life anxiety and ensuring full-day range. Powerful octa-core processor with a maximum CPU frequency of 2. 2GHz, more balanced performance, reduced lags, and more fun to enjoy. You can choose the side fingerprint or AI face to easily unlock your phone. Suitable for more unlocking scenarios, safer and more convenient. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBProduct Weight 199 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 71 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Midnight BlackDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 14Processor Number G36What's In The Box Mobile Phone | Adapter | USB Type-C Cable | SIM Eject Tool | Quick Start Guide | Safety InformationNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080pNetwork Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 168 mmProduct Height 8. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 76. 3 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number 23129RN51XModel Name Redmi A3 (4+128)Primary Camera (MP) 8+QVGA MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6ce530ed-88fb-4dfd-9e2c-ba1235fb45e2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ed08874d-91b6-443d-9948-0e6ccdedd336/web/1_1727676140069.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>302.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054833539749</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5356466722</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 5G Indian Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ display6. 5" FHD+ super amoled5G x Octa-core processor50MP cameraOverviewProcessor 2. 2GHz, 2GHz CPU Type Octa-Core Size (Main_Display) 163. 9mm (6. 5") Weight (g) 200SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2. 2 GHzSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Blue BlackDisplay Type Super AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability yesNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name Samsung Exynos 7Number of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla Glass 5Primary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080p (100fps), 1080p(30fps), 1080p(60fps), 1440P (30fps), 1440P (60fps), 4K (30fps), 720P(200fps)Wireless 5GWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Accelerometer, Fingerprint Sensor, Gyro Sensor, Geomagnetic Sensor, Light Sensor, Virtual Proximity SensingModel Number SM-A156EZKGMEA, SM-A156M/DSN, SM-A156E/DSModel Name Galaxy A15Pixels Per Inch 1080 x 2340Primary Camera (MP) 50</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/db15346e-9e05-4801-ad8b-1855147e8ddd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ca6e77cc-9270-4d62-86ef-0a452b928986/web/1_1727676284712.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>679.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053564667226</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9623228108</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Yellow 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name YellowOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZYHMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bcf0798c-4884-4a40-8d77-37af71b3f8cc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8622c477-cd72-483e-a307-20bc45163d6f/web/1_1727674430025.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096232281089</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
