<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>4622820923</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Camera Mini 12 Pastel Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompact and cute design. Easily twist the lens to turn on and offAutomatic exposure and automatic flashFujinon 60mm lens with selfie mirrorDedicated selfie/close-up shooting modeFocal length : 60mmOverviewDedicated to the joy of living in the moment, the FUJIFILM INSTAX MINI 12 Instant Film Camera provides easy-to-use controls and quickly produces memorable credit-card-sized photos. Offered here in clay white, this instant camera is ready to go with a simple twist of the lens. SpecificationsProduct Weight 453. 59 GColour Name Pastel BlueProduct Length 10. 41 CmProduct Height 12. 19 CmProduct Width/Depth 6. 6 CmCamera Resolution 16 MPModel Number Instax Mini 12Model Name Instax Mini 12Inbuilt Flash Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4a48ed09-773e-4cea-aea6-f979c2d6b0b0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/374f95b0-25ad-4c8c-86f6-32c52544f7c8/web/1_1730358914954.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0046228209238</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1974345179</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put pc-like power in your pocket, galaxy z fold6. Now super-charged with galaxy AI on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displaySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 4 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 MAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 7. 6 InSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber Of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number Fold 6Model Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bd4a114f-24d4-47aa-b765-1be52a479caa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e27116f5-6888-404a-a5c7-9b7723e858e8/web/1_1730358410327.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019743451796</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
