<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>7783454868</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 46mm Rose Gold Aluminium Case With Light Blush Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Light Blush Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 46 mmModel Number MWWT3QA/A, MWWU3QA/A, MWWT3ZP/A, MWWT3LW/A, MWWU3ZP/A, MWWU3LW/AModel Name MWWT3QA/A, MWWU3QA/A, MWWU3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/19c9b497-927f-4cbe-9739-4d4ea17f66d3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e1ca15bb-3af3-4d24-9b47-2fe9408878d9/web/1_1736248777200.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>1699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077834548688</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3185816564</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Series 10 GPS 46mm Jet Black Aluminium Case With Black Sport Band</g:title>
      <g:description>Series 10 has the largest screen area of any Apple Watch. It has up to 75% more screen area than Series 3 and up to 30% more screen area than Series 4, 5, 6 and SE. So you can see and do even moreFrom sleep tracking to heart health notifications and much more, the advanced sensors in Series 10 help you better understand your healthSleep on it. Get help setting up a bedtime routine and tracking your sleep. See the time you spent in REM, Core and Deep sleep, as well as when you might have woken up. You can even get 8 hours of sleep tracking with just an 8-minute chargeNew Vitals app helps you identify changes in your daily health status. 6 Quickly see your key overnight health metrics right on your wrist — including blood oxygen18, heart rate, respiratory rate, wrist temperature7 and sleep durationApple Watch has an innovative sensor that tracks your temperature while you sleep. 7 The Cycle Tracking app uses this data to provide a retrospective estimate of when you likely ovulated, which can be helpful for family planningOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Sport BandConnection Type GPSBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Trending Apple Watch SeSmartwatch Dial Size 46 mmModel Number MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/A, MWWQ3ZP/A, MWWQ3LW/A, MWWP3ZP/AModel Name MWWP3QA/A, MWWQ3QA/A, MWWP3LW/A, MWWQ3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d9f980a3-9547-4a1c-8183-85c8576169e6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/319e01b7-e980-4503-b41c-5d80d7154526/web/1_1736248073076.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2100 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031858165641</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2821854346</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Show Variants iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6R3AH/A,MU793AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/59333e1e-42b8-474a-9ce5-b250871234a2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/216dc8c8-b102-49b4-a7d3-2e528ba7c534/web/1_1736248521844.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028218543461</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8836461768</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Black Titanium Case With Black Trail Loop - M/L</g:title>
      <g:description>Featuring a stunning, new black titanium case, Apple Watch Ultra 2 is the ultimate sports and adventure watch. It has all the connectivity, health and safety features for the every day. And it takes training further with the most accurate GPS in a sports watchUltra 2 is built for extremes. Now available in black titanium, the 49 mm case is designed for the toughest environments, and it’s certified to EN13319, the internationally recognised standard for diving accessoriesAction on the spot. The customisable Action button gives you precise control over starting a workout, marking a segment or moving on to the next intervalA battery made for the long run. Wherever you find yourself, the last thing you want to worry about is your battery. Ultra 2 is engineered to perform at peak conditions longer, so you can perform at yoursApple Watch Ultra 2 is the perfect partner whether you’re riding indoors, road cycling, mountain biking or commuting. From Bluetooth-enabled accessories to metrics to seeing them easily while you’re riding, you’re always ready to rollOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Trail Loop - M/LConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size Medium/LargeSmartwatch Dial Size 49 mmModel Number MX4V3QA/AModel Name MX4V3QA/A, MX4V3ZP/A, MX4V3LW/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/57d0daa2-d529-40f1-8321-5188d8a62d00</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dff74677-8d05-4b74-ba5a-c38f01fbcc02/web/1_1736249001538.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>2920 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088364617683</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6087318989</g:id>
      <g:title>JVC 55 Inch Edgeless 4K UHD Android 13 Smart TV With Dolby Audio And Quadcore Processor LT-55N775 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsNarrow frame helps the TV look slim and attractiveDiscover a thrilling world of extraordinary clarity with every single pixel enhanced beautifullyHigh quality materials ensures durabilityCome with innovative cinema sound 2D acoustic and surround sound processorSupports auto-mega-contrast to view clear more clearer imagesThe Screen Maintains its Integrity from any viewing angle,This allows you to enjoy dynamic,vibrant colour from every seat in room &amp;amp; This TV Brings you the excitement of movies and games,4K UHD means the TV screen has a minimum resolution of 3840 pixels wide and 2160 pixels highThis Impex LED smart TV features multi-language support that translates your favorite TV shows in the language that you understandThis Impex UHD LED smart TV provides a wide viewing angle to enhance your visual experienceExceptional gaming performance with quick response action, colour and detail of hdr brings everything you watch is clear,bright and incredibly realisticIt also features a Wi-Fi connection that enables you to watch a trending web series directly online directlyOverviewTV episodes, music, news, sports, kids’ shows and free programming than any other streaming player. Experience all your movie, video, and music experience in crystal clear, sharp, vibrant picture quality thanks to the built-in CrystalColor engine and hear the difference with JVCs innovative XinemaSound 2D acoustic and surround sound processor. Designed our UHD ready TVs with super-slim bezels, so you can enjoy more of the sports, shows and movies you love. JVC Smart UHD ready TV flashes a single image with these fantastic features of response time less than 5ms, contrast Ratio: 5000:1, Brightness: 300CD/m², Aspect ratio:16:9, built-in camera, smart browser, smart remote, face recognition, HDMI, and USB ports. With USB port function, simply plug your USB memory drive into the TV and instantaneously enjoy movies, photos or music. Now, you can experience a wide variety of content in the comfort of your living room on your TV. SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 4KRAM Size 8 GBInternal Memory 8 GBProduct Weight 12. 9 KGScreen Size 55 inRefresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box TelevisionsNumber of Cores Dual CoreViewing Distance 3. 2 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 93 cmProduct Height 72. 9 cmProduct Width/Depth 124. 8 cmFeatures Bluetooth, AndroidModel Number LT-55N775Model Name LT-55N775 NewNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/13242cf5-54dd-41f0-898e-7f0a5cfa94bb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/57f03295-f9ce-4cdf-8664-25e3e34b19e5/web/1_1732009084907.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>JVC</g:brand>
      <g:price>1089 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060873189899</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7815299285</g:id>
      <g:title>Renewed - iPhone 15 Pro Max With Facetime 256GB White Titanium 5G</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Overview"Renewed Premium: Never been used/Negligible use, but may have been looked at. These items have zero scratches or bruises. They are checked, renewed and re-packed in a generic/OEM box. You will get original accessories With 3 -months warranty. 1. Product is Never been used/Negligible use. It is Renewed like new with zero scratches and packed in a new generic box. It comes with original accessories. 2. Product has passed standard functionality checklist and has been renewed by certified sellers to Like new condition3. All products sold on are 100% functional. The grade of any product only signifies its physical appearance4. Product will come with 3 -months warrantySpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSGrade PremiumVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition RenewedModel Number iPhone 15 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d9da90ea-ad2f-4784-88c9-4872f07a5f2f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cd8df4e2-ee9b-4c6c-b90d-1b9f3af05f1e/web/6_1732516110344.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078152992856</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
