<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>3837230122</g:id>
      <g:title>Rechargeable Portable Speaker, Portable Handle with 1500 MAH Huge Battery</g:title>
      <g:description>Wireless PA speakers have built-in Bluetooth for wireless audio streaming There are 4 modes available It is used as a karaoke machine, music player, PA system, FM radio, etc The portable speaker karaoke PA system is equipped with a USB flash drive and SD card reader so it can serve as an MP3 player, 35mm AUX input and mic/guitar input The LED light of this Geepas PA speaker changes with the music playing, which can create a colourful and joyful effect The body design of the audio system is highly mechanical and can satisfy your rhythm at karaoke You will carefully notice that you have the rhythm pattern of a deformed robot The portable karaoke speaker with 2 flexible wheels on the bottom has a medium-sized, light and wear-resistant hard shell and is easy to move The speaker has a short handle which is suitable for people of all walks of life It is suitable for family reunions, indoor gatherings, classroom teaching, public speaking, and small stage performancesSpecificationsProduct Weight 2. 14 KGColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Warranty Card &amp;amp; User manualProduct Length 41. 3 cmProduct Height 18. 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 21. 3 cmWattage 25000 WFeatures Amplifier, Compact Size, USB, Smart, WirelessModel Number GMS11187Model Name Geepas GMS11187Number of HDMI Ports 0</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/01db1185-a236-4696-9e32-b42e52f53fba</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/513fddac-e852-4141-bc2d-c49dbed10496/web/5_1736858406344.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>98 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038372301227</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8353208215</g:id>
      <g:title>Geeoas 4 Way Extension Socket 13A - Extension Strip With Led Indicators | Child Safe</g:title>
      <g:description>This Geepas 4 Way Extension Socket/Strip is damage-resistant and fireproof housing protects circuits from fire, impact or rust, and prevents dents and scratches. The built-in power indicator light makes it easy to know its ON/OFF mode. Compatible for connecting various devices like washing machines, Iron boxes, TV, Hair Dryer, Mobile, Drill machines, Printer, Computer, Refrigerator, Vacuum cleaners and more. 1. PREMIUM PROTECTION FOR YOUR ELECTRONICS -The Geepas strip features high-quality construction and a durable design with damage-resistant housing that protects circuits from fire, impact, and rust. Three protected AC outlets make this surge protection strip an ideal solution for home offices, media rooms, and other areas where multiple devices need to be connected. 2. 750 DEGREE FLAME RETARDANT MATERIAL - Built with durable material which is fireproof ABS plastic and has a high melting and heating point, protecting your connected devices. The material is 750 degree Celsius Flame Retardant. 3. ERGONOMIC DESIGN -This extension strip has 4 plugs that are angled so it does not block the other outlet. This keeps it free for use with additional items. The size of this socket is 35. 2x13. 4x3. 6cm. 4. 3 METER POWER CORD - Along with its slim, sleek design that effortlessly slides into narrow spaces, the three-outlet, power strip provides a 3-meter extra long power cord to prevent a tripping hazard and to minimize clutter. 'SpecificationsProduct Weight 560 gColour Name White/OrangeSize 35. 2x13. 4x3. 6 cmModel Number GES58012Model Name GES58012Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1e82caa1-e407-4e96-9230-63ec828c8150</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cea8b311-343b-417b-b532-0206a66c008c/web/3_1736848668247.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083532082157</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3470310029</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas 32 Inch HD Smart LED TV With Remote Control, HDMI And USB Ports, Head Phone Jack,</g:title>
      <g:description>"Delivers a picture that is smooth and clear, full of rich colors and detailed contrast. Enjoy unmatched clarity and crispness with the Geepas 32"" Smart LED TV. An immersive experience with a captivating visual and audio experience as real as possible with a high-quality display A device engineered to offer high speed, quality performance, and other stunning details. You can now quickly access the contents and control them with a remote control. For a truly remarkable viewing experience, picture quality is enhanced by an advanced 176x176 viewing angle and wide color enhancement. It optimizes every scene for splendid expression. It is engineered with the latest technology to produce high speed, quality performance, and stunning details. It has an impressive, design and will elevate your interior style and ambience. You can watch your favorite movies, shows, and much more. Android 12. 0 provides a wide range of entertainment options. The sound is intelligently optimized according to audio content or customized to your personal taste with effects and stereo sound quality. With HDMI and USB ports that allow for a physical connection, the TV makes it simple to connect. Furthermore, these ports allow for multiple input and output options. This TV is full HD compatible, so you can enjoy HD movies and TV shows. Using the remote control, you can switch between watching your favorite movies, shows, and much more all in one place without leaving your seat. The package includes a remote control. The LED TV uses eco-efficiency technology to offer you a wonderful theatrical experience while being light in your pocket. "SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 720pRAM Size 1 GBInternal Memory 8 GBProduct Weight 8 KGScreen Size 32 inRefresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box 1 x Television, 2 x BaseProcessor Name Cortex-A53Number of Cores Quad CoreRAM Type DDR2Viewing Distance 1. 7 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 32 cmProduct Height 70. 84 cmProduct Width/Depth 39. 85 cmFeatures Android, USB, HDMIModel Number GLED3202SCHDModel Name GLED3202SEHDNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 2Processor Version A55 Quad Core</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0576718a-81f6-450f-9db5-cd8c664fd9ef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5c5b267a-1166-4f12-a0fe-0d1cbdc9892c/web/1_1736849474924.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>339 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034703100293</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
