<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9881578729</g:id>
      <g:title>GEEPAS 43" Frameless Full HD Smart Slim LED TV With Remote Control | HDMI & USB Ports, Head Phone Jack, PC Audio In,Wi-Fi, Android 14.0, AV Mode| YouTube, Netflix | HQ Sound | GLED4324SFHD Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights43 Inch Frameless Full HD LED Display for a sleek, modern lookSmart TV with Android 14. 0 for a seamless and intuitive user experienceIncludes remote control with voice search functionality3 HDMI Ports and 2 USB Ports for diverse connectivity optionsHeadphone Jack for private listeningPC Audio In for versatile audio connectionsBuilt-in Wi-Fi for easy access to online contentPre-installed YouTube and Netflix for instant streamingHigh-quality sound with HQ Sound technologyColor temperature adjustment for personalized viewing experienceFull HD 1080p resolution for crystal-clear picture qualityOverviewEnhance your home entertainment experience with the 43" Frameless Full HD Smart Slim LED TV, a perfect blend of cutting-edge technology and stylish design. Featuring a sleek, frameless display, this TV provides an immersive viewing experience with its Full HD 1080p resolution, ensuring crystal-clear picture quality that brings your favorite content to life. Powered by Android 14. 0, this Smart TV offers a seamless and intuitive user experience, allowing you to access a vast array of apps, games, and streaming services. Pre-installed with YouTube and Netflix, you can enjoy instant entertainment at your fingertips. The included remote control with voice search functionality makes it easy to find and control your content. Connectivity is a breeze with 3 HDMI ports and 2 USB ports, enabling you to connect multiple devices such as gaming consoles, Blu-ray players, and external storage drives. The PC Audio In option and headphone jack provide versatile audio connections, while built-in Wi-Fi ensures easy access to online content without the need for additional cables. Experience high-quality sound with HQ Sound technology, delivering clear, rich audio that enhances your viewing experience. The color temperature adjustment feature allows you to customize the display settings to match your preferences, ensuring vibrant, lifelike colors. AV Mode optimizes the audio-visual settings for different types of content, providing an immersive experience for movies, sports, and more. Designed to complement any room décor, the slim and stylish profile of this TV adds a touch of elegance to your living space. Energy-efficient operation helps reduce power consumption, making this TV an eco-friendly choice. The sleep timer and auto power-off functions further contribute to energy savings. Parental controls ensure a safe viewing environment for children, while multi-language support makes this TV accessible to a global audience. The fast and responsive user interface allows for smooth navigation, and the advanced color enhancement technology delivers vibrant and lifelike images. The 43" Frameless Full HD Smart Slim LED TV also supports screen mirroring from compatible devices, enabling you to share content from your smartphone or tablet directly on the big screen. With its compatibility with various audio and video formats, this TV provides a versatile entertainment solution for all your needs. Upgrade your home entertainment system with the 43" Frameless Full HD Smart Slim LED TV and enjoy a world of entertainment in stunning high definition. SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 3Video Format 1080pScreen Size 43 inColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System AndroidAudio Jack 3. 5 mmViewing Distance 2. 6 mModel Year 2024Streaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxFeatures Android, HDMI, Smart TV, USB, Wi-FiModel Number GLED4324SFHDModel Name GLED4324SFHDNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c1c50448-a659-416a-abcb-cdce554514d7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/567cd586-b2e6-4073-9f8c-d7ebf27443d8/web/1_1730177369119.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>619 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098815787292</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4895633275</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (2024) GPS + Cellular 49mm Black Titanium Case With Black Ocean Band</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFeaturing a stunning, new black titanium case, Apple Watch Ultra 2 is the ultimate sports and adventure watch. It has all the connectivity, health and safety features for the every day. And it takes training further with the most accurate GPS in a sports watchUltra 2 is built for extremes. Now available in black titanium, the 49 mm case is designed for the toughest environments, and it’s certified to EN13319, the internationally recognised standard for diving accessoriesAction on the spot. The customisable Action button gives you precise control over starting a workout, marking a segment or moving on to the next intervalA battery made for the long run. Wherever you find yourself, the last thing you want to worry about is your battery. Ultra 2 is engineered to perform at peak conditions longer, so you can perform at yoursApple Watch Ultra 2 is the perfect partner whether you’re riding indoors, road cycling, mountain biking or commuting. From Bluetooth-enabled accessories to metrics to seeing them easily while you’re riding, you’re always ready to rollOverviewLife is full of the unexpected. That’s why Apple Watch is there to call for help when you need it most. And now it can let someone know when you’ve safely made it to a destination. Need help? Apple Watch has your back. Just press and hold the side button to call emergency services and share your location. Apple Watch can automatically detect if you’ve taken a hard fall or been in a severe car crash. If you need help, it will call emergency services, share your location and notify your emergency contacts. Check In notifies someone when you arrive at a destination. If you’re going for a run after dark, you can start a Check In for the duration of your workout to automatically notify a friend when you’re done. What matters to you matters to Apple too. From using more recycled materials that minimise environmental impact. To privacy protections that give you more control over your data. To creating built‑in features that make Apple Watch accessible to all. SpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name Black Ocean BandConnection Type GPS &amp;amp; CellularBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 49 MmModel Number MX4P3QA/AModel Name MX4P3QA/A, MX4P3LW/A, MX4P3ZP/A</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8074a3d6-580f-46df-b75c-d32f4de41ab8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76cc1764-1f79-4011-87a7-36e9e136a081/web/1_1730192051003.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048956332752</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4282864176</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPad Air 2024 (6th Generation) M2 11-Inch 256GB Blue Wi-Fi - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe new ultra retina XDR display introduces groundbreaking tandem OLED technology. Extreme brightness, incredibly precise contrast and advanced technologies like ProMotion and True Tone give you a jaw-dropping visual experienceIntroducing M2, the next generation of Apple silicon, delivering outrageous performance in the exceptionally thin and light design of iPad AiriPadOS is designed to let you power through advanced workflows and do all the things you love with ease and simplicityOverviewThe all-new iPad Air packs astonishing power into an unbelievably thin, light and portable design. Push the limits of what’s possible on iPad with a super-portable 11″ iPad Air and an expansive 13″ iPad Air that is the thinnest product Apple has ever created. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 7606 MAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 11 InPrimary Camera Resolution 12 MPColour Name BlueCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Single SIMSIM Type ESIMConnection Type WifiDisplay Type IPS LCDDisplay Resolution Type Full HDOperating System IOSNetwork Type Wi-FiTablet Screen Size 10. 1 - 11 InchesSecondary Camera 12 MP &amp;amp; AboveVoice Calling Capability NoProcessor Number M2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band WiFiProcessor Name AppleCamera Type Primary CameraPrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash Dual Tone FlashWireless WirelessBattery Type Lithium PolymerWater/Dust Properties Water Proof And Dust ProofModel Number IPad AirModel Name IPad AirPrimary Camera (MP) 12mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4b3c8880-2c1f-4c5c-8d26-90c30e6c065b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c61345e1-f17f-4387-b0e8-1fc683a85538/web/1_1730191762279.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042828641768</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
