<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>6129860786</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Personalise your home screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your lock screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the action buttonIn the redesigned photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like people and petsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a181a94e-8280-4bd3-81c7-c012671651bd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a2933ac5-03da-47e7-b156-a50a68c7748b/web/6_1736247460615.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061298607869</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6080075728</g:id>
      <g:title>laptops</g:title>
      <g:description>🚀 DELL LATITUDE 3540 – Built for Performance! 🚀🔹 Intel Core i5, 13th Gen – Power like never before🔹 16GB RAM + 512GB SSD – Speed meets ample storage🔹 15” Full HD Display – Crystal-clear visuals🔹 Backlit Keyboard – Work anytime, anywhere🔹 Includes Original Charger, Bag &amp;amp; Mouse – All-in-one package🔹 FREE UAE-Wide Delivery – Right to your doorstep🔹 Unbeatable Price – Don’t miss out!📦 Your Ultimate Productivity Partner Awaits!</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/14b30dfc-678c-405f-a49b-493092333f60</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4a5f453c-93c7-40d7-bdb3-3a32c66fd6fd/web/image_picker_476704E6-7F74-41C0-B2B6-76453F01680F-522-000000070F347E75.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Dell</g:brand>
      <g:price>1200 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060800757283</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7100018845</g:id>
      <g:title>HYPERX Cloud II Wired Over-Ear Gaming Headphones For PS4, PS5, XOne, XSeries, Nintendo Switch And PC</g:title>
      <g:description>The HyperX Cloud II Gaming Headset is ideal for high intensity gaming. Its frequency range of 15 to 25,000Hz makes it perfect for in game chat and team communication. The accessory’s USB Audio Sound Card helps the headset generate virtual 7. 1 surround sound, making it perfect for gaming tournaments where nothing but the best is required. The HyperX Cloud II Gaming Headset’s memory foam ear pads ensure the audio that is generated is heard clearly, even in environments with a lot of background noise. The pads sit comfortably on your ears, enabling you to don the headset for hours on end at a time. Lets you game comfortably and get the best audio experience on PC, Mac and consolesInterchangeable ear cups for varying sound profiles and different texture optionsEasily toggle Surround Sound 7. 1 on and off with a touch of a button. Includes independent audio and microphone volume controls for added convenience. The Internal sound card DSP amplifies audio and voice for optimal HiFi gaming experienceHyperX Cloud II is HiFi capable with 53mm drivers and delivers superior audio performance in gaming or professional audio environments. Its crystal-clear low, mid and high tones plus enhanced bass-reproduction create an immersive gaming experienceTeamSpeak certifies the voice quality to be clear and crisp with excellent sound quality. No audible echoes, background noises or voice distortions were detected in tests. Other compatible chat clients include Skype, Mumble and VentriloHyperX Cloud II comes with 100% memory foam ear pads and interchangeable ear cups for varying sound profiles and different texture options. Generate a virtual surround sound experience to create distance and depth that enhances any gaming, movie or music experience. It’s plug and play, which means no drivers are neededOverviewThe HyperX Cloud was built to be an ultra-comfortable gaming headset with amazing sound. We put a lot of thought into the details of our HyperX signature memory foam, the premium leatherette, clamping force, and weight distribution to create a headset that’s comfortable through long gaming sessions. It’s no wonder that it’s become the preferred gaming headset for millions of gamers. Whether you want to focus on the competition or relax with some of your favorite games, there’s a Cloud that’s perfect for you. SpecificationsProduct Weight 275 gColour Name Black/RedConnection Type WiredWhat's In The Box 1 X Microphone &amp;amp; HeadsetsType of Console Software PC GamesProduct Length 17 cmProduct Height 12 cmProduct Width/Depth 7 cmFeatures With Microphone, Noise CancellingModel Number 4P5M0AAModel Name KHX-HSCP-RD</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9d4bab75-31b0-4636-a08c-81314f3bbe00</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/50838fd2-1ab1-44d5-9232-d435bbdc792d/web/6_1736771232110.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>325 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071000188456</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6402208463</g:id>
      <g:title>Amazfit Pop 3s Ultra-large 1.96" HD AMOLED Display,Fashionable Curved & Metallic Design</g:title>
      <g:description>Pop 3s Ultra-large 1. 96" (4. 9 Cm) HD AMOLED Display,Fashionable Curved &amp;amp; Metallic Design with bluetooth phone calls. Music Control, Camera Control, Find Phone, Breath Training, 12/24-hour, Stopwatch, Clock, Weather Forecast, Date Display, Dial, Cloud Multi-Dial, Custom Dial, OTA Upgrade, Multi-Language UI Interface, Multi-Language, Data Storage, All-Day Data, Call Notification, Message Reminder, Alarm Reminder, Step Goal Completion Reminder, Binding Confirmation Reminder, Low Battery Reminder, Brightness Adjustment, Vibration Adjustment, Wear Monitoring, Lift Wrist to Wake Screen, Power Saving Mode, Smart DND, Quick Settings, Female Cycle, Voice Assistant, Blood-oxygen Saturation Measurement,Monitoring of Heart Rate, Sleep and Sports DataSpecificationsMaterial SiliconeColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Smartwatch, Magnetic Charger, User ManualBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 96 inModel Number A2318Model Name A2318</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/53cf06a6-c8d2-4529-99fd-aa1745cf85e4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9bd8cd29-d59d-4e5a-a45a-d60ab6b225af/web/2_1736772419907.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>159 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064022084639</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4532629800</g:id>
      <g:title>JBL PartyBox 110 Portable Bluetooth Speaker Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Start a party with powerful sound and a dynamic light show. Bring a whole new dimension to any party with the unique dynamic LED lighting, synced to the powerful sound and deep bass of the PartyBox 110. Take the PartyBox wherever you go with the splashproof design and plug in a guitar and mic for the ultimate immersive experience. With Bass Boost and loud, powerful JBL Original Pro Sound, your friends won’t just hear the music, they’ll feel it as 12 hours of playtime keeps the party rocking all day or night. Use the PartyBox app for total control as you stream your tunes wirelessly. Features: Powerful JBL Original Pro Sound Dynamic light show that syncs to the beat 12 hours of playtime IPX4 splashproof Mic and Guitar inputs PartyBox app Multisource playback Pair your speakers for an even bigger sound Powerful JBL Original Pro Sound Whether you’re at home or outdoors, the JBL PartyBox 110 makes your music amazing with two levels of deep, adjustable bass and powerful JBL Original Pro Sound. Dynamic light show that syncs to the beat Every kind of music is better with a dynamic light show! Colors synched to the beat make you want to move your feet, while customizable strobes and patterns dazzle your eyes. It’s a unique, immersive audiovisual experience that transforms any party into a work of art. 12 hours of playtime Power the party all day or all night. With 12 hours of playtime and a built-in rechargeable battery, the beat will go on (and on)! IPX4 splashproof Whether your guests are dancing on the beach or sipping drinks by the pool, the JBL PartyBox 110 is IPX4 splashproof so you never have to worry about the party getting too wet and wild. Mic and Guitar inputs With mic and guitar inputs, you can show your talents as you sing and play along. Not only will you sound great but you’ll look great, too, with the perfect light show for rocking out! PartyBox app The JBL PartyBox app makes it easier than ever to control your music, update settings, and customize the colors and patterns of your light show for the perfect party vibe. Multisource playback Stream your tunes wirelessly via Bluetooth, connect a USB stick or plugin with an aux cable. The JBL PartyBox 110 offers the ultimate adaptability for your music. Pair your speakers for an even bigger sound One JBL PartyBox not enough? Pair two speakers with a cable or Wireless by True Wireless Stereo (TWS) technology for an even bigger, bolder sound. SpecificationsCharging Type Lightning PortBattery Size 7500 mAhProduct Weight 10. 5 KGColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box 1 x JBL PartyBox 110 AC power cord (AC plug and Quantity varies by region) 1 x Quick start guide 1 x Safety sheet 1 x Warranty cardProduct Length 11. 6 inProduct Height 22. 4 inProduct Width/Depth 11. 8 inFeatures Ergonomic, Travel, Rechargeable, Business, PersonalModel Number JBLPARTYBOX110UK, JBLPARTYBOX110EU/AMModel Name JBLPARTYBOX110UKItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/400bf4b5-ada1-4aaf-bb93-f92ae4f5d37e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/503f9475-c076-4705-bfb7-ca2ffb1ac6d7/web/1_1736771944528.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1095 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045326298007</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4209636795</g:id>
      <g:title>Canon PowerShot SX740 HS Digital Camera With Optical Zoom</g:title>
      <g:description>This camera’s slim, compact body packs in a 40x zoom, and also features the DIGIC 8 image processor for enhanced image quality. With its short startup time and shooting interval, users can look forward to capturing unexpected photo opportunities. Also includes a variety of movie shooting functions such as 4K movies, 4K time lapse movies and the new Video Snapshot function. Quick, convenient Wi-Fi connection and smartphone pairing enables easy sharing of images and movies on social media. 40x optical zoom (24mm - 960mm) with 80x ZoomPlus 4K movie recording (including 4K time lapse movies and 4K Frame Grab) DIGIC 8 processor Wi-Fi/Bluetooth low energySpecificationsProduct Weight 299 gColour Name BlackOptical Zoom 20x to 49. 9xView Finder Type LCDSensor Type CMOSAutofocus YesProduct Length 39. 3 mmProduct Height 63. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 110 mmCamera Resolution 20. 3 MPModel Number PSSX740HSBKModel Name PowerShotZoom Yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cd4f4fed-5f3c-4ca3-b243-9ac48c045d52</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ddad9084-b7fc-4175-a219-6bbcebe00290/web/1_1736773007092.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>2849 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042096367957</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9822792441</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Smart TV, Crystal UHD, 75 Inch TV Backlight T2 Lighting, With Dual Cameras,</g:title>
      <g:description>Samsung 75" Crystal UHD DU8000 4K Tizen OS Smart TV (2024) 1. Dynamic Crystal Color 2. 4K Upscaling 3. Samsung Tizen OS Govee Envisual Technology: Zone-division capture scheme provides real-time color matching to enhance your visual experience Innovative Dual Camera Design: Upgraded dual camera design captures content 40% more accurately. Enhanced RGBIC Lighting: Double the light beads for more vivid and natural lighting Enhanced Music Mode: Choose between 4 modes (Energetic, Rhythm, Spectrum, Rolling) and energize your parties Unlock Home Theater Magic: Control your T2 TV Backlight using Alexa and Google AssistantSpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 4KProduct Weight 20 KGScreen Size 75 inRefresh Rates 50 HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System TizenWhat's In The Box TV, User Manual, Power Cable, Remote ControlViewing Distance 4. 1 mModel Year 2024Streaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 1676 mmProduct Height 960. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 26. 6 mmModel Number 75DU8000+6974316993087Number of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6e0f6faf-8bce-499a-bcf3-bea845face46</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9cdacc16-b42a-4839-a3f3-08aa06f2a1f0/web/1_1736771739949.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>4025 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098227924414</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5892483435</g:id>
      <g:title>Canon EOS 2000D Camera + EF-S 18-55mm IS II Lens (with Optical Image Stabilizer)</g:title>
      <g:description>EOS 2000D 18-55 IS--CANON DSLR EOS 2000D 24 Megapixels 3fps 18-55 IS Lens WiFi NFC Black. Self Timer - 2, 10, 10 sec +, Image Processor - DIGIC 4+, ISO Sensitivity - Auto (100-6400), Expandable Memory Type - SD/SDHC/SDXC Card, Viewing Angle - 170-DegreeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type CombinationProduct Weight 475 gScreen Size 2. 7 inColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box 1 x DSLRVideo Recording Resolution Type Full HDBattery Type Lithium IonWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantOptical Zoom Optical ZoomMagnifying Factor 20x and aboveView Finder Type OpticalSensor Type CMOSAutofocus YesNight Vision Lens YesCamera Zoom Type OpticalProduct Length 129 mmProduct Height 101. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 77. 7 mmCamera Resolution 24. 1 MPFeatures Wi-Fi enabled, Exposure Control, Wi-Fi enabled, Removable Memory Card, Wi-Fi enabledModel Number 2000DModel Name EOS 2000DItem Quantity 1Inbuilt Flash YesZoom YesInterchangeable Lens NoImage Stabilization YesMax Shutter Speed 30-1/4000 sec</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e68c1b63-cfc9-4437-ab28-fd1658f75393</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/70dd134d-92cb-4270-9211-87a999259248/web/1_1736772244067.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>1398 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058924834355</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
