<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>3012946735</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Watch 5 Active Midnight Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsExperience a vibrant 2. 0″ LCD display, ensuring crystal-clear visibility in any lighting conditions. Enjoy the convenience of Bluetooth calling, allowing seamless communication directly from your wrist. SpecificationsMaterial TPUColour Name Midnight BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 11. 4 mmFeatures Heart Rate Monitor, Sleep Monitor, SpO2 MonitorModel Number BHR8784GL, BHR8785INModel Name Redmi Watch 5 Active</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/25db6032-9145-4b1e-a4a5-a8304c1ada78</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5561cc31-f2e3-48c7-81d6-b3c88fe1de7e/web/1_1731144786108.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>117 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030129467354</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1121837941</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Camera C301 | 3MP with 2K Image Quality | MJA1 Security Chip | Voice Control | 8GB to 256GB microSD Supported | Cloud Storage</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights2K image quality, more reliable home protectionPhysical lens shielding protecting privacy at the sourceMJA1 security chip, finance-grade data protectionFully encrypted data transmission, AES-128 encryption for cloud data, and customisable sleep time. With 3MP and a resolution of 2304×1296, the camera displays 2K imagesLarge aperture and 4P lens delivering more vivid images360° Horizontal view 107° Vertical viewReal-time two-way voice callsLarge-diameter speaker for clear remote callsFull colour night vision for longer colour image timeEnhanced infrared night vision for clear images on dark nightsHuman detection and active alertOverviewPhysical lens shielding, protecting privacy at the source The camera lens can be hidden upwards into the body for physical shielding, ensuring security and peace of mind MJA1 security chip, finance-grade data protection Each chip has a unique key and credential, effectively ensuring data communication and storage security, and providing reassuring finance-grade protection. Fully encrypted to protect your privacy Fully encrypted data transmission, AES-128 encryption for cloud data, and customisable sleep time. 3MP ultra-clear visual experience With 3MP and a resolution of 2304x1296, the camera displays 2K images, providing more subtle details and more realistic visuals. Large aperture and 4P lens, delivering more vivid images Featuring a large aperture and 4P lens, the camera effectively reduces light refraction, delivering clear and crisp image quality that provides a transparent and lifelike viewing experience. Dual gimbals for flexible rotation, worry-free large viewing angle The dual-axis pan-tilt-zoom motor enables you to control the camera’s lens with your smartphone, allowing it to rotate in any direction—up, down, left, or right—for a wider viewing angle and a more secure viewing experience. Real-time two-way voice calls, remote communication with family Real-time two-way voice calls and a 5-meter sound pickup range allow you to chat with family anytime, anywhere. Large-diameter speaker for clear remote calls Using an embedded large-diameter speaker with a separate sound cavity and a microphone featuring intelligent noise cancellation, the camera provides a loud and clear voice during your remote calls with your family. Full colour night vision for longer colour image time With the assistance of the built-in high-sensitivity image sensor, the camera can better adapt to low-light environments and retain colour images for a long period of time. Enhanced infrared night vision for clear images on dark nights The camera has six built-in infrared illuminators and can capture clear images even on dark nights without producing red light or disturbing your family's sleep. Human detection and active alert The camera supports local AI-based human detection to detect humans more accurately and quickly without on-cloud processing. When someone is detected, the camera automatically sends an alert to your smartphone Easy to view Slide through the timeline to easily find and view videos. Voice control Work with Alexa or Google Assistant Support for flat and inverted mounting, suitable for multiple scenarios Thoughtful design for a seamless user experience Two storage options, choose as you like H. 265 encoding technology Save storage space and bandwidth with smooth video playbackSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 3 MPModel Number BHR8683GL | MBC23 | C301Model Name Xiaomi Smart Camera C301Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5b515ecd-886c-4f77-af45-b3a43e98a95f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b3fb941d-e909-470f-b391-ad15375bed7e/web/1_1731145152515.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>108.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011218379413</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3338492249</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mesh System AC1200 (2-pack) | 2.4GHz and 5GHz dual-band 1200Mbps |Covers up to 2,800 ft² /260 m² White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPrearranged kit pairing2. 4Ghz and 5GHz dual band supportCovers up to 2,800 ft² /260 m²Full Gigabit Ethernet portSleek and minimalistic designEffortless self-networkingOverviewAntenna: Internal Antennas Network Port: 2 x 10/100/1000Mbps WAN/LAN auto-sensing port Indicator: 1 Mesh/Reset Button: 1 Power Port: 1 Protocol Standards: IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab Bands: 2. 4GHz, 5GHz 2. 4GHz Wi-Fi: 300Mbps (802. 11ac) 5GHz Wi-Fi: 867Mbps (802. 11ac) Operating System: MiWi-Fi ROM Wi-Fi Encryption: WPA-PSK/WPA2-PSK/WPA3-SAE encryption Management Applications: Supports Web, Mi Home/Xiaomi Home App (Android, iOS) Operating Temperature: 0-40℃ Storage Temperature: -40-70℃ Operating Humidity: 10%-90%RH (non-condensing) Storage Humidity: 5%-90%RH (non-condensing) Product Dimensions: 8. 9 x 8. 9 x 15. 4cm (per unit)SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 9 KGColour Name WhiteSet Includes 2x mesh system, 1x power adapter, 1x network cable, 1x user manual, 1x warranty cardWireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard ACProduct Length 25. 8 cmProduct Height 9. 4 cmProduct Width/Depth 15. 9 cmFeatures App Enabled, Wireless AC, Wireless NModel Number DVB4451GL | RD13Model Name Xiaomi Mesh System AC1200 (2-pack)Wireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/171c1779-0cd6-45eb-940a-d1a2a2d3fffe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8cd06ea7-6c55-4fb5-b81e-beb90cc10c55/web/1_1731145424947.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033384922491</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3385602649</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W Portable Speaker Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEnjoy dynamic and powerful sound with transparent and balanced audio, thanks to its large mesh area design. Rich Bass: Dual large-size passive woofer radiators and exclusive woofer boost mode deliver fuller and richer bass for energetic sounds. Expertly tuned with dynamic equilibrium, smart volume balancing, and dynamic woofer extension for superior audio. Up to 12 hours of uninterrupted playback on a full charge, with Type-C 15W fast charging support for extended enjoyment. Sleek and Portable Design: Curved lightweight body design makes it easy to hold and carry, perfect for music enjoyment anywhere. Dust and Water Resistance: IP67-rated protection ensures reliable performance outdoors in any weather condition. Bluetooth 5. 4: Faster and more stable connection for lossless audio quality. TWS Stereo Combo: Connect two identical speakers for superior immersive sound experiences in smart stereo mode. Hands-Free Calling: Answer calls with a single tap for clear and crisp hands-free conversations while multitasking. OverviewXiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W Portable SpeakerSpecificationsProduct Weight 730 gColour Name RedConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life 6 HoursProduct Length 9. 2 cmProduct Height 18 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 1 cmModel Number 30W SpeakerModel Name 30W Speaker</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/46836351-ba1f-4947-8559-e2f5b61c72b6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6c70b9ed-c85e-4c66-9aab-bd0524b4521b/web/1_1731145857914.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033856026498</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6942347842</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi AX3000T 2.4GHz/5GHz Dual-band 1.3GHz CPU Router Supports NFC Connection White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsStandards and protocols: Wireless network connection 802. 11gSupports 2. 4GHz and 5GHz frequencies, enjoy faster and more stable Internet speedsHigh-performance CPU and WAN LED provide better and more reliable internet connection, ideal for use at home and officeSet up your router quickly and easily using NFC connectivity, making it easy and secure without complex passwords or codesThe router supports Wi-Fi 802. 11g standard and protocol to ensure you get the best Internet connection and speed1. 3GHz CPU ensures smooth and seamless performance, perfect for gaming and streamingNFC connectivity allows easy and secure access to the internetFull-power WiFi 6 covers multiple rooms, doubles throughput, and extremely fast Internet speedOverview*Xiaomi Router AX3000T has four antennae, including one for 2. 4G+5G frequencies, two for 5G signals, and one for 2. 4G signals. *Xiaomi Router AX3000T product images on the page are for illustrative purposes only. Actual use requires connecting with a power cord and a network cable. *The data for the power supply stability test, hardware structural reliability test, memory stress test, multiple device simultaneous connection test, harsh environment test, and flash memory reliability test are from the Xiaomi Internal Lab Routing Reliability Test Report *The content and features shown on the above pages cannot be guaranteed to remain permanent and may change due to changes in copyright, commercial, or technical conditions. In case of any changes without individual notification, please refer to the actual contents and features of the product. *Product images, models, data, features, performance, specifications, user interface, and other product information may change depending on factors such as product batches or supplier replacements. Xiaomi may modify the above content. Please refer to the actual product and product manual for specific information. *The data comparison regarding signal coverage area is based on the Mi Router 4A Gigabit Edition. Data involved in comparison are sourced from Xiaomi Internal Lab. Actual user experience may vary depending on factors such as wall materials, house layout and size, and environmental interference. *Unless otherwise indicated, the comparisons mentioned on this page were made with Xiaomi products. Information on this page comes from our internal lab data, design and technology parameters, and data provided by vendors. Actual data may differ slightly depending on the test software version, the specific test environment, the specific version, and industry measurement methods. SpecificationsProduct Weight 1. 5 KGColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Dual BandWireless Standard NProduct Length 9. 7 cmProduct Height 22. 2 cmProduct Width/Depth 9. 7 cmModel Number RD23Model Name AX3000TItem Quantity 1Wireless Standard Value NView Full Overview</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/97c647d0-fa2d-4440-ac90-4e56be629675</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1b3c5bab-6801-4180-9963-c487723ecde6/web/1_1731145655374.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>187 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069423478421</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2262073908</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Xiaomi Sound Pocket Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsImmersive Sound with 5W outputPortable Pocket designSupport Bluetooth 5. 4Upto 10 hours long lasting batteryTrue Wireless Stereo SoundIP67 rated dust and water resistanceFashionable and more personalisedRubber anti loss lanyardSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 1000 mAhProduct Weight 200 gColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothAverage Battery Life 10 HoursWhat's In The Box Xiaomi Sound Pocket x1 Charging cable x1 User manual x1Product Length 90. 8 mmProduct Height 74. 4 mmProduct Width/Depth 42. 6 mmFeatures Bluetooth, Water ResistantModel Number MDZ-37-DBModel Name Xiaomi Sound PocketItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/97839f25-06bc-4fbd-aa59-926f3983af57</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5e741136-4b6e-43c5-bcf4-70f3a614f0c9/web/1_1731146280534.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>81.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022620739085</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2738080293</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI B320-323 - 4G Router, WiFi 4, Unlocked Supports All SIM Cards & Networks, White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHUAWEI 4G CPE 5s keeps the signal rapid, raring, and ready to go, whether it's your apartment, office, shop—or somewhere else!Plug-and-play Wi-Fi has never been so easy! Just insert a nano-SIM card and power on the device, to get connected without the hassle of broadband or network cables!Whether you're conferencing, streaming, downloading, or simply surfing the web, this mobile router makes everything seamless. HUAWEI 4G CPE 5s is powered by High Power User Equipment (HPUE). This ensures that the signal remains robust even in rural, mountainous, and industrial areas, and underground parking garages. HUAWEI 4G CPE 5s connects with up to 32 devices at the same time,4 so that everyone can watch, listen, game, and browse to their heart's contentSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFi 4Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard 4GModel Number B320-323Model Name B320-323Wireless Standard Value 300</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ac6d79a3-aad0-4909-89e8-8940dc8f2edf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5d3d1e26-0661-40b9-aa63-3f6d9586dae2/web/1_1731147044308.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>223 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027380802932</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2316391364</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Outdoor Camera CW300 EU | 2.5K Ultra-Xlear Picture Quality 4MP | IP66 Water And Dust Resistant | AI Human Tracking | Two-Way Intercom | White</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights2. 5K ultra-clear picture quality, smart security in any weather 4MPSmart full-color night visionBidirectional gimbal movementIP66 water and dust resistantAI Human TrackingAudible and visual alarmTwo-way IntercomWired + Wi-Fi dual networkMJA1 security chipOverviewUltra-clear picture quality Amazing details even zoomed in The 4MP camera with the f/1. 6 large aperture lens presents 2. 5K ultra-clear picture quality, offering a clearer and finer image when you zoom in for more details. Four full-color night vision LEDs Achieve clear visibility at night The camera comes with a white light that automatically lights up at night when it recognizes a human figure, providing a colored image in dark surroundings. Horizontal and vertical gimbals Greater viewing angle for more peace of mind The dual-motor pan-tilt zoom design allows users to rotate the lens in all directions via their smartphone, allowing for a larger viewing angle as well as more flexible and reassuring protection. Professional IP66 water and dust resistant design No fear of adverse weather conditions The IP66 water and dust resistance rating enables stable performance in adverse weather conditions. Human detection supported Automatic notification when someone approaches The camera uses a next-generation local AI human-detection algorithm to detect humans more accurately and faster, no cloud needed. When a person is detected, the camera automatically records alert videos and sends notifications to your smartphone. Track a human body as it moves The camera intelligently tracks human movement. When someone is detected and locked on to, it automatically tracks and records videos of the person as they move and sends notifications to your smartphone. Audible and visual alarm for active defense With alarm notifications sent to your smartphone When the camera detects someone in the monitoring area, it will automatically trigger an audible alarm with high-frequency flashing lights to drive away potential intruders. It will also simultaneously send an alarm message to Mi Home/Xiaomi Home app. Two-way voice calling Handle noisy outdoor environments with ease The camera comes with a built-in high-sensitivity microphone and high-quality high-power speaker, boosted with an AI noise cancellation algorithm. The long pickup range ensures loud and clear sound even under complex outdoor conditions. Voice Control Voice control works with Amazon Alexa or Google Assistant Wired + Wi-Fi dual network Say goodbye to lag 2. 4GHz Wi-Fi network supported. The camera also comes with a built-in Ethernet port so you can choose your preferred connection method. The connection is more stable, reducing connection disruptions and providing a smooth user experience. Hardware-level protection Your privacy is safe Each built-in MJA1 security chip is provided with a unique key and credential to effectively protect the data communication and privacy of users with financial-grade security measuresSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 4 MPModel Number CW300 | BHR8097EU | BHR8095GBModel Name Xiaomi Outdoor Camera CW300</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d0f94f8e-23dc-43f4-bf03-c8b5124b82de</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/02c80161-a651-436c-9438-5edf60bc503e/web/1_1731147443808.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>190 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023163913642</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2831876596</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI Band 9 Smart Watch, Ultra-Thin Design And Comfortable Wearing, Scientific Sleep Analysis, Durable Battery Life, IOS And Android Starry Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra design: 1. 47 Inch amoled screen, 8. 99mm thin, 14g weightScientific sleep tracking: Upgraded sleep efficiency analysis, and sleep basic physiological analysisFast charging, durable battery life: 45 minutes to fully charge, 5 minutes fast charge can be used for 2 days. Maximum 2-week battery life, 9 days of normal useCustomized workout types: Huawei band 9 offers a multitude of workouts that you can customize as requiredCompatible with android and iOSOverviewHUAWEI Band 9 is a brand new, high-end sports band which has a full-sized color touchscreen, side button control, and is water resistant to 50 meters. This smart wearable product integrates a wide range of features, including workout detection, smart heart rate monitoring, workout assistant, multiple workout modes, sleep monitoring, message notifications, automatic SpO2 measurement, and music playback control. SpecificationsMaterial FluoroelastomerBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 14 gColour Name Starry BlackBand Material FluoroelastomerDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDFace/Dial Shape RectangularBand Size Medium/LargeProduct Length 43 mmProduct Height 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 25 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 47 inModel Number KIM-B19Model Name Huawei Band 9</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4a05b3a2-c07b-46ae-9d8b-470221e969d7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/89104710-6415-424a-ada8-36dd697d8e8a/web/8_1731148045481.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028318765961</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4046257300</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 34 inch MI Curved Gaming Monitor (G34WQ) 1ms Fast Response 21:9 180Hz High Refresh Rate 1500R Curvature WQHD 3440x1440 Resolution sRGB Wide Colour Gamut Free-Sync (DP x2, HDMI x2, Audio Port x1, DC IN x1) Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights95% DCI-P3 wide color gamut1ms rapid response180Hz high refresh rate34 inch large screenRGB ambient light, esports appearanceSpecificationsScreen Size 34 inDisplay Resolution 3440x1440Screen Features High Refresh RateRefresh Rates 180HzMonitor response time Upto 1 msColour Name BlackDisplay Type OLEDAdaptive Sync Technology V-SyncWattage 24 WModel Number G34WQNumber of HDMI Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b3a49da7-4a4f-4749-a511-37c0eae11ad4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2db0e644-86f3-4fff-9d0c-f330b60e3ad3/web/1_1731148704092.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>944 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040462573001</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3080897877</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 4 Active White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsType-C charging portUp to 28 hours listeningSupport low latency modeGoogle fast pairMade of plastic materialOverview12mm dynamic driver - Experience powerful bass: The 12mm dynamic driver is even larger than before. With expert tuning by the Xiaomi Acoustic Lab, it delivers enhanced bass and heightened acoustics, providing a pleasing listening experience for users worldwide. Noise cancellation for calls - Outstanding performance in noisy environments: Each earbud comes equipped with a high-sensitivity microphone that leverages to mitigate ambient background noise interruptions, ensuring optimal clarity of speech for effective communication even in noisy environments. 28-hour ultra-long battery life - Let good music keep you company longer: The earbuds’ battery life lasts up to 5 hours on a single charge and up to 28 hours* with the portable charging case, so you can enjoy great music day and night. Bluetooth 5. 3 - Fully upgraded: The earbuds are now equipped with the latest Bluetooth 5. 3 technology, which allows for reduced power consumption, greater signal stability, and stronger resistance to interference. Even when surrounded by multiple devices, it still provides reliable transmission without any interference. Low-latency mode - Smooth gaming experience: With Bluetooth 5. 3, you can easily initiate low-latency mode for an immersive gaming experience with exceptional precision. Ensuring you don't miss any crucial moments in the game and enabling you to efficiently control it with accuracy. Touch control - Control from anywhere: The touch control operations* allow you to smoothly and easily switch between different modes using light touches. ENC: Enjoy crystal-clear conversations even in noisy environments, as the powerful mic captures your voice with remarkable clarity while Environmental Noise Cancellation (ENC) actively reduces background noise for an uninterrupted and immersive calling experience. Stay connected and communicate effortlessly with our premium audio solution. IPX4: Designed to withstand the elements, our Redmi Buds 4 Active are built with an IPX4 rating, providing reliable protection against water splashes and sweat. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteDepartment UnisexConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type In-EarFeatures BluetoothModel Number BHR8000GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/05d27c6e-00c9-4ac6-ad96-9a49cbe14118</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cdd74ef0-aeb0-4dc9-9057-53128de35c00/web/1_1731149346156.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>58.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030808978775</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1466485721</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi TV A Pro 32 Inch HD Smart LED Google TV With 360° Bluetooth Remote Control Chromecast Built-In L32M8-A2ME Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPremium metallic frame with bezel-less design32" HD smart LED TV, Google TVGoogle Assistant built-in, Smart home control hub, Chromecast built-in, Supports MiracastNetflix, Prime Video and Youtube pre-installed. Thousands of apps available in Google PlaySpeaker (Sound Output) 2 × 10W, Supports Dolby Audio™, DTS-X and DTS® Virtual: X SoundOverviewThe ultra-narrow bezel design provides a high screen-to-body ratio far beyond that of standard TVs. From the instant you turn on the TV, high-resolution images in stunning colors blanket the screen for an immersive experience. Featuring an exquisite metallic frame with a unibody design, Xiaomi A Pro Series makes a real statement in any home. The 2 × 10W high-power stereo speakers fill the room with rich high and bass tones and provide an immersive sound experience. Google TV™ brings together movies, shows, and more from across your apps and subscriptions and organizes them just for you. Discover new things to watch with recommendations based on what you watch and what interests you, from across your subscriptions and content available to you. Your TV is more helpful than ever. Ask Google to find movies, stream apps, play music, and control the TV - all with your voice. Even get answers, control smart home devices, and more. Just say "Ok Google" or press the Google Assistant button on the remote to get started. Easily control your smart TV with the 360° Bluetooth remote control. The Chromecast built-in™* and Miracast allow you to continue watching what's on your smart mobile devices on a bigger screen, elevating your visual experience. The powerful quad-core A55 CPU combined with 1. 5GB RAM + 8GB ROM* offers smoother operation and more space for your favourite apps. Designed with a 2. 4GHz/5GHz Wi-Fi solution, various commonly used ports and Bluetooth 5. 0 to easily connect to different devices and adapt to more audio and video entertainment scenarios,SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 1080pInternal Memory 8 GBProduct Weight 3. 9 KGScreen Size 32 inRefresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System Google TVWhat's In The Box 60° bluetooth remote control × 1 Screws bag × 1 Stand × 2 Power cable × 1 User manual × 1 Warranty card × 1Number of Cores Quad CoreViewing Distance 1. 7 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 715. 7 mmProduct Height 423. 7 mmProduct Width/Depth 82. 5 mmFeatures Smart TV, Wi-Fi, AndroidModel Number L32M8-A2MEModel Name Xiaomi TV A Pro 32"Number of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c6ab1113-073b-4617-a4a2-3d4a8b41cee7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/95ff79f9-6d20-4afc-a490-371b9a1007a9/web/1_1731149110772.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>649 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014664857214</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1058835146</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 5 | Bluetooth Wireless Earbuds With Active Noise Cancellation | Bluetooth 5.3 | Up To 40 Hour Battery | Multi-Functional Touch Control Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRedmi Buds 5 has a noise reduction depth of 46dB, which is 11dB higher than Redmi Buds 4. And the noise reduction effect has been improved to 3. 5 times. Up to 99. 5% reduction in background noiseSupport broadband noise reduction at 2000Hz, covering more low-frequency scenes in daily lifeSupports three gear noise reduction and transparency mode adjustment, allowing for comfortable gear selection in different environmentsSupporting call anti wind noise function, Redmi adopts Xiaomi's self-developed AI anti wind noise algorithm for the first time, which can withstand wind speeds up to 6m/sIndependent rear chamber structure design, four sound effects settingsSingle 10 hours battery life for full day useEquipped with a charging box, the 40 hours battery life for one week useEquipped with super-fast charging, charging for 5 minutes and listening to music for 2 hoursSupport for Google Fast pair, dual device connectivitySpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type On-EarModel Number M2316E1 | BHR7627GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/13d04268-5bd9-4c76-bc48-32c845fb3e66</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eeaa97c8-3592-4f05-9b2a-57469f1c2f8c/web/1_1731149707391.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>110 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010588351463</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8078759520</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Band 8 Pro, High-Resolution Large 1.74" AMOLED Display Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1. 74”AMOLED screen,60Hz high refresh rate,336PPICorning GG3 cover glass, more solid compare to 7proSupport ambient light sensor that allow the display brightness to automatically adjust for your eyes4-channel monitoring channel(Increase heart rate accuracy by 10% and blood oxygen accuracy by 5%)All-day SpO2 level tracking, continuous sleep monitoring, 24-hours heart rate monitoring, and sleep breathing monitoring150+ workout modes to record your heart rate and burned calories. 10 on-wrist running courses, could vibrate and light the screen to remind you to meet your heart rate and pace goals. 3D warm up and Relaxation Private Education CoursesBuilt-in GNSS Support independent GNSS, supporting 5-star positioning system: Beidou, GPS, GLONASS, Galileo, qzss. Up to 14-day battery lifeSupport 14 days daily use and 6 days AOD use. 5ATM water resistanceSupports 50 meter deep waterproofingOverviewXiaomi Smart Band 8 Pro Black, 1. 74”AMOLED screen,60Hz high refresh rate,150+ workout modes to record your heart rate and burned calories, Updated ID apperance, metallic frame that coated with NCVM, Support 14 days daily use and 6 days AOD use, Supports 50 meter deep waterproofingSpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 74 inModel Number BHR8017GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/634af246-9818-4dc0-81f2-d3dc50fe231b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/91444105-f1d3-4d38-9470-be5caac32f2f/web/1_1731149512212.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>248 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080787595203</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3270171807</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Watch 4 | 1.97″ AMOLED Display | Supports Bluetooth Calling | Aluminum Alloy Frame | Up To 20 Days Battery Life Obsidian Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra large 1. 97″ AMOLED display, LTPS 5Hz / 60Hz refresh rateExquisite aluminum alloy frameUp to 20 days long battery lifeSupports Bluetooth CallingSupports 5-system GNSSAdvance health and workout trackingOverviewRedmi Watch 4 adopts a sturdy and reliable aluminum alloy frame for the first time for a more elevated design feel. Make a fashion statement with two available color options. The exquisite stainless-steel rotating crown adds high-end finesse to even the smallest details and its gentle spin gives a more comfortable experience. Upgraded next-gen quick-release structure makes strap replacement easier. Diverse strap options mean you can switch up your style on a whim. Discover our extensive range of chic watch faces to match your unique style. Featuring a variety of fun watch faces and customizable components, style and functionality are yours to command. Outfitted with a sizeable battery and an energy-efficient chip optimized for longevity. Enjoy a 20-day extra-long battery life in typical usage mode. Portable magnetic charging lets you power up with a simple touch, for worry-free use. Redmi Watch 4 connects to your smartphone via Bluetooth, allowing you to view and reject calls on your watch, and engage in conversations with the built-in microphone and speaker without the need to take out your smartphone. With the help of scientific, meticulous sleep monitoring technologies, the watch records your real-time sleep condition at different stages, such as deep sleep, light sleep and REM, improving your sleeping habits and quality. Blood oxygen saturation monitoring throughout the day. Sends vibration alerts when blood oxygen saturation is too low. Heart rate monitoring throughout the day. Continuous and precise heart rate monitoring safeguards your cardiovascular health at all times. Stress monitoring Breathing exercise prompts will be sent when your stress level reaches 80 twice in a row during your awake time. SpecificationsMaterial Aluminium AlloyColour Name Obsidian BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 97 inModel Number BHR7854GL | M2315W1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0757f38a-8abd-4979-8f5c-abd12d78f364</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eebb6c0a-5099-4dac-8265-0b2079d324e4/web/1_1731149924729.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032701718076</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7286731004</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 13C Dual SIM Glacier White 6GB RAM 128GB 4G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPowerful mediatek helio G85Smooth 6. 74 inch 90Hz display50MP AI triple cameraSupport 18W fast chargingSpecificationsSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 74 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Glacier WhiteCondition NewModel Number 2311DRN14I | 23106RN0DAModel Name Redmi 13C</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bf671a7f-370c-48f2-bde1-eb53d46d67bd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8193f96d-e706-494a-a3b0-7a83d216d987/web/1_1731150122294.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>398 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0072867310042</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6895394310</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi WiFi Range Extender N300 | 2x2 External Antenna | Easy Setup | 300Mbps White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBoost your wireless network2×2 external antenna, with a transmission rate of up to 300mbpsSupport up to 16 devices connected simultaneouslySpecificationsColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Single BandWireless Standard NModel Number RD10/RD10M | DVB4398GLWireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11b/g/n</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/279c1a44-a187-40cf-8efb-dc76dfb48e22</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/718c5a8f-4455-4dda-a896-1183c466dc15/web/1_1731149848071.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>38.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068953943102</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9346784763</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Monitor A22i | FHD | 75Hz Refresh Rate | 8-Bit Color Depth 99% SRGB Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFull hd screen with wide viewing angle and stunning experienceAccurate color reproduction with 99% sRGB coverage and 8-bit color depthHigh brightness 250 alloy to withstand strong lighting conditionsSmooth visual with 75Hz refresh speed for a smooth movement lookEye protection with low blue light mode and tuv certificationVersatile connectivity options with hdmi and vga interfacesAdjustable stand for personalized viewing angle and wall-mount compatibility (75x75mm VESA mount, additional purchase required)SpecificationsScreen Size 21. 45 inDisplay Resolution 1080x1920Screen Features Low Blue LightRefresh Rates 75HzMonitor response time 16 ms &amp;amp; AboveColour Name BlackDisplay Type FHDAdaptive Sync Technology NoneWattage 24 WModel Number A22FAB-RAGL | A22iNumber of HDMI Ports 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/adca0ad9-6617-4049-8359-20f98ba0a292</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9b323010-b532-49b2-98dc-bc58e736aad5/web/1_1731152299571.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>264 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093467847639</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2324265964</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI AX3 AX3000 (WS7100) Dual Band Wi-Fi Router, Dual-core Wi-Fi 6 Plus Revolution, Wi-Fi Speed up to 3000 Mbps, Supports Access Point Mode, Parental Control, Guest Wi-Fi white</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsOffers ample space to store all your essentialsMade of durable quality materialIt is accented with gold-tone detailingSpecificationsColour Name whiteWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Dual BandWireless Standard AXMax Data Transfer Rate 2. 4 GbpsModel Number 53038507Model Name 53038507</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9d239fbd-a128-4380-bef2-2daadcbaa15d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/587e0590-2d97-4127-84bc-1e0ad79e31b8/web/1_1731152744331.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>177 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023242659645</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1048987925</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Band 8 Gold</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay 1. 62 display resolution 192 x 490200+ Custom watch facesHeart rate and sleep monitoring150+ Workout modesUp to 16 days battery lifeBluetooth 5. 1 BLE connectivityOverviewXiaomi Smart Band 8 has been upgraded with Easy-detachable Straps that not only allow you to easily switch between different strap designs and materials, but also allows you to remove the strap entirely. The elegant body features a stylish metallic finish, now available in two new midframe colours: Champagne Gold and Graphite Black. A higher refresh rate delivers a super smooth experience, with eye-catching operation and swipe motions. Stepless automatic brightness adjustment with precise adaptation to the ambient brightness. Whenever you raise your wrist, the brightness will adjust to the perfect level that is also gentle on your eyes. SpecificationsColour Name GoldBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Model Number BHR7166GL/CI51440Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a5b0fe53-7c84-4c84-a98a-e4200ea1755f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3e426151-7110-4873-b3b2-d42187f716b7/web/1_1731152453857.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>116 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010489879257</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7315448508</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 4 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHybrid active noise cancellation brings you closer to the musicDual transparency mode keeps you connected to your surroundingsUp to 35dB hybrid active noise cancellation3 ANC level options and adaptive ANC modeAI noise reductionDual transparency mode10mm dynamic driver unit, 0. 006mm ultra-thin diaphragmUp to 30 hours long battery life with caseSpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number M2137E1/47554/BUDS4</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c2ef0175-5fe9-4731-87a1-8ff5eca5d21e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2a072877-c19c-4149-8f73-af961a52a821/web/1_1731152520837.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073154485085</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4502166656</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 4 Active Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsType-C charging portUp to 28 hours listeningSupport low latency modeGoogle fast pairMade of plastic materialOverview12mm dynamic driver - Experience powerful bass: The 12mm dynamic driver is even larger than before. With expert tuning by the Xiaomi Acoustic Lab, it delivers enhanced bass and heightened acoustics, providing a pleasing listening experience for users worldwide. Noise cancellation for calls - Outstanding performance in noisy environments: Each earbud comes equipped with a high-sensitivity microphone that leverages to mitigate ambient background noise interruptions, ensuring optimal clarity of speech for effective communication even in noisy environments. 28-hour ultra-long battery life - Let good music keep you company longer: The earbuds’ battery life lasts up to 5 hours on a single charge and up to 28 hours* with the portable charging case, so you can enjoy great music day and night. Bluetooth 5. 3 - Fully upgraded: The earbuds are now equipped with the latest Bluetooth 5. 3 technology, which allows for reduced power consumption, greater signal stability, and stronger resistance to interference. Even when surrounded by multiple devices, it still provides reliable transmission without any interference. Low-latency mode - Smooth gaming experience: With Bluetooth 5. 3, you can easily initiate low-latency mode for an immersive gaming experience with exceptional precision. Ensuring you don't miss any crucial moments in the game and enabling you to efficiently control it with accuracy. Touch control - Control from anywhere: The touch control operations* allow you to smoothly and easily switch between different modes using light touches. ENC: Enjoy crystal-clear conversations even in noisy environments, as the powerful mic captures your voice with remarkable clarity while Environmental Noise Cancellation (ENC) actively reduces background noise for an uninterrupted and immersive calling experience. Stay connected and communicate effortlessly with our premium audio solution. IPX4: Designed to withstand the elements, our Redmi Buds 4 Active are built with an IPX4 rating, providing reliable protection against water splashes and sweat. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CColour Name BlackDepartment UnisexConnection Type USB Type CAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type On-EarCharging Case Type WirelessFeatures BluetoothModel Number BHR6992GL / M2232E1Model Name BHR6992GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0a95793a-a32f-46d5-9026-bb486a2ed0d7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eec87d3f-39f8-4690-9ab2-969a0d1cf497/web/1_1731152849227.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045021666569</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9584389787</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi AX3200 High-Speed Performance Wi-Fi 6 802.11ax Wireless Frequency Dual-band Wi-Fi Offers Both 2.4GHz and 5GHz Swift Wireless Speed Up to 2976Mbps Reliable Connection For Up to 254 Devices Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFast 3202Mbps Wi-Fi 6*ultra-fast wireless experienceMesh networking support. Seamless, whole-home Wi-Fi 6 coverageOFDMA Multi-device transmission with less congestionSupports 4x4 MU-MIMO multiple antennas on the router to serve multiple devicesSpecificationsColour Name BlackWireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard 5GModel Number AX3200/DVB4314GLModel Name AX3200/DVB4314GLWireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac/ax，IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/04df9cc1-0e64-41e2-a0f5-f6336ae1207a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9c24e899-939d-4842-8ffe-8908f96ec0f0/web/1_1731153000573.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>188 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095843897870</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1957270415</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Smart Band 8 Chinese Version Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBattery: 190mAh Battery capacity, up to 16 days charging time approximately 1 hoursWater resistance: 5Atm has a water resistance of up to 50mActivity tracking: Calculate steps, distance, calories burned, female health monitor, blood oxygenHealth monitoring: 24-Hour heart rate monitoringSensor: Six axis accelerometer, six axis gyroscopeSpecificationsColour Name BlackBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Model Number Smart Band 8Model Name Smart Band 8Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b321b4ed-1dc5-418f-a1c5-c3ea77266ccd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/216bb99c-164b-4cd0-ab1e-93f28208291d/web/1_1731153386042.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>116 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019572704155</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5210990175</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 33W Charging Combo Type A White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmart device identification. AC 100-240V wide range voltageAutomatic power adjustmentEnhanced safetySpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number 40038Model Name 40038Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/26572d53-f766-44f3-ba9a-6c97988cf037</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3e9f297d-8498-4b77-a0c1-581727c880c9/web/1_1731154295807.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052109901757</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9678132806</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 65W GaN Charger Type-A And Type-C White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFits in the palm of your handType-C 65W maxDual port fast chargingGaN gallium nitride smaller, lighter, more efficientSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number 40095Model Name 40095Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c3d08e0c-b2c5-44df-a7e0-884282f874c8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4db2b55a-2070-40f6-9cfe-2b81af3a9a27/web/1_1731154150975.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>109 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096781328068</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4890583531</g:id>
      <g:title>Nothing Ear Stick White</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewNothing Ear (stick) - Wireless Half In-Ear Earbuds, Bass Lock Technology, Bluetooth 5. 2, Waterproof, White. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 36 mAhProduct Weight 54. 6 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessAverage Battery Life Less than 8 hrsUsage Type Business (Call/work)What's In The Box 1. TWS set (a pair of earbuds and 1 charging case. ) 2. Type-C to Type-C cable 3. User guide 4. Safety and Warranty informationAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WiredEarplug Type EarbudsProduct Length 88 mmProduct Height 30 mmFeatures Bluetooth, Volume Control, Water ResistantModel Number B157Model Name B157Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/360049c9-1af5-465a-95b1-ac4881da4f43</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b1601ca2-c24d-4cc5-9ed5-ad97abce14a0/web/1_1731154719948.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048905835310</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6495405437</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi MI AX9000 9000MBPS Enhanced Version TRI-BAND WIFI6 Router Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsQualcomm IPQ8072 Quad-Core A53 2. 2GHz CPU,Dual-Core 1. 7GHz NPU,1GB RAM, 2. 4G Wi-Fi: 4x4 (IEEE802. 11ax 1148Mbps), 5. 2G Wi-Fi:4x4(IEEE802. 11ax 4804Mbps), 5. 8G Wi-Fi: 4x4(IEEE802. 11ax 2402Mbps)Antenna External High Gain Antenna External AIOT Antenna Heat Dissipation: Active Heat DissipationFrom The Physical Interface:1* 10/100/1000 WAN/LAN (Auto MDI / MDIX),1* 10/100/1000 WAN/LAN (Auto MDI / MDIX), 3* 10/100/1000LAN(Auto MDI / MDIX)Wireless Channel2. 4GHz Channel:1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13/ 5. 2GHz: Channel:36,40,44,48,52,56,60,64/ 5. 8GHz Channel:149,153,157,161,165Operating System: MI WIFI ROM, an intelligent router operating system deeply customized based on Open WRTSpecificationsColour Name BlackWireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Tri BandWireless Standard 5GModel Number AX9000Model Name AX9000Wireless Standard Value 802. 11</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8b7e939a-4272-41db-bf4f-73e82d785378</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7cf00f79-3966-4fbe-9795-c8f17227a15e/web/1_1731156206355.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>759 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064954054373</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4399162773</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Poco M4 Dual SIM Power Black 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 58 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Colour Name Power BlackDisplay Type IPS LCDOperating System Version Android 11Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 11Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile, chargerNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2022Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 128 GBModel Number 22041219PGModel Name POCO M4 5GPrimary Camera (MP) 13+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/561d143d-5ca9-447b-b170-952dfa7f8f87</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d237ac8e-627a-40b3-aafc-8fa3b8f4875b/web/1_1731156006342.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>494 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043991627733</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6360364969</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Band 7 Pro Smart Bracelet AMOLED Screen GPS Blood Oxygen Fitness Waterproof Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsBand 7 Pro Smart Bracelet AMOLED Screen GPS Blood Oxygen Fitness WaterproofWrist Voice Assistant Xiao AIQuick Call Reply5 ATM WaterproofOverviewMassive 1. 64" rectangle AMOLED display: For the first time, the band features a large, full-color rectangular display. The layout of all features on the band display is similar to that of a smartphone. Text and icons own more space and become much easier to tap and swipe. Xiaomi Smart Band 7 Pro can be seen as a convenient extension of your smartphone. More open interface, more open-minded, Xiaomi Smart Band 7 Pro: With a brand new display, each feature now has a fresh look, simply presented and easy to understand at a glance. Xiaomi Smart Band 7 Pro: 150+ watch faces ready for you to show off Always-on display is gentle on your eyes. Refined, stylish, sporty. Find the perfect display to fit your mood. No need to raise your arm to light up the display. Adaptive display brightness to comfortably shine: Ambient light sensors allow the band display to automatically adjust for your eyes. Every time you raise your wrist, it lights up just right. The beauty is in the details, Designed to be glamorous: This is the first Xiaomi smart band to be available in metallics, graphite grey and light gold for a subtle classiness. Coated with NCVM for lightness and comfort. Smooth to the touch, with a high-gloss metal texture. A complete selection of customisable straps: With six classic colours, you can be elegantly understated or loud and vibrant — it's up to you. Make a statement, starting from your wrist. The strap has a easy to do clip which is practical for maximum convenience. Designed to make running a breeze, With satellite positioning and movement tracking: Built-in GNSS can be synced to your phone or used solo for minimalist workouts, Support BeiDou, GPS, GLONASS, Galileo and QZSS systems. Count every step, because every step counts. Professional training starts anytime, anywhere, On-wrist running courses:10 pre-loaded running courses of varying intensity, calculated via time and heart rate. The band can vibrate and light the screen to remind you to meet your heart rate and speed goals, making sure that you get the most out of your workout. SpecificationsMaterial PolyurethaneColour Name BlackConnection Type GPSWhat's In The Box SmartwatchSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 64 inFeatures Water ResistantModel Number Band 7 Pro Black (M2141B1)Model Name Band 7 Pro BlackItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/161a0f3e-628a-4547-96a1-46dfadc4dd2d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/603531ad-a473-4be3-af90-77a0452fccb4/web/1_1731156086396.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>219 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063603649694</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9967075212</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 86-Inch Ultra-HD 4K Smart Android TV 11 With 120Hz Refresh Rate | 178 Degrees Angle | 3D Sount Effects Dolby Atmos Supports Google Voice Assistant, Chromecast Built-In | Xiaomi TV Max 86" Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsXiaomi TV Max 86" features ultra-large 86" and full-screen display, ultra-high screen-to-body ratio, wide viewing area and 4K ultra HD resolution, bringing you a cinematic experience at home120Hz ultra-high refresh rate coupled with 4K 120Hz MEMC (Motion Estimation and Motion Compensation) technology enables millisecond-level frame interpolation, delivering stutter-free images of high-speed scenesThe Full-Array Local dimming backlighting system has multiple zones, which allows the large display to have better control over light and shade, rendering images with more layersOverviewUltra-large 86" display. Xiaomi TV Max 86" features ultra-large 86" and full-screen display, ultra-high screen-to-body ratio, wide viewing area and 4K ultra HD resolution, bringing you a cinematic experience at home. Dual 120Hz For a refreshing viewing experience. 120Hz ultra-high refresh rate coupled with 4K 120Hz MEMC (Motion Estimation and Motion Compensation) technology enables millisecond-level frame interpolation, delivering stutter-free images of high-speed scenes. Your viewing experience is greatly improved whether you watch a sporting event, an action film or play a competitive video game. Full-Array Local dimming Stunning contrast. The Full-Array Local dimming backlighting system has multiple zones, which allows the large display to have better control over light and shade, rendering images with more layers. 1. 07 billion colors* DCI-P3 restores the true colour of films. Adopting the cinema-level DCI-P3 wide color gamut, Xiaomi TV Max 86" can rendering accurate colors just as the film director intended. With 1. 07 billion color depth, the image looks smoother than ever between color transitions. HDMI 2. 1 Smooth video gaming experience. With the new HDMI 2. 1 port, you can connect your TV to the game consoles for a 4K 120Hz ultra-high quality transmission of images. Featured by low latency and high-speed response, the TV brings additional fun to the family. Dolby Vision HDR transforms your TV experience with an ultra vivid picture that brings entertainment to life, and with Dolby Vision IQ, it leverages the full intelligence of your TV to deliver a perfect picture in your room at every moment. Speaker system with 4 drivers. Superior audio experience. The speaker system with 4 drivers and air-duct bass boost design make sounds played out from the TV richer and more powerful, providing more immersive audio experience. The TV has a powerful quad-core A73 CPU and 3GB RAM + 32GB ROM, which can process multiple tasks simultaneously and high-frame-rate images with ease. Wi-Fi 6 For next generation network connections. The TV is among the first to support the next-generation Wi-Fi 6, or IEEE P 802. 11ax protocol. With the higher network bandwidth, the TV can significantly increase the transmission efficiency and network environment*Feel free to pick your favourites from more than 400,000 films and TV shows* or download from over 7,000 apps and games available in the Google play* store. The TV can also play online videos from multiple streaming media platforms such as Netflix, Prime Video, and YouTube. 360° Bluetooth remote control. Control the TV more freely. It also has a one-button access to Netflix and Prime video, so that your favorite contents are just one click away. SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 2Video Format 4KRAM Size 32 GBInternal Memory 3 GBProduct Weight 43. 6 KGScreen Size 86 inRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name GreyDisplay Type LEDOperating System AndroidProcessor Brand MediaTekWhat's In The Box 360° bluetooth remote control x 1 | Screws bag x 1 | Stands x 2 | Power cable x 1 | User manual x 1 | Warranty card x 1Viewing Distance 4. 1 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 208 cmProduct Height 128 cmProduct Width/Depth 22 cmModel Number Xiaomi TV Max 86"Model Name Xiaomi TV Max 86"Number of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6ffc7fd7-17dc-43f8-8ba1-371438f0ba2f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/60142a22-d752-4560-838f-5ff59eded19a/web/1_1731155663402.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>4189 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099670752128</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4965676802</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart MI Wireless Switch House White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEnsures optimum performance and extended lifeArticulated to blend well with the existing decor schemeWireless electrical switch that can connect to a wide range of appliancesPremium material construction exhibits abrasion-resistant durabilitySpecificationsMaterial PlasticColour Name WhiteProduct Length 50 mmProduct Height 50 mmProduct Width/Depth 13 mmModel Number WXKG01LMModel Name Mi Wireless Switch</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5c5de13e-a776-470e-b927-8440d07d1faa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6990e473-24a8-4358-b908-3f8b6acdddf6/web/1_1731158003628.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049656768025</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2638219463</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI WATCH FIT 2 Active Edition Smartwatch With 1.74"FullView Display Durable Battery Life Automatic SpO2 Monitoring Midnight Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe ambient light display allows automatic adjustment of brightness on the watch suited to your environmentTrack all stages of sleep every night and keep a tab on your sleep health with the sleep monitoring feature on the watchSports friendly it is splash and sweat resistance makes it the perfect fitness companion to haveKeep a track of your well being and health right from your wrist with noise health suite featuring a variety of health featuresMonitor your heart rate and blood oxygen levels on the go with the heart rate and spo2 monitor and it also comes with guided breathing to help you relax and embrace mindfulnessOverviewA smartwatch is a wearable computer in the form of a watch; modern smartwatches provide a local touchscreen interface for daily use, while an associated smartphone app provides for management and telemetry (such as long-term biomonitoring). While early models could perform basic tasks, such as calculations, digital time telling, translations, and game-playing, smartwatches released since 2015 or later have more general functionality closer to smartphones, including mobile apps, a mobile operating system and wifi/bluetooth connectivity. Some smartwatches function as portable media players, with fm radio and playback of digital audio and video files via a bluetooth headset. Some models, called watch phones (or vice versa), have mobile cellular functionality like making calls. while internal hardware varies, most have an electronic visual display, either backlit lcd or oled. some use transflective or electronic paper, to consume less power. They are generally powered by a rechargeable lithium-ion battery. Peripheral devices may include digital cameras, thermometers, accelerometers, pedometers, heart rate monitors, altimeters, barometers, compasses, gps receivers, tiny speakers, and microsd cards, which are recognized as storage devices by many other kinds of computers. software may include digital maps, schedulers and personal organizers, calculators, and various kinds of watch faces. The watch may communicate with external devices such as sensors, wireless headsets, or a heads-up display. Like other computers, a smartwatch may collect information from internal or external sensors and it may control, or retrieve data from, other instruments or computers. It may support wireless technologies such as bluetooth, wi-fi, and gps. For many purposes, a "watch computer" serves as a front end for a remote system such as a smartphone, communicating with the smartphone using various wireless technologies. Smartwatches are advancing, especially their design, battery capacity, and health-related applications. health-related applications include applications measuring heart rate, spo2, workout, etc. SpecificationsCharging Type Lightning to USBMaterial FluoroelastomerBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 30 gColour Name Midnight BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box Watch x 1 Charging Cradle (including the charging cable) x 1 Quick Start Guide &amp;amp; Safety Information &amp;amp; Warranty Card x 1Band Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Dial Material MetalTrending Huawei Watch FitProduct Length 46 mmProduct Height 10. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 33. 5 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 74 inFeatures Indicator Lights, Rechargeable, Pocket Size, Water Resistant, Sweat ResistantModel Number YDA-B09SModel Name Watch Fit 2 Active EditionItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/05417fd4-b553-40d9-89f1-9d07871766a2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/506b37b2-6ac3-4c65-b8dd-b7ae342d37f6/web/1_1731157748854.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>498 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026382194632</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5785452908</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi True Wireless Redmi Buds 3 With Charging Case White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsThe dual high-sensitivity microphones built into the Redmi Buds 3, coupled with mic with Qualcomm cVc echo canceling and noise suppression technology, dynamically reduce ambient noise and effectively minimize echoesDelivers crystal clear voice quality no matter where you are. And with a 95ms ultra-low latency function to ensure sound and picture synchronization when playing gamesThe Pop-up function just needs to simply open the charging case and tap the phone screen when the pop-up window appears, connecting and paring so easyThe battery levels of the earbuds and the charging case can be seen at a glanceRedmi buds 3 equips Qualcomm QCC3040 chip and Bluetooth 5. 2 technology delivers faster sound transmission, more stable, low power consumptionEquipped with a 12 mm dynamic driver deliver rich 3D surround stereo bass tones, clear high tones, and consistently superior sound qualitythe built-in light sensor will pause the music when one earphone is removed, and then put it on, the music will be resumed automaticallyOverviewThe dual high-sensitivity microphones built into the redmi buds 3, coupled with mic with qualcomm cvc echo canceling and noise suppression technology, dynamically reduce ambient noise and effectively minimize echoes. Delivers crystal clear voice quality no matter where you are. And with a 95ms ultra-low latency function to ensure sound and picture synchronization when playing games. 【Miui pop-up window function brings easy and quickly paring】: the pop-up function just needs to simply open the charging case and tap the phone screen when the pop-up window appears, connecting and paring so easy. And the battery levels of the earbuds and the charging case can be seen at a glance. Note please: only support xiaomi smartphones(mi 11 lite 5g, mi 10 lite 5g, mi 10t, redmi note 10 5g, redmi note 10 pro, etc. ), And the miui version should be upgraded to the latest stable version. 【In-ear detection &amp;amp; bluetooth 5. 2 &amp;amp; Stereo sound】: redmi buds 3 equips qualcomm qcc3040 chip and bluetooth 5. 2 Technology delivers faster sound transmission, more stable, low power consumption. Equipped with a 12 mm dynamic driver deliver rich 3d surround stereo bass tones, clear high tones, and consistently superior sound quality. And the built-in light sensor will pause the music when one earphone is removed, and then put it on, the music will be resumed automatically. 【Type-c interface fast charging &amp;amp; extra long battery life】: equipped type-c interface and 10-minute fast charge can enjoy up to 1. 5 Hours playback. Though small and lightweight, the redmi buds 3 offers both power and comfort. Enjoy up to 5 hours of battery life on a single charge, or up to 20 hours' use when paired with the charging case. 【Ultra-light &amp;amp; ip54 dust water resistant】: weighing only 4. 5G(0. 158Oz) each, the small exquisite fuselage which closely fit the contours of your ear canal, it's not easy to lose or fall out when you wear them moving or running. Redmi buds 3 true wireless earbuds have been expertly designed to meet ip54* dust and water resistance standards(level 5 dustproof and level 4 water-resistant), making the earbuds safe from spills and sweat. SpecificationsBattery Size 310 mAhProduct Weight 27. 7 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box Headphone AccessoriesAudio Headphone Type In-EarProduct Length 5. 9 inProduct Height 1. 02 inProduct Width/Depth 2. 95 inModel Number M2104E1/BHR5174GLModel Name Redmi buds 3Item Quantity 1View Full Overview</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b7a3bcbb-8101-4064-b388-2d4a0a83c146</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e6c4b53d-9576-4e0c-995f-bbd826d5affe/web/1_1731158438955.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>43.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057854529089</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3810228611</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI WiFi AX2 Dual-Band Home Router White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHighest in customer satisfaction for wireless routers 2017 and 2019Certified for Humans: Smart home made easy for non-experts. Setup with Alexa is simpleIt focuses signal strength to your devices far away using Beamforming technology, 4 high-gain antennas and an advanced front-end module (FEM) chipsetThe build quality is excellent and the autonomy is very longWi-Fi 6 technology communicates more data to more devices simultaneously using revolutionary OFDMA technologyHUAWEI WiFi AX2 comes equipped with 5 GHz and 2. 4 GHz bands that operate simultaneously, and automatically switches devices between 5 GHz and 2. 4 GHz bands to ensure that they enjoy an optimal connection at all times. 5 GHz is ideal for high-speed gaming and streaming, whereas 2. 4 GHz provides for broader coverageMultiple routers placed can be grouped under a single Wi-Fi name, when you link your HUAWEI WiFi AX2 with the other HUAWEI routers3 throughout your home, with automatic switching as you move around. This means that you'll always enjoy an optimal connection, regardless of whichever room you're inHUAWEI WiFi AX2 comes with three Gigabit Ethernet ports, each of which supports WAN/LAN auto-adaptation4, sparing you from having to distinguish between them, and making broadband installation a sheer breezeOverviewHuawei's mission is to bring digital to every person, home and organization for a fully connected, intelligent world. To this end, we will drive ubiquitous connectivity and promote equal access to networks to lay the foundation for the intelligent world; provide diversified computing power to deliver ubiquitous cloud and intelligence; build powerful digital platforms to help all industries and organizations become more agile, efficient, and dynamic; redefine user experience with AI, offering consumers a more personalized and intelligent experience across all scenarios, including home, travel, office, entertainment, and fitness and health. Trending offers a new visual experience and greatly improved productivity via a more vivid home screen layout. Customize the Service Widgets13 to enjoy shortcuts to frequently used apps and services. Discover more easy-to-view features to make you workflow smoother, feel the smooth, delicate touch of its fine texture, whether it's the vegan leather version in lively Olive Green, or the classic version in refined Matte Grey. Different styles and same elegance n 2021, Huawei invested even more in research and innovation, as part of our greater efforts to sustain development in the future. We are sparing no efforts as we explore the endless frontiers of science and technology. We are also devoting efforts to identifying the needs of different industries and overcoming global challenges. Guided by our vision of a fully connected, intelligent world, we will work openly with the global scientific community to explore new theories, architectures, and technologies, which will support the ongoing development of the industry. Huawei works with customers to balance opportunities and risks, quickly responding to their needs and achieving sustainable growth. Also undertakes to provide customers quality-assured products, services, and solutions and consistently enable customers to experience our commitment in creating value for each of them. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableWhat's In The Box 1 x RoutersWireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandConnector Type RJ45Antenna Type ExternalWireless Standard 5GProduct Length 163. 5 mmProduct Height 29 mmProduct Width/Depth 257. 6 mmMax Data Transfer Rate 1500 MbpsFeatures Personal, Business, Ergonomic, Indicator LightsModel Number WS7001-20Model Name WS7001-20Item Quantity 1Wireless Standard Value 802. 11v</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/583b33a3-af25-45fb-a0ab-8da8f72b608a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e8c8d0ee-4222-40a9-802e-c2ab8120eae8/web/1_1731158350753.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038102286114</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7570397955</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Smart Plug Wi-Fi White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsControl and automate your electrical devices anywhere with your fingertips with the connected WiFi socket. Plug works with any box without the need for a hub or paid subscription serviceVoice control of your devices connected to the outlet via Google AssistantSpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name WhiteConnection Type WifiModel Number GMR4015GLModel Name Smart PlugItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a5950527-80e6-4041-88f3-48862b01a666</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9f06f432-2412-4ddf-ad45-4305642385dd/web/1_1731159244255.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>79 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075703979557</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5778011838</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 20000mAh High-Speed Charging Technology Powerbank 18 watt Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEnergy saving and High capacity polymer batteryCompatible with multiple devicesOver charge and over discharge protectionRapid chargingIt is compatible with all USB charging devices so you stay connected alwaysRedmi Power Bank comes with high-density advanced Li-polymer batteries that makes it more durable and optimizes charging efficiencyThe new Redmi Power Bank comes with 18W Fast Charging. It supports 5. 1V/2. 4A, 9V/ 2A MAX and 12V/1. 5A MAX charging outputs that ensures efficient and quick charging for your devicesNow charge not just mobiles but tablets, BT speakers, earphones, headsets, fitness bands etcOverviewHigh capacity of 20,000 mAhEnough capacity to fully charge four phones and still have power left. High capacity of 20,000 mAh; built-in smart USB charging controller; compatible with most phones and digital devices; enough capacity to fully charge four Mi 9 phones and still have power left. Rapid charging and self-chargingThe 20,000-mAh Redmi Fast Charge Power Bank has two USB-A output ports, each with a maximum output of 18 W. It also has two input ports, a USB-C and a Micro-USB port, each with a maximum input of 18 W. A smart power bank that offers more efficient charging and discharging and saves you valuable time. Two types of input portsIt's better to have a choice. The 20,000-mAh Redmi Fast Charge Power Bank has two input ports, a USB-C and a Micro-USB port, making it fully compatible with standard Android device cables and ensuring fast charging of the power bank itself. SpecificationsCharging Type Micro USBNumber of Charging Ports 2 PortProduct Weight 447 gColour Name BlackConnection Type WiredWhat's In The Box Power BankProduct Length 15. 4 cmProduct Height 2. 7 cmProduct Width/Depth 7. 4 cmWattage 18 WFeatures Personal, Indicator LightsModel Number PB200LZM / VXN4304GLModel Name Xiaomi 20000mAh Redmi 18W Fast Charge Power Bank - BlackItem Quantity 1Number of USB Ports 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/87a6451b-bac8-4cbb-8bb5-40dc576aa732</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dd014672-f3ce-4c57-9f28-af33a5d64d38/web/1_1731159519811.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>79 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057780118388</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4285679089</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi 4A Router Gigabit Edition 2.4GHz 5GHz WiFi 16MB ROM 128MB DDR3 4 Antenna Remote APP Control IPv6 White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDual Core CPU for faster network speed featuring dual core four threading CPUWireless dual band support 2. 4GHz and 5GHz two frequency bandsHigh gain 4 antennas for stronger signal 4 external high-gain omnidirectional antennasHugely improves transmission performance and do great job under various complex environmentStrong performance easily support gigabit network and dual band WiFi data transmissionOverviewXiaomi Corporation was founded in April 2010 and listed on the Main Board of the Hong Kong Stock Exchange on July 9, 2018 (1810. HK). Xiaomi is an internet company with smartphones and smart hardware connected by an Internet of Things (IoT) platform at its core. With an equal emphasis on innovation and quality, Xiaomi continuously pursues high-quality user experience and operational efficiency. The company relentlessly builds amazing products with honest prices to let everyone in the world enjoy a better life through innovative technology. Xiaomi ranked 3rd globally in terms of smartphone shipments in the fourth quarter of 2020. The company has also established the world’s leading consumer AIoT (AI+IoT) platform, with 324. 8 million smart devices connected to its platform, excluding smartphones and laptops. Xiaomi products are present in more than 100 countries and regions around the world. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box 1x Router, 1x Product Power Supply (12V/0. 6A)Wireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Dual BandConnector Type RJ45Antenna Type ExternalWireless Standard ACMax Data Transfer Rate 1 GbpsFeatures Wireless AC, Personal, Business, Indicator LightsModel Number DVB4224GLModel Name MiItem Quantity 2Wireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9db87901-a53c-4c60-84c4-52f815e31030</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/20de91c1-fb48-4c2b-885a-006fee134977/web/1_1731159655891.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>129 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042856790896</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9102179870</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Wi-Fi Range Extender Pro Wifi Repeater, Network Expander/ 2 External Antenna/ Up to 300Mbps / Up to 16 devices Connectivity / Plug & Play Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCompatible with other brands routerSupport up to 64 devices to fulfill the needs of the whole familyManage your network settings easily with the xiaomi Mi WiFi appTwo powerful high gain external antennas give wider coverage and better performanceWireless function make your wireless coverage largerOverviewSpecificationsColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Network ExpanderWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Dual BandConnector Type RJ45Antenna Type ExternalWireless Standard ACProduct Length 10 cmProduct Height 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 10 cmWi-Fi Range 2500 ft²Max Data Transfer Rate 300 MBpsFeatures Business, Cordless, Ergonomic, PersonalModel Number Pro 300M XINNUO MM-1 / R03Model Name Pro 300M XINNUO MM-1Item Quantity 1Number of Ports 6Wireless Standard Value ‎802. 11a/b/g/n</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ca84a0bd-6ff5-4bef-94a6-bbf452ea8566</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8ce4424d-23ff-45d3-86df-ce7b1c773372/web/1_1731162149300.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>47 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091021798700</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2170825533</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi WIFI Router 4C Roteador APP Control 64 RAM 802.11 b/g/n 2.4G 300Mbps 4 Antennas Wireless Routers Repeater for Home White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsFour high gain antennas for strong signal and quick transmission64MB capacity for up to 64 smart devices accessionIntelligent speed limit function for faster performanceIntelligent network watching function for ensuring network securitySmart management function for remote controlOverviewProcessor-MT76228DA,Ram-64 MB DDR2,WiFi Distance -10 mSpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 24 KGColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableWhat's In The Box RouterWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Single BandConnector Type RJ45Antenna Type InternalWireless Standard ACProduct Length 195 mmProduct Height 25. 3 mmProduct Width/Depth 107 mmWi-Fi Range 400 ft²Max Data Transfer Rate 300 MbpsFeatures Ergonomic, Personal, Eco FriendlyModel Number R4CMModel Name routerItem Quantity 1Number of Ports 6Wireless Standard Value 802. 11n</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/846416bd-b379-431d-ae93-f85126c2f0d5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bf927356-6c9a-406b-8da8-ff20f4175ef8/web/1_1731161999637.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>43 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021708255332</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5819994278</g:id>
      <g:title>Razer Viper V2 Pro Wireless Gaming Mouse</g:title>
      <g:description>Razer Viper V2 Pro Wireless Gaming Mouse in Perfect Condition Under a Razer Warranty with box and all accessories including Razer Stickers and Grip Tape. Selling to Upgrade to a V3 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4d76f11e-84d9-48d9-99d5-c36e015ccb56</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f78ed2d0-f6b0-4758-b1ee-f12af9d59b45/web/image_picker_E09898C4-D388-4F84-BFA8-E809D967ECD9-75095-00000DEF7DCA92FF.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>375 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058199942786</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3454276337</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mesh System AC1200 (1-pack) | 2.4GHz and 5GHz dual-band 1200Mbps | Covers up to 1,500 ft² /140 m² White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPrearranged kit pairing2. 4Ghz and 5GHz dual band supportCovers up to 1,500 ft² /140 m²Full Gigabit Ethernet portSleek and minimalistic designEffortless self-networkingOverviewAntenna: Internal Antennas Network Port: 2 x 10/100/1000Mbps WAN/LAN auto-sensing port Indicator: 1 Mesh/Reset Button: 1 Power Port: 1 Protocol Standards: IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab Bands: 2. 4GHz, 5GHz 2. 4GHz Wi-Fi: 300Mbps (802. 11ac) 5GHz Wi-Fi: 867Mbps (802. 11ac) Operating System: MiWi-Fi ROM Wi-Fi Encryption: WPA-PSK/WPA2-PSK/WPA3-SAE encryption Management Applications: Supports Web, Mi Home/Xiaomi Home App (Android, iOS) Operating Temperature: 0-40℃ Storage Temperature: -40-70℃ Operating Humidity: 10%-90%RH (non-condensing) Storage Humidity: 5%-90%RH (non-condensing) Product Dimensions: 8. 9 x 8. 9 x 15. 4cm (per unit) Weight: 250gSpecificationsProduct Weight 481 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableSet Includes Router × 1, Power adaptor × 1, Network cable × 1, User manual × 1, Warranty notice × 1Wireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandAntenna Type InternalWireless Standard ACProduct Length 9. 5 cmProduct Height 22 cmProduct Width/Depth 9. 5 cmWi-Fi Range 1500 ft²Features App Enabled, Wireless AC, Wireless NModel Number DVB4452GL | RD13Model Name Xiaomi Mesh System AC1200 (1-pack)Item Quantity 1Number of Ports 2Wireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e3fcee97-bc40-4c65-bb30-27ade953e6e8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0b184b65-eff0-4afd-89ea-e2d53b50e277/web/1_1731144931486.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034542763376</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3858493749</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Outdoor Speaker 30W IP67 Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPOWERFaUL SPEAKER: With a power output of 30W, this Xiaomi Sound Outdoor speaker delivers high-quality sound and impressive volumeHEAVY DUTY DESIGN: Built for outdoor use, features a water and dust resistant housing, ideal for camping, pools, or outdoor parties. Long battery life: Enjoy up to 12 hours of continuous playback on a single charge thanks to its 2600mAh battery. Wireless connectivity: Bluetooth 5. 4 compatible0 for stable connection and hassle-free audio streaming from your device. OverviewThe Xiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W is a powerful portable speaker designed to bring sound to your outdoor adventures. With 30W output power and sturdy construction, this Bluetooth speaker will let you enjoy your favorite music with high-quality sound anywhere. Its long battery life gives you up to 12 hours of continuous playback, while its IP67 rating makes it water and dust resistant, ideal for camping, going to the beach, or just relaxing in the backyard. In addition, its compact and lightweight design makes it easy to carry. With a Bluetooth range of up to 25 meters, you can control your music wirelessly from your smart device. The Xiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W is the perfect companion for your outdoor adventures, offering you powerful and long-lasting sound in a portable, rugged package. SpecificationsColour Name BlueConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life 6 HoursProduct Length 9. 2 cmProduct Height 18 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 1 cmModel Number 30W SpeakerModel Name 30W Speaker</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/72704f22-4b9e-4950-b474-cdeb2c26b9e0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9384131e-9aee-4c32-aa8f-fd3b06999c6b/web/1_1731145963446.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038584937498</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7082364802</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 5, Up To 46dB Active Noise Reduction,12.4mm Titanium Plated Diaphragm White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSupport for Google Fast pair. Supports dual device connectivity. Support for Xiaomi earphone appSupports three gear noise reduction and transparency mode adjustment, allowing for comfortable gear selection in different environments12. 4mm titanium plated diaphragm speaker. Independent rear chamber structure design. Four sound effects settingsOverviewXiaomi Redmi Buds 5 has a noise reduction depth of 46dB, Support broadband noise reduction at 2000Hz,12. 4mm titanium plated diaphragm speaker, Equipped with a charging box, The 40 hours battery life for one week use. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type True WirelessAverage Battery Life 16hrs - 24hrsAudio Jack Type-CAudio Headphone Type In-EarEarplug Type EarbudsFeatures Active Noise Cancellation, Bluetooth, Volume Control, Voice Assistant, External MicModel Number BHR7628GLModel Name Xiaomi Redmi Buds 5-White</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/79a5569d-ff6f-4153-a73c-363cef34a791</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0b5ee0cf-394e-4570-baec-90fc3751a1c2/web/1_1731148139372.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>109 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070823648024</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3239157253</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Solar Outdoor Camera BW400 Pro Set | Multi-Level Data Encryption | IP66 Waterproof And Dust-Resistant | 2.5K Ultra-Clear Night Vision | 10000mAh Battery | AI Detection</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights10000mAh high-capacity battery132° FOV expanded horizonMulti-level data encryption. Protect personal privacyIP66 rating. Waterproof and dust-resistant4MP clear 2. 5K Ultra-clear night visionAI detection. Precise recognitionPair with the indoor base station. Worry-free installation and useBuilt-in solar-powered panel convert sunlight into power for night-time useOverview1/2. 7-inch sensor. Clear imaging in any environment. Day and night, clear picture quality in any outdoor environment. f/1. 6 larger aperture. Enhanced light sensitivity. Hardware-level HDR. Optimized for ambient light. Expanded horizon to eliminate blind spots. 132° wide FOV. 113. 3° Horizontal view. 58. 7° Vertical view. Clear night vision Feel safer at night. High-power infrared lights and full-color LED lights capture clear images, even when it's dark outside. 10000mAh battery. Uninterrupted online protection. High-capacity battery for a steady supply of power. 180 days* of continuous operation with normal use. Built-in solar-powered panel. Convert sunlight into power for night-time use. Solar cells conversion rate of 20%* for efficient power storageSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 4 MPModel Number BW400 ProModel Name BW400 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/99395594-3371-4d20-8dbf-9550f6ac9ae9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d8dfc4dc-4bc5-4234-ae0f-abdab385cb0c/web/1_1731148243622.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>394 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032391572538</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1770253114</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Outdoor Camera Bw500 | 2.5K Full-Colour Night Vision | Ip67 Dust And Water Resistance | 8Gb Built-In Storage | Encrypted Data Transmission | White</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights2. 5K clear and smooth imaging A leap in picture quality that is truly outstandingf/1. 6 large aperture Superior imaging with more light transmission36° wide field of view Enhanced wide-angle coverage minimises blind spots10m full-colour night vision Security around the clockBlack and white night visionFull-colour night visionSuper large battery capacity for 180 days of worry-free recordingThe 10,000mAh* high-capacity battery ensures long-lasting power for up to six monthsLow-power consumption system design Energy-efficient on-demand power distribution5W solar panels Keep recording even during power outages that can buy separatelyProfessional IP67* dust and water resistance rating Protection against wind and rain1. 2T computing chip Efficient detection for intelligent protectionOverviewAI-powered for efficient protection and security. Boasts 6 fantastic features and is powerful and durable. 6-month durable battery ensures worry-free usage. Feel more assured about your movement. 2. 5K full-colour night vision. Enhanced security with clear nighttime imaging. 1. 2T powerful computing power. Fast and accurate detection. Professional IP67 dust and water resistance rating. Stay protected in tough weathers. Encrypted data transmission Protect your data privacy. 8GB built-in storage. Keep data secureSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 2. 5 pxModel Number MJSXJ06BY | BW500Model Name Xiaomi Outdoor Camera BW500</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ba221271-84fb-4018-9b7e-c42984ead795</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/30ee8b21-5781-4f2e-8e79-483077efb154/web/1_1731146658154.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>343.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017702531145</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2405429420</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI 1500 mAh 4G Mobile WIFI 5 LTE 195 Mbps | Up to 16 Device Connects White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsTravel The world with Huawei's super-fast 4G mobile Wi-Fi a pocket-sized solution to low-cost travel Wi-FiParental Control and guest network - A simplified system to help you ensure online safety on all connected devices and disconnect any device at the touch of a buttonPowerful, Rechargeable 1500mAh battery with 6 hours working time so you can stay connected for longerThis router supports up to 16 different users at once,4 equipping it to meet the needs when you are on a trip or in a busy office, or sharing mobile data with other devices. Display: LED Lights 1xSignal, 1xBattery, 1xSMSHUAWEI 4G Mobile WiFi 5’s Type-C port, which supports reversible plugging and is compatible with cables of other devices (such as mobile phones and tablets), is a marked improvement over the micro ports seen on previous generations. HUAWEI 4G Mobile WiFi 5 is 14% slimmer than its predecessor, packing a high-speed network straight into your pocket. 1With download speeds 30% higher than the previous generation, and upload speeds 110% higher, conferences and films breeze by, whether they’re on a phone, tablet or laptop. 3SpecificationsProduct Weight 90 gColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard 4GProduct Length 10 cmProduct Height 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 2 cmModel Number E5586-326Model Name E5586-326Wireless Standard Value 802 11 B, 802 11 G, 802 11 N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/42209c0a-0d2a-47ca-bd47-66754607cdf1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a92c1b23-93c6-4f55-a654-e8247ce4e6bb/web/1_1731147170557.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>214.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024054294208</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7442321674</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Band 8 Pro, High-Resolution Large 1.74" AMOLED Display Light Grey</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights1. 74”AMOLED screen,60Hz high refresh rate,336PPICorning GG3 cover glass, more solid compare to 7proSupport ambient light sensor that allow the display brightness to automatically adjust for your eyes4-channel monitoring channel(Increase heart rate accuracy by 10% and blood oxygen accuracy by 5%)All-day SpO2 level tracking, continuous sleep monitoring, 24-hours heart rate monitoring, and sleep breathing monitoring150+ workout modes to record your heart rate and burned calories. 10 on-wrist running courses, could vibrate and light the screen to remind you to meet your heart rate and pace goals. 3D warm up and Relaxation Private Education CoursesBuilt-in GNSS Support independent GNSS, supporting 5-star positioning system: Beidou, GPS, GLONASS, Galileo, qzss. Up to 14-day battery lifeSupport 14 days daily use and 6 days AOD use. 5ATM water resistanceSupports 50 meter deep waterproofingOverviewXiaomi Smart Band 8 Pro Light Grey, 1. 74”AMOLED screen,60Hz high refresh rate,150+ workout modes to record your heart rate and burned calories, Updated ID apperance, metallic frame that coated with NCVM, Support 14 days daily use and 6 days AOD use, Supports 50 meter deep waterproofingSpecificationsMaterial AluminumColour Name Light GreyBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 74 inModel Number BHR8007GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5921c948-376f-4645-bfc2-1233c23c00d3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f82e0e9e-2ac8-4e41-8f76-097883dc9a23/web/1_1731149265640.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>198 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074423216744</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5533428496</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Instant Photo Printer 1S Set White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHigh-quality 8. 6 × 10. 2 cm* and 10 × 14. 8 cm photos directly from your smartphoneFine details and natural colorsAutomatic laminationPrinting photos in various sizesSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number BHR6747GL/ZPDYJ03HTItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/70e5352e-35ca-487f-860a-003e7dba0838</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fb2be922-e0e9-4920-9a2d-31675be31d58/web/1_1731152074130.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055334284961</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3905165593</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI Band 9 Smart Watch, Ultra-Thin Design And Comfortable Wearing, Scientific Sleep Analysis, Durable Battery Life, IOS And Android Charm Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra design: 1. 47 Inch amoled screen, 8. 99mm thin, 14g weightScientific sleep tracking: Upgraded sleep efficiency analysis, and sleep basic physiological analysisFast charging, durable battery life: 45 minutes to fully charge, 5 minutes fast charge can be used for 2 days. Maximum 2-week battery life, 9 days of normal useCustomized workout types: Huawei band 9 offers a multitude of workouts that you can customize as requiredCompatible with android and iOSOverviewHUAWEI Band 9 is a brand new, high-end sports band which has a full-sized color touchscreen, side button control, and is water resistant to 50 meters. This smart wearable product integrates a wide range of features, including workout detection, smart heart rate monitoring, workout assistant, multiple workout modes, sleep monitoring, message notifications, automatic SpO2 measurement, and music playback control. SpecificationsMaterial FluoroelastomerBattery Size None NoneProduct Weight 14 gColour Name Charm PinkBand Material FluoroelastomerDepartment UnisexDisplay Type AMOLEDFace/Dial Shape RectangularBand Size Medium/LargeProduct Length 43 mmProduct Height 9 mmProduct Width/Depth 25 mmSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 47 inModel Number KIM-B19Model Name Huawei Band 9, KIM-B19</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e75db7c8-ea7b-4070-9e1a-e2c15dc4ee03</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d86e293c-639a-4ba3-b141-ce127ee4f284/web/1_1731147954556.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>198 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039051655938</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5692527518</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Outdoor Camera CW400 | 2.5K Ultra-Clear Picture Quality | IP66 Water Resistance | 360° Horizontal View And 160° Vertical View | AI Human Detection | Dual-Antenna Network</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights4MP with large aperture ultra-clear 2. 5K picture qualityFour-light, smart full-colour night vision truly clear images, even in the dark nightProfessional design with IP66 water resistance ready for tough-weather conditionsHorizontal and vertical dual gimbals more flexible and reliableHigh-gain dual-antenna design enhanced, clearer wi-fi signalTwo-way voice calling to make conversation easier Smart noise cancellation for any outdoor environmentAI human detection to effectively filter out false alarms warning you only when a person is detectedAudible and visual warning, active defense instant alarms sent to your smartphoneTime-lapse photography record your wonderful memoriesMJA1 security chip maximum privacy and safetyLocal and cloud dual storage double protection of critical informationSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 4 MPModel Number BHR7625HK | MJSXJ04HL | CW400</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5266e92f-4e9d-4ab6-af11-e85aea56b4de</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b132b6a3-8a2c-4822-b848-5ecc99d5c65f/web/1_1731151752622.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>247.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056925275184</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5105324043</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Portable Bluetooth Speaker 16W GL | HQ Sound | Dual EQ Mode | IPX7 | TWS Red</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHigh quality soundAbility to connect two speakers for stereo soundLong working time of up to 13 hoursWaterproof IPX7Built-in microphoneSpecificationsColour Name RedConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life 13 HoursModel Number MDZ-36-DB | QBH4242GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dac8ddc8-d603-4777-97f4-54817ff0747a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dbde43f4-92a7-41fd-9db9-1d39ed234ac8/web/1_1731150212145.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051053240431</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2645610244</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Multi 4 USB Splitter High Speed Hab White</g:title>
      <g:description>SpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number UZ125Model Name UZ125YF</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ebfe825f-c41f-43c2-bfeb-0545c929f9fa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/58866940-2e77-4458-b9b8-dbff8968473e/web/1_1731157122935.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>57 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026456102440</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7374114900</g:id>
      <g:title>realme Buds T100 True Wireless Earbuds With AI Noise Cancelling Blue</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsTrue wireless bluetooth headset. Call noise reductionLong battery life 28h. Support flash chargeLow latencyOverviewModel：Realme Buds T100. Wireless connection：Bluetooth 5. 3. Battery life：Headphone + charging compartment: 28h music playback. Function：AAC, SBC. Charging port：Type-C. Water resistant： IPX5 (earbuds only). Dynamic driver size：10mmSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 400 mAhProduct Weight 35 gColour Name BlueConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life Less than 8 hrsWhat's In The Box Realme Techlife Buds T100 *1, User Guide *1, Silicone Eartips *6Audio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type In-EarCharging Case Type WiredEarplug Type EarbudsProduct Length 6. 1 mmProduct Height 4. 8 mmProduct Width/Depth 2. 8 mmFeatures Bluetooth, Water Resistant, Active Noise CancellationModel Number RMA2109Model Name BUDS T100</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/26339322-6378-4cc7-ba99-33c2dd9a6b78</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/061de3b4-316d-418d-ac01-26ccedb9baf3/web/1_1731153772694.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>81 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073741149000</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2836354841</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi AX3000 Mesh System NE (2- Pack) WiFi 6 White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMesh Seamless Roaming : Xiaomi Mesh technology enables your smartphone to seamlessly and automatically switch to higher-speed Wi-Fi nodes. Whether you are moving from room to room or from upstairs to downstairs. NFC Quick Connection : Simply touch the NFC area of your phone to the top of the router to quickly connect to wi-fi without manually entering the password. Extensive Multiple Connection : Supporting simultaneous connections for up to 256 devices. Whether streaming, gaming, or working, it delivers a robust network experience. Easy To Use : The two router are pre-paired at the factory. Choose any one of the routers to complete the network configuration, the other one will automatically establish a mesh network with it upon power- on. You can use the MI Home/Xiaomi App. Package Content : Router x 2, Power Adaptor, Network Cable, User Manual. OverviewIt works with routers that support Xiaomi Mesh for networking, to achieve seamless network coverage for larger households so you can connect anywhere. SpecificationsProduct Weight 460 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableSet Includes Package Content : Router x 2, Power Adaptor, Network Cable, User Manual. What's In The Box Router x 2, Power Adaptor, Network Cable, User Manual. Wireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard AXProduct Length 8. 9 cmProduct Height 21. 4 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 9 cmModel Number RD28Model Name AX3000 NEItem Quantity 1Wireless Standard Value AX3000</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/373d1929-bb79-40f6-b0a6-7f8737f05e08</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4c29ab0b-485c-4f62-a953-6bec82e7b29e/web/1_1731146475710.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028363548410</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3481706473</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Bedside Lamp 2 White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEmits a powerful beam of light which illuminates the area with a bright radiancePremium housing construction proffers added protection against elemental hazardsHigh operating voltage range and lightweight fits easily into existing socketEnabling higher light intensity with energy efficient features with 9 watts of powerSpecificationsColour Name WhiteShape CylindricalModel Number MJCTD02YL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e9d1a22c-e9ea-452a-bf9e-95b64ab55339</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eb63a2e9-8a5d-45a2-b591-a22b5d87ae1b/web/1_1731161888547.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>129 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034817064733</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9797048412</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin USB-C PD Power Bank 10K (Fast Charge Portable Charger w/ USB-C + USB Ports, 10000mAh Capacity) Battery Pack for Galaxy, Pixel, iPhone more Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights18W USB-C [ower delivery 10,000 mAh power bank supports fast charging for smartphonesDesigned with SMART CIRCUITRY that automatically detects your devices' power levelInput/Output USB-C port for your latest tablet, smartphones or any USB-C deviceLED indicator light shows power bank’s battery status to signal when it’s time to rechargeBoost Charge tested to be safe, complete with over voltage and over heating protectionSpecificationsNumber of Charging Ports 1 PortColour Name BlackConnection Type WiredFeatures Personal, Travel, Business, RechargeableModel Number BPB001btBKModel Name BoostchargeNumber of USB Ports 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/30dccbd5-96d6-4f53-983e-45fe7f6ee251</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b1a6eaba-080f-40b1-8691-5e212019b9e6/web/1_1731161311485.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>123 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097970484121</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8364380263</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI WS7100 WiFi Ax3 Dual Core Router White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsWi-Fi 6 has made several improvements over Wi-Fi 5 to cope with the increasing demand for faster and more efficient Wi-FiAX3 and Wi-Fi 6-enabled HUAWEI phones are the perfect pair because both are equipped with HUAWEI's self-developed Wi-Fi chipset, which support 160 MHz frequency bandwidthHUAWEI Wi-Fi 6-enabled phones are able to send 6dB stronger signals back to AX3 in stable, 2 MHz narrow bandwidth using Dynamic Narrow Bandwidth technology, which is based on Chipset SynergyYou will be impressed with the blazing fast speed delivered by AX3. Thanks to 1024-QAM and 160 MHz frequency bandwidth, its theoretical speed can reach up to 3000 MbpsUnlike traditional routers, the AX3 supports the ability to connect a large number of devices without compromising performanceThe Built-in Firewall can Protect you from DoS/ARP AttacksOverviewNo Of LAN Ports-3,No Of Antennas-4,Processor-Gigahome Dual-core 1. 2 GHz CPUSpecificationsProduct Weight 143. 78 KGColour Name WhiteSet Includes RouterWhat's In The Box WS7100 WiFi Ax3 Dual Core RouterWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Dual BandAntenna Type InternalWireless Standard 4GProduct Length 6. 27 cmProduct Height 1. 56 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 86 cmWattage 5 WWi-Fi Range 490 ft²Storage Capacity 1 TBFeatures Business, Indicator LightsModel Number WS7100Model Name WS7100Item Quantity 4Number of Ports 4Wireless Standard Value WS7100</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6ac98072-e97b-4d1c-a4a4-771bf73f9758</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2d6e1204-a945-4c75-8926-2d10c96e18a9/web/1_1731159779918.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>198 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083643802637</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3260420155</g:id>
      <g:title>TP-LINK 300Mbps Wireless N ADSL2+ Modem Router White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAll-in-One Device ADSL2+ Modem, NAT Router, 4-Port Switch and Wireless N Access PointWireless N speed up to 300Mbps makes it ideal for heavy bandwidth consuming or interruption sensitive applications like online gaming, Internet calls and even the HD video streamingEasy Setup Assistant with multi-language support provides quick &amp;amp; hassle-free installationEasy one-touch wireless security encryption with the ‘WPS’ button and easy Wi-Fi On/Off buttonSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number TD-W8961NModel Name TD-W8961N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f3edc8d4-138c-4656-9f5a-1bfb3a24444d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6c76881f-42e7-4f2e-b5b0-5eb77a44ee10/web/1_1731156904006.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>77.60 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032604201552</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2767612846</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Power Bank 3 Ultra Compact 10000 mAh Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsOur world is getting faster and faster. That's why we have the best Power Banks, such as the new Xiaomi Power Bank 3. Designed to allow you to charge everything, it allows you to charge up to 3 devices at the same time as it has one USB-A port and two high-quality USB-C ports. You can charge all kinds of devices in the easiest way thanks to its maximum power of 22. 5W. It also has the latest fast-charging technology, which will keep your devices charged in the best way. This is a high-powered model which only takes 3. 5 hours to fully charge a device if we use a USB port, charging two devices simultaneously in 6 hours. The most interesting powerbank by Xiaomi. Take this easy-to carry model eveywhere. This new PowerBank is very thin, so you can carry it with you without any problem. As for its design, it includes four LEDs located under a button that indicates power parameters and the current maximum capacity, you can check at all times the amount of energy we have in our portable battery. These will light up intermittently to indicate the percentage that is left. It is made of aluminium alloy and is highly resistant to sudden changes in temperature, short circuits, hardware overheating and other problems you may have when using it. The most spectacular model you will find. Battery type: lithium polymer battery Capacity: 10000mAh 3. 7V (37Wh) Nominal Capacity: 5500mAh 5. 1V / 2. 6A Maximum output power: 22. 5W Operating temperature: 0 ° C ~ 40 ° C Input port: Micro-USB, USB-C Output port: 2 x USB-A 1 x USB-C 1 x Micro USB Input: 5. 0V 2. 0A / 5. 0V 2. 4A Output: USB-A port: 5V 2. 4A / 9. 0V 2A / 12. 0V 1. 5A MAX USB-C port: 5V 3A (22. 5W MAX) Charging time: Approximately 3. 5 hours (9V / 2A or 12V / 1. 5A adapter, standard cable) Approximately 6 hours (5V / 2A adapter, standard cable) Quick charge: 3. 0 + PD Dimensions: 90 x 63. 9 x 24. 4 mm Weight: 200 grOverview1 x USB-A, 1 x USB-C - Power Protection - Status Button - LED indicator - Black Colour - Lightweight &amp;amp; Portable Design - Simultaneous Charging of 3 Devices - Fast ChargeSpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WiredModel Number BHR4412GLModel Name Power BankItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6703ef68-d32f-4f34-9f9f-c4c0852692b0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/38e9cc26-a2d0-4b83-bc21-818567d2cb09/web/1_1731159329187.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>71 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0027676128463</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9683638291</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin 25W Power Delivery USB C PPS Wall Charger with Included USB C to Lightning MFi Cable, USB Type C PD Power Adapter PPS enabled fast charger for iPhone 14/14 Plus, 13, 12, Pro, Pro Max, Mini, and More White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSturdy construction ensures longevity and durabilityMoulded from high-grade material to avoid chipping even through prolonged usageExudes an exquisite craftsmanship that manifests an accentuating showSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number WCA004my1MWH-B5Model Name BKN-WCA004my1MWH-B5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/947fbdc0-99ca-46db-a2b2-c918f0957824</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/34e5b54e-73a3-4780-aa2a-e3e7ce44597e/web/1_1731157858737.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>83.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096836382915</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3424279702</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi AX1500 ROUTER | Wi-Fi 6 High Speed Connectivity White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsXiaomi Router AX1500 EU smart Wi-Fi 6 Xiaomi Mesh network technology supports various hybrid network methods that allow up to 10 devices to be connected OFDMA technology enables simultaneous data transmission from multiple devices IPTV supportSecurity: WPA-PSK/WPA2-PSK/WPA3-SAE wireless access control hidden SSIDPorts: 4x 10/100/1000Mb/s self-adaptive WAN/LAN (auto MDI/MDIX) 1x power connectorWiFi: 2. 4G Wi-Fi: 2x2 (supports protocol up to IEEE 802. 11n, theoretical maximum speed is 300Mb/s) 5GHz Wi-Fi: 2x2 (supports protocol up to IEEE 802. 11ax, theoretical maximum speed is 1201Mb/s)Antenna: four high gain antennas Standards: IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac/ax, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab Operating System: MiWiFi ROM Management app: Mi Home/Xiaomi Home App (Android, iOS), web support White color Dimensions: 247x143x178. 7mmOverviewXiaomi Router AX1500 supports IPTV multi-line multiplexing and can be connected with a TV set-top box, simplifying your home wiring for streamlined operation and a better viewing experience. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box 1x Xiaomi Router AX1500 1x network cable 1x power adapter 1x warranty card 1x instruction manualWireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard NModel Number AX1500Model Name AX1500Wireless Standard Value N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a1de6a66-2d56-401b-9593-17d8f6e06c47</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/273c6e1b-3ce6-4524-8807-2b5c99d7a76a/web/1_1731147625601.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>159 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034242797022</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6741116547</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 13C Dual Sim Clover Green 6Gb Ram 128Gb 4G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmooth 6. 74" 90Hz display50MP AI triple cameraMassive 5000mAh (typ) battery, Up to 23 hours of video streamingSupports 18W fast charging* 5 mins for 5 hours music playbackPowerful octa-core processor Up to 1tb expandable storageDurable quality you can trust, 500,000 times power button tests, 300 times Roller test, 20,000 times Headphone jack test, 20,000 times charging port testCorning® Gorilla® glass screen reliable protectionRedmi 13C's display helps reduce visual fatigue with both TÜV low blue light certification and TÜV flicker-free certificationRedmi 13C delivers smooth and stable performance thanks to the reliable MediaTek Helio G85, an octa-core processor that balances power and efficiencyOcta-core processor, Up to 2. 0GHz cpu speed, 290070 Antutu V10 benchmarkUp to 16gb with 8gb extended ramUp to 1tb expandable storageSpecificationsSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 74 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Clover GreenOperating System AndroidOperating System Number 13Processor Number G85Network Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTekNumber of Cores Octa CoreCondition NewModel Number 2311DRN14I | 23106RN0DAModel Name Redmi 13C Dual SIM Clover Green 6GB RAM 128GB 4G</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/89b636b7-70de-4ed6-aec3-008cad9ec318</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8828722f-86ad-4786-a737-1daddb786f0f/web/1_1731151857237.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>298 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0067411165476</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9749081173</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Router 4A Gigabit Edition | 1200 Mbps | Dual-Core CPU | Gigabit Ports | Up to 64 Devices White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDual-core CPU for faster connection speedsWireless dual-band 1167 Mbps for faster and smoother internet connectionsFiber-optic full-gigabit for high-speed broadband over 100 MbpsDual-band integration with one Wi-Fi name eliminates confusionThe smart error correction algorithm improves weak signals for greater stability and efficiencySpecificationsColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard ACModel Number DVB4305GL/R4AModel Name DVB4305GL/R4AWireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, 802. 3/3u</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3cc1326d-28fd-49ed-9b2c-88ea2185c97d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5c7e92d2-e3fe-43af-841a-0a84e1826680/web/1_1731153125677.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>84.45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097490811735</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3515648712</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Speaker Lite with built in Alex Bluetooth, Wi-Fi Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights2Mics, with far field voice wake up supportPowerful sound with large 1. 75" speakerIEEE 802. 11 a/b/g/n, 2. 4GHz/5GHz, BT 5. 1 &amp;amp; A2DPSmart living with Alexa*Supports Spotify Connect*SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessModel Number 07GModel Name 07G</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0f337ec0-2f9f-46e1-8318-549a846fb418</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3f30f608-5d12-426c-9580-5f9fea490082/web/1_1731153521350.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>111 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035156487122</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1883460311</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro 40dB 3 Modes Noise Cancellation 28h Long Battery Life Black</g:title>
      <g:description>OverviewUp to 40 dB Hybrid ANC The active noise cancellation can reduce up to 40dB of surrounding noise. 3 ANC modes You can switch to 3 different ANC modes in different environments, Office mode for light noise, Daily mode for outdoor noise, and Airplane mode for loud noise. 5-minutes Charge for 2 Hours Usage Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro supports fast charging, only 5 minutes charge you can use 2 hours. Never be afraid of battery off. Dual Device Connection Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro can be connected with two devices simultaneously. The devices include smartphones, tablets, PCs, and other smart devices. QCC 5151 SoC Qualcomm QCC5151 flagship SoC provides experience with robust connectivity, enhanced functionality and utilizes Low Energy technology. aptX Adaptive Qualcomm aptX Adaptive codec provides crystal clear audio performance and dynamic scalability. 11mm Dynamic Driver Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro adopts an 11mm dynamic driver and tuned by Xiaomi Sound Lap, offering you an immersive audio experience. Supports Wireless Charging Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro is compatible with Qi-certified chargers. Up to 28 hours battery life A single charge brings you up to 7 hours listening time with ANC off, and up to 28 hours when coupled with the charging case. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number BHR5114GLModel Name BHR5114GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e2c68f2d-11a6-4379-b15d-6fabfc28500d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/21be58c3-e7d7-4631-b256-223283e67b4a/web/1_1731157642829.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>309 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018834603113</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7035480283</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin MagSafe Charger, Magnetic Wireless Phone Charging Pad (For iPhone 14, 13 and 12 Series and Other MagSafe Enabled Devices, Power Adaptor Not Included) white</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMAGSAFE COMPATIBLE: Utilizing Apple's MagSafe Technology, this Belkin wireless charger delivers efficient and secure charging wireless charging. PERFECT MAGNETIC ATTACHMENT: Aligns perfectly with the MagSafe feature of your iPhone 12 to charge, and keeps your phone from being bumped and disconnecting from power while allowing you to easily snap it in place with one hand. TRAVEL FRIENDLY: A slim, portable design allows you to easily slip the pad into purses or laptop cases and take it with you anywhere. SAFE AND SECURE: An LED light on the stand indicates if there’s any charging interruption from a foreign object that could potentially harm your phone. OverviewSeamless magnetic attachment creates new iPhone 12 experiences. Designed so that you can keep using your phone while it charges, and place or take it anywhere with an extra-long cable. SpecificationsColour Name whiteConnection Type WirelessFeatures Indicator Lights, Wireless AC, TravelModel Number WIA005btWHModel Name WIA005btWH</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/acce059c-ed19-4340-ab16-ff21df85a998</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/31d85cc6-1ee5-4229-aa1e-93dd47ce3549/web/1_1731158697139.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>127 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070354802834</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9688962604</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin Boostcharge Braided Usb C To A Cable Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMade Of High QualityFast ChargerLight WeightSpecificationsColour Name BlackCable Length 6 to 7. 9 FeetProduct Length 200 cmModel Number CAB002bt2MBKModel Name Accessories-182Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/29dd0940-aa52-4a14-b9a4-24a5158727a2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1347a91b-461c-4bf0-a41f-f3dd60287bbd/web/1_1731158823894.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>43 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096889626042</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8626389663</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 50W Wireless Charging Stand Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEfficient and safe. Optimal viewing angle. Quiet heat dissipationCharging on the go, 100% charge in 42 minutes. Compatible with the Qi wireless charging standardOptimal tilt angle. Built-in silent cooling fan perfect for desks or bedsides minimal noise12 layers of smart protection secure layered protectionSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number 40460Model Name 40460Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3f824779-0381-46f5-9d38-8c4d15757296</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2c0edba9-cc76-41e0-8ff7-08ce262319b1/web/1_1731154245914.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>169 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086263896635</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8643378993</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 10W Wireless Power Bank Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights10w wireless charging10000mah capacityDual usb a output portsUsb c input portLed indicator lightsCompatible with qi enabled devicesMulti layer safety protectionSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number BHR5460GL/WPB15PDZMModel Name BHR5460GL/WPB15PDZMItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5d7ecfeb-2a03-4fa1-b7c1-4ece06e939da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/79cfebda-5965-4164-90c4-4e23032cb23a/web/1_1731153226532.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>83.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086433789934</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8459991018</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 4 White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUp to 35db hybrid active noise cancellation. 3 ANC level options and adaptive ANC modeAI noise reduction. Dual transparency mode10mm dynamic driver unit, 0. 006mm ultra-thin diaphragmUp to 30 hours long battery life with caseOverviewHi-Res Audio Wireless - Supports advanced LDAC audio codec: Redmi Buds 5 Pro is certified by Hi-Res Audio Wireless and supports LDAC audio codec with a sampling rate of up to 24bit/96kHz*, enabling Ultra HD audio with minimal distortion. Custom coaxial dual driver design - High-resolution, Hi-Fi sound quality: Redmi Buds 5 Pro features a coaxial dual driver design, which consists of an 11mm bass driver with titanium diaphram and a 10mm piezoelectric ceramic tweeter. This design delivers precise sound reproduction across all frequencies, ensuring a balanced performance with smooth highs, rich mids, and solid lows, allowing you to experience high-quality Hi-Fi sound at any time. Built-in immersive sound: Providing enhanced audio immersion across a range of content, Redmi Buds 5 Pro is ideal for watching movies on TV, computers, or tablets, delivering a captivating audio experience every time*. Vegan leather texture design - Understated and refined: For the first time, vegan leather was incorporated into the lower part of the black version of the case to provide a unique texture with a delicate feel and a more refined appearance. Marble texture design: The ear stem design incorporates natural elements using a multi-layer coating process to create a distinctive marble texture effect. Subtle yet distinctive, it suggests a personality both low-key and full of charm. Up to 52dB active noise cancellation: With industry-leading 52dB active noise cancellation technology, the upmost noise reduction capability has tripled compared to Redmi Buds 4 Pro, allowing you to enjoy your music in peace. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type USB Type CAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number 38561 / M2137E1Model Name 38561</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8d9dd4fd-87ce-4e2c-9510-e48e5fc8f8d1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c6518a89-bcc0-489d-8dda-55eef68e0d2f/web/1_1731154023309.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>162 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084599910186</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2691145548</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Camera C400 4MP 360° Rotation AI Human Detection 2.4GHz/5GHz Wi-Fi Support Compatible With Alexa Google Home</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltra-clear video in 2. 5K with 4MP camera:Updated to a 4MP camera with a resolution of 2560x1440With the large aperture and the 6P lens, the images delivered are more vivid:Combined with the 6P lens, the camera effectively reduces light refraction. Night vision with no visible red glow for clearer and safer monitoring:Sleep undisrupted with no visible red glow at night and no visual pollution. Smart IoT connectivity and interaction with other smart devices. Works with Google Home and AlexaHuman voices heard through large-diameter speakers with separate sound cavity are so real as if they are speaking to you in personOverviewThe dual-motor pan-tilt zoom design enables the lens to rotate up, down, left and right. When checking your smartphone outside your home, you can have a panoramic view of what happens at your home, giving you a complete sense of security. Real-time two-way voice calling with smart noise reduction enabled for clear conversations. AI-driven human detection and tracking; Smart IoT connectivity and interaction with other smart devices. Works with Google Home and Alexa. Fully encrypted to protect your privacy; Support for 2. 4GHz / 5GHz Wi-Fi; The H. 265 encoding technology allows you to save storage space and enable smoother data transmission. The high-quality, large diameter design of speakers enhances the stereo sound quality of speakers, while amplifying and restoring the true nature of sounds. When making two-way voice calls with your baby, you feel as if your baby is next to you. The product supports two-way real-time voice calling* and can pick up audio within a distance of up to 5 metres* for smoother call conversations; smart noise reduction is enabled for the microphone for clearer conversations. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 4 MPModel Number MJSXJ11CMModel Name MJSXJ11CM</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/709b7ab4-d046-4758-b492-fbb260548b02</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/457500e8-8383-48c3-bc40-55af61b5aeff/web/1_1731153835581.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>138 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026911455487</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1811828934</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin Boostcharge Braided Usb C To A Cable White</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMade Of High QualityFast ChargerLight WeightSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCable Length 6 to 7. 9 FeetProduct Length 200 cmModel Number CAB002bt2MWHModel Name Accessories-183Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a698eb0f-1f60-4da2-8198-e516a18e3348</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/23eef702-b58a-4413-9456-0655668570b2/web/1_1731158873544.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>49 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018118289347</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3766876144</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Wireless Mouse Lite 1000DPI Ergonomic Optical Portable Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights2. 4ghz wireless transmission. Full grip, strong controlLightweight body, flexible movement. 1000DPI precision sensor, stable outputLow battery prompt. Receiver built-in. Teflon foot padOverviewWireless mouse is one of the products of Xiaomi and XMWXSB01YM model is one of its popular mousses. It is equipped with a AAA battery and has a sleep power-saving function. The buttons are not procrastinating، the rhythm of the scroll wheel is clear، and the click and movement are very accurate and smooth. Its interface to the computer is USB. The mouse itself is an inappropriate size and a style full of the palm of your hand. Besides having a simple and classic design، it is durable and comfortable to use. In comparison to its price، has good quality. SpecificationsMaterial ABSProduct Weight 60 gColour Name BlackConnection Type RF WirelessOperating System WindowsTracking Method OpticalProduct Length 113 cmProduct Height 60 cmProduct Width/Depth 36 cmModel Number XMWXSB01YMModel Name Xiaomi Wireless Mouse Lite</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/916d6b21-88d7-47f2-84c0-ea71c7df8336</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1a21f585-206b-421b-a847-95c9b3f83ad4/web/1_1731154798775.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037668761448</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
