<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>1059916492</g:id>
      <g:title>Limimart 40''-130'' Smart Mini Projector 4K 5G WIFI, Big Screen Experience with Premium 360 Sound, 5.0 Bluetooth Movie Projector Compatible With Android/iOS/Windows/TV Stick/HDMI/USB/Audio 3.5 white</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemEXPERIENCE MAGIC OF PRESS AND PLAY : Simply press the portable mini iphone projector button and immerse yourself in a world of entertainment. This versatile smart theater-to-go allows you to place it, tilt it, and watch it wherever you desire. With its sleek design and cradle stand that rotates 180 degrees, you can project images and videos from the floor, table, wall, or even the ceiling. PORTABLE MINI HD PROJECTOR : Limimart mini projector wth WI-FI and Bluetooth is the epitome of convenience with its compact size of 6. 5 x 4. 3 x 3. 5 in, almost palm-sized. Weighing just 1. 1 lbs, the movie projector indoor effortlessly fits into your handbag, making it the perfect companion for your travels and camping adventures. Comparable to the size of a smartphone, it's so lightweight you'll forget it's even there. Aspect Ratio: 4:3 / 16:9, Contrast Ratio: 5000:1, Lamp lifetime: 50,000 hours. 130 '' BIG SCREEN and ±15 ° KEYSTONE CORRECTION: Prepare to be captivated by the small movie projector's ability to provide a display area of 40 '' to 130 '' with projection distances between 4-13 ft. To ensure a crystal-clear and high-quality image, we recommend a viewing distance of 5. 5 ft. With the focus and keystone ±15°correction adjusting, the home theater projector automatically adjusts the image angle, delivering your perfect picture in seconds. MULTIMEDIA COMPATIBILITY : The wall projector is equipped with HDMI, USB, 3. 5 mm AU headphone jack, making it compatible with various devices such as Fire TV Stick, Roku, DVD player, laptop, USB drive, computer, headphone, external speaker, iPhone, Android device, iPad, and even PS5. From garden parties to home theaters, outdoor camping to video conferences, online teaching to education, ceiling projector is your ideal companion. It's a fantastic choice for birthday, Christmas, or holiday gifts. WHISPER-QUIET OPERATION : Say goodbye to noisy distraction with our mini projector for phone ! With noise level &amp;lt;25 dB, our premium heat dissipation system ensures a serene movie-watching environment. Immerse yourself fully and enjoy stunning visuals accompanied by crystal-clear sound from the built-in HI-FI speaker. Our commitment to quality is unmatched, offering 2-Year Satisfaction Assurance, 24/7 customer support. Don't hesitate to reach out if any issues arise with your movie projector. Technical DetailsBrand ‎LimimartProduct Dimensions ‎16. 51 x 10. 92 x 8. 89 cm; 500 gItem model number ‎2711Manufacturer ‎LimiteccSeries ‎LMT-30Color ‎WhiteForm Factor ‎PortableStanding screen display size ‎130 InchesScreen Resolution ‎1280 x 720Resolution ‎1280x720 PixelsConnectivity Type ‎5G + 2. 4G WiFiNumber of HDMI Ports ‎1Voltage ‎120 VoltsWattage ‎60 wattsPower Source ‎ACAre Batteries Included ‎NoItem Weight ‎500 g</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/64d425fe-1c29-4f9c-b3f8-5d484eb06f57</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c427c203-8f00-4b6d-bcd2-d5afddb0e3d6/web/1_1728896922111.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>144.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010599164922</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4520655950</g:id>
      <g:title>babybrezza</g:title>
      <g:description>Used for a couple of months,working in a excellent shape</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/737eecf2-3ef1-41b7-a08e-1eaea43706b1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ff379c9b-df0d-435f-b13b-615f4887dc65/web/image_picker_447F7EE8-40B1-49FB-B799-8884F3982A65-19405-0000134E9DA95869.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045206559501</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9810767408</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/af7074dc-eaa4-4cd3-9793-a5b32fb3126e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/aae5939e-73e7-4a59-a62c-76f98f4b5769/web/1_1727440889602.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098107674088</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2323722066</g:id>
      <g:title>EleTab Dual Arm Monitor Desk Mount Height Adjustable, Tilt, Swivel, Counterbalance Gas Spring Stand | VESA Bracket Arm Fits Most Screens 13" to 27" (STAND-V002O)</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemFULL MOTION: EleTab dual monitor arms allow you to twist and turn your monitors to help improve group meetings as well as your individual working experience. Allow you to multi-task and maximize your performance. GAS SPRING ARM: Provide a height adjust range of 6. 3" to 16. 1". The gas spring device perfectly balances the weight of the display and provides a smooth adjustment motion. UNIVERSAL FIT: EleTab dual monitor mount for all shapes and sizes 17" - 27" and each arm can hold up to 14. 3 pounds! Supports VESA 75 x 75 mm and 100 x 100 mm. Technical DetailsBrand ‎EleTabProduct Dimensions ‎40. 49 x 30. 51 x 16. 99 cm; 173. 5 gItem model number ‎8541636672Manufacturer ‎New-starAre Batteries Included ‎NoItem Weight ‎173 g</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ec407dd8-a4f3-4efa-bb01-c5259cad8b43</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1af57b95-b7f5-4a48-b869-86098c71f92f/web/1_1728908006987.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0023237220669</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3540337696</g:id>
      <g:title>Honor X9b Dual SIM 5G Sunrise Orange 12GB RAM 256GB - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Drop Resistance Certification / 5-fold Eye Protection[12GB RAM + 25G GB Memory] Enjoy great performance &amp;amp; plenty of room for photos, movies, songs, and apps—and 20GB Super large memory(RAM Turbo)108MP Lossless Capture Camera, 108MP main Camera/ Motion Capture/ 3X lossless Zoom[Superfast 5G performance] Unleash entertainment at 5G speed with the Qualcom Snapdragon, a powerful octa-core processor with frequencies up to 2. 1GHz. [Massive battery and speedy charging] Work and play nonstop with a long-lasting 5800mAh battery, then recharge quickly. OverviewA luxury look and Xtra power, Honor X9b 5G is designed to stand out with HONOR Ultra-Bounce Anti-Drop Display 360° Anti-Drop Protection, 6. 78" Amoled+ 120Hz display. Capture incredibly clear photos and smoother videos with a 108MP+5MP+2MP camera system featuring motion capture &amp;amp; 3X lossless zoom. Honor X9b 5G is a device you will fall in love with at first touchSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 16 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 16 - 31. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 5800 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 185 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 78 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Sunrise OrangeDisplay Type AMOLEDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13Processor Number Qualcomm snapdragon SM6450Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDAudio Jack Type-CWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 163. 6 mmProduct Height 75. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 7. 98 mmSensor Fingerprint Scanner, Accelerometer, Proximity SensorsModel Number ALI-NX1Model Name X9bPrimary Camera (MP) 108+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/59dbbecd-1953-4b4e-9979-c650af000d99</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d60cb044-bcc1-4939-ac6d-a101cb61512a/web/7_1728906434026.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>925 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035403376964</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2080453634</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple Watch 8</g:title>
      <g:description>Selling my apple watch 8 (41 mm) with originl straps and charger. Box isn't included</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fc610163-2b03-4b36-9f98-9e2ff683ae4e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/94de939e-4358-4d9f-9af9-b189f065950d/web/1_1711347180893.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020804536345</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3033731789</g:id>
      <g:title>OIVO Switch OLED Case for Nintendo Switch OLED Accessories, Switch Carrying Case with Stand, Switch Portable Travel Bag with Game Storage for Nintendo Switch/Switch OLED Model (2021)</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemCarrying Case for Nintendo Switch OLED Mode&amp;amp;Nintendo Switch: This case designed for Nintendo Switch OLED mode/original switch. It can be transformed into a desktop stand, with removable hand strap allows comfortable holding or carrying, perfect for travel. Travel Case with Stand for Playing: This travel case doubles up as a way to play your console in tabletop mode. The centerfold has two straps on either side, which strap your Switch's tablet section down nicely, allow you play games often almost anywhere. Large Storage: This carrying case has dedicated compartments for all your gaming needs. It can accommodate a Switch Console with joycon, and up to 10 game cards. The top mesh pocket is also capable to hold two Joy-Cons and AC adapter. Unique Protect Design: The Sturdy and splash-proof hard shell has raised areas to prevent pressure from being applied directly to the joysticks and buttons. which guarantees your Switch console always safe from knocks, bumps and drops; additional soft interior protects and covers the screen from scratches while the case is closed. Products Guarantee: Sturdy hard shell; heavy-duty and durable world-leading YKK zipper; friendly support team; 12 months worry-free replacement for any defective products due to production process.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/33b8deb7-ae3e-4a80-bc82-cbaea8eea731</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e0d62f54-65f9-4faf-b00d-59f7e61a8dd7/web/1_1728891833698.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>49.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030337317892</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8784905146</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ea2ccf61-abe8-4e55-a6ed-d5773472fcb8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/15d8c291-73e1-4983-b779-a165156df917/web/1_1728634708657.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087849051462</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1437805180</g:id>
      <g:title>OIVO PS5 Charging Station, OIVO 2H Fast PS5 Controller Charger for Playstation 5 Dualsense Controller, Upgrade PS5 Charging Dock with 2 Types of Cable, PS5 Charger for Dual PS5 Controller, USB</g:title>
      <g:description>About this item【2 HOURS FAST PS5 CHARGING DOCK 】This ps5 controller charger is specially designed to charge 2 PS5 controllers at the same time, powered by PS5 console through 2 kinds of cable included. This ps5 charger kit is the best replacement for official docking station【SAY GOOD BYE TO 5V/3A POWER ADAPTER】This PS5 charging station has built-in Quick &amp;amp; Safe smart chip to increase voltage, it is powered by playstation 5 console through 2 kinds of cable included, 1×USB-C to USB-C cable, 1× 2 in 1 USB-C cable, rapidly charge two PS5 controllers in 2 hours. 【LED INDICATORS】The LED the screen will blink while in charging status, both sides of it are provided with ambient lighting effect, this icons will change from blue and red while actively charging and revert back to blue once fully charged. 【ENERGY-SAVING DESIGN】After hearing some suggestions from ps5 gamers, upgraded with On/Off switch near input port, very convenient to turn it off while in standby status. it’s a must need ps5 accessories for playstation 5 gamers who have multiple ps5 controllers. 【EASY TO USE】 Just connect the ps5 charger dock with playstation 5 console, and place two dualsense controllers on the ps5 charger cradle, the charging port on dock is firm and keeps the ps5 controller securely seated. (Note: (Please tear the Offering anti-scratch film on front screen）</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b5ea980e-c824-4a0b-a28f-2d4a61330cd7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/930ea381-ba54-45fc-ab28-7b4acada3147/web/1_1728887324860.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>58.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014378051809</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5594993274</g:id>
      <g:title>Mount-It! Single Monitor Arm Desk Mount | Gas Spring Monitor Arm | Full Motion Articulating Height Adjustable | Fits 21 22 23 24 27 30 32 Inch VESA Compatible Computer Screen | Clamp and Grommet Base</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemUNIVERSAL SINGLE MONITOR ARM MOUNT: Fits all brands of 19 20 21 24 27 29 30 32 inch computer screens, with a maximum support weight of 20 pounds each, using the 75x75mm or 100x100mm VESA square bolt hole pattern found on the back of the monitors. Comes with interchangeable C-clamp or grommet base mount for use on desktops up to 3. 3 inches thick. FEATURES: Gas spring monitor arm is heavy duty, counterbalanced and makes for effortless adjustments and comes with integrated, hide-away cable management. Aircraft grade aluminum alloy construction will stand the test of time. FULLY ADJUSTABLE: Single arm monitor mount can tilt, swivel, raise and/lower (see 6th image down for details). Screen can be rotated a full 360 degrees for portrait or landscape orientation. Use included hex key to turn the hex bolt on top of computer monitor arm to adjust the gas spring tension to hold screens in place (please see 5th image down for reference). EASY INSTALLATION: Monitor arm desk mount quickly mounts to desks and comes with all mounting hardware, tools, and instructions necessary for assembly. Quick-release detachable VESA plate mounts to back of monitor first, then slides onto arm in seconds! See instructional video for additional tips on functionality and assembly. US-BASED CUSTOMER SUPPORT: Our friendly and responsive customer support team is available to answer any questions you may have and mount comes with a 5-YEAR WARRANTY. Technical DetailsManufacturer ‎Mount-It!Part number ‎MI-1771BItem Weight ‎192 gProduct Dimensions ‎42. 93 x 33. 27 x 11. 68 cm; 192. 78 gItem model number ‎MI-1771BSize ‎Single MonitorColor ‎BlackStyle ‎GrayFinish ‎Solid SteelMaterial ‎OtherInstallation Method ‎stand-mounted-installationItem Package Quantity ‎1Plug Profile ‎Tabletop MountSpecification met ‎certified frustration-freeIncluded components ‎All Necessary Hardware, Single Monitor Mount With Gas Spring ArmBatteries Included? ‎NoBatteries Required? ‎No</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/40898333-3345-4298-8670-ab8a14a2d703</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3ca4eae2-85ed-44ed-97ca-dc9e44e9fd98/web/1_1728894630921.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>84.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055949932745</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3642408557</g:id>
      <g:title>De'Longhi Autentica Cappuccino Bean-To-Cup Coffee Machine</g:title>
      <g:description>Autentica Cappuccino Bean-To-Cup Coffee Machine 1. 4 L 1450. 0 W ETAM 29. 660. SB Silver/BlackHighlightsAutomatic Coffee Machine offering the Bean-to-Cup functionality; preparing Espresso and Cappuccino has never been so easy thanks to the touch control panel and the one touch technologyEnjoy a wide variety of espresso based drinks at the touch of a button: Espresso, Coffee, Long Doppio+; easily customize aroma level and coffee length according to your tasteCreates frothed or steamed milk to serve exquisite drinks; the carafe’s thermal double-wall keeps milk at an ideal temperature when out of the fridge and is self-cleaningSlim and elegant design of a coffee machine for barista-quality coffee at homeThe carafe comes with an integrated clean function: After beverage preparation, all parts in contact with milk are automatically washed with hot water and steam. SpecificationsColour NameSilver/BlackCapacity1. 4 LWattage1450 WModel NumberETAM 29. 660. SBModel NameETAM 29. 660. SB</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5e558528-5742-4bf3-9159-b1dd1623d771</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4e927233-1511-45e6-8d2e-11d94b6912a5/web/1_1728894392261.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036424085576</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8522280229</g:id>
      <g:title>Vivos Dual LCD LED Monitor Desk Mount Stand with C-clamp and Bolt-Through Grommet Options | Heavy Duty Fully Adjustable Arms Hold Two (2) Screens up to 27" (STAND-V002)</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemFULL ARTICULATION Adjustable arm offers 80 to 90 degree tilt, 180 degree swivel, 360 degree rotation, and height adjustment along the center pole. Monitor can be placed in portrait or landscape shapesINTEGRATED CABLE MANAGEMENT Keep your power and AV cables clean and organized with detachable cable clips on the arms and center poleEASY INSTALLATION Mounting your monitors is simple process with detachable VESA bracket plates. We provide step by step manual and the necessary tools hardware for assemblyTechnical DetailsBrand ‎VivosProduct Dimensions ‎15. 88 x 15. 24 x 44. 45 cm; 64. 86 gItem model number ‎STAND-V002-crManufacturer ‎OtherAre Batteries Included ‎NoItem Weight ‎64. 8 g</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d1424cbb-9511-4940-9134-80fafa6a766d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ca4445ed-a315-426b-aa5a-027baa9fd13b/web/1_1728896306998.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>65.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085222802298</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6755418837</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + ESIM Pink 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>SAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 1TB Storage, Pink, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BLIHMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b4acd1c4-99b9-4e64-a1af-07b5445453be</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1065b068-6a5d-4fac-b49e-17e016cb8687/web/1_1728909648184.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0067554188370</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6434277276</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - White Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN13</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b08d0c75-5b5c-4cca-985f-d22ca8ad2f12</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/68e0240a-36ca-49c2-8c9f-0c184b6f52af/web/1_1728908571200.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064342772766</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7601602236</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWL3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f0c7d159-69e1-4c2b-b3d9-29917b0c72e2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/23c7190a-499e-40a6-b96c-6cba673a57f2/web/1_1728908022973.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0076016022367</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8294818468</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Natural Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN33</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c62c9ee-4f80-4de3-8f9e-2c2abf4fa0c5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a3114cd5-3600-4466-8d62-423dc53db9b4/web/1_1728907294574.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082948184684</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
