<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>3790123823</g:id>
      <g:title>GEEPAS 50" Smart Ultra HD LED TV With 4K Resolution, Android 14 , Frameless Design, HQ Sound / Multiple HDMI & USB Ports, Progressive Scan, Full Color Optimizer / Smart Features with Netflix, YouTube, and More</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights4K Ultra HD Resolution: Enjoy stunning visuals with a resolution of 3840 x 2160 pixels, providing exceptional clarity and detail for all your favorite content. Frameless Design: The sleek, frameless design maximizes screen space and enhances the aesthetic appeal of your living room, making it a stylish addition to any decor. HQ Sound: Experience immersive audio with high-quality sound that brings every dialogue and sound effect to life, enhancing your overall viewing experience. Multiple HDMI &amp;amp; USB Ports: Connect various devices effortlessly with multiple HDMI and USB ports, allowing for easy switching between gaming consoles, Blu-ray players, and more. Progressive Scan Technology: This feature reduces flicker and improves image stability, ensuring smooth playback of fast-moving scenes, perfect for action movies and sports. Full Color Optimizer: The Full Color Optimizer technology enhances color accuracy and vibrancy, ensuring that every hue is displayed as intended for a lifelike viewing experience. Progressive Scan: This feature enhances the quality of video playback by reducing flicker and improving image stability. It ensures that fast-moving scenes are displayed smoothly, making it ideal for action movies and sports. Smart TV: This TV is equipped with smart technology, allowing you to access a variety of streaming services and apps directly from the screen. Enjoy seamless browsing and a user-friendly interface that makes finding your favorite shows and movies a breeze. AV Mode: The AV mode automatically adjusts sound and picture quality depending on the content you're watching, providing the best audiovisual experience for movies, sports, and gaming. Brightness/Contrast: Featuring 200 cd/m2 brightness and a 3000:1 contrast ratio, this TV delivers sharp and vibrant images with deep blacks and bright whites for enhanced picture quality. Energy Saving Technology: Equipped with energy-saving features, this TV optimizes power consumption without compromising performance, ensuring an eco-friendly viewing experience. Convenience: Progressive scan, UHD, color temperature adjustment. OverviewThe Geepas 50" Ultra HD Smart LED TV is designed to transform your home entertainment experience with its stunning 4K resolution of 3840 x 2160 pixels. This TV delivers exceptional clarity and detail, making every movie, show, and game come to life. The frameless design not only enhances the aesthetic appeal of your living space but also maximizes the screen area, allowing you to immerse yourself fully in the action. Equipped with smart technology, the offers seamless access to a variety of streaming services, including Netflix, YouTube, and more. The user-friendly interface makes it easy to navigate through apps and settings, ensuring that you can find your favorite content quickly. The high-quality sound system complements the stunning visuals, providing an immersive audio experience that enhances every scene. Connectivity is a breeze with multiple HDMI and USB ports, allowing you to connect various devices such as gaming consoles, Blu-ray players, and external storage. The TV also features Progressive Scan technology, which reduces flicker and improves image stability, making it ideal for fast-paced action scenes. With its Full Color Optimizer, colors are rendered accurately and vibrantly, ensuring that every hue is displayed as intended. Whether you're hosting a movie night or enjoying a quiet evening at home, the Geepas 50" Ultra HD Smart LED TV promises to elevate your entertainment experience, making it a must-have for any media enthusiast. SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 3Video Format 4K Ultra HDProduct Weight 7. 7 KGScreen Size 50 inColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Remote Control , Users Manual and Warranty CardViewing Distance 3. 2 mModel Year 2024Features Android, Bluetooth, HDMI, Smart TV, USBModel Number GLED5023SCUHDModel Name GLED5023SCUHDNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3cda4087-cccf-421a-86c1-78e9a4a741c8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a96a49a1-6fd2-4c6a-a6bb-e4c3633ae8e1/web/1_1729851598229.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037901238232</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9216708476</g:id>
      <g:title>GEEPAS 43" Frameless Full HD Google LED TV With Remote Control| HDMI And USB Ports, PC Audio In | Chromecast build-in, Dolby Audio, DVBT2/S2| Wall-mount Bracket| GLED4314SGXHD Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights43 Inch Frameless Full HD LED Display for immersive viewingGoogle TV with Chromecast built-in for seamless streamingIncludes remote control with voice search functionality3 HDMI Ports and 2 USB Ports for extensive connectivity optionsPC Audio In for versatile audio connectionsDolby Audio for superior sound qualityDVBT2/S2 support for high-quality digital TV receptionWall-mount Bracket included for easy installationFull HD 1080p resolution for crystal-clear picture qualityBuilt-in Wi-Fi for easy access to online contentOverviewUpgrade your home entertainment system with the 43" Frameless Full HD Google LED TV, designed to deliver stunning visuals and seamless smart features. This TV boasts a frameless design, maximizing your viewing area and adding a touch of modern elegance to any room. With Full HD 1080p resolution, you can enjoy sharp, detailed images that bring your favorite content to life. Powered by Google TV, this LED TV provides a user-friendly platform that allows you to access a wide range of streaming services and apps. Chromecast is built-in, enabling you to stream content directly from your smartphone, tablet, or laptop with ease. The included remote control features voice search functionality, making it simple to find what you want to watch without navigating through menus. This TV offers extensive connectivity options with 3 HDMI ports and 2 USB ports, allowing you to connect multiple devices such as gaming consoles, Blu-ray players, and external storage drives. The PC Audio In feature provides additional flexibility, enabling you to connect your computer and use the TV as a monitor for a larger display. Experience superior sound quality with Dolby Audio, which delivers clear, rich audio that enhances your viewing experience. The TV also supports DVBT2/S2, ensuring compatibility with the latest digital TV signals for high-quality broadcasts. For added convenience, a wall-mount bracket is included, making it easy to install the TV on your wall and save valuable space. Built-in Wi-Fi allows you to access online content effortlessly, and the energy-efficient design helps reduce power consumption, making this TV an eco-friendly choice. The slim and sleek frameless design enhances any room décor, providing a modern and stylish look. The fast and responsive user interface ensures smooth navigation, while compatibility with Google Assistant offers hands-free control for added convenience. Advanced color enhancement technology ensures vibrant, lifelike colors, making every scene look more realistic. The TV supports screen mirroring from compatible devices, allowing you to share content from your smartphone or tablet directly on the big screen. Additional features like the sleep timer and auto power-off function help save energy, while parental controls provide a safe viewing environment for children. Pre-installed apps such as YouTube and Netflix offer instant entertainment, giving you access to a world of content right out of the box. With multi-language support and compatibility with various audio and video formats, the 43" Frameless Full HD Google LED TV is designed to meet the needs of a global audience. Enjoy a world of entertainment in stunning high definition with this feature-packed smart TV. SpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 3Video Format 1080pScreen Size 43 inColour Name BlackDisplay Type LEDOperating System Google TVViewing Distance 2. 6 mModel Year 2014Streaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxModel Number GLED4314SGXHDModel Name GLED4314SGXHDNumber of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/48c6f7dd-5281-478b-a8e9-1a76cce5884a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/47c955dc-d314-4a0c-b437-e4286fe130fd/web/1_1729857634319.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other brand</g:brand>
      <g:price>659 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092167084764</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
