<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9470959924</g:id>
      <g:title>DubaiGallery 360 Degree Wireless WIFI Light Bulb Security Camera with Motion Detection and two Way Audio system.</g:title>
      <g:description>Overview1080P &amp;amp; Panoramic Viewing: This bulb camera can provide you with a clear vision at any time. You can use the APP to control the camera to achieve 360 viewing without blind area. Wireless &amp;amp; Simple installation:This camera can be installed using a normal E27 bulb base(110V~240V),then you just need to connect the camera system to the router and open the app to setup the camera within minutes. Remote Viewing &amp;amp; Night Vision:This bulb camera can control the viewing angle through APP,you can access remotely view anywhere and any time through your Phone. Even in complete darkness, you can view clear images. Two-Way Audio &amp;amp; High Quality Service:Designed with built-in mic and speaker,this bulb security camera allows you to listen to your guests and to talk with your family in real-time. Motion Detection &amp;amp; Real-time Alerts:As soon as motion detection is triggered,this bulb will automatically send out email alerts and app alarm pushes. Thus,you can know what happened in your house and take appropriate precautions in time Overview Features: 1080P &amp;amp; Panoramic Viewing: This bulb camera can provide you with a clear vision at any time. You can use the APP to control the camera to achieve 360 viewing without blind area. Wireless &amp;amp; Simple installation:This camera can be installed using a normal E27 bulb base(110V~240V),then you just need to connect the camera system to the router and open the app to setup the camera within minutes. Remote Viewing &amp;amp; Night Vision:This bulb camera can control the viewing angle through APP,you can access remotely view anywhere and any time through your Phone. Even in complete darkness, you can view clear images. Two-Way Audio &amp;amp; High Quality Service:Designed with built-in mic and speaker,this bulb security camera allows you to listen to your guests and to talk with your family in real-time. Motion Detection &amp;amp; Real-time Alerts:As soon as motion detection is triggered,this bulb will automatically send out email alerts and app alarm pushes. Thus,you can know what happened in your house and take appropriate precautions in time. Specification: Sensor：1/3 inches CMOS Frame Rate：15 fps Resolution：1080P Illumination：0. 02Lux@(2. 0,AGC ON),0Lux with IR Lens：6mm Movement Tracking：Support Voice Intercom：Support two-way voice intercom Night Vision Mode：IR-CUT Auto Switch Movement Detection：Support Local Storage：Support TF card storage，Connect video/event recording， Maximum support 128G TF card Wired connection：Standard Powered by：DC 110V-220V Power consumption：&amp;lt;24W Working Temperature：-20°C ~ 80°C Non-condensing Working humidity：10% ~ 95% Non-condensing Package List: 1x Camera 1x User Manual 1x Bag of ScrewsSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box 1x Camera 1x User Manual 1x Bag of ScrewsModel Name Ip wifi cameraItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c3288acf-137d-4b40-b67a-9b73f69b1f2c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/914dfba1-4983-469b-9216-d287f2ee7a64/web/1_1724917557432.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>69 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094709599248</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2171310075</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Home-Security IP Camera Wirelessly Intelligent WiFi Cameras WI-FI Audio Record Baby Monitor</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsIt has the functions of AP hotspot, remote control, two-way voice, infrared night vision and mobile alarm. Simple operation and installation, quick completion. Clear Two-Way audio. Level 355 °, 100 ° vertically mobile phone remote flexible rotation. Realize no dead angle monitoring, arbitrary installation. SpecificationsColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box CameraModel Number PA4711B-EU_PModel Name Black &amp;amp; European standard wireless wifi camera pet baby monitoring network surveillance camera</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6251627b-1ea7-4522-bdba-b9de97fc31d7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0df807b8-4605-4b22-b8a2-528c52fb7339/web/1_1724916856885.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>98.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021713100757</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3032416182</g:id>
      <g:title>SUP 400 In 1 Portable Handheld Retro Console</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsMultiplatform Digital Device That Can Be Played On A Television. Support The Av Interface400 Games Update, In Addition To Big Screen, It Will Take You Back To ChildhoodEquipped With Rechargeable Lithium Battery And Usb Cable, Playing Games For 6 Hours In A RowConvenient size and light weight, perfect for traveling or going out, sharing with friendsEnjoy your game anywhere, at any time, with this portable, lightweight devicePlease feel free to buy. If you have any problem with the handheld game console, please contact us anytimeAlways the one that can raise your childhood memory. Enough games for you to play for a long time. Along with original sound for better playing experienceMany vintage games are included like Mario and Contra. So this is a great gift for kids as well as 90s adultsOverview400 retro games that can be played on a TV are incorporated inside the handheld 400 in 1 Sup Game Box, which also has a rechargeable battery and USB cord. After a full charge, the device offers 4-5 hours of nonstop play. Children, collectors, and aficionados of vintage video games will love receiving this game box as a present. Games are available in Chinese and English. We provide Mario, Tank, Turtle, Contra, arcade vintage games, logic and mathematical, sports, puzzle, arcade, shooting, action, racing, fighting games, strategy, adventure, card games, and more to fulfil your desire to play a range of games that you enjoy. It offers you a high-quality gaming and viewing experience, as well as assisting you in unwinding and feeling better. It also supports AV output and features a brilliant LCD screen. Meanwhile, because to its slim design, you could carry it wherever. SpecificationsProduct Weight 200 gColour Name Black/WhiteConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box Portable ConsoleType of Console Software Retro Handheld ConsoleProduct Length 10 cmProduct Height 16 cmProduct Width/Depth 5 cmModel Number 965478Model Name Retro Console</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b66a4d98-435e-4481-8f52-662cdb6600e0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1496431a-135e-40ff-9c93-1e856cfa39a0/web/1_1724933182803.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030324161828</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7545112454</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Desert Titanium, Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>STUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN23</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7d0f3626-e449-473c-b231-fa5b46f7ca95</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0b7bf3bb-904d-420a-9b45-aab7925b44ba/web/1_1727775645731.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4749 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075451124544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2964551012</g:id>
      <g:title>Generic Telescope Compact HD</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsHave the best view of your outdoor adventure project , understand that the 12 x image is clear and bright, and the 50 mm objective lens is wideEnhances the key monocular to ensure high-quality light transmission and brightness, making your line of sight brighter, cleaner and providing clear imagesNon-slip armor provides a firm gripSpecificationsColour Name BlackModel Number DT014</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0abcc0e8-9393-4dec-bbff-bbf9f76feb02</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/05c7ba69-d950-4012-aa9d-e07747dc1602/web/1_1724921896561.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>69 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0029645510125</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
