<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>7315667764</g:id>
      <g:title>e world unbox happiness e World Fixed Wall Mount for 32-85 inch screen – SH 65F - Heavy-duty Fixed TV Wall Mount I Vesa 600x400mm I Weight up to 60kg (Black).</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemProduct Dimensions: ‎ 65 x 15 x 43 cm; 1. 6 kgBULLET POINTS UNIVERSAL TV COMPATIBILITY- Our TV wall mount is compatible with most of 32"-85" TVs with VESA from 75x75mm to 600x400mm. Max. Weight capacity up to 60 kg. The wall mount is compatible with all major TV brands. Please check the VESA pattern, weight, size of your TV before purchasing. Can be mounted to single wood stud wall and concrete/brick wall. STABLE AND RELIABLE CHOICE - This TV bracket is constructed with premium steel materials, more sturdy and flexible. It has been stress tested to hold 4 times its weight. We are so confident in the construction, strength and durability of this wall bracket. It will keep your new TV safe. SPACE SAVING - Save valuable space and add a nice, uncluttered look to your household with our TV bracket. EASY TO TURN - You can slide both TV mounts left and right to make your TV center easily and get the most comfortable viewing experienceSATISFACTION GUARANTEED – We believe in the quality of our TV mount and satisfaction of our customers is our top priority. If you are not happy with our mount for any reason, Please feel free to contact us to get a FULL REFUND.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e7fc58f7-0a55-49cd-8575-45260491fdbd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e3b36549-c5c9-4b70-99ec-9d84fb58f4e2/web/1_1729074247460.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>34.95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073156677648</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5204908881</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 3 Lite Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Advanced Bluetooth 5. 2Upto 18 hours battery lifeAutomatic connectionSpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphonesAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number M2110E1 / M2133E1Model Name Redmi Buds 3 Lite (Black)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3970f707-b4ec-4b81-83cd-b89b8f3b8227</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fa2d3e18-daa3-47ab-89ae-871580cb52ca/web/1_1729077203044.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052049088815</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4152551560</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 5, Up To 46dB Active Noise Reduction,12.4mm Titanium Plated Diaphragm White</g:title>
      <g:description>Support for Google Fast pair. Supports dual device connectivity. Support for Xiaomi earphone appSupports three gear noise reduction and transparency mode adjustment, allowing for comfortable gear selection in different environments12. 4mm titanium plated diaphragm speaker. Independent rear chamber structure design. Four sound effects settingsOverviewXiaomi Redmi Buds 5 has a noise reduction depth of 46dB, Support broadband noise reduction at 2000Hz,12. 4mm titanium plated diaphragm speaker, Equipped with a charging box, The 40 hours battery life for one week use. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type True WirelessAverage Battery Life 16hrs - 24hrsAudio Jack Type-CAudio Headphone Type In-EarEarplug Type EarbudsFeatures Active Noise Cancellation, Bluetooth, Volume Control, Voice Assistant, External MicModel Number BHR7628GLModel Name Xiaomi Redmi Buds 5-White</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/288a5e02-5f54-408c-bd69-56fdf7f2a900</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/18eb8a88-1b85-493a-80f1-4eb25f665b09/web/1_1729077649562.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041525515600</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6412542089</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin USB-C PD Power Bank 10K (Fast Charge Portable Charger w/ USB-C + USB Ports, 10000mAh Capacity) Battery Pack for Galaxy, Pixel, iPhone more Black</g:title>
      <g:description>18W USB-C [ower delivery 10,000 mAh power bank supports fast charging for smartphonesDesigned with SMART CIRCUITRY that automatically detects your devices' power levelInput/Output USB-C port for your latest tablet, smartphones or any USB-C deviceLED indicator light shows power bank’s battery status to signal when it’s time to rechargeBoost Charge tested to be safe, complete with over voltage and over heating protectionSpecificationsNumber of Charging Ports 1 PortColour Name BlackConnection Type WiredFeatures Personal, Travel, Business, RechargeableModel Number BPB001btBKModel Name BoostchargeNumber of USB Ports 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e7cc7d01-a5ef-4f96-b7b2-de1d649a8b1a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/af13137e-cb81-4a9b-a79c-debe8c2be6d6/web/1_1729077388924.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>124 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064125420891</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2400690691</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 4 White</g:title>
      <g:description>Up to 35db hybrid active noise cancellation. 3 ANC level options and adaptive ANC modeAI noise reduction. Dual transparency mode10mm dynamic driver unit, 0. 006mm ultra-thin diaphragmUp to 30 hours long battery life with caseOverviewHi-Res Audio Wireless - Supports advanced LDAC audio codec: Redmi Buds 5 Pro is certified by Hi-Res Audio Wireless and supports LDAC audio codec with a sampling rate of up to 24bit/96kHz*, enabling Ultra HD audio with minimal distortion. Custom coaxial dual driver design - High-resolution, Hi-Fi sound quality: Redmi Buds 5 Pro features a coaxial dual driver design, which consists of an 11mm bass driver with titanium diaphram and a 10mm piezoelectric ceramic tweeter. This design delivers precise sound reproduction across all frequencies, ensuring a balanced performance with smooth highs, rich mids, and solid lows, allowing you to experience high-quality Hi-Fi sound at any time. Built-in immersive sound: Providing enhanced audio immersion across a range of content, Redmi Buds 5 Pro is ideal for watching movies on TV, computers, or tablets, delivering a captivating audio experience every time*. Vegan leather texture design - Understated and refined: For the first time, vegan leather was incorporated into the lower part of the black version of the case to provide a unique texture with a delicate feel and a more refined appearance. Marble texture design: The ear stem design incorporates natural elements using a multi-layer coating process to create a distinctive marble texture effect. Subtle yet distinctive, it suggests a personality both low-key and full of charm. Up to 52dB active noise cancellation: With industry-leading 52dB active noise cancellation technology, the upmost noise reduction capability has tripled compared to Redmi Buds 4 Pro, allowing you to enjoy your music in peace. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type USB Type CAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number 38561 / M2137E1Model Name 38561</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/46740ada-1794-4c6f-9592-902b0ed482ce</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0b2f00c4-c10f-444e-84c6-9ab482d6f67d/web/1_1729077795991.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0024006906913</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8286767765</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin MagSafe Charger, Magnetic Wireless Phone Charging Pad (For iPhone 14, 13 and 12 Series and Other MagSafe Enabled Devices, Power Adaptor Not Included) white</g:title>
      <g:description>MAGSAFE COMPATIBLE: Utilizing Apple's MagSafe Technology, this Belkin wireless charger delivers efficient and secure charging wireless charging. PERFECT MAGNETIC ATTACHMENT: Aligns perfectly with the MagSafe feature of your iPhone 12 to charge, and keeps your phone from being bumped and disconnecting from power while allowing you to easily snap it in place with one hand. TRAVEL FRIENDLY: A slim, portable design allows you to easily slip the pad into purses or laptop cases and take it with you anywhere. SAFE AND SECURE: An LED light on the stand indicates if there’s any charging interruption from a foreign object that could potentially harm your phone. OverviewSeamless magnetic attachment creates new iPhone 12 experiences. Designed so that you can keep using your phone while it charges, and place or take it anywhere with an extra-long cable. SpecificationsColour Name whiteConnection Type WirelessFeatures Indicator Lights, Wireless AC, TravelModel Number WIA005btWHModel Name WIA005btWH</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b3fcd19e-88ca-441b-91e7-51b26f893a9d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3730b18f-e0e6-44ee-b7f7-7c83681f3862/web/2_1729078158608.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>128 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082867677656</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4779693964</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI 1500 mAh 4G Mobile WIFI 5 LTE 195 Mbps | Up to 16 Device Connects White</g:title>
      <g:description>Travel The world with Huawei's super-fast 4G mobile Wi-Fi a pocket-sized solution to low-cost travel Wi-FiParental Control and guest network - A simplified system to help you ensure online safety on all connected devices and disconnect any device at the touch of a buttonPowerful, Rechargeable 1500mAh battery with 6 hours working time so you can stay connected for longerThis router supports up to 16 different users at once,4 equipping it to meet the needs when you are on a trip or in a busy office, or sharing mobile data with other devices. Display: LED Lights 1xSignal, 1xBattery, 1xSMSHUAWEI 4G Mobile WiFi 5’s Type-C port, which supports reversible plugging and is compatible with cables of other devices (such as mobile phones and tablets), is a marked improvement over the micro ports seen on previous generations. HUAWEI 4G Mobile WiFi 5 is 14% slimmer than its predecessor, packing a high-speed network straight into your pocket. 1With download speeds 30% higher than the previous generation, and upload speeds 110% higher, conferences and films breeze by, whether they’re on a phone, tablet or laptop. 3SpecificationsProduct Weight 90 gColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard 4GProduct Length 10 cmProduct Height 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 2 cmModel Number E5586-326Model Name E5586-326Wireless Standard Value 802 11 B, 802 11 G, 802 11 N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5ae32fdb-1d6e-4159-ab7f-c246cc358ca0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/baea2870-b789-4fae-97cf-027b5992832d/web/1_1729078806080.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>215 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047796939640</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9487878615</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin 25W Power Delivery USB C PPS Wall Charger with Included USB C to Lightning MFi Cable, USB Type C PD Power Adapter PPS enabled fast charger for iPhone 14/14 Plus, 13, 12, Pro, Pro Max, Mini, and More White</g:title>
      <g:description>Sturdy construction ensures longevity and durabilityMoulded from high-grade material to avoid chipping even through prolonged usageExudes an exquisite craftsmanship that manifests an accentuating showSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number WCA004my1MWH-B5Model Name BKN-WCA004my1MWH-B5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9a18cdcf-8726-4df3-b687-52221760fe76</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f2046731-6445-4a06-965d-8f426290ca81/web/1_1729078913740.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>84 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094878786159</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1804922235</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Wireless Charging Stand Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Built-in double coil, can be charged horizontally and vertically, you can use mobile phone while chargingCan be charged when you drop it, fast response Compatible with Samsung, iPhone, OnePlus, Huawei, QI Enabled Devices4mm sensing distance can be charged with a mobile phone caseIntelligent foreign object detection, multiple security protection Protect your device while chargingEco-friendly material, safe and durableSpecificationsColour Name BlackBrand Compatibility XiaomiPhone Case Material CombinationModel Number GDS4145GLModel Name ChargerItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/600a618b-f2c9-4fdf-bfc9-d0c138093189</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2aae74b0-7889-4715-9337-bebc823cfe2b/web/1_1729079008013.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018049222352</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4856733456</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi AX1500 ROUTER | Wi-Fi 6 High Speed Connectivity White</g:title>
      <g:description>Xiaomi Router AX1500 EU smart Wi-Fi 6 Xiaomi Mesh network technology supports various hybrid network methods that allow up to 10 devices to be connected OFDMA technology enables simultaneous data transmission from multiple devices IPTV supportSecurity: WPA-PSK/WPA2-PSK/WPA3-SAE wireless access control hidden SSIDPorts: 4x 10/100/1000Mb/s self-adaptive WAN/LAN (auto MDI/MDIX) 1x power connectorWiFi: 2. 4G Wi-Fi: 2x2 (supports protocol up to IEEE 802. 11n, theoretical maximum speed is 300Mb/s) 5GHz Wi-Fi: 2x2 (supports protocol up to IEEE 802. 11ax, theoretical maximum speed is 1201Mb/s)Antenna: four high gain antennas Standards: IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac/ax, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab Operating System: MiWiFi ROM Management app: Mi Home/Xiaomi Home App (Android, iOS), web support White color Dimensions: 247x143x178. 7mmOverviewXiaomi Router AX1500 supports IPTV multi-line multiplexing and can be connected with a TV set-top box, simplifying your home wiring for streamlined operation and a better viewing experience. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box 1x Xiaomi Router AX1500 1x network cable 1x power adapter 1x warranty card 1x instruction manualWireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard NModel Number AX1500Model Name AX1500Wireless Standard Value N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2c21bfca-a6bd-44f8-9f78-057bc463d09f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e4f31b58-c48a-4b85-a3ce-686315075a48/web/1_1729079287687.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>144 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048567334565</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5138817499</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Router 4A Gigabit Edition | 1200 Mbps | Dual-Core CPU | Gigabit Ports | Up to 64 Devices White</g:title>
      <g:description>Wireless dual-band 1167 Mbps for faster and smoother internet connectionsFiber-optic full-gigabit for high-speed broadband over 100 MbpsDual-band integration with one Wi-Fi name eliminates confusionThe smart error correction algorithm improves weak signals for greater stability and efficiencySpecificationsColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandWireless Standard ACModel Number DVB4305GL/R4AModel Name DVB4305GL/R4AWireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, 802. 3/3u</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9cf672be-425e-4ce5-9acf-00cb2fd4f9a0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/af7ab2ad-5254-4821-be1b-9a465272f1bb/web/1_1729079104297.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>88 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051388174999</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8350704379</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin Boostcharge Usb-C To Usb-A Charger Cable, Type C Cable, Usb C Cable For Iphone 15, Samsung Galaxy S24, S24+, S24 Ultra, Pixel, Ipad Pro, Nintendo Switch And More - 1M White</g:title>
      <g:description>Universal compatibility: Our boostcharge usb-c to usb-a charger cable is compatible with a wide range of devices, including iphone 15, samsung galaxy s24 series, s24, s24+, s24 ultra, pixel, ipad pro, nintendo switch, and moreVersatile type-c cable: Designed for convenience and efficiency, this usb c cable supports fast charging and data transfer, ensuring seamless connectivity across various gadgetsDurable construction: Crafted with high-quality materials, our type c cable is built to last, providing reliable performance and longevity even with daily useOptimal length: With a 1m length, this usb-c to usb-a cable strikes the perfect balance between flexibility and convenience, suitable for use at home, in the office, or on the goSleek white design: Finished in a stylish white color, our charger cable adds a touch of elegance to your charging setup while maintaining a modern aestheticOverviewIntroducing our BoostCharge USB-C to USB-A Charger Cable, the ultimate solution for your charging needs. With universal compatibility, this cable supports a wide array of devices, including the latest iPhone 15, Samsung Galaxy S24 series (S24, S24+, S24 Ultra), Pixel, iPad Pro, Nintendo Switch, and more, ensuring seamless connectivity across your entire tech ecosystem. Designed for versatility, our Type-C cable facilitates fast charging and efficient data transfer, making it indispensable for your everyday tasks. Crafted with durability in mind, its high-quality construction ensures reliable performance and longevity, even with frequent use. The optimal 1m length provides flexibility for use at home, in the office, or while on the move, while its sleek white design adds a touch of sophistication to your charging setup. Say goodbye to tangled cords and hello to effortless charging with our BoostCharge USB-C to USB-A Charger Cable. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteCable Length 2 to 3. 9 FeetProduct Length 1 mModel Number CAB001bt1MWHModel Name CAB001bt1MWH</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b2880060-583c-4a2e-910a-c2a197edca15</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/40f20f01-8366-4998-a136-87d8e331df53/web/1_1729077959292.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>30.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083507043794</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8195080704</g:id>
      <g:title>TP-LINK 300Mbps Wireless N ADSL2+ Modem Router White</g:title>
      <g:description>All-in-One Device ADSL2+ Modem, NAT Router, 4-Port Switch and Wireless N Access PointWireless N speed up to 300Mbps makes it ideal for heavy bandwidth consuming or interruption sensitive applications like online gaming, Internet calls and even the HD video streamingEasy Setup Assistant with multi-language support provides quick &amp;amp; hassle-free installationEasy one-touch wireless security encryption with the ‘WPS’ button and easy Wi-Fi On/Off buttonSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number TD-W8961NModel Name TD-W8961N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9c087267-ebf9-45ab-84c0-f3c06c3784cd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/85f307e4-a98b-4b37-aac7-16c419e6072e/web/1_1729078444594.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>81 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081950807048</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6933588854</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi OpenWear Stereo | AI Noice Reduction With Dual mic | IP54 Dust And Water Resistance | Hi-Res Audio | Cosmic Gray</g:title>
      <g:description>Open-ear design for all-day comfort and a secure fitHi-Res Audio with 17x12mm dynamic driver and optimized bass performance, LHDC10mm sound leakage reduction driver to keep audio personal beyond 25cm*Up to 38. 5 hours of extended battery life with charging case*Dual-mic with AI noise reduction for clear callsFlexible nickel-titanium memory alloy Sturdy, durable, and anti-slip17x12mm super-linear loudspeaker Unparalleled tweeter, midrange, and wooferAI noise-cancellation for calls Clear communicationSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CColour Name Cosmic GrayDepartment UnisexConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAudio Jack No Audio JackAudio Headphone Type Open EarFeatures Active Noise Cancellation, Adjustable Tilt Function, Bluetooth, Fast-Charging, ErgonomicModel Number M2319E1Model Name Xiaomi OpenWear StereoItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4a432ac0-6c3e-4a6c-bc16-d09c7b4ed98b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/586d693a-6a0c-4e20-bdba-65029863a75b/web/1_1729081294851.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>599 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069335888547</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4858073885</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi AX3000T 2.4GHz/5GHz Dual-band 1.3GHz CPU Router Supports NFC Connection White</g:title>
      <g:description>*Xiaomi Router AX3000T has four antennae, including one for 2. 4G+5G frequencies, two for 5G signals, and one for 2. 4G signals. *Xiaomi Router AX3000T product images on the page are for illustrative purposes only. Actual use requires connecting with a power cord and a network cable. *The data for the power supply stability test, hardware structural reliability test, memory stress test, multiple device simultaneous connection test, harsh environment test, and flash memory reliability test are from the Xiaomi Internal Lab Routing Reliability Test Report *The content and features shown on the above pages cannot be guaranteed to remain permanent and may change due to changes in copyright, commercial, or technical conditions. In case of any changes without individual notification, please refer to the actual contents and features of the product. *Product images, models, data, features, performance, specifications, user interface, and other product information may change depending on factors such as product batches or supplier replacements. Xiaomi may modify the above content. Please refer to the actual product and product manual for specific information. *The data comparison regarding signal coverage area is based on the Mi Router 4A Gigabit Edition. Data involved in comparison are sourced from Xiaomi Internal Lab. Actual user experience may vary depending on factors such as wall materials, house layout and size, and environmental interference. *Unless otherwise indicated, the comparisons mentioned on this page were made with Xiaomi products. Information on this page comes from our internal lab data, design and technology parameters, and data provided by vendors. Actual data may differ slightly depending on the test software version, the specific test environment, the specific version, and industry measurement methods. SpecificationsProduct Weight 1. 5 KGColour Name WhiteWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Dual BandWireless Standard NProduct Length 9. 7 cmProduct Height 22. 2 cmProduct Width/Depth 9. 7 cmModel Number RD23Model Name AX3000TItem Quantity 1Wireless Standard Value N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3bf67aff-6a72-4949-85fa-9f2271b7d72d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1fcdfbda-eeba-4250-934d-549e5b50f4f2/web/1_1729080861761.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>188 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048580738852</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2660970876</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mesh System AC1200 (1-pack) | 2.4GHz and 5GHz dual-band 1200Mbps | Covers up to 1,500 ft² /140 m² White</g:title>
      <g:description>Prearranged kit pairing2. 4Ghz and 5GHz dual band supportCovers up to 1,500 ft² /140 m²Full Gigabit Ethernet portSleek and minimalistic designEffortless self-networkingOverviewAntenna: Internal Antennas Network Port: 2 x 10/100/1000Mbps WAN/LAN auto-sensing port Indicator: 1 Mesh/Reset Button: 1 Power Port: 1 Protocol Standards: IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab Bands: 2. 4GHz, 5GHz 2. 4GHz Wi-Fi: 300Mbps (802. 11ac) 5GHz Wi-Fi: 867Mbps (802. 11ac) Operating System: MiWi-Fi ROM Wi-Fi Encryption: WPA-PSK/WPA2-PSK/WPA3-SAE encryption Management Applications: Supports Web, Mi Home/Xiaomi Home App (Android, iOS) Operating Temperature: 0-40℃ Storage Temperature: -40-70℃ Operating Humidity: 10%-90%RH (non-condensing) Storage Humidity: 5%-90%RH (non-condensing) Product Dimensions: 8. 9 x 8. 9 x 15. 4cm (per unit) Weight: 250gSpecificationsProduct Weight 481 gColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableSet Includes Router × 1, Power adaptor × 1, Network cable × 1, User manual × 1, Warranty notice × 1Wireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandAntenna Type InternalWireless Standard ACProduct Length 9. 5 cmProduct Height 22 cmProduct Width/Depth 9. 5 cmWi-Fi Range 1500 ft²Features App Enabled, Wireless AC, Wireless NModel Number DVB4452GL | RD13Model Name Xiaomi Mesh System AC1200 (1-pack)Item Quantity 1Number of Ports 2Wireless Standard Value IEEE 802. 11a/b/g/n/ac, IEEE 802. 3/3u/3ab</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fbb8e8a8-9c10-47b4-8107-dcad9b39e7eb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/94a40b1e-72a9-4f86-abc8-aef6a109912e/web/1_1729079588958.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>149 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026609708765</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9327346271</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI WiFi AX2 Dual-Band Home Router White</g:title>
      <g:description>Huawei's mission is to bring digital to every person, home and organization for a fully connected, intelligent world. To this end, we will drive ubiquitous connectivity and promote equal access to networks to lay the foundation for the intelligent world; provide diversified computing power to deliver ubiquitous cloud and intelligence; build powerful digital platforms to help all industries and organizations become more agile, efficient, and dynamic; redefine user experience with AI, offering consumers a more personalized and intelligent experience across all scenarios, including home, travel, office, entertainment, and fitness and health. Trending offers a new visual experience and greatly improved productivity via a more vivid home screen layout. Customize the Service Widgets13 to enjoy shortcuts to frequently used apps and services. Discover more easy-to-view features to make you workflow smoother, feel the smooth, delicate touch of its fine texture, whether it's the vegan leather version in lively Olive Green, or the classic version in refined Matte Grey. Different styles and same elegance n 2021, Huawei invested even more in research and innovation, as part of our greater efforts to sustain development in the future. We are sparing no efforts as we explore the endless frontiers of science and technology. We are also devoting efforts to identifying the needs of different industries and overcoming global challenges. Guided by our vision of a fully connected, intelligent world, we will work openly with the global scientific community to explore new theories, architectures, and technologies, which will support the ongoing development of the industry. Huawei works with customers to balance opportunities and risks, quickly responding to their needs and achieving sustainable growth. Also undertakes to provide customers quality-assured products, services, and solutions and consistently enable customers to experience our commitment in creating value for each of them. SpecificationsColour Name WhiteConnection Type Ethernet CableWhat's In The Box 1 x RoutersWireless Technology WiFi 5Band Technology Dual BandConnector Type RJ45Antenna Type ExternalWireless Standard 5GProduct Length 163. 5 mmProduct Height 29 mmProduct Width/Depth 257. 6 mmMax Data Transfer Rate 1500 MbpsFeatures Personal, Business, Ergonomic, Indicator LightsModel Number WS7001-20Model Name WS7001-20Item Quantity 1Wireless Standard Value 802. 11v</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/621534c3-3dbb-4575-a4df-53883a17f344</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/96694890-4705-4706-8d18-1708aee0e12a/web/1_1729079902021.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>137.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093273462712</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8383655455</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Smart Speaker Lite with built in Alex Bluetooth, Wi-Fi Black</g:title>
      <g:description>2Mics, with far field voice wake up supportPowerful sound with large 1. 75" speakerIEEE 802. 11 a/b/g/n, 2. 4GHz/5GHz, BT 5. 1 &amp;amp; A2DPSmart living with Alexa*Supports Spotify Connect*SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessModel Number 07GModel Name 07G</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9745c1ea-4323-4145-aaea-7b64d09322d5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/56f1d71f-3307-43b9-866b-bd01e6354a9e/web/1_1729078620834.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>112 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083836554558</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8221954293</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Poco M4 Dual SIM Power Black 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Expandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 58 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2408Colour Name Power BlackDisplay Type IPS LCDOperating System Version Android 11Operating System AndroidOperating System Number 11Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile, chargerNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2022Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 128 GBModel Number 22041219PGModel Name POCO M4 5GPrimary Camera (MP) 13+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c8ef35f5-fb95-4918-816d-46af6feb33bf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d73df0f9-45f3-414f-ae66-2d1da4554875/web/1_1729054532025.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>494 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082219542939</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8405320709</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi Buds 4 Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Hybrid active noise cancellation brings you closer to the musicDual transparency mode keeps you connected to your surroundingsUp to 35dB hybrid active noise cancellation3 ANC level options and adaptive ANC modeAI noise reductionDual transparency mode10mm dynamic driver unit, 0. 006mm ultra-thin diaphragmUp to 30 hours long battery life with caseSpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type WirelessAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number M2137E1/47554/BUDS4</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a3707d46-ea36-402a-8d49-0fbca13f4bf4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2e2f2a1e-d5ff-4eab-9316-8ce0c71363ff/web/1_1729061542567.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>154 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084053207098</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7396030933</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Buds 3T Pro | 3+1 Active Noise Cancelling Modes | Dual-Device Connectivity | Supports Wireless Charging | 24h Long Battery Life With Charging Case White</g:title>
      <g:description>Up to 40dB adaptive ANC Equipped with a powerful independent ANC processor, bringing up to 40dB hybrid noise cancellation capability. 3-mic noise cancellation for calls: clear calls even in noisy places. 3+1 ANC modes Light mode for Relaxing in a park, Balanced Mode for Walking in an office building, Deep mode for Noisy subway commute. And in adaptive mode, intelligently detect ambient noise level and choose the most suitable noise cancellation level for you. Dual Transparency modes in transparency mode, you can stay alert of your surroundings without taking out the earbuds. It also supports voice enhancement to keep voice frequencies clear, making it easier to chat with friends in noisy environments. Luxury dynamic driver 10mm dual-magnet dynamic driver coated with DLC diaphragm. Studio level sound quality designed with luxury unit. Surround sound Surround sound can position sound all around you and provide a true-to life listening experience Dual-device connectivity It can be connected with two devices simultaneously. The devices include smartphones, tablets, PCs, and other smart devices. Supports LHDC 4. 0 codec LHDC 4. 0 enables users to experience a better sound quality with more details. LHDC 4. 0 supports premium sound quality streaming. Track head movement Brings you a relatively fixed sound space. Every detail stays where it should be when you move your head. IP55 Rated Dust and Water Resistance It is rigorously designed and certified IP55 dust and water resistant. Worry-free listening while sweating at the gym. Comfortable &amp;amp; secure wearing Each earbud of Xiaomi Buds 3T Pro only weighs approx. 4. 9g. Focus ear buds design around tragus, antitragus and cavum conchae for comfortable and secure fit. Super large vent design creates air flow and balances the pressure around your ear. Supports Wireless Charging It is compatible with Qi-certified chargers. SpecificationsBattery Size 480 mAhColour Name WhiteConnection Type WirelessWhat's In The Box HeadphoneAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number BHR5177GLModel Name Xiaomi Buds 3T Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eea6f990-5a5a-4f0d-badf-76ba49536b0e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/af688441-17b4-4d0c-9917-fa3640b9bfde/web/1_1729062153560.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>217 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073960309339</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3869819885</g:id>
      <g:title>belkin Boostcharge Braided Usb C To A Cable Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Made Of High QualityFast ChargerLight WeightSpecificationsColour Name BlackCable Length 6 to 7. 9 FeetProduct Length 200 cmModel Number CAB002bt2MBKModel Name Accessories-182Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/022b6f59-4048-4fb8-88e7-c5ccd8046876</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/57d6ef04-9a7a-49c6-b7cb-b628c89edfd0/web/1_1729054765990.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>44 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038698198853</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7565847827</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Portable Bluetooth Speaker 16W GL | HQ Sound | Dual EQ Mode | IPX7 | TWS Red</g:title>
      <g:description>High quality soundAbility to connect two speakers for stereo soundLong working time of up to 13 hoursWaterproof IPX7Built-in microphoneSpecificationsColour Name RedConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life 13 HoursModel Number MDZ-36-DB | QBH4242GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/aff5cdde-098b-4638-aa02-838c5d3e6a3e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0e3b0df6-5610-4c8e-b735-15cfab4a90fd/web/1_1729057737851.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>109 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075658478273</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8028307080</g:id>
      <g:title>HUAWEI WS7100 WiFi Ax3 Dual Core Router White</g:title>
      <g:description>Wi-Fi 6 has made several improvements over Wi-Fi 5 to cope with the increasing demand for faster and more efficient Wi-FiAX3 and Wi-Fi 6-enabled HUAWEI phones are the perfect pair because both are equipped with HUAWEI's self-developed Wi-Fi chipset, which support 160 MHz frequency bandwidthHUAWEI Wi-Fi 6-enabled phones are able to send 6dB stronger signals back to AX3 in stable, 2 MHz narrow bandwidth using Dynamic Narrow Bandwidth technology, which is based on Chipset SynergyYou will be impressed with the blazing fast speed delivered by AX3. Thanks to 1024-QAM and 160 MHz frequency bandwidth, its theoretical speed can reach up to 3000 MbpsUnlike traditional routers, the AX3 supports the ability to connect a large number of devices without compromising performanceThe Built-in Firewall can Protect you from DoS/ARP AttacksOverviewNo Of LAN Ports-3,No Of Antennas-4,Processor-Gigahome Dual-core 1. 2 GHz CPUSpecificationsProduct Weight 143. 78 KGColour Name WhiteSet Includes RouterWhat's In The Box WS7100 WiFi Ax3 Dual Core RouterWireless Technology WiFiBand Technology Dual BandAntenna Type InternalWireless Standard 4GProduct Length 6. 27 cmProduct Height 1. 56 cmProduct Width/Depth 8. 86 cmWattage 5 WWi-Fi Range 490 ft²Storage Capacity 1 TBFeatures Business, Indicator LightsModel Number WS7100Model Name WS7100Item Quantity 4Number of Ports 4Wireless Standard Value WS7100</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/57653b9b-99ac-4d91-b64c-b283a5d82b41</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c83244bb-5847-4bb4-be6c-219cab248e2a/web/1_1729053380378.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>187.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080283070808</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7066537479</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Wireless Mouse Lite 1000DPI Ergonomic Optical Portable Black</g:title>
      <g:description>2. 4ghz wireless transmission. Full grip, strong controlLightweight body, flexible movement. 1000DPI precision sensor, stable outputLow battery prompt. Receiver built-in. Teflon foot padOverviewWireless mouse is one of the products of Xiaomi and XMWXSB01YM model is one of its popular mousses. It is equipped with a AAA battery and has a sleep power-saving function. The buttons are not procrastinating، the rhythm of the scroll wheel is clear، and the click and movement are very accurate and smooth. Its interface to the computer is USB. The mouse itself is an inappropriate size and a style full of the palm of your hand. Besides having a simple and classic design، it is durable and comfortable to use. In comparison to its price، has good quality. SpecificationsMaterial ABSProduct Weight 60 gColour Name BlackConnection Type RF WirelessOperating System WindowsTracking Method OpticalProduct Length 113 cmProduct Height 60 cmProduct Width/Depth 36 cmModel Number XMWXSB01YMModel Name Xiaomi Wireless Mouse Lite</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c26e259e-b74a-4831-af61-94f8fc3adc5b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a5b35431-6fa3-4043-af54-4629c5497a26/web/1_1729061035342.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>35 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070665374792</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5194487207</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi MI AX9000 9000MBPS Enhanced Version TRI-BAND WIFI6 Router Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Qualcomm IPQ8072 Quad-Core A53 2. 2GHz CPU,Dual-Core 1. 7GHz NPU,1GB RAM, 2. 4G Wi-Fi: 4x4 (IEEE802. 11ax 1148Mbps), 5. 2G Wi-Fi:4x4(IEEE802. 11ax 4804Mbps), 5. 8G Wi-Fi: 4x4(IEEE802. 11ax 2402Mbps)Antenna External High Gain Antenna External AIOT Antenna Heat Dissipation: Active Heat DissipationFrom The Physical Interface:1* 10/100/1000 WAN/LAN (Auto MDI / MDIX),1* 10/100/1000 WAN/LAN (Auto MDI / MDIX), 3* 10/100/1000LAN(Auto MDI / MDIX)Wireless Channel2. 4GHz Channel:1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13/ 5. 2GHz: Channel:36,40,44,48,52,56,60,64/ 5. 8GHz Channel:149,153,157,161,165Operating System: MI WIFI ROM, an intelligent router operating system deeply customized based on Open WRTSpecificationsColour Name BlackWireless Technology WiFi 6Band Technology Tri BandWireless Standard 5GModel Number AX9000Model Name AX9000Wireless Standard Value 802. 11</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/223f6b10-12b4-437f-9502-4be61934ebc1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/86179336-e3ee-45f2-b099-162139e9c08a/web/1_1729058411608.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>680 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051944872079</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4483672804</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Wireless Outdoor Security Camera 1080p Kit</g:title>
      <g:description>IP65 Dustproof And Waterproof No fear of high and low temperatures. Adapt to different temperatures, stable and reliable operation. It can operate normally in the environment of -20 to 50C*, endure the heat and cold, and guard outdoor safety in all seasons. WDR Technology + Smart Night Vision Backlight and dark light, all can be seen clearly. WDR wide dynamic technology, F2. 1 large aperture, backlight, dark light can also shoot fine picture details. 7m long-distance night vision, clearly showing the situation outside the house at night. 130°Wide-Angle 130° wide viewing angle help to capture more content. With 1080P resolution, the camera will restore the real scenes. A Variety Of Storage Methods Indoor video storage to prevent the leakage of shooting information. Optional local TF card, U disk, cloud storage are three ways to meet the needs of screen storage. With a new generation of H. 265 video encoding technology, it saves video storage space. Under the same network conditions, the connection is more stable and the screen viewing is smoother. Base Anti-Theft Design Illegal touch timely warning. The body adopts an anti-theft screw structure and a built-in gyroscope, When the fuselage is detected to be abnormal, the warning information will be sent to the mobile phone in time *safety information will be known immediately. PIR Humanoid Detection Changes outside the house, timely notification. Perceive temperature changes and object movements within 7m, start recording immediately, and push alarms. Intelligent detection of human contours, and through cloud AI face recognition technology, can judge acquaintances and strangers and give effective alarms. SpecificationsBattery Size 0 mAhInternal Memory 0 GBColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box Surveillance CameraCamera Resolution 2 MPModel Number BHR4435GLModel Name BHR4435GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/01ceff2f-0e56-41d4-89b9-a3bde94c3541</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/070b3160-9535-44ac-8653-5d861edcf8fd/web/1_1729061689870.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>248 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044836728042</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2124364842</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Sound Outdoor Portable Speaker 30W Black</g:title>
      <g:description>POWERFUL SPEAKER: With a power output of 30W, this Xiaomi Sound Outdoor speaker delivers high-quality sound and impressive volumeHEAVY DUTY DESIGN: Built for outdoor use, features a water and dust resistant housing, ideal for camping, pools, or outdoor parties. Long battery life: Enjoy up to 12 hours of continuous playback on a single charge thanks to its 2600mAh battery. Wireless connectivity: Bluetooth 5. 4 compatible0 for stable connection and hassle-free audio streaming from your device. OverviewThe Xiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W is a powerful portable speaker designed to bring sound to your outdoor adventures. With 30W output power and sturdy construction, this Bluetooth speaker will let you enjoy your favorite music with high-quality sound anywhere. Its long battery life gives you up to 12 hours of continuous playback, while its IP67 rating makes it water and dust resistant, ideal for camping, going to the beach, or just relaxing in the backyard. In addition, its compact and lightweight design makes it easy to carry. With a Bluetooth range of up to 25 meters, you can control your music wirelessly from your smart device. The Xiaomi Sound Outdoor 30W is the perfect companion for your outdoor adventures, offering you powerful and long-lasting sound in a portable, rugged package. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type Bluetooth/WirelessAverage Battery Life 6 HoursProduct Length 9. 2 cmProduct Height 18 cmProduct Width/Depth 6. 1 cmModel Number MDZ-38-DBModel Name 30W Outdoor Speaker</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/66c21dfb-2ae2-4240-8d87-52682540c12f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d606162e-f566-47b8-898a-238425ace20f/web/1_1729062015155.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>166 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021243648422</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8337929872</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Mi Xiaomi Sound Pocket Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Immersive Sound with 5W outputPortable Pocket designSupport Bluetooth 5. 4Upto 10 hours long lasting batteryTrue Wireless Stereo SoundIP67 rated dust and water resistanceFashionable and more personalisedRubber anti loss lanyardSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CBattery Size 1000 mAhProduct Weight 200 gColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothAverage Battery Life 10 HoursWhat's In The Box Xiaomi Sound Pocket x1 Charging cable x1 User manual x1Product Length 90. 8 mmProduct Height 74. 4 mmProduct Width/Depth 42. 6 mmFeatures Bluetooth, Water ResistantModel Number MDZ-37-DBModel Name Xiaomi Sound PocketItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8702899b-4f83-49a0-8cef-99b25298b81e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ba02f397-752b-49a3-b481-490fc8bddcf3/web/1_1729064398868.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>108 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083379298728</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5050751894</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro 40dB 3 Modes Noise Cancellation 28h Long Battery Life Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Up to 40 dB Hybrid ANC The active noise cancellation can reduce up to 40dB of surrounding noise. 3 ANC modes You can switch to 3 different ANC modes in different environments, Office mode for light noise, Daily mode for outdoor noise, and Airplane mode for loud noise. 5-minutes Charge for 2 Hours Usage Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro supports fast charging, only 5 minutes charge you can use 2 hours. Never be afraid of battery off. Dual Device Connection Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro can be connected with two devices simultaneously. The devices include smartphones, tablets, PCs, and other smart devices. QCC 5151 SoC Qualcomm QCC5151 flagship SoC provides experience with robust connectivity, enhanced functionality and utilizes Low Energy technology. aptX Adaptive Qualcomm aptX Adaptive codec provides crystal clear audio performance and dynamic scalability. 11mm Dynamic Driver Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro adopts an 11mm dynamic driver and tuned by Xiaomi Sound Lap, offering you an immersive audio experience. Supports Wireless Charging Xiaomi FlipBuds Pro is compatible with Qi-certified chargers. Up to 28 hours battery life A single charge brings you up to 7 hours listening time with ANC off, and up to 28 hours when coupled with the charging case. SpecificationsColour Name BlackConnection Type BluetoothWhat's In The Box HeadphoneAudio Headphone Type In-EarModel Number BHR5114GLModel Name BHR5114GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a7d815bb-46fc-4415-8b7a-dfb24a1c3e50</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e28b9cb3-3503-4159-96db-806a83ef5f27/web/1_1729064554903.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>295 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050507518942</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4202033783</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi 65W GaN Charger Type-A And Type-C White</g:title>
      <g:description>Fits in the palm of your handType-C 65W maxDual port fast chargingGaN gallium nitride smaller, lighter, more efficientSpecificationsColour Name WhiteModel Number 40095Model Name 40095Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/890524e2-d74f-4ec3-af8c-c67129fa2ce0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eb7fafdd-c3f3-41d1-9b57-52e39c81371f/web/1_1729058568871.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>100.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042020337834</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3484723926</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Solar Outdoor Camera BW400 Pro Set | Multi-Level Data Encryption | IP66 Waterproof And Dust-Resistant | 2.5K Ultra-Clear Night Vision | 10000mAh Battery | AI Detection</g:title>
      <g:description>10000mAh high-capacity battery132° FOV expanded horizonMulti-level data encryption. Protect personal privacyIP66 rating. Waterproof and dust-resistant4MP clear 2. 5K Ultra-clear night visionAI detection. Precise recognitionPair with the indoor base station. Worry-free installation and useBuilt-in solar-powered panel convert sunlight into power for night-time useOverview1/2. 7-inch sensor. Clear imaging in any environment. Day and night, clear picture quality in any outdoor environment. f/1. 6 larger aperture. Enhanced light sensitivity. Hardware-level HDR. Optimized for ambient light. Expanded horizon to eliminate blind spots. 132° wide FOV. 113. 3° Horizontal view. 58. 7° Vertical view. Clear night vision Feel safer at night. High-power infrared lights and full-color LED lights capture clear images, even when it's dark outside. 10000mAh battery. Uninterrupted online protection. High-capacity battery for a steady supply of power. 180 days* of continuous operation with normal use. Built-in solar-powered panel. Convert sunlight into power for night-time use. Solar cells conversion rate of 20%* for efficient power storageSpecificationsColour Name WhiteCamera Resolution 4 MPModel Number BW400 ProModel Name BW400 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/67853cfe-dabe-4a58-a258-3bb78f708015</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0be3a887-c39d-47a0-a1cb-65731c0e2cd9/web/2_1729058262511.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>419 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034847239262</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8694175787</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi S3 1.43-Inch Amoled Display Bluetooth Calling Smart Watch 5ATM Waterproof Sports Band Silver</g:title>
      <g:description>Heart rate sensor (including blood oxygen), acceleration sensor, gyroscope, geomagnetic sensor, air pressure sensor, ambient light sensorFast charging and long battery life1. 43″ AMOLED large screenThe new lug shape is smaller and slimmer, cleverly reducing the bulk of the watch and making it easier to wear5ATM waterproofOverviewThe ever-changing bezel has one watch with thousands of faces. The appearance can be easily replaced and the style can be switched at will. Supported by Xiaomi HyperOS, the refreshed experience is more convenient, Stunning performance, remarkable. 1. 43-inch classic large screen, HD, and high brush. Variety of bezels, the screen provides strong anti-scratch and anti-drop protection, but also lets the screen and the bezel as one, bringing the visual enjoyment of the full field of vision screen, a light, full of dazzling colors •The integrated back case design, delicate multi-ring, and warm texture. Screwless integrated process, sensor integrated concentric ring design, minimalist and more elegant. High-gloss coating for a warmer touch •12-channel heart rate detection module, accuracy, summit new heights. 20% improved accuracy of heart rate detection; 97. 95% average heart rate accuracy •L1+L5 dual-frequency GNSS five-star positioning, independent recording of the movement track •5ATM waterproof, very good in water. No fear of life splash, more can accompany your pool swimming trainingSpecificationsMaterial CombinationColour Name SilverWhat's In The Box 1 x Smart Watch , 1 x Charging Cable , 1 x ManualBand Size One Size (Adjustable Band)Smartwatch Dial Size 1. 43 inModel Number M2323W1Model Name BHR7873GL</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d657d026-12a1-4cbb-8786-4003241f843c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/be4a2709-8a26-4f6c-97b2-b9ad34e551a5/web/3_1729061294782.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086941757876</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3018754407</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Band 7 Pro Smart Bracelet AMOLED Screen GPS Blood Oxygen Fitness Waterproof Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Band 7 Pro Smart Bracelet AMOLED Screen GPS Blood Oxygen Fitness WaterproofWrist Voice Assistant Xiao AIQuick Call Reply5 ATM WaterproofOverviewXiaomi Mi Smart Band 7 Pro flaunts a 1. 64-inch AMOLED panel that supports 280×456 pixels resolution, 326PPI, and an Always-on display. Users get an option to choose from over 180 built-in watch faces. The gear has built-in GPS, NFC, GLONASS, Galileo, Beidou, and QZSS. SpecificationsMaterial PolyurethaneColour Name BlackConnection Type GPSWhat's In The Box SmartwatchSmartwatch Dial Size 1. 64 inFeatures Water ResistantModel Number Band 7 Pro Black (M2141B1)Model Name Band 7 Pro BlackItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/dbfc21e9-c5e6-451b-b9c5-921dbfcb140c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c896b5d9-afcd-40f6-a156-6ade3d12ebb2/web/1_1729061863175.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>166 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030187544073</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5342792939</g:id>
      <g:title>VISEART Sheer Velvet Pressed Powder Cream</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights Provides skin with an overall healthy glow and brightens your complexion Helps prepare a flawless base for a perfect makeup look Covers facial blemishes, dark circles and skin spots effortlessly Overview The highly pigmented formula of the Viseart Sheer Velvet Pressed Powder creates a medium to full-coverage and durably sets makeup for a long-lasting wear. Its lightweight texture blends perfectly into the skin for a shine-free, pore-less, photo-filter finish. Marketing Claim: Free of parabens, fragrance, sulfates, phthalates and mineral oil. Specifications Colour Name Cream Department Women Finish Sheer Target Skin Type Normal UV Protection High SPF Formation Powder Skin Tone Medium Skin Coverage Medium Model Number VVP103 Model Name VVP103</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/44ae6217-3fb3-4c53-ba04-dada3a0464d3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bdd2af69-06f8-44cd-92d1-a2155cad3224/web/1_1717410235444.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>VISEART</g:brand>
      <g:price>72 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053427929393</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8324987613</g:id>
      <g:title>VISEART Sheer Velvet Pressed Powder Cream</g:title>
      <g:description>Highlights Provides skin with an overall healthy glow and brightens your complexion Helps prepare a flawless base for a perfect makeup look Covers facial blemishes, dark circles and skin spots effortlessly Overview The highly pigmented formula of the Viseart Sheer Velvet Pressed Powder creates a medium to full-coverage and durably sets makeup for a long-lasting wear. Its lightweight texture blends perfectly into the skin for a shine-free, pore-less, photo-filter finish. Marketing Claim: Free of parabens, fragrance, sulfates, phthalates and mineral oil. Specifications Colour Name Cream Department Women Finish Sheer Target Skin Type Normal UV Protection High SPF Formation Powder Skin Tone Medium Skin Coverage Medium Model Number VVP103 Model Name VVP103</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cba3cca4-5e5e-4f76-b33e-61c8be8ce353</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76423039-f96d-4387-9aab-a17d3403adc9/web/1_1717410325219.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>VISEART</g:brand>
      <g:price>72 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083249876131</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
