<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>7815299285</g:id>
      <g:title>Renewed - iPhone 15 Pro Max With Facetime 256GB White Titanium 5G</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Overview"Renewed Premium: Never been used/Negligible use, but may have been looked at. These items have zero scratches or bruises. They are checked, renewed and re-packed in a generic/OEM box. You will get original accessories With 3 -months warranty. 1. Product is Never been used/Negligible use. It is Renewed like new with zero scratches and packed in a new generic box. It comes with original accessories. 2. Product has passed standard functionality checklist and has been renewed by certified sellers to Like new condition3. All products sold on are 100% functional. The grade of any product only signifies its physical appearance4. Product will come with 3 -months warrantySpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name White TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSGrade PremiumVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition RenewedModel Number iPhone 15 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d9da90ea-ad2f-4784-88c9-4872f07a5f2f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cd8df4e2-ee9b-4c6c-b90d-1b9f3af05f1e/web/6_1732516110344.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078152992856</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6336652489</g:id>
      <g:title>Meta Wearable x headliner RW4009 601/9A 50 Polar G15 Green Shiny Black</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCapture exactly what you see and hear with the new ultra-wide 12 MP camera and five-mic system. Take high-quality photos and immersive videos and share it all to Facebook and Instagram. Toggle between your phone and glasses cameraSeamlessly switch between your favorite tracks, calls, and surroundings with discreet, open-ear speakers. They’re custom built to deliver extended bass and high maximum volume for a rich listening experience, even in noisy or windy environments. Up to four hours of battery life, plus a sleek, portable charging case – which provides up to nine more charges on the go (4) – means you can focus on your day without interruption. The slim case (5) fits in your back-pocket or bag,Choose from an original frame and lens palette featuring timeless classics and bold new tints exclusive to the Ray-Ban Meta collection. Our improved companion app enhances the experience of your glasses. Pair multiple glasses to your phone, and manage them in one place. Take an interactive tour and discover key features via a new Home tab. Add special effects to content,OverviewRay-Ban | Meta Headliner With Ray-Ban Meta Headliner smart glasses you can express yourself with the most unique perspective there is – yours. Integrated with AI-enhanced wearable tech, the lightweight frame enables you to listen, call, capture and livestream, all while staying present in the moment. The Headliner panthos shape is a hybrid of the Wayfarer and the Round, bringing together the best of two icons. SpecificationsColour Name Shiny BlackStorage Capacity 32 GBModel Number RW4009Model Name RW4009Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1eb0856b-aba9-473d-abd3-4b556dbc1611</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6ad10f93-7336-4306-9193-c43dad7ecaed/web/1_1732118754579.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063366524894</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9403791888</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation VR2 Headset</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsEscape into worlds that feel, look and sound truly real as virtual reality gaming takes a huge generational leap forward with PlayStation VR2. Experience new sensations with stunning 4K HDR visuals1, ground-breaking new controllers and genre-defining games, all made possible by the power of PS5Experience breath-taking virtual reality environments in clear focus with 4K High Dynamic Range visuals and up to 120fps1, as two 2000 x 2040 OLED displays deliver over four times the resolution generated by the original PlayStationVR headset. Enjoy comfortable play sessions through a vast 110º field of view and a light, well-balanced Fresnel lensInteract in new and lifelike ways, as the PS VR2 headset detects the motion of your eyes1, allowing for heightened emotional response and enhanced expression when meeting fellow players online. SpecificationsVersion International VersionColour Name WhiteType of Console Software PlayStation 5 (PS5)Model Number CFI-ZVR1Model Name CFI-ZVR1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/50906d32-f9d5-4d4c-bd29-afef8969952c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bee0ad62-e066-4289-b94e-cda45dbb002f/web/1_1732011459978.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094037918889</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
