<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>7332771245</g:id>
      <g:title>SAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + ESIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLrge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 512GB Storage, Silver Shadow, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BZSGMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5d4c6b7c-d3a3-4f41-9540-ace3846117b1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3ecc57e6-e956-421e-a3dc-b8c255fe9463/web/1_1726836717826.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073327712451</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9919349350</g:id>
      <g:title>Microsoft Surface Pro4</g:title>
      <g:description>Microsoft Surface Pro4 Core i5 RAM 8GB SSD 256GBTouch Screen Detachable keyboard Original charger Neat And Clean No issueEverything working</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c0cd1d6a-99a5-4031-a056-7469a32fcfa1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2a3a0471-456c-4776-ac6a-90f922b65783/web/IMG_20240716_173103.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Microsoft</g:brand>
      <g:price>600 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099193493508</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8641481728</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FZKGMEA, SM-A055FZKDMEA, SM-A055F/DSModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/415fe784-ad54-4a5f-b2b9-2bcc2ad9e226</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ea9251cb-801e-433e-a6e1-ac25c8f18400/web/1_1726571092193.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>355 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0086414817281</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2080428609</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A55 Dual SIM Awesome Navy 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Design: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A55 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 32MP front camera, the 12MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 32 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 32 MP &amp;amp; AboveRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome NavyOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A556EZKWMEAModel Name SM-A556EZKWMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+12+5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7f8739f1-0920-4fc9-b8ed-93229e4979c4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/67aaaceb-3242-4ae5-8f39-549f70c6e5bd/web/1_1726556932045.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1369 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020804286097</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4046563196</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 13C Dual SIM Star Frost White 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Indian Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSmooth 6. 74" 90Hz Display50 MP AI Triple CameraMassive 5000 mAh Battery with 18W DP Fast ChargingPowerful Octa-Core ProcessorUp-to 16GB RAM with 8GB Expandable MemoryOverviewSmooth 6. 74" 90Hz Display | 50 MP AI Triple Camera | Massive 5000 mAh Battery with 18W DP Fast Charging |Powerful Octa-Core Processor |TUV Low blue light / Flicker-free Certification | Up-to 16GB RAM with 8GB Extendable Memory | MIUI Dedicated Optimization | Support NFCSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 192 gVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 74 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1600x900Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name WhiteDisplay Type FHDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidProcessor Number 12nm process, octa-coreFast Charging Supports 18W fast chargingWhat's In The Box Mobile Phone/Adapter/USB Type-C Cable/SIM Eject Tool/Quick Start Guide and Warranty Card/Safety InformationNetwork Frequency Band GSM, WCDMA FDD - LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores 8-CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 1080p@60fps, 1080p@30fps, 720p@120fpsWireless 4G/3G/Wireless/Bluetooth/NFCWater/Dust Properties Water Resistant and Dust ResistantModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 8. 09 mmProduct Height 168 mmProduct Width/Depth 78 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBSensor Virtual proximity sensor | Ambient light sensor Accelerometer | Electronic compassModel Number REDMI 13C 4GModel Name REDMI 13C 4GPixels Per Inch 1600x720, 260 ppiPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+QVGA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/21316adc-6277-470a-9a8f-f98470a24648</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2df6b028-b1e0-4376-8ed6-49399a5e2faf/web/1_1726557075625.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>411.05 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040465631968</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7340279840</g:id>
      <g:title>Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Navy 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 1TB Storage, Navy, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name NavyDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BDBHMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5c138593-7cce-4ebd-b0d4-b6aa1a7cd56a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c7029360-43e3-4efc-881e-00d65fec225a/web/1_1726561919287.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073402798400</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9827902199</g:id>
      <g:title>Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Navy 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB Storage, Navy, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name NavyDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BDBDMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2fe50c7a-6e46-4dcc-a5d0-2a5a5c8cfe25</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6c0f399c-84af-4a47-9c24-1f94f1c0438d/web/3_1726561222232.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>6199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098279021994</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3897545718</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN43</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8ed1564c-794e-4eb0-b044-46c362445abf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/93298253-4f5f-479e-8136-8a526047d5ab/web/1_1727088467215.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5650 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038975457185</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5421228005</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (128 GB) - Desert Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYMX3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/60fd3087-4333-4276-a3e4-2a2c099cec45</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9d1e2800-32f5-478c-a290-e0dbe975a1e1/web/1_1727087305403.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054212280057</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8982557383</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (256 GB) - Desert Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWJ3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b21feb54-d60a-48b5-8e6d-805a655ea234</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/264fa2ac-7845-4b1b-b465-54bd6e3794d9/web/1_1727092365508.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6300 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089825573838</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8583235351</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (512 GB) - Desert Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN63</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7268d88c-ecea-469b-969b-a1a36e519d25</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b8d85970-cf73-48cc-9ba3-66382268407d/web/1_1727091995510.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>5650 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085832353517</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8548399270</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWL3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ae9517fb-d0a4-4ea5-913c-fbd47d7fe243</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/13ea4973-01d1-49ad-8881-1dd33aa9be20/web/1_1727093327709.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085483992707</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7869620327</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (256 GB) - Natural Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWK3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/92c7186e-3edd-46db-aa4f-73723a06aae1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/983f584b-0ec7-4cc2-a65c-761693b3781e/web/1_1727092944601.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6150 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078696203272</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2560015926</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (256 GB) - White Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWH3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8526ffcb-d22a-4c09-8ca6-db886c515e4c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2bf13546-ce54-4e14-b7ee-f7afc030c1e7/web/1_1727093141789.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6100 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025600159262</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3090958477</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (256 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWG3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/04a93647-a324-4ec3-8d15-dd93f9f973a8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cc2944e6-5f05-48b1-a393-784e2c4053c6/web/1_1727092659854.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6100 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030909584776</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9254876967</g:id>
      <g:title>Nintendo Switch Splatoon 3</g:title>
      <g:description>7-inch OLED screen - Enjoy vivid colors and crisp contrast with a screen that makes colors popWide adjustable stand – Freely angle the system’s wide, adjustable stand for comfortable viewing in Tabletop modeWired LAN port - Use the dock’s LAN* port when playing in TV mode for a wired internet connection64 GB internal storage - Save games to your system with 64 GB of internal storage (a portion of which is reserved for use by the system)Enhanced audio – Enjoy enhanced sound from the system’s onboard speakers when playing in Handheld and Tabletop modesOverviewThis Nintendo Switch system takes on a totally fresh look from the new Splatoon 3 game. Ink up the Splatlands in style with this Splatoon themed Nintendo Switch – OLED Model system! Fresh features include; blue and yellow gradient Joy-Con controllers with a white underbelly, a white dock adorned with graffiti, and a splat-tastic design on the back of the system. Game not included. Colour NameSplatoonType of Console SoftwareNintendo SwitchModel Numberheg-s-kcaaa / 4902370549706Model Nameheg-s-kcaaa</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f99cb359-ef38-4763-ae83-ebfc041ac9c8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bf719857-d837-4d5a-81bf-87b4f97645b7/web/1_1727171851376.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092548769679</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7728644490</g:id>
      <g:title>PlayStation 5 Slim Console (International Version) Disc Version With Controller - New Model 2023</g:title>
      <g:description>PS5 model is having same technology features that make PS5 the best to play are packed into a smaller form factor, along with an attachable Ultra HD Blu-ray Disc and a 1TB SSD for more internal storageThe new PS5 has been reduced in volume by more than 30%, and weight by 18% and 24% compared to the previous models. There are four separate cover panels, with the top portion in a glossy look, while the bottom remains in matt. VersionInternational VersionColour NameWhiteConnection TypeWirelessType of Console SoftwarePlayStation 5 (PS5)LanguageEnglishModel NumberCFI-2016 A01Y/CFI-2000 A01/CFI-2018 A01/CFI-1216AModel NameRZ021894186C</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ba454482-45ed-4971-8c8d-975977b93cf0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bd5966bf-1368-4f73-a45d-bfbec84cc3f8/web/2_1727171344411.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0077286444903</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9499984051</g:id>
      <g:title>Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 256GB Storage, Silver Shadow, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BZSDMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f9644cbf-a1cd-467b-ac46-e2586f66426a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c43d1d29-4f65-4dbc-9a41-9cd60e025974/web/1_1726559856420.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7199 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094999840518</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8438749381</g:id>
      <g:title>Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 1TB Storage, Silver Shadow, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BZSHMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d3d2a2e0-6c7b-410b-b941-cd0ffac0b12f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ef2d54bc-d93a-499e-b2f7-5a94c966002b/web/1_1726564543187.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084387493815</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3193948772</g:id>
      <g:title>Energizer E282SC Flip Dual SIM Feature Phone 4GB 512 MB 4G LTE Carbon Black</g:title>
      <g:description>Battery A powerful battery: 1400mAh is a big battery for a feature phone. Is it really useful, you may ask ! The new E282SC takes all the benefits of this battery using its new KAIOS operating system. We found the best balance to let you enjoy all of your favourite apps without worrying about running out of battery. Display A size matter : We have an excellent 4G, a new OS to enjoy all of your favourite apps, but you also need a good screen big enough to see everything in detail. The E282SC comes with a 2. 8 screen, the perfect balance to fit in your pocket and let a good comfort for your eyesCamera Live in a picture world! We're living in a world where everything is caught by an image, your first smile in the morning and your morning walk. The new E282SC is built with a front and a back camera to let you take every picture you need. Main Camera: 2MP. Front camera: 2MP. Android and Google: The mobile phone revolution for everyone: Enjoy all the advantages of a smartphone on your mobile. The KaiOS operating system is designed to bring essential smartphone functions to classic mobile phones. The Energizer® E282SC enables you to access 4G Internet, Wi-Fi and GPS, to download apps, plus lots of other services. 4G LTE speed The speed of a "CLAP" : He has everything you need up to date to let you enjoy the ride. From 2G to 4G/LTE you'll be able to enjoy all of your favourite apps with the speed you deserve. All of your tweet, picture or even mail will be live in no time. Dual SIM Dual SIM or SD card : The E282SC can support two SIM cards or a SIM card and a SD card. You can increase storage memory or benefit from two separate lines in a single mobile. You can combine pro and personal, national and international packages or choose two different operators for better network coverage. Type : micro SIM. SD card up to 32GB. Design Bring Color in your life : You need a personalized phone: we bring 8 original colours for the E282SC. 4 bright colours with rhinestones that will make your heart flip: gold, silver, sparkling pink and white. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 1. 1 GHzRAM Size 512 MBBattery Size 1400 mAhInternal Memory 4 GBProduct Weight 129 gVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 2. 8 inSIM Type Micro SIMDisplay Resolution 240x320Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Carbon BlackDisplay Type TFTDisplay Resolution Type WVGAOperating System Version Android 12Operating System KaiOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number GE8100Processor Number MT6731Fast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Feature PhoneNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name MediaTek MT SeriesNumber of Cores Quad CoreGlass Technology SapphirePrimary Camera Feature SingleFlash LEDVideo Recording Resolution Type 288pBattery Type Lithium IonWater/Dust Properties Dust ResistantFinish PlasticModel Year 2022Network Type 4GProduct Length 58 mmProduct Height 108. 5 mmProduct Width/Depth 18. 5 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 32 GBSensor Proximity Sensors, sp02, AccelerometerModel Number UPENE282SCARCModel Name UPENE282SCARCPrimary Camera (MP) 2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/db0973b2-3f97-4021-931e-4698b475d886</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1e3405d9-9de7-4908-847b-8b6f498bbc4f/web/1_1726563485606.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Other</g:brand>
      <g:price>190 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031939487723</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1890352135</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Black Titanium</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN03</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/eb96e3df-6271-425e-bb2a-d3eb0b9fd1aa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7dd758ab-9a5c-4772-9f43-742d80176b3c/web/1_1727334175008.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018903521355</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9925513532</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Natural Titanium</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN33</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a96887a9-2fa7-43ca-872f-b6eddf70e9ad</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c60ac4f6-b57f-4d29-b267-c614e3df4cd7/web/1_1727333972018.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099255135322</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7618653458</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Smart TV, Crystal UHD, DU8000, 55 Inch, 2024, Dynamic Crystal Color, 4K Upscaling, Tizen OS, AirSlim Design UA55DU8000UXZN Titan Gray</g:title>
      <g:description>Dynamic Crystal Color: Take your UHD experience to another level with our advanced phosphor technology. Dynamic Crystal Color delivers lifelike variations of colors, so you see subtle details of each shade4K Upscaling: Powerful 4K upscaling ensures you get up to 4K resolution for the content you loveSamsung Tizen OS: Get more out of your TV with the latest apps &amp;amp; services on Samsung Tizen OS. Enjoy free live TV channels and thousands of movies with Samsung TV Plus, and seamless cloud gaming with Gaming HubAirSlim Design: Sleek and slim. The mind-blowing slim design of your TV fits harmoniously with its surroundingsBuilt-in SmartThings Hub: With a built-in SmartThings hub in your TV, you can seamlessly connect and control smart devices compatible with Matter and HCA standards, without needing any additional deviceOverviewSamsung Smart TV, Crystal UHD, DU8000, 55 Inch, 2024, Dynamic Crystal Color, 4K Upscaling, Samsung Tizen OS, AirSlim Design, Titan Gray, UA55DU8000UXZNSpecificationsTV HDMI Ports 3Video Format 4KProduct Weight 22 KGVersion UAE VersionScreen Size 55 inRefresh Rates 100HzColour Name Titan GrayDisplay Type LEDOperating System TizenWhat's In The Box TV, User Manual, Power Cable, Remote ControlViewing Distance 3. 2 mStreaming Services Netflix,YouTube,Disney+,Apple Tv+,Starzplay Arabia,Osn Streaming,Mbc Shahid ,Eros Now,Viu,Sonyliv,HBO MaxProduct Length 2. 57 cmProduct Height 70. 88 cmProduct Width/Depth 123. 21 cmModel Number UA55DU8000UXZNModel Name DU8000Number of USB Ports 2Number of HDMI Ports 3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5ef0bb99-8bda-4e7a-969d-d2f62214e871</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1479e9a0-a108-4b60-a663-918d5e6a6b3f/web/1_1726834459476.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1757 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0076186534585</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5721869698</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 15 Pro 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>A17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 1” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for a 3x optical zoom and 15x digital zoom. Up to 23 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. cificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMPrimary Camera Resolution 48 MPRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MTUF3AH/A,MTV53AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7e34a1c8-58e0-49da-b8e5-5866c9e9935c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9c35ffd6-93cd-4f68-9cd7-e85102bf8015/web/1_1726835630373.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057218696983</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1477496729</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 15 Pro Max 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 7” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for 120 mm of pure Pro zoom with 5x optical zoom. Up to 29 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro Max features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. iPhone 15 Pro Max has the longest optical zoom in iPhone ever. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4852 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MU6R3AH/A,MU793AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro Max</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2a63ed42-3278-4ca7-80b3-0f4107be5a99</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d7e3c437-1cb1-47d3-98eb-dfcdde257e6a/web/4_1727088818053.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014774967292</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4525068311</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Natural Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN33</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b5a387fb-c4e4-4cba-9681-7e138bb185b4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0574a871-6b8a-4b21-a392-16d79818af2f/web/1_1727087806815.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4850 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045250683115</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3211939897</g:id>
      <g:title>Microsoft Surface Pro4 4/128</g:title>
      <g:description>Microsoft Surface Pro4. Core i5, RAM 4GBS, SD 128GBTouch ScreenFREEPEN (For Touch Screen)KEYBOARD CHARGER No issueVERY good conditionEverything workingWhatsApp 0553779558</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/af1996b1-aa25-40cf-af32-40d49598fcce</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1d5a9371-7698-4859-92ad-bed19681b0f4/web/IMG-20240916-WA0008.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Microsoft</g:brand>
      <g:price>450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032119398976</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5972591430</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro (256 GB) - Black Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 3-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glassTAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 27 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYN03</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/47165848-c982-4107-9ce7-310c92fa28d7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/da4913c1-eb93-4606-b7a8-6b6c08506d05/web/1_1727091401902.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>4850 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059725914307</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4946380615</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Natural Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWP3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/82e158ed-bc8c-47b3-bab9-d0f9bcd5fb76</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ecba5e51-02e7-406c-aa03-8fa22fd29eb8/web/1_1727093514776.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6800 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049463806156</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5423149033</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max (512 GB) - Desert Titanium - HK Version - Dual Sim</g:title>
      <g:description>Non-returnableAbout this itemSTUNNING TITANIUM DESIGN—iPhone 16 Pro Max has a strong and light titanium design with a larger 6. 9-inch Super Retina XDR display. It’s remarkably durable with the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material that’s 2x tougher than any smartphone glass. TAKE TOTAL CAMERA CONTROL—Camera Control gives you an easier way to quickly access camera tools, like zoom or depth of field, so you can take the perfect shot in record time. MAGNIFICENT SHOTS—Thanks to a more advanced 48MP Ultra Wide camera, you can capture mesmerizing detail in macro and sweeping, wide-angle photos. Want sharper shots from farther away? The 5x Telephoto camera makes it easy. PRO VIDEO—Take your videos a whole new level with 4K 120 fps Dolby Vision—enabled by the 48MP Fusion camera—and studio-quality mics for higher-quality audio recording. A Pro studio in your pocket. PHOTOGRAPHIC STYLES—The latest-generation Photographic Styles give you greater creative flexibility, so you can make every photo even more you. And thanks to advances in the image pipeline, you can now reverse any style, any time. THE POWER OF A18 PRO—A18 Pro chip enables advanced photo and video features like Camera Control, and delivers exceptional graphics performance for AAA gaming. A HUGE LEAP IN BATTERY LIFE—iPhone 16 Pro Max delivers an incredibly power-efficient performance with up to 33 hours video playback. Charge via USB-C or snap on a MagSafe charger for faster wireless charging. CUSTOMIZE YOUR IPHONE—With iOS 18 you can tint your Home Screen icons with any color. Find your favorite shots faster in the redesigned Photos app. And add playful, animated effects to any word, phrase, or emoji in iMessage. VITAL SAFETY FEATURES—With Crash Detection, iPhone can detect a severe car crash and call for help if you can’t. MYWN3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9e927daf-3d8d-47ac-8266-9860ef89626f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/012c29b9-aaa9-4c7b-a495-6818e04eaaba/web/1_1727093682071.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6900 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054231490338</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5244899916</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 13C Dual SIM Navy Blue 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Smooth 6. 74" 90Hz Display50 MP AI Triple CameraMassive 5000 mAh Battery with 18W DP Fast ChargingPowerful Octa-Core ProcessorUp-to 16GB RAM with 8GB Expandable MemoryOverviewSmooth 6. 74" 90Hz Display | 50 MP AI Triple Camera | Massive 5000 mAh Battery with 18W DP Fast Charging |Powerful Octa-Core Processor |TUV Low blue light / Flicker-free Certification | Up-to 16GB RAM with 8GB Extendable Memory | MIUI Dedicated OptimizationSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 192 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 74 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Navy BlueDisplay Type LCDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13Processor Number MediaTek Helio G85Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDFinish PlasticModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 168 mmProduct Height 8. 09 mmProduct Width/Depth 78 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 16 GBModel Number 2311DRN14I | 23106RN0DA | 22120RN86C I 23108RN04YModel Name Redmi 13CPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+QVGA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0646900a-2e5f-442f-86e2-555ae59ee0d6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/971f19ab-d6dc-492d-a3c4-37da4f027759/web/1_1726575176841.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>285 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052448999163</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5601684984</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Silver 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign available in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name SilverOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FZSDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4c12c069-c118-4ae0-947e-fb6cdf88b463</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/26d8d8be-3a48-4e6c-805c-da1f40ba8fa0/web/1_1726574782179.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>325 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056016849843</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9132735720</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Blue Black 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Blue/BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZKIMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/185b19b1-1767-43f1-ad70-9bec3f30276c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2c7f06ba-7b59-4463-93cc-fb78d9c5ba9d/web/1_1726575151852.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>600 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091327357205</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6317117844</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Blue Black 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Blue BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZKDMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/1D6NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a2a844d5-8a87-4f1a-a797-91aec6c0cfd2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d61d1f3c-2094-4153-baea-915d024c6400/web/1_1726574557262.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063171178442</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6969523284</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Pink 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>SAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 1TB Storage, Pink, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BLIHMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fdca7c22-7e68-4324-bad7-780d0a1b9859</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e019b391-8be4-46e4-8e6c-5529dec31255/web/1_1726574644260.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069695232844</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1821517120</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Light Blue 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Display: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FLBDMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/1D4NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0d2aa8eb-80e7-4530-b7e3-bf5c90327fbd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8e94a699-d676-4304-9cbc-55084809839e/web/1_1726574325602.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>490 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018215171200</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1395921319</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Light Blue 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FLBIMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/15409472-2493-4f79-8ab1-f9996a7f090f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eee6ef74-de62-4083-9d4f-b5782302c4aa/web/1_1726571652094.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>600 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013959213193</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1966824910</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Navy 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome NavyOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356EZKPMEAModel Name SM-A356EZKPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5fd85be7-ac65-43a5-839b-378d9c6c81da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76361278-ae30-4b88-b370-6a48213676e5/web/1_1726573659471.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>900 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019668249102</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8516834440</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Yellow 4GB RAM 128GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name YellowOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZYDMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/1D4NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7a89ba09-7076-48e9-b2bd-fc4bcb0d204f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/542fafab-6f60-4af8-84f1-ab264395b7a5/web/1_1726571375737.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>440 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085168344401</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3833580142</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9b4c16b4-7343-4a45-8b9a-87f9b9d2f3c8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2239fde1-6d76-407b-ac4f-5c891873e01a/web/1_1726558163289.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>405 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038335801429</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5726687460</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 13C Dual Sim Midnight Black 8Gb Ram 256Gb 5G - Indian Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsRedmi 13c,8 gb ram 256gb,5gBrand new Redmi 13c with front and back cameraOverviewHighlights Smooth 6. 74" 90Hz Display 50 MP AI Triple Camera Massive 5000 mAh Battery with 18W DP Fast Charging Powerful Octa-Core Processor Up-to 16GB RAM with 8GB Expandable Memory Overview Smooth 6. 74" 90Hz Display | 50 MP AI Triple Camera | Massive 5000 mAh Battery with 18W DP Fast Charging |Powerful Octa-Core Processor |TUV Low blue light / Flicker-free Certification | Up-to 16GB RAM with 8GB Extendable Memory | MIUI Dedicated Optimization | Support NFCSpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion India VersionScreen Size 6. 74 inSIM Type Nano SIMColour Name Midnight BlackCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraModel Number Redmi 13C</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/de6bddbd-3ed4-4c70-8448-3135a417e72b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a022fab5-42ac-44f6-80a4-a25f5c767a78/web/1_1726556779849.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>580 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057266874609</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6694014804</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 14C Dual SIM Dreamy Purple 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Expandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5160 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 211 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 88 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1640Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Dreamy PurpleDisplay Type LCDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number Xiaomi HyperOSProcessor Number MediaTek Helio G81-UltraFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile, USB Type-C Cable, SIM Eject Tool, Quick Start Guide, Warranty Card, CPE Bag, Adapter, Protective Film, Protective CaseNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDAudio Jack 3. 5 mmModel Year 2024Network Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 171. 88 mmProduct Height 8. 22 mmProduct Width/Depth 77. 8 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number 2409BRN2CY, 2409BRN2CAModel Name Redmi 14CPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP + QVGA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/580d22f3-c5ca-4df1-95a9-89174d8c109f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/27ccbb76-9958-406d-8ac2-04fba41f738b/web/6_1726555503966.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>509 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066940148042</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2149417611</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 14C Starry Blue Dual SIM 4GB RAM 128GB ROM - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Immersive 6. 88-inch displayRefined and stylish design50MP AI dual cameraMassive 5160mAh (typ) batteryOverviewRedmi 14C features a 6. 88-inch display, the largest on Redmi number series to date, offering a spacious and immersive viewing area for reading, watching videos, or gaming. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5160 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 88 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name BlueDisplay Resolution Type HDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 2Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTE/UMTSProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDAudio Jack 3. 5 mmModel Year 2024Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 128 GBSensor Accelerometer, Gyroscope, Digital compassModel Number 2409BRN2CAModel Name Redmi 14CPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP+2MP+QVGA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fa919591-5eff-409f-8c60-ab4c23048d90</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/20d1696e-fc1c-473b-8964-68e804261d3d/web/6_1726556360662.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Realme</g:brand>
      <g:price>379 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021494176118</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3431476517</g:id>
      <g:title>HB25 3.5MM Expansion interface HUB Function Seven Colorful RGB Muiti Functionel Headphone Holder</g:title>
      <g:description>HB25 USB Hub with RGB Multifunctional BracketOverview: The HB25 USB Hub is a versatile solution for expanding your connectivity options, combining functionality with vibrant RGB lighting. Featuring 3 USB 2. 0 ports and a 3. 5mm headphone jack, this hub offers seamless data transfer and charging, while its stylish RGB stand doubles as a practical holder for your headphones, watch, or other small items. Key Features:3-Port USB Splitter: Expand your USB connectivity with 3 USB 2. 0 ports. 3. 5mm Audio Jack: Perfect for connecting headphones or external speakers. RGB Lighting: Enjoy seven colorful RGB lighting options to personalize your setup. Multifunctional Bracket: The RGB stand serves as a stylish holder for your headphones, watch, or other accessories. Fast Charging Support: Capable of supporting up to 100W fast charging for laptops, tablets, or mobile phones. Data Transfer: Supports efficient data reading across connected devices. Specifications:USB Ports: 3 USB 2. 0Audio Interface: 3. 5mm headphone jackCharging Capacity: Up to 100W fast chargingLighting: Seven RGB lighting modesBracket Use: Headphone/watch/accessory holderIdeal for gamers, content creators, or anyone looking to add convenience and style to their workspace.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3892ad8a-e4ef-4fe0-b68f-a25174906e7a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/97aa2cbd-9694-4924-84e7-4f52269d41cf/web/1_1726569539794.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>74.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034314765171</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3089240926</g:id>
      <g:title>OPPO A31 Dual SIM Mystery Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Sleek and distinctive design makes it comfortable to grip and fashionable to carry aroundBrilliant display that produces sharper contrast and more dynamic color for a much more immersive viewing experienceFosters the latest android operating system that opens a host of contentProfound RAM assures immense multitaskingCutting-edge graphics aid through high-end gaming and graphic-intensive tasksSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Micro USBSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 4230 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Colour Name Mystery BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box mobileNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2020Condition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 256 GBModel Number A31Model Name A31Primary Camera (MP) 2MP,f/2. 4(marco) 2MP,f/2. 4(depth)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f4e8af9c-3df9-4e73-9d5e-172ef31d46fa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2b32115b-346e-4f1c-8347-5dbbe27a4fae/web/1_1726561622182.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Oppo</g:brand>
      <g:price>188 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030892409261</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1727168035</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony PlayStation 5 Pulse Explore Wireless Earbuds</g:title>
      <g:description>Full-frame performance with high sensitivity and wide dynamic rangeHigh performance BIONZ XR image-processing engine4K (QFHD) high-frame-rate 120fps recordingCinematic color science with S-CinetoneEnhanced mobility for solo operationOverviewSony's FX3 Cinema Line camera brings the visions of passionate content creators to life. Cinematic expression is matched with reliable performance and streamlined operation to serve the needs of today's creative community. Compact and lightweight, it's easy to carry and handle. The FX3 Cinema Line camera offers high sensitivity and full-frame cinematic expression in an amazingly compact design. With enhanced mobility for easy solo shooting, alongside pro operability, it's the ideal creative tool to capture a cinematic vision anywhere. SpecificationsColour Name BlackCamera Resolution 12. 9 MPModel Number ILME-FX3Model Name ILME-FX3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/98a4b9dc-5653-4391-8a54-6f6ae6b9bbc9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/29a9ba37-066f-4dfb-b623-6dcace40f3f6/web/1_1726835087019.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>688 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017271680350</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3283143007</g:id>
      <g:title>Sony FX3 Full-Frame Cinema Line Camera, ILME-FX3</g:title>
      <g:description>Full-frame performance with high sensitivity and wide dynamic rangeHigh performance BIONZ XR image-processing engine4K (QFHD) high-frame-rate 120fps recordingCinematic color science with S-CinetoneEnhanced mobility for solo operationOverviewSony's FX3 Cinema Line camera brings the visions of passionate content creators to life. Cinematic expression is matched with reliable performance and streamlined operation to serve the needs of today's creative community. Compact and lightweight, it's easy to carry and handle. The FX3 Cinema Line camera offers high sensitivity and full-frame cinematic expression in an amazingly compact design. With enhanced mobility for easy solo shooting, alongside pro operability, it's the ideal creative tool to capture a cinematic vision anywhere. SpecificationsColour Name BlackCamera Resolution 12. 9 MPModel Number ILME-FX3Model Name ILME-FX3</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fda32a1f-d4ae-4f61-bd51-a1946b47ef9b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/61abe276-7f14-435a-b43a-8ae0426c9ca3/web/1_1726834749136.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Sony</g:brand>
      <g:price>13798 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032831430077</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9038587970</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual Sim Yellow 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05 gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name YellowOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZYIMEAModel Name BSM-A155F/2D8NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/47f89b17-6a80-4324-ad64-2bc88876f3a8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d3f4ef8f-2c9e-4da5-a888-19bcc3ee58c3/web/1_1726562052898.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>602 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090385879704</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3915195396</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish available in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide-angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZKHMEA/SM-A057FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/acf750bb-8a40-40fa-9987-ccd3674c21a8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5cd2338a-a23e-4354-b48f-817cbca0aa1d/web/1_1726563253223.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>460 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039151953965</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3084249031</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVGMEA / SM-A057FLVDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mpShow Less</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b465011c-895b-412c-98aa-b2b8df0ee65a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a8bae3b1-3390-48b2-8398-b54473239165/web/1_1726560326023.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>425 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030842490318</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8877644579</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Light Green 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Display the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 4 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Light GreenOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FLGDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8de8c108-3f16-4c70-8620-fdfc641ebc3d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9655ffb0-eb46-47d7-9f92-9ac03b587ced/web/1_1726562214352.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>296 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088776445799</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3357833634</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Light Green 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 4 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name Light GreenOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FLGGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7f40073a-86d6-4673-b045-610b5a317f15</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d3fac368-9da2-448e-833b-7130facc5207/web/1_1726561206073.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>326 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033578336349</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6158392069</g:id>
      <g:title>SAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Pink 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and Pro Visual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 512GB Storage, Pink, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BLIGMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b5db3a4e-371b-4341-ae0a-edb1f62386f0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eccacb30-3059-4d5f-a95b-b3532cc8b920/web/1_1726564005371.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>6579 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061583920697</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1214767791</g:id>
      <g:title>SAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Silver Shadow 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsGalaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 512GB Storage, Silver Shadow, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name Silver ShadowDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BZSGMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e496f508-e6a9-4696-baa3-87525d2afd5e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ea173598-79d0-45de-9ef6-84dda3ed3bb0/web/1_1726565458827.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012147677915</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5917332188</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Lilac 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome LilacOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356ELVPMEAModel Name SM-A356ELVPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6d8f1244-6991-4f3c-83d5-0c06f8c1badf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/cabafb24-873a-4046-aa35-0f7a11e16f33/web/1_1726564195122.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>930 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059173321887</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5635556746</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A55 Dual SIM Awesome Lilac 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A55 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 32MP front camera, the 12MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 32 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 32 MP &amp;amp; AboveRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome LilacOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A556ELVWMEAModel Name SM-A556ELVWMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+12+5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bce842fa-ab1f-475c-81c8-2a912db91973</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6bb5c84c-f03b-422b-ba0a-0d0535b75958/web/1_1726565850807.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1126 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056355567460</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7151253315</g:id>
      <g:title>Realme C55 Dual SIM Sunshower / Dorado 8GB RAM 256GB 4G LTE - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAs a entry-level smartphone, realme C55 offers a higher-resolution display, faster hardware, improved cameras, and much faster 33W wired chargingThere is a dual camera on the back with a 64MP primary and a 2MP depth sensor, while the selfie camera is now 8MP with 1080p capturing, up from 5MP and 720p videosIt offers a large 6. 72-inch LCD screen with extended 1080p resolution and a 90Hz refresh rateIt runs on top of the Helio G88 chipset, and the base configuration now starts with 8GB RAM and 256GB storage, expandable, of courseRealme has implemented its 33W SuperVOOC charging for the 5,000mAh battery , a first for the C seriesSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 72 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Sunshower / DoradoDisplay Type IPS LCDOperating System AndroidOperating System Number 13Processor Number G88Fast Charging YesProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number C55 , RMX3710Model Name C55Primary Camera (MP) 64+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d14b9724-f0f3-4d5b-b438-bbbde95f8665</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2c164062-a3f5-4d71-9265-a8a814740335/web/1_1726564389871.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Realme</g:brand>
      <g:price>390 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071512533157</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4419135802</g:id>
      <g:title>Galaxy A55 Dual SIM Awesome Ice Blue 8GB RAM 256GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Design: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A55 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 32MP front camera, the 12MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 32 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 32 MP &amp;amp; AboveRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome Ice BlueOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A556ELBWMEAModel Name SM-A556ELBWMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+12+5</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9f409e18-f40d-4bc7-94fc-f95b5bb45b8d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a24d49af-c7b5-474f-85a8-8b0ed10d54a3/web/1_1726564185947.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>1195 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044191358021</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3060639058</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A15 Dual SIM Blue/Black 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Display: The galaxy A15's 6. 5-inch super amoled display boasts vibrant clarity even in direct sunlight with vision booster, smooth-scrolling with improved 90Hz refresh rateDesign: The galaxy A15 showcases its refined aesthetics through an intuitive frame, glossy backcover and tidy camera layout. Available in blue black, blue, light blue and yellowCamera: The galaxy A15 boasts a 50MP main camera for your masterpiece, 5MP ultra wide and 2MP macro cameras for landscapes and close-ups, and a 13MP front camera for profile-worthy selfiesPerformance: Your day runs smoother with an octa-core processor for powerful performance while spacious memory and storage options keep your data and contents ready at handBattery: More time to get productive with a 5,000mAh typical battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 5 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 5 - 7. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTEPrimary Camera Feature TripleNetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A155FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A15Primary Camera (MP) 50+5+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/28c2140a-782e-4b5b-a0bd-6866e6d09738</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c498d383-3c24-4cf3-b4ef-252a87e52308/web/1_1726569070834.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>499 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030606390588</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3638380762</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Black 4GB RAM 64GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Display the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 64 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name BlackOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FZKDMEA / SM-A055FZKGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f5c52e68-51bd-4133-a931-453901431fd2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/238669d0-08b4-4a25-9896-b797450d4781/web/1_1726568780800.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>315 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036383807622</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1417169103</g:id>
      <g:title> SAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Pink 12GB RAM 1TB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 1TB Storage, Pink, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BLIHMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/12ed5504-5ee7-40cc-a490-c01761c4153f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/eb37f93c-fc1a-4e31-99ac-ebbfc9b9ab0f/web/3_1726568595029.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>7449 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014171691035</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1493035305</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6 Single SIM + eSIM Pink 12GB RAM 512GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Galaxy AI: Put PC-like power in your pocket, Galaxy Z Fold6. Now super-charged with Galaxy Al on foldablesDesign: Thinner and lighter- with a pocket-worthy silhouette, and an even brighter, awe inspiring fold-out screenDurability: Durable, reliable and built to last. Meet our slim and innovative flexhingeGaming Performance: Powerful gaming with the fastest processor on a Samsung foldable. Enjoy silky-smooth gaming at high specsBattery: Our battery ensures all-day enjoyment. It's not just a massive battery, but also leverages an efficient displayCamera: Meet Fold's most powerful camera system yet. Topped with an upgraded NPU, mind-blowing specs and ProVisual Engine, it'll transform your multimedia experienceSuper HDR: Brighten things up. Super HDR puts the right emphasis on details to pop and impress, even befort you take the pictureLarge Screen: Fold open a mobile gaming beast with a massive screen made better with the vision booster's powerful brightness and clarity even in broad daylight. OverviewSAMSUNG Galaxy Z Fold6, AI Phone, 12GB RAM, 512GB Storage, Pink, Android Smartphone, 50MP Camera, Big Screen, Multi-tasking, S Pen, Long Battery LifeSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 14 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 12 GBBattery Size 4400 mAhInternal Memory 512 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 7. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1812x2176Colour Name PinkDisplay Type AMOLEDDisplay Resolution Type FHD+Operating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesNetwork Frequency Band GSM/LTEProcessor Name Qualcomm SnapdragonNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-F956BLIGMEAModel Name Fold 6Primary Camera (MP) 50 MP + 12 MP + 10 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/984923f4-3fbb-4dca-99e4-5d506538dd9a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/696c8528-5a63-4392-990d-f516685efb20/web/1_1726568210489.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>6579 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014930353051</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5726150591</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 14C Dual SIM Sage Green 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Immersive 6. 88" display, Up to 120Hz High refresh rateRefined and stylish design, 8. 22mm ultra-slim body50MP AI dual camera, 13MP super-clear selfiesMassive 5160mAh (typ) batteryPowered by 33W fast chargingPowerful octa-core processorSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5160 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 211 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 88 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1640Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Sage GreenDisplay Type LCDOperating System Version Android 14Operating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number Xiaomi HyperOSProcessor Number MediaTek Helio G81-UltraFast Charging YesWhat's In The Box Mobile, USB Type-C Cable, SIM Eject Tool, Quick Start Guide, Warranty Card, CPE Bag, Adapter, Protective Film, Protective CaseNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDAudio Jack 3. 5 mmModel Year 2024Network Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 171. 88 mmProduct Height 8. 22 mmProduct Width/Depth 77. 8 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number 2409BRN2CY, 2409BRN2CAModel Name Redmi 14CPrimary Camera (MP) 50MP + QVGA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/698af985-dd1a-424b-9b4e-45c2d830a462</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/37cffaa6-988a-49d2-be37-e8ef205d1d1a/web/1_1726567667054.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>509 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057261505911</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4166034372</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Silver 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish available in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name SilverOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FZSGMEA / SM-A057FZSDMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9f480dbd-c97c-47e8-8072-81845f1bd70b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8bcee8a5-8e87-4d5f-a89f-62d1f507c7bc/web/1_1726572666948.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>410 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0041660343724</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6913192520</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05 Dual SIM Silver 4GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay the screen keeps going enjoy your favorite games movies and content with the vast 67-inch HD+ displayDesign availabe in black silver and light green galaxy A05 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera the front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 8MP Front camera the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP Wide angle cameraPerformance equipped with a powerful octa-core 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05 offers efficient performance for the task at handBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05 gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 4 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 720x1600Refresh Rates 60HzColour Name SilverOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A055FZSGMEAModel Name Galaxy A05Primary Camera (MP) 50+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b012896a-054c-4330-aff8-9e696b18b372</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1f94ea2d-2c50-42c7-a97b-7b4784bbb5ee/web/1_1726563029062.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>326 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069131925200</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8363914645</g:id>
      <g:title>Xiaomi Redmi 13C Dual SIM Clover Green 8GB RAM 256GB 4G - Global Version</g:title>
      <g:description>Smooth 6. 74" 90Hz Display50 MP AI Triple CameraMassive 5000 mAh Battery with 18W DP Fast ChargingPowerful Octa-Core ProcessorUp-to 16GB RAM with 8GB Expandable MemoryOverviewSmooth 6. 74" 90Hz Display | 50 MP AI Triple Camera | Massive 5000 mAh Battery with 18W DP Fast Charging |Powerful Octa-Core Processor |TUV Low blue light / Flicker-free Certification | Up-to 16GB RAM with 8GB Extendable Memory | MIUI Dedicated OptimizationSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMProcessor Speed 2 GHzSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBProduct Weight 192 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 74 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Clover GreenDisplay Type LCDOperating System AndroidVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 13Processor Number MediaTek Helio G85Fast Charging YesNetwork Frequency Band LTEProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CoreGlass Technology Gorilla GlassPrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDFinish PlasticModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewProduct Length 168 mmProduct Height 8. 09 mmProduct Width/Depth 78 mmMaximum Expandable Memory 16 GBModel Number 3106RN0DA, 22120RNSC, 23106RN0DA , 23108RN04Y, 23124RN87C, 22120RN86CModel Name Redmi 13CPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+QVGA</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5b584d94-6c03-477a-83fa-a577a69bfed4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d52ba018-d77d-4c6e-a982-fbeb1e59b446/web/1_1726563770290.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Xiaomi</g:brand>
      <g:price>292.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083639146455</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1864187683</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Yellow 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 5-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, light blue, yellow comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A05 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 2MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraBattery: The 5,000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love—streaming, sharing, gaming and more. And with up to 25W of super fast charging, galaxy A05s gets back to full power, quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name YellowOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256EZYDMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/1D6NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/815509b9-35d9-48c5-9dc7-1a12a129e3da</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/80091cea-5895-444a-a867-49a6a9e98d9b/web/1_1726572210646.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>610 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018641876830</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6347478311</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A25 Dual Sim Light Blue 6GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The galaxy A25 5G's 6. 5-inch, super amoled display details up to 1,000 nits brightness while enhanced with vision booster for clear outdoor visibilityDesign: Clean camera layout, sleek profile, unique patterns and haze finish. Available in blue black, blue and yellowCamera: Equipped with a 50mp main camera, the device is ready to capture high-resolution images assisted with OIS. Captures crisp selfies with an enhanced 13mp front cameraBattery: A 5,000mah battery that lasts for 2 days and recharges rapidly with super fast chargingSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 128 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 5 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Light BlueOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box USB-C Type Cable, SIM Tray Ejector, Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band GSMPrimary Camera Feature TripleModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A256ELBDMEAModel Name BSM-A256E/1D6NPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/42e9ef9e-65ee-4219-ba78-7063cc2c23a3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c0e1cf45-a4a5-43f3-8ffb-054f2adf1295/web/1_1726570937596.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>615 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063474783114</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7228733312</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A35 Dual SIM Awesome Lemon 8GB RAM 128GB 5G - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDisplay: The screen keeps going. Enjoy your favorite games, movies and content with the vast, 6. 6-inch HD+ displayDesign: Available in black, silver and light green, galaxy A35 comes in a sturdy frame with a linearly patterned backsideCamera: The front and back of the galaxy A35 are shown to showcase its three multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera, the 8MP depth camera and the 50MP wide-angle cameraSpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 13 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 8 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 6 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 2340x1080Refresh Rates 120HzColour Name Awesome LemonOperating System AndroidModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number SM-A356EZYPMEAModel Name SM-A356EZYPMEAPrimary Camera (MP) 50+8+2</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7cf6ad6b-5889-453e-9646-ff58951efa2a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/38abeb37-c022-4fb7-8214-deaae5717126/web/1_1726573053071.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>840 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0072287333126</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8448328582</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung Galaxy A05s Dual SIM Light Violet 6GB RAM 128GB 4G LTE - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsDISPLAY enjoy it all in stellar clarity With the 67-inch FHD+ display your favorite contents and games become immersive with seamless vivid picture qualityDesign refined build and finish availabe in light violet light green Silver and black galaxy a05s brings the style in form factorCamera the front and back of the Galaxy A05s are shown to showcase its four multiple cameras including the 13MP front camera the 2MP macro camera the 50MP wide angle camera and the 2MP depth cameraPerformance With a powerful Snapdragon® 680 processor 4 6GB of memory and 64 128GB internal storage Galaxy A05s is equipped with the Performance capacity for seamless gaming viewing and sharing on social mediaBattery The 5000mAh typical battery gives you more time to do what you love streaming sharing gaming and more And with up to 25W of Super Fast charging Galaxy A05s gets back to full power quicklySpecificationsExpandable Memory Type MicroSDSecondary Camera Resolution 2 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera Upto 4. 9 MPRAM Size 6 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 6 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 7 inSIM Type Nano SIMDisplay Resolution 1080x2400Refresh Rates 90HzColour Name Light VioletOperating System AndroidWhat's In The Box Usb-c Type Cable SIM Tray Ejector Quick Start GuideNetwork Frequency Band LTENetwork Type 4GCondition NewMaximum Expandable Memory 1 TBModel Number SM-A057FLVHMEAModel Name Galaxy A05sPrimary Camera (MP) 50+2+2 mp</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1d00fd17-e78c-4c5f-a6ff-9098a76c5ff9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/58ac3f97-0d0b-41a6-bda7-7d6da47a53a2/web/1_1726563507919.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>465 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084483285826</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4271658349</g:id>
      <g:title>Realme C55 Dual SIM Rainy Night / Negro 8GB RAM 256GB 4G LTE - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsAs a entry-level smartphone, realme C55 offers a higher-resolution display, faster hardware, improved cameras, and much faster 33W wired chargingThere is a dual camera on the back with a 64MP primary and a 2MP depth sensor, while the selfie camera is now 8MP with 1080p capturing, up from 5MP and 720p videosIt offers a large 6. 72-inch LCD screen with extended 1080p resolution and a 90Hz refresh rateIt runs on top of the Helio G88 chipset, and the base configuration now starts with 8GB RAM and 256GB storage, expandable, of courseRealme has implemented its 33W SuperVOOC charging for the 5,000mAh battery , a first for the C seriesSpecificationsSecondary Camera Resolution 8 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 8 - 11. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 5000 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 72 inSIM Type Nano SIMRefresh Rates 90HzColour Name Rainy NightDisplay Type IPS LCDOperating System AndroidOperating System Number 13Processor Number G88Fast Charging YesProcessor Name MediaTek HelioNumber of Cores Octa CorePrimary Camera Feature DualFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 4GCondition NewModel Number C55Model Name C55Primary Camera (MP) 64+2 MP</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5dd7d30b-98f9-4f40-ab98-38cd1ad69923</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/64f479c9-829f-4f16-bb1a-07fc6a95d9a3/web/1_1726570769354.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Realme</g:brand>
      <g:price>390 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042716583491</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7565460480</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple IPhone 15 Pro 256GB Natural Titanium 5G With FaceTime - Middle East Version</g:title>
      <g:description>DescriptionModel Number : MTUF3AH/A,MTV53AA/AHighlightsA17 Pro game-changing chip for a groundbreaking performance. 6. 1” Super Retina XDR display with ProMotion Technology. Megapowerful 48MP camera capable for a 3x optical zoom and 15x digital zoom. Up to 23 hours video playback. Facetime is available on the product &amp;amp; would be accessible in regions where facetime is permitted by telecom operatorsOverviewThe iPhone 15 Pro features an aerospace‑grade titanium design with an all‑new Action button to fast track to your favorite feature. The powerful camera system offers multiple focal lengths for super‑high‑resolution photos with a new level of detail and color. SpecificationsCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 3650 mAhInternal Memory 256 GBVersion Middle East VersionScreen Size 6. 1 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMPrimary Camera Resolution 48 MPRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Natural TitaniumDisplay Type Dynamic AMOLEDOperating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesOperating System Number 17. 0Processor Number A17 ProFast Charging YesProcessor Name Apple BionicNumber of Cores Octa CoreCamera Type Primary Camera + Secondary CameraPrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash LEDModel Year 2023Network Type 5GCondition NewModel Number MTUF3AH/A,MTV53AA/AModel Name iPhone 15 Pro</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b46b39bb-2e5b-4537-b107-742917d378dc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/16905120-1f13-4aa1-83f0-f1052533cab6/web/1_1726663241396.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>3799 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075654604805</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
