<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>6363003999</g:id>
      <g:title>Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max 1TB Desert Titanium 5G With FaceTime - International Version</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPersonalise your Home Screen. Tint your icons with any colour. Rearrange and resize apps and widgets. You can even lock or hide apps to protect sensitive information — it’s your callChoose your controls. Swap out your Lock Screen controls for ones you love to use more often. Or you can assign a control to the Action buttonIn the redesigned Photos app, your Collections are automatically organised by topic, like People &amp;amp; PetsPersonalise every style even more with the new control pad, which makes it easy to adjust tone and colour simultaneously. You can also use the slider to adjust the intensity of the specific colours, instead of applying a one-size-fits-all approachOur improved image pipeline also enables more creative styles, which allow you to customise the different moods of a photo through colourOverviewApple Intelligence protects your privacy at every step. With on-device processing and Private Cloud Compute, no one but you can access your data — not even Apple. The new Passwords app makes it even easier to access account passwords, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, two-factor authentication codes and more. It stores them securely and syncs across your devices with end-to-end encryption. You can also control which contacts to share with an app, rather than giving it access to all your contacts. And you can choose to share more contacts over time. SpecificationsExpandable Memory Type No Expandable MemorySecondary Camera Resolution 12 MPCharging Type Type-CSIM Count Dual SIMSecondary Camera 12 - 15. 9 MPRAM Size 8 GBBattery Size 4676 mAhInternal Memory 1 TBProduct Weight 227 gVersion International VersionScreen Size 6. 9 inSIM Type Nano + eSIMRefresh Rates 120HzColour Name Desert TitaniumDisplay Type OLEDOperating System Version iOS 18Operating System iOSVoice Calling Capability YesProcessor Number A18 ProFast Charging YesNumber of Cores Hexa CorePrimary Camera Feature TripleFlash Dual Tone flashModel Year 2024Network Type 5GCondition NewProduct Length 77. 6 mmProduct Height 163 mmProduct Width/Depth 8. 3 mmModel Number iPhone 16 Pro MaxModel Name iPhone 16 Pro MaxPrimary Camera (MP) 48+48+12</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b0a50f4d-479a-4915-b9b4-69ad3bf3bcdb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1b9bb2fd-241b-46dc-a3d7-8043ccfe6d52/web/1_1732192623912.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Apple iPhone</g:brand>
      <g:price>6399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063630039994</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4882250789</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM 60 Sheets of Instax Mini Film</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsCapture life's moments instantly with this pack of 80 Fujifilm Instax Mini Plain Film, tailored for all Instax mini cameras and the Instax SHARE SP-2 Smartphone Printer. *Contains 80 sheets. - Abundant supply for all your photographic adventures. - *High-quality prints. - Delivers stunning instant photos that fit perfectly in wallets or frames. - *Professional-grade technology. Ensures vivid colours and sharp details in every shot. - *Hi-Speed ISO 800. - Captures images in vibrant colour with exquisite grain quality. - *Universal compatibility. - Perfect match for Fujifilm Instax Mini Cameras and SHARE SP-2 Printers. Vivid memories in instant clarity Engineered with Hi-Speed ISO 800 film, it captures your moments in brilliant colour and remarkable detail. Each shot is a celebration of vibrant hues and clearcrisp images,Instant satisfaction, lasting impressions Gone are the days of waiting for photos to develop. Fujifilm's cutting-edge film technology prints your pictures in seconds, offering you instant gratification without compromising on quality. OverviewInstax Mini Film is for all Instax mini cameras. It offers stunning instant pictures that you can fit into a purse, wallet or mini photo frame. Compatible with all FUJIFILM Instax Mini Cameras &amp;amp; Instax SHARE SP-2 Smartphone Printers. SpecificationsColour Name whiteModel Number 87305</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/67b63b3e-1887-4566-8f52-3323e4faa1ee</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2f3ef4cb-f135-4439-8fe8-b34e16d9c5e8/web/1_1732112484418.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>225 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048822507895</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7324275792</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM 20-Sheet Instax Film Photo Paper</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsSpecially designed and labeled cartridge facilitates easy loadingHelps you to create vivid colour photographs with natural skin tonesThe compact size enables you to place it in your walletinstax mini film offers stunning-quality instant pictures that fit in a purse, wallet or mini photo frame. Professional quality instant film technology ensures accurate colour and sharpness with every frame, not to mention a unique and highly attractive way to capture and share your memories. OverviewThis 54X86mm film is designed for Fujifilm Instax Mini 7s/8/25/90/9. With white photo edge for DIY information. Good partner for your unforgettable journey. 20 sheets photo paper designed for Fujifilm Instax Mini 7s/8/25/90/9. High-speed ISO 800, with excellent grain, create photos of vibrant color and natural skin tones. The cartridge is specially designed and labeled for easy loading. 54X86mm credit card size, can be placed in your wallet or purse, easy to carry. 46X62mm image size, with white paper edge for you to DIY photo information. Usage:1. To install the film correctly, please match the yellow mark on film with that on camera film slot. 2. Please don't press the black surface of film or the sunken part of package. 3. After the photo slide out, you can shake it, place it into pocket or just wait until image emerges. 4. Do not open the rear camera cover until you get all the photo paper filmed. Film Type: Color, Instant Film Roll: Yes, Film Format: 45 mmSpecificationsColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box Instax MiniProduct Length 62 mmProduct Width/Depth 46 mmModel Number GE34Model Name GE34Item Quantity 20</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e820def3-0f87-4bd1-be6c-684905aefcfc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/26c97a19-3322-46b8-affb-edd3b04fa4e0/web/1_1732112253735.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>72 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073242757926</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9037563044</g:id>
      <g:title>FUJIFILM Instax Pal Digital Camera</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsPocket-friendly design in five exciting colorsWide-angle lens for more expansive and creative shotsMulti-use detachable ring for a better hold, remote shooting, and a viewfinderPre-shutter sounds for personalized and fun photographyBluetooth transfer for easy image sharing and editing. Lithium-ion battery with USB Type-C chargingBluetooth TransferSmartphone App comes with 18 filtersOverviewThe one and only Instax Pal, a super small digital camera, eager to capture small spontaneous moments, helping to make them feel powerful. Then, when you are ready for the big reveal, transfer your images (Pal can store 50 maximum) to your smartphone via Bluetooth. Select the camera roll on the Instax Pal app to transfer, add one of 18 filters, text or decorate with stickers, you can even select the size of your mini, square, wide, film before printing images via your Instax Link printer. SpecificationsColour Name PinkProduct Length 4. 23 cmProduct Height 4. 43 cmProduct Width/Depth 4. 3 cmModel Number Instax Pal</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7c2828fd-b80e-464e-a1c6-865cd7b52be6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d31d9184-6d19-4f46-96d6-3168a8b7704a/web/1_1732113326537.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Fujifilm</g:brand>
      <g:price>375 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090375630445</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6968201644</g:id>
      <g:title>Microsoft Surface Pro Edition Copilot+ PC 13 Inch OLED Display, Snapdragon X Elite Processor</g:title>
      <g:description>HighlightsUltimate combination of performance and speed to edit photos and videos fasterCustomise performance, fan speed and noise, and external temperature all to the meet your needsSpecificationsProcessor Speed 3. 4 GHzRAM Size 16 GBInternal Memory 1 TBScreen Size 13 inDisplay Resolution 2880x1920Colour Name SAPPHIREKeyboard Language EnglishGraphics Processor Version Intel Iris XEDisplay Type PixelSenseDisplay Resolution Type QHDConnection Type HDMIAverage Battery Life 14 HoursStorage Type SSDOperating System Version Windows 11 HomeOperating System WindowsUsage Type BusinessModel Series Microsoft Surface ProProcessor Version Number/Generation Not ApplicableNumber of Cores 12-CoreRAM Type DDR5External Graphics IntegratedGraphic Memory None NoneFeatures AI Laptop/PCModel Number ZIB-00040Model Name Surface Pro 11 Copilot+ PCHDMI Output YesNumber of USB Ports 2SD Card Slot YesNumber of HDMI Ports 1Processor Version Qualcomm Snapdragon X Elite</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/062a6747-7747-4ab4-9a83-18f080dda574</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1459c344-a8ec-4b3c-9833-7967233fe294/web/1_1732193522575.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Microsoft</g:brand>
      <g:price>8999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069682016440</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9003451841</g:id>
      <g:title>Samsung A74</g:title>
      <g:description>​​Samsung Galaxy Vietnam version brand new phone. Bought it weeks ago very good conditions. .</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/29a7b0fc-8a27-40ad-8e1f-f3ce7e626ff2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ed7021d5-4a9a-443d-97ac-281e3032fa70/web/1_1731615576022.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand>Samsung</g:brand>
      <g:price>350 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090034518411</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
